<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/az-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Quaintise in Phoenix, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Quaintise is expanding rapidly and is looking for a part-time, contract-based Senior Graphic Designer with at least five years of fast-paced agency experience. Agency experience is a MUST.  While this job will start out as part-time, it will likely evolve to full-time status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our agency has offices in both Scottsdale and Los Angeles.  We are seeking a Senior Graphic Designer for our Scottsdale office, however, this position is contract and telecommute.  Are you a “rockstar” designer with advanced knowledge of graphic design and production best practices? Do you have extensive experience designing for online, print and mobile media channels and a portfolio that showcases your work? Do you have experience mentoring other designers? Do you eat, sleep and breathe all things creative? If so, Quaintise would like to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept, design, revise and deliver innovative and effective graphic work for print, online and mobile media channels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide senior-level design insights, best practices and creative inspiration to our Creative Services team to further the development of our design capability and help take our work to the next level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize, revise and pre-flight client-supplied and/or existing graphics to ensure production specifications are met&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work across the full scope of Creative Services deliverables to concept, design and deliver high-quality, production ready marketing, internal, and sales collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adhere to project timelines and effectively communicate project status to internal partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide quality control on all completed projects to ensure design quality and production accuracy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage your assigned projects and maintain project data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively participate in Creative Department meetings and contribute to our culture of creativity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up-to-date on design trends, production technology and brand marketing, with a focus on the healthcare industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as a Creative Services subject matter expert in design and production-related areas, and create and maintain production templates, documentation and best practices in assigned areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Archive completed projects and maintain Creative Services servers and file archives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide assistance to the general design/production needs of the department as directed, and perform other duties as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Profile of Ideal Candidate:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Graphic Designer position is responsible for the concept, design and production of high-quality print, digital and mobile creative deliverables including advertisements, corporate marketing materials and sales support materials. This role will also assist with mentoring our design team by providing senior-level design insights, best practices and creative inspiration to help take our work to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need to Get our Attention:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A top-notch portfolio of your design work that includes print and online examples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of graphic design experience in an agency or in-house setting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A bachelor’s degree in Graphic Design or a related subject, or the equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced skills in Adobe Creative Suite CS6, with a focus on InDesign, Photoshop &amp;amp; Illustrator (Flash &amp;amp; HTML5 experience is a major plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong artistic abilities and a portfolio that demonstrates your knowledge of design, layout, typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong graphic production skill sets and knowledge of pre-press preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of digital media channels and digital advertising requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail with emphasis on accuracy and quality, and a critical eye for design aesthetics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong work-standard and an ability to innovate and think critically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional organizational abilities and proven ability to multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, customer service and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong passion for all things creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please send resume, cover letter and portfolio samples&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Quaintise:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based Scottsdale and Los Angeles, Quaintise develops dynamic marketing and advertising campaigns for some of the most recognized brands in healthcare. Insightful strategy combined with emotionally charged storytelling has successfully helped our clients deliver impactful and revenue generating campaigns. As the industry leader in healthcare marketing, Quaintise is the Agency of Record for some of the largest specialty medical groups in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-quaintise-phoenix-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-quaintise-phoenix-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Freelance Senior Graphic &amp; Web Designer at TextLinkBrokers.com in Mesa, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a top notch designer to help us with a wide variety of projects.  We prefer to hire on a contract basis, but part-time or full-time employment is possible if we find the right person.  The person we hire must be willing and able to visit our Mesa office occassionally for design spec meetings.  100% remote is possible for extrodinary candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Work we are looking for help with:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website Design for several of our own properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occassional banner design for ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brochure/Proposal design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrations and Infographics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occassional work of our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We can keep the right candidate fairly busy for the foreseeable future.  We will consider working with a team or a company if the rates are reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are only interested in high end designers, and we are willing to pay well for the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A portfolio must be submitted with your application to be considered&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About TextLinkBrokers.com&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TextLinkbrokers.com is a leading search engine marketing (SEM) and search engine optimization (SEO) agency. Our global mission is to help companies, from small businesses to Fortune 500&amp;rsquo;s, achieve stellar growth through effective online marketing. Utilizing advanced link building methods, optimized content development, landing page optimization (LPO), social media and other relevant marketing techniques; we have helped our clients around the globe to increase their revenues measured in the billions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/freelance-senior-graphic-and-web-designer-textlinkbrokers-com-mesa-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/freelance-senior-graphic-and-web-designer-textlinkbrokers-com-mesa-az</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>