<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/az-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Freelance Senior Graphic &amp; Web Designer at TextLinkBrokers.com in Mesa, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a top notch designer to help us with a wide variety of projects.  We prefer to hire on a contract basis, but part-time or full-time employment is possible if we find the right person.  The person we hire must be willing and able to visit our Mesa office occassionally for design spec meetings.  100% remote is possible for extrodinary candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Work we are looking for help with:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website Design for several of our own properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occassional banner design for ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brochure/Proposal design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrations and Infographics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occassional work of our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We can keep the right candidate fairly busy for the foreseeable future.  We will consider working with a team or a company if the rates are reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are only interested in high end designers, and we are willing to pay well for the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A portfolio must be submitted with your application to be considered&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About TextLinkBrokers.com&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TextLinkbrokers.com is a leading search engine marketing (SEM) and search engine optimization (SEO) agency. Our global mission is to help companies, from small businesses to Fortune 500&amp;rsquo;s, achieve stellar growth through effective online marketing. Utilizing advanced link building methods, optimized content development, landing page optimization (LPO), social media and other relevant marketing techniques; we have helped our clients around the globe to increase their revenues measured in the billions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/freelance-senior-graphic-and-web-designer-textlinkbrokers-com-mesa-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/freelance-senior-graphic-and-web-designer-textlinkbrokers-com-mesa-az</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>