<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/az-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Career Evolutions in Phoenix, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Career Evolutions is searching for a Sr. Graphic Designer for a fast-growing CPG company headquartered in Phoenix, AZ. It’s a full-time position with annual salary up to $55,000 + Bonus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be part of a smaller team of five Graphic Designers who have a lot of fun together while creating wonderful designs for the organization. Your team works closely with the members on the Production team.  The atmosphere is open, collaborative, and team oriented.  Problem-solving and multi-tasking is a part of your day. You also enjoy working independently and applying your creativity with the mindset of getting things done on time with a smile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will design and produce top quality dies and templates to support our new product offering so you probably have geometric layout and productions skills as well. Thorough knowledge of electronic file construction, file layering, and geometry is great as well. You may also calculate dimensions of new products or product enhancements and estimates material needed. You will provide graphic designs for branding/identity, ads (web &amp;amp; print), brochures, and various other prints. Quite likely, you’ll at times also assist with the creation, organization and management of social media channels and the upkeep of the design of the company website as well as other projects/requests as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associates Degree required, Bachelor’s Degree a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years Graphic Design working experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge/technical expertise in Adobe Creative Suite (CS6): Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Acrobat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Hand Drawing + Computer Drawing Experience required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Creative Mindset mixed with a strong Logic understanding and Attention-to-Detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple tasks, meet deadlines, and turn projects around quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team Spirit, Self-Motivated, High-Energy, Global Mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-career-evolutions-phoenix-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-career-evolutions-phoenix-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer/ Video Specialist at Canyon Ranch in Tucson, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;JOB SUMMARY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graphic Designer / Video Specialist position is responsible for creative concepting and implementation through the channels of graphic design and video production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES (Percentage of time spent on each task.):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic Design – Develop concepts for, and design original, innovative brand advertising collateral and marketing communications (brochures, interactive graphics, flyers, signage, etc.) utilizing creativity, talent and imagination as well as layout, typography and composition skills (60%)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video Production – Produce innovative, brand specific video projects using creative concepting, pre-production planning and recommendations, shooting and editing skills (40%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an appropriate relationship with department heads and executive management in order to carry out assigned duties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adheres to and exemplifies the Canyon Ranch and Marketing department&amp;rsquo;s mission and values in all relationships with co-workers and guests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adheres to and exemplifies Canyon Ranch standards for guest service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refers guest problems or complaints to supervisor according to Canyon Ranch guest problem resolution policy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education/Experience/Minimum Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education: BS/BA in advertising, communications, graphic design or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience: Three to five years of graphic design/video production experience with a corporate in-house marketing department, or advertising, public relations or marketing services agency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills &amp;amp; Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Artistic sensibility – Must show a proficiency of aesthetic and sense of design that meets or exceeds the high-quality standard of the brand. Must possess a thorough knowledge of design elements (i.e., color and composition), typography, handling and manipulation of images and freehand graphics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptual development and judgment  – Must possess a talent for generating innovative, original concepts surrounding design and video projects that meet business objectives while complying with brand standards – ultimately developing work that moves the brand communications into new creative directions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical skill – Must possess an understanding of Macintosh technology, and a mastery of Final Cut Pro, the Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator) and Microsoft Office. Must have the technical skills necessary to capture raw video footage including the use of audio and lighting equipment, as well as edit and deliver final video in various formats depending on final usage (familiarity with SLR video camera a plus). Knowledge of web design software is also a plus. Must be able to adhere to tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication skill/Client relations – Must possess excellent listening skills and be able to interact with account executives/clients and translate ideas into effective design and video projects. Must also be able to effectively present these concepts once executed – both verbally and visually to account execs/manager/director/client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working style – Must have the ability to handle multiple projects at once, meet tight deadlines, thoroughly think through the process and follow through with all aspects and needs surrounding the execution of the design/video/photography project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-video-specialist-canyon-ranch-tucson-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-video-specialist-canyon-ranch-tucson-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Designer at VariQ Corporation in Scottsdale, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a Web Designer, you will have a passion for clean code, professional graphic design and staying on top of the latest web technologies. This job entails working with various clients and our internal teams to ensure our products look visually remarkable and our websites are cleanly coded to the latest web standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should possess and show strong interest in web and graphic design, as well as pushing the boundaries with the latest web trends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and setup ongoing client websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical website support for internal departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and design new company products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate with clients in a professional manner to ensure their websites are properly designed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with in-house departments to complete tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot and problem solve website based issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to hand code HTML/CSS (WE DO NOT USE DREAMWEAVER)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with SEO, SEM, SMM and related web marketing strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe Photoshop (Illustrator a huge plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be comfortable in a PC environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be able to quickly learn and adapt to new technologies, tools and software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be outgoing, upbeat and able to thrive in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Java Script and Jquery is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and manage multiple tasks simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have a sense of humor and love dogs too!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In order to qualify for this position, a competency test will be administered to evaluate your skills in design and hand coding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time, Monday through Friday in-house position.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-designer-variq-corporation-scottsdale-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-designer-variq-corporation-scottsdale-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Entry Level Web Designer/Advanced Customer Support at Retailer Web Services in Scottsdale, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a student or self-taught web designer looking for a break into the industry? Are you frustrated that to get a position in the web design industry you need experience, but no one will hire you without experience? We are looking for recent graduates and entry level web designers who want to put their skills to use and learn all the things you can&amp;rsquo;t learn in school or on your own by reading books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position will focus on talking with customers, supporting the websites that our senior design team builds and interacting directly with clients. Duties include designing promotional material for client websites, making simple HTML or CSS changes, hand coding website pages that consist of images and text, and learning more than you can imagine on a team that dominates in our industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like an exciting time and great opportunity, please contact us. We are beefing up our team and currently have multiple openings for this position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Our perfect person has&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to write and edit HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loves working with people; great at explaining complicated tech jargon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Photoshop (even if you know just enough to be dangerous)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outgoing and upbeat (we&amp;rsquo;re all just a bunch of geeks and nerds)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to pick things up quickly and learn new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to date with online trends such as social media and online payment methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous domain, DNS, and SEO experience is a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takes pride in their work and genuinely wants to do a good job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job details&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is an in-house position and we work Monday through Friday 7:30am to 4:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your own office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All equipment provided (fast computers and multiple monitors!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We start at $16/hour and also offer paid time off, health insurance, and other benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Interested?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think you’re a good fit? To apply for this job send you resume and portfolio to careers@retailerwebservices.com and tell us why you are the person we have been looking for.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/entry-level-web-designer-advanced-customer-support-critical-mass-scottsdale-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/entry-level-web-designer-advanced-customer-support-critical-mass-scottsdale-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Quaintise in Phoenix, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Quaintise is expanding rapidly and is looking for a part-time, contract-based Senior Graphic Designer with at least five years of fast-paced agency experience. Agency experience is a MUST.  While this job will start out as part-time, it will likely evolve to full-time status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our agency has offices in both Scottsdale and Los Angeles.  We are seeking a Senior Graphic Designer for our Scottsdale office, however, this position is contract and telecommute.  Are you a “rockstar” designer with advanced knowledge of graphic design and production best practices? Do you have extensive experience designing for online, print and mobile media channels and a portfolio that showcases your work? Do you have experience mentoring other designers? Do you eat, sleep and breathe all things creative? If so, Quaintise would like to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept, design, revise and deliver innovative and effective graphic work for print, online and mobile media channels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide senior-level design insights, best practices and creative inspiration to our Creative Services team to further the development of our design capability and help take our work to the next level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize, revise and pre-flight client-supplied and/or existing graphics to ensure production specifications are met&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work across the full scope of Creative Services deliverables to concept, design and deliver high-quality, production ready marketing, internal, and sales collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adhere to project timelines and effectively communicate project status to internal partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide quality control on all completed projects to ensure design quality and production accuracy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage your assigned projects and maintain project data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively participate in Creative Department meetings and contribute to our culture of creativity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up-to-date on design trends, production technology and brand marketing, with a focus on the healthcare industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as a Creative Services subject matter expert in design and production-related areas, and create and maintain production templates, documentation and best practices in assigned areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Archive completed projects and maintain Creative Services servers and file archives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide assistance to the general design/production needs of the department as directed, and perform other duties as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Profile of Ideal Candidate:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Graphic Designer position is responsible for the concept, design and production of high-quality print, digital and mobile creative deliverables including advertisements, corporate marketing materials and sales support materials. This role will also assist with mentoring our design team by providing senior-level design insights, best practices and creative inspiration to help take our work to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need to Get our Attention:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A top-notch portfolio of your design work that includes print and online examples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of graphic design experience in an agency or in-house setting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A bachelor’s degree in Graphic Design or a related subject, or the equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced skills in Adobe Creative Suite CS6, with a focus on InDesign, Photoshop &amp;amp; Illustrator (Flash &amp;amp; HTML5 experience is a major plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong artistic abilities and a portfolio that demonstrates your knowledge of design, layout, typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong graphic production skill sets and knowledge of pre-press preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of digital media channels and digital advertising requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail with emphasis on accuracy and quality, and a critical eye for design aesthetics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong work-standard and an ability to innovate and think critically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional organizational abilities and proven ability to multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, customer service and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong passion for all things creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please send resume, cover letter and portfolio samples&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Quaintise:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based Scottsdale and Los Angeles, Quaintise develops dynamic marketing and advertising campaigns for some of the most recognized brands in healthcare. Insightful strategy combined with emotionally charged storytelling has successfully helped our clients deliver impactful and revenue generating campaigns. As the industry leader in healthcare marketing, Quaintise is the Agency of Record for some of the largest specialty medical groups in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-quaintise-phoenix-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-quaintise-phoenix-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Freelance Senior Graphic &amp; Web Designer at TextLinkBrokers.com in Mesa, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a top notch designer to help us with a wide variety of projects.  We prefer to hire on a contract basis, but part-time or full-time employment is possible if we find the right person.  The person we hire must be willing and able to visit our Mesa office occassionally for design spec meetings.  100% remote is possible for extrodinary candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Work we are looking for help with:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website Design for several of our own properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occassional banner design for ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brochure/Proposal design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrations and Infographics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occassional work of our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We can keep the right candidate fairly busy for the foreseeable future.  We will consider working with a team or a company if the rates are reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are only interested in high end designers, and we are willing to pay well for the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A portfolio must be submitted with your application to be considered&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About TextLinkBrokers.com&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TextLinkbrokers.com is a leading search engine marketing (SEM) and search engine optimization (SEO) agency. Our global mission is to help companies, from small businesses to Fortune 500&amp;rsquo;s, achieve stellar growth through effective online marketing. Utilizing advanced link building methods, optimized content development, landing page optimization (LPO), social media and other relevant marketing techniques; we have helped our clients around the globe to increase their revenues measured in the billions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/freelance-senior-graphic-and-web-designer-textlinkbrokers-com-mesa-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/freelance-senior-graphic-and-web-designer-textlinkbrokers-com-mesa-az</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>