<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/az-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web UX Developer at Isos Technology in Phoenix, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Isos Technology is looking for a Web UX Developer for one of our clients in Phoenix, AZ.   If you have experience in the following&amp;hellip;apply NOW&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Node.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ROLE/RESPONSIBILITY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and apply creative visual solutions for Client&amp;rsquo;s products and services (both existing and new products).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the direction of the corporate and product brand strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish modular visual systems with well-documented guidelines and templates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define color palettes, icon systems, typographic and photographic programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be the sole force behind creating visionary design solutions from concept to completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;SKILLS/QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have experience with Javascript, AJAX and jQuery framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MUST HAVE: Client-side scripting, JavaScript / AJAX / DOJO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in advanced CSS techniques (float layouts, fluid layout, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in JSP/JSTL and/or Velocity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable in best practices of writing unobtrusive Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PhotoShop and/or Fireworks a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-browser (X)HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dynamic HTML/DOM manipulation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI templates and wiring to back-end controllers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debugging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with user-centered design and usability practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Web accessibility standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of development and programming principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional markup and client-side scripting talents applicable to a wide range of contexts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the separation of content, presentation, and behavior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superb problem solving skills and troubleshooting abilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and documentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Command of industry development and source code control tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;NO SPONSORSHIP and NO Relocation Assistance are available&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-ux-developer-isos-technology-phoenix-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-ux-developer-isos-technology-phoenix-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Platform Developer at Retailer Web Services in Scottsdale, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a Front End Developer, you are dedicated and passionate about developing streamlined website foundations. You are a critical thinker and enjoy a mix of HTML, CSS, jQuery and JavaScript. Clean markup, layout, user interface, cross browser functionality and W3C compliance allows you to sleep well at night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You take pride in constructing clean, large scale web applications from scratch and your code validates to the latest W3C standards. You must possess and show strong interest in HTML/CSS and front end programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build, maintain and continually improve large scale, internal website platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and develop new company products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical website support for internal departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and work closely with partners utilizing our platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work very closely with in-house departments to complete tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot and problem solve website and platform related issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be fluent with JavaScript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to hand code HTML/CSS (WE DO NOT USE DREAMWEAVER)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe Photoshop (Illustrator a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must possess extreme attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be comfortable in a PC environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be able to quickly learn and adapt to new technologies, tools and software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and manage multiple tasks simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be a positive thinker, outgoing, upbeat and able to thrive in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have a sense of humor and love dogs too!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In order to qualify for this position, a competency test will be administered to evaluate your skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time, Monday through Friday in-house position.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-platform-developer-retailer-web-services-scottsdale-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-platform-developer-retailer-web-services-scottsdale-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer/Developer at Angel MedFlight in Scottsdale, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Angel MedFlight is a leader in international air medical transportation. We are a game-changer in the medical flight industry, and as such, we are seeking a highly talented Web Designer to complement our creative Business Development team. A successful candidate will embrace challenge, flourish in a dynamic environment and excel at producing and maintaining creative, powerful websites. As our visual storyteller, you will convey the essence of Angel MedFlight to both a worldwide community of health care professionals well-versed in medical transport and the lay public who may not understand medical flights at all. Responsibilities Operates effectively as a member of the development team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also operates effectively as an individual for quick turnaround of enhancements and fixes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for meeting expectations and deliverables on time and in high quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the development of web pages, sites and components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the design and development of web pages, graphics, multimedia, GUIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively develops in a clean, well structured, easily maintainable format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilizes storyboarding and graphic pre-designs where appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrates creative, technical and analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrates ability to communicate effectively in both technical and business environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills Required:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree with a minimum of 2 years experience as a Web Designer / Developer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to script and debug JavaScript and jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in web browser compatibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of server side programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of basic marketing principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiastic collaborator who thrives in both team and individual settings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized, efficient self-starter who is attentive to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage workload and prioritize multiple projects for completion within expected time frame&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication and proofreading skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing websites and/or web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing ability a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordpress experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salesforce experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video and photography (execution and editing) skills a bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Educational Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree with a minimum of 2 years experience as a Web Designer / Developer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you fullfill above requirements please use our Online Employment Form. Alternatively, you can send us your Resume, Cover letter and completed Employment Application at: careers@angelmedflight.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-developer-angel-medflight-scottsdale-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-developer-angel-medflight-scottsdale-az</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr JavaScript Developer at Web Incentive Management in Phoenix, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you excited by Javascript, HTML5, and CSS3? Do you believe users should come first? Have you ever wanted to make a difference in the lives of millions of people? Go Daddy is looking for a highly motivated Sr. JavaScript Engineer to build the ultimate experience for our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position can be based in Scottsdale, Gilbert, Denver or Sunnyvale&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;In this role you will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write low maintenance, high reliability code to be used in a highly trafficked 24/7 environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the UX design team and build front-end interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive API design requirements to be deliver the User Experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot technical issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Do you have what it takes?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mature, independent, yet receptive to team participation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work at a fast pace and iterate rapidly over a design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firm grasp of object-oriented Javascript and prototypal inheritance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of software design principles and ability to guide others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal, communication and organizational skills with the ability to interact effectively with employees at all levels within the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in Javascript development including Node.JS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with MVC frameworks such as Ember, Angular, Backbone.JS or SproutCore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience implementing responsive designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NoSQL experience (Redis, Cassandra, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid academic background &amp;ndash; business, engineering or I/T related degree preferred (additional experience may substitute).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Understanding of HTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and understanding of cross browser compatibility issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL knowledge and relational database design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Go Daddy’s award-winning technical teams design and support the innovative technologies that are transforming the cloud, the internet and the world.  From product developers to network engineers, data center technicians to platform engineers, our expertise ensures our customers have the technical solutions to meet their needs. We develop world-class products that help our customers establish, enhance and evolve their online presence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Are you ready to GO with us?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you GO with Go Daddy, you have the opportunity to be part of something special by making a meaningful difference in the lives of our customers. Their success is our success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what you need:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion to contribute to a truly exceptional customer experience, no matter your job title&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding that innovation and creativity is a part of what we do every day
Agility and action orientation – we move at the speed of tech&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the privilege and obligation of being part of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what we’ll provide:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fun, dynamic and challenging work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formal and informal opportunities and support for ongoing learning, growth and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team building activities and recognition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive base plus bonus incentive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer-paid medical, dental, and insurance coverage for all benefit-eligible Go Daddy employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three weeks paid vacation your first year of employment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Go Daddy has been recognized because of its outstanding benefits, compensation, unique perks, diversity and company camaraderie. Go Daddy was awarded the 2011 and 2012 Alfred P. Sloan Award for Business Excellence in Workplace Flexibility Honoree &amp;ndash; Arizona, Iowa &amp;amp; Denver. Go Daddy is the #1 IT Company on Inc. Magazine&amp;rsquo;s inaugural Hire Power list of job creators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go Daddy’s philanthropic work supports a wide variety of charitable and community organizations dedicated to causes including women and children, domestic violence, child abuse, teenage homelessness, animal shelters and more. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.GoDaddyCares.com&quot;&gt;http://www.GoDaddyCares.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-javascript-developer-web-incentive-management-phoenix-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-javascript-developer-web-incentive-management-phoenix-az</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>