<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/az-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Web Developer at HomeSmart in Phoenix, AZ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you like being on the cutting edge of what you do? Want to think creatively while solving the problems of the world? Well, not quite&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a technology company working in the real estate industry and we&amp;rsquo;re changing the way the industry works through technology and new ideas. If you&amp;rsquo;re ready to constantly challenge the idea of what can or can&amp;rsquo;t be done, let&amp;rsquo;s see where you can put your talents to work.
BTW &amp;ndash; We hope you like heat! You must be in the Phoenix area or willing to relocate to Phoenix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You gotta want it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want team members that are reliable, friendly, and have an eye for design and visual detail, a knack for end-user useability, and a love for solving problems, along with the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and Design Mobile websites in HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write quality code in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Lead Developer to ensure smooth code and design integration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure code is consistently version controlled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take ownership of the code you write.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Lead Developer and ensure an exceptional user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 in a Mobile Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating SmartPhone peripherals ie. Camera, GPS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Posses skills in User Experience and User Interface design (UI/UX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript and Ajax&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS/CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coldfusion knowledge is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compensation &amp;amp; Benefits:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k w/ Match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fun and friendly environment!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining a profitable, growing, and dynamic company, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Instructions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email your resume as well as links to any portfolio samples to reply to email.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-developer-homesmart-phoenix-az</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-developer-homesmart-phoenix-az</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>