<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Trinet Internet Solutions Inc. in Irvine, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Trinet is a full-service web firm with expert capabilities in web strategy consulting, interactive marketing, creative and design services, web development, and web campaign management services. Basically, we are all about developing great websites and applications that allow our clients to breathe new life into their communication efforts and increase revenue or contributions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We not only work to help businesses achieve success online, but we also help many non-profits and faith based ministries as they work to meet the physical and spiritual needs of people both around the world and here at home.  Some of the organizations we have done work for include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coca Cola&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;World Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harvest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IMAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Billy Graham Evangelistic Organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toyota Racing Development (TRD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on the Family&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samaritan&amp;rsquo;s Purse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cisco / Linksys&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Red Cross, and many more…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a full-time Web Programmer/Developer for our corporate office in Irvine, CA.  The selected candidate will be a motivated, career focused team player with a desire to work in a growing small to medium sized company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis, development, deployment of client websites using standardized processes and development guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to problem solve and troubleshoot web applications and code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide time estimates for development of web projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and learn new technologies and acquire new skills through independent study&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to play a direct role in maintenance, technical support, documentation and administration of company-used technologies and code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2-3 years of related experience in hands on development of PHP + MySQL websites including HTML/XHTML, CSS and ideally JavaScript/jQuery, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience preferred with implementing Drupal and/or WordPress and/or Joomla and their modules a PLUS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a fast-paced, agency-type environment is a PLUS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree in Computer Science highly preferred with a good GPA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-trinet-internet-solutions-inc-irvine-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-trinet-internet-solutions-inc-irvine-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Symantec in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Relentlessly protect the world’s information. Make a difference at Symantec. Across the globe, we are an ‘essential’ partner to both consumers and businesses of all sizes. We combine our talents, our brains, and our creative energy to reinforce our place as a world-class technical community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the Worldwide eCommerce team, you will have the opportunity to enhance online sales of the company&amp;rsquo;s Norton-branded consumer products, as well as the development and management of Symantec&amp;rsquo;s eCommerce platform. The online storefront is built on cutting-edge technologies and includes stores across the world, supporting 18 languages, various payment methods, international currencies, and more than 230 countries worldwide. The eCommerce organization is focused on delivering an online shopping experience that anticipates customer needs and exceeds their expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Function&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SYM Cross Functional&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are currently looking for a talented individual to join our team in the role of Web Developer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a position responsible for developing front end systems, guiding architecture and new technologies and guiding team members to deliver re-usable well architected solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position requires demonstrated proficiency in hand-coding HTML/XHTML/CSS/JS with a thorough knowledge of JavaScript frameworks (such as JQuery) with 5+ years of experience in Web Production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ideal candidate will have a comprehensive knowledge of all aspects of web development, web production, site architecture, DOM, content management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience of adding Omniture tracking code to HTML pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be comfortable with standards-compliance and handling cross-browser compatibility issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years front end (web client &amp;amp; server side scripting) development at a high traffic eCommerce or consumer site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for developing pixel precision, high performing web pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience with Web 2.0 technologies including AJAX and XHTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of JavaScript libraries and frameworks such as jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong competency in HTML, CSS and semantic markup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of OOP, XML, XSL, Web Service&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of data structures, algorithms and architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with performance optimization for highly-trafficked web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of SEO best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Interwoven Teamsite and Perforce is highly desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with others in a demanding, fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated individual able to complete projects quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communicator and team player skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-symantec-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-symantec-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Application Developer at Jawbone in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Jawbone is looking for an experienced Web Application Developer to build the front-end user interface for various web applications. The ideal candidate is a self-motivated team player with a solid understanding of web design, development, and deployment practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website development, unit testing, implementation, and production application support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing front-end HTML/XHTML,CSS and JavaScript from interface wireframes and visual designs, following Web standards and promoting user experience best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping to develop processes and select frameworks and tools for web content management and web application development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gathering functional requirements to generate technical design specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Following specifications to implement high fidelity visual and UX designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience with AJAX, JavaScript, CSS, DHTML, HTML, XHTML.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated track record of successfully designing, developing, and supporting web-based applications and websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of cross-browser and platform compatibility requirements including IE rendering issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of best practices for implementation of multi-language / international websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity interfacing and developing with Java/J2EE backend technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. in Computer Science or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Desired Skills and Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and organizational skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and problem solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with cloud-based hosting services and external hosting partners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with disciplined software release build/deploy processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating with social media applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating with third party applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Omniture integration experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple overlapping projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently with minimal supervision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated by continuous learning and development, dedicated to delivering exceptional solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more than a decade, Jawbone has developed human-centered wearable technology and audio devices unparalleled in their technical innovation, ease-of-use and sophistication of design. A 2010 IDSA Design of the Decade winner, the company is the creator of the award-winning and best-selling Jawbone ERA and ICON Bluetooth® headsets; NoiseAssassin® technology, the world&amp;rsquo;s first and only military-grade noise-eliminating technology; and the JAMBOX and BIG JAMBOX wireless speakers and speakerphones. Jawbone’s approach to lifestyle tracking is unique, with over 110 patents filed related to UP and its wearable technology manufacturing processes. Jawbone is privately held and headquartered in San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jawbone is an equal opportunity employer, offers an exciting opportunity for qualified career-motivated professionals. We provide competitive compensation, stock options and the chance to work with talented people in a winning, successful, and pleasant environment. We offer many premium benefits including 401(k), medical, dental, life insurance, Paid Time Off and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-jawbone-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-jawbone-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Ruby Rails Developer at goBalto in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Who we are&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;goBalto is about re-imagining how study teams get clinical trials started and done. We’re building the modern way to work together; a fast and versatile web application that connects sponsors, CROs and sites with what’s going on, their shared priorities, and who owns each part of the effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are software engineering, clinical operations, and thought leaders from companies like Amgen, Genentech, Quintiles, Roche, Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, CERN, McKinsey &amp;amp; Company, Intuit, Cisco WebEx, E*TRADE, Peoplesoft and Sun Microsystems. We are backed by Aberdare Ventures, Singapore EDBI, Qualcomm Life Fund of Qualcomm Ventures, West Health Investment Fund, and an experienced team of advisors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why we’re here&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The clinical study startup process is awful. Existing tools used to track site activation tasks and documents are manual, bloated and complex. To take the next step in clinical study productivity, we need a fresh start. We created goBalto to help take that step; to improve the productivity of sponsors, CROs and sites, to ultimately get medicines to those in need faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you’ll do…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with product management and the engineering team to build functionality in the Tracker application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operate as a member of the goBalto agile development team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pair program with other top notch rails engineers, developing across the full stack of functionality from database to front end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build full stack automation tests to ensure that the shipped product is as solid and reliable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills we&amp;rsquo;d like to see&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 – 5 years experience at a senior level with Ruby on Rails.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal skills in order to help fellow team engineer members with coding/scripting issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable expertise and recent experience with the following:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Service Oriented Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working and deploying on Linux systems (required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with cloud based deployments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database experience, preferably with PostgreSQL or a similar system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Team attributes&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not just another social app – we’re building a meaningful product with the potential to speed the delivery of new medicines to market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile bones – we promote an agile, test-driven engineering practice that emphasizes team collaboration through pair programming, daily standups, retrospectives, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technology you’re already passionate about, and want to do more – we’re using the latest technologies (ruby, rspec, angular) to build solid, well-tested, and beautiful web applications, and challenge our engineers to learn and do more with them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What’s in it for you…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become part of a team that is new, energized, and going places…fast.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grow and develop right along with goBalto.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earn a generous compensation package, including benefits from day 1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental, vision care, commuter checks and a 401(k).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reap the fruits of stock options as a reward for your energy, contributions, and dedication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A PTO plan that starts accruing the moment you start.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in the Financial District close to transportation, dining, wine, and shoe shine stands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And, the best part…the opportunity to catch a house set with in-house DJ Robyn, during our Casual Hour Fridays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Interested? Send your CV or LinkedIn profile to jobs@gobalto.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-rails-developer-gobalto-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-rails-developer-gobalto-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Alcatel-Lucent in Calabasas, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;With operations in 130 countries, Alcatel-Lucent is the first truly global communications solutions provider, offering the most complete end-to-end portfolio of solutions and services in the industry.  Our passionate and experienced team converts challenges into opportunities in the areas of fourth-generation mobile networking, metro optical and packet, circuit-to-packet, broadband access, advanced network and professional services, and next-generation operations support systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Team:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team the intern will be joining is the Business Operations, Web Group.  This team is responsible for all aspects of the Enterprise public website and the Enterprise intranet.  Development and maintenance of web based tools and content is the team’s primary responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Position:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The student will be responsible for maintenance and creation of web pages for the enterprise intranet and public websites.  Development of lightweight applications to facilitate web publication.  Working with ColdFusion, stylesheets, JavaScript and html.  Maintaining day to day web ops with web browser based tools as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Alcatel-Lucent student co-op program runs parallel to a student’s current class work allowing them to remain in school while gaining work experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Co-op&amp;rsquo;s must be actively pursuing an undergraduate or graduate degree to be eligible for the program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Essential Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a working knowledge of Web Design and Stylesheets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a familiarity with HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Required Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be pursuing a bachelors degree or higher in Web Design or Computer Science from an accredited college/university&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have at least a 3.0 GPA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work from the Calabasas, CA office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Alcatel-Lucent is an equal opportunity employer committed to diversity in the workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-alcatel-lucent-calabasas-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-alcatel-lucent-calabasas-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior JavaScript Developer at iLaunch.it in Silicon Valley, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you excited by Javascript, HTML5, and CSS3? Do you believe users should come first? Have you ever wanted to make a difference in the lives of millions of people? Go Daddy is looking for a highly motivated Sr. JavaScript Engineer to build the ultimate experience for our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position can be based in Scottsdale, Gilbert, Denver or Sunnyvale&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;In this role you will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write low maintenance, high reliability code to be used in a highly trafficked 24/7 environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the UX design team and build front-end interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive API design requirements to be deliver the User Experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot technical issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Do you have what it takes?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mature, independent, yet receptive to team participation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work at a fast pace and iterate rapidly over a design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firm grasp of object-oriented Javascript and prototypal inheritance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of software design principles and ability to guide others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal, communication and organizational skills with the ability to interact effectively with employees at all levels within the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in Javascript development including Node.JS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with MVC frameworks such as Ember, Angular, Backbone.JS or SproutCore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience implementing responsive designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NoSQL experience (Redis, Cassandra, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid academic background &amp;ndash; business, engineering or I/T related degree preferred (additional experience may substitute).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Understanding of HTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and understanding of cross browser compatibility issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL knowledge and relational database design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Go Daddy’s award-winning technical teams design and support the innovative technologies that are transforming the cloud, the internet and the world.  From product developers to network engineers, data center technicians to platform engineers, our expertise ensures our customers have the technical solutions to meet their needs. We develop world-class products that help our customers establish, enhance and evolve their online presence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Are you ready to GO with us?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you GO with Go Daddy, you have the opportunity to be part of something special by making a meaningful difference in the lives of our customers. Their success is our success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what you need:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion to contribute to a truly exceptional customer experience, no matter your job title&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding that innovation and creativity is a part of what we do every day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agility and action orientation – we move at the speed of tech&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the privilege and obligation of being part of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what we’ll provide:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fun, dynamic and challenging work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formal and informal opportunities and support for ongoing learning, growth and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team building activities and recognition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive base plus bonus incentive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer-paid medical, dental, and insurance coverage for all benefit-eligible Go Daddy employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three weeks paid vacation your first year of employment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Go Daddy has been recognized because of its outstanding benefits, compensation, unique perks, diversity and company camaraderie. Go Daddy was awarded the 2011 and 2012 Alfred P. Sloan Award for Business Excellence in Workplace Flexibility Honoree &amp;ndash; Arizona, Iowa &amp;amp; Denver. Go Daddy is the #1 IT Company on Inc. Magazine&amp;rsquo;s inaugural Hire Power list of job creators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go Daddy’s philanthropic work supports a wide variety of charitable and community organizations dedicated to causes including women and children, domestic violence, child abuse, teenage homelessness, animal shelters and more. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.GoDaddyCares.com&quot;&gt;http://www.GoDaddyCares.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go Daddy is proud to be an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-javascript-developer-ilaunch-it-silicon-valley-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-javascript-developer-ilaunch-it-silicon-valley-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer - Internship at Rafter.com in San Mateo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Rafter, Inc., the leading course materials management platform, lowers the cost of education by providing colleges and universities with much needed tools to manage the rapidly changing world of course materials on campus. To learn more visit www.rafter.com and watch our video. Rafter evolved from BookRenter.com, the first online textbook rental site, launched in 2008 with a mission to make education more affordable by allowing students to rent textbooks for up to 80% off the retail price. Rafter is one of the few private ed tech companies that is truly lowering the cost of higher education for students. By working directly with more than 300 schools to turn the painful and archaic process of managing course materials into a low cost, student-centric service, Rafter has saved students more than $250m. By taking an enterprise approach to course materials management, the Rafter Course Materials Network takes a more holistic approach that provides colleges and universities with a path to discover, adopt, distribute and manage physical and digital course materials. 500+ schools run on Rafter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Super smart junior developers looking for internships to join our front-end web development team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be responsible for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with front-end developers and product managers on the enhancement and development Rafter Products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively contributing ideas for product improvements and solutions to technology challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Showing a passion for continued learning, staying abreast of new technology and trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivering clean code supporting consistent user experience and product quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable or comfortable writing code in HTML, CSS, Javascript/jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passable knowledge of Ruby on Rails or a related interpreted language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for developing excellent software and an appreciation for elegant code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and appreciation for industry UX standards and beautiful UI and design &amp;ndash; complex, modern web page look-and-feel and interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with agile development techniques including test-driven development and priority-based planning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written/verbal communication skills and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a team as well as independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listens and takes direction and critiques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent problem solver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academic Experience in the following areas: Computer Science, Computer Engineering, Electrical Engineering or Mathematics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we can offer you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to gain professional experience in a vibrant, young company that really makes a difference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The chance to learn new skills and develop existing ones alongside an experienced team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permanent role is also a possibility for candidates demonstrating the capabilities and attitudes that we value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Are you an active contributor to open source software?  We love to see your work &amp;ndash; send us a link to your GitHub projects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-internship-rafter-com-san-mateo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-internship-rafter-com-san-mateo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Speck Products in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Speck is obsessed with designing cases that are just as smart and indispensable as the gadgets they protect. Founded in 2001 by a group of design engineers, and located in the heart of Silicon Valley, we are captivated by technology, fanatical about our gadgets, and consumed with making products people love. Our focus on what people care about inspires us to craft cases that are a perfect fit. We make cases that don’t just protect phones, MacBooks, ereaders and tablets – they also contain clever details that spark delight in our customers. Speck&amp;rsquo;s line of products can be found at Apple retail stores, AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, Target, Toys R Us and at speckproducts.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a well-rounded Web Developer that can design and code.  In this role you will use your HTML, CSS3 and jQuery skills to enhance and polish our eCommerce platform making our shopping experience delightfully unexpected, yet intuitive.  Are you a designer, too?  Can you design layouts without much direction and you bring it to life using Adobe Creative Suite?  Even better!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What You’ll Do:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as the bridge between technology and design/content.  Success will require working closely and effectively with team members, colleagues, and cross-functional partners (internal &amp;amp; external) to develop and deliver superb, highly engaging consumer experiences online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be relentless in learning, adopting and adapting to bleeding edge technology in order to consistently produce best-in-class work, deploying quality assured, well-tested code to production. Knowledge of and proven experience with agile deployment and rapid application development without compromising quality is strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm, collaborate, design and produce web graphics, online marketing assets and interface design solutions that drive conversions, but also convey our brand message and feel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create webpage wireframes with as little as napkin sketch (and do so quickly, within reason, of course).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create beautifully responsive, pixel-prefect layouts that are highly useable and perform well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using your UX and UI skills, create multiple layout experiences for A/B testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code HTML email newsletters that look great on web and mobile devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create interesting advertising assets for social, Amazon, ebay, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn new stuff all the time:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maybe you will be needed to help create presentations that tell a story with builds and animations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maybe you will be asked to create a fun animated GIF&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maybe you’ll want to learn how to create beautifully rendered cases in 3D Studio Max, Maya, or KeyShot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generative Art&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About You:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience partnering, liaising, and working with creatives (e.g. designers, copywriters, etc).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design skills and strong experience in Adobe Photoshop (Adobe Illustrator a plus).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of content management systems (e.g. Magento).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to assist with HTML templates for e-mail newsletters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript and jQuery. Using out-of-the box JS plugins and styling to existing designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to develop and implement maintainable and scalable cross-browser code across large sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to troubleshoot cross-browser compatibility issues with multiple versions of Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari, Google Chrome, and mobile browsers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the latest HTML5/CSS3 standards and tricks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge, skills and abilities to code and deliver Photoshop designs in HTML/CSS format within tight deadline requirements (sometimes you may just get a JPG and you’ll need to design without specs just to get the ball rolling).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to quickly create rough, working prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A team player to flex between a leader and/or implementation contact as required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A perfectionist who makes sure every pixel is in the right place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;A Big Plus:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating visual effects for web or video.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The capacity and desire to learn Photoshop, After Effects, or Processing (e.g. http://weavesilk.com/).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with eCommerce CMSs (Magento in particular).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coding HTML newsletter templates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile front end development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decipher CSS specs from Adobe Illustrator files (e.g. Selecting type and determining size, line-height, and color).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web usability expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Your Professional Profile:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS or MS in computer science, graphic design, MIS and/or related degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of related work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Speck Products does not accept agency resumes. Do not forward resumes to our jobs alias, contact Speck employees, or our community. Speck Products is not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates who move forward in the final selection process will be subject to both reference and background checks, conducted by a third party, as a condition of our hiring policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speck Products is a proud equal opportunity workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-speck-products-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-speck-products-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Lunarpages in Anaheim, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for people who want a career in web development. This position is for a PHP web developer. We need someone with a passion for web programming and a reputation for doing great work. We offer great benefits and a casual, fun work environment. Remote and local applicants accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, develop, implement and maintain new PHP web applications, adhering to coding standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and enhance existing services and internal applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills/Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability in PHP and MySQL development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. in Computer Science, Engineering, or related field (experience accepted in lieu of degree)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to hand-code HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript/DHTML (Prototype/Scriptaculous a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of object oriented design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate effectively, both orally and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux shell environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version control systems (Subversion, CVS, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other languages such as Perl and Ruby a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-browser/cross-platform compatibility testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MVC application frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database schema design and optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-lunarpages-anaheim-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-lunarpages-anaheim-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Python Developer at Luma Pictures in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Luma Pictures is an artist centric feature film VFX studio located two blocks from the beach in Santa Monica, California. We maintain a unique culture with an amazingly talented staff and are always on the lookout for exceptional people for full time and project positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an exceptional freelance web developer to work on site for roughly 2-6 months, with the possibility of full time staff. You will lead the development of new python-based web applications to extend our proprietary project management system. The ideal candidate will have experience building both backend and frontends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;design, develop, and maintain our proprietary project management system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;create various Javascript/AJAX rich tools from spec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;python web development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP / LAMP development experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;understanding of MVC frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience with Javascript, jQuery and jQuery UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demonstrated understanding of good UX principles and design aesthetics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solid work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;relentless attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;strong problem solving and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent with time management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/python-developer-luma-pictures-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/python-developer-luma-pictures-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>