<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Pulsepoint in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is a highly independent self-starter with at least two-three years of experience and a great sense of humor. The User Experience and Creative Group is made up of a motivated group of close-knit professionals, including developers, information architects, Web designers and other creative types who work hard every day to provide an intuitive and innovative experience for the customer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like to laugh hard, live life harder, and desire to work in a dot-com start-up type environment that relies on collaboration and imagination, then we’d like to talk to you right away. Okay, there are a few other requirements we’re asking for — so take a look at the list below. If you have all, or most, of these qualifications, we’d like to hear from you right away!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What we’re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two to three years experience in web interface and layout design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree (or comparable work experience) and experience in a web-related environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate understanding of HTML/CSS, with direct experience optimizing design concepts around these technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio that displays an understanding of user-centered design (online portfolio preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to work closely with information architects, copywriters, developers and others to produce a team-driven end product that leads to a top-notch user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to deliver high quality work consistently and on time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An appreciation for the excellence that the above collaboration can produce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail, while also considering the big picture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Although production work is part of the daily responsibilities of this position, this designer will routinely be called upon to create cutting-edge designs that align with the brand of the site while enhancing the user experience. This position will include, but not be limited to, designing navigation, splash/landing pages and icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:Core Competencies:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong HTML, XHTML, DHTML, CSS, XML programming skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in JavaScript / Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Macromedia HomeSite or IDM UItraEdit, Adobe Photoshop / Image Ready, Adobe Illustrator, Macromedia Fireworks, Macromedia Dream Weaver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of interaction design and user-centered design methods &amp;amp; practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience collaborating with design and development teams on large-scale projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and track multiple tasks across multiple projects, under tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy working closely with others, respectful of other perspectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert conflict resolution skills and being able to negotiate with stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and manage multiple tasks across multiple projects, under tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized, self-directed, efficient and able to manage complex projects in a timely manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to switch gears quickly and be flexible to work on concurrent projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create clean, precise browser-compatible code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience with HTML, XHTML, DHTML, CSS, XML, RSS, JavaScript, AJAX, Flash and other related interactive technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years experience in e-commerce, retail merchandising/marketing, advertising, product development, e-commerce or related fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Website Localization Issues and Web Accessibility Standards a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with IBM Web Sphere, JSP, Swing, Struts would be a definite asset but not necessarily required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Marketing, Visual Communication, Graphic Arts, Computer Science or related area a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agency/Design Firm experience a big plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio of your best recent work will be reviewed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Onward ITG in Burlingame, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Excellent opportunity for an experienced Front End Web Developer in San Mateo, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our latest Web Developer position will be responsible for the development of complex sites and web applications or large components of our client&amp;rsquo;s web site. You&amp;rsquo;ll be architecting solutions from requirements gathering through execution and implementation for high profile clients in a range of different industries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain the latest next generation web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;developing high performance, responsive user interfaces for modeling, wrangling, processing and storing massive datasets and managing server clusters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;developing a user interface that plays a critical role in the companies user experience &amp;mdash; allowing users to navigate through data and visually manipulate massive data sets to gain new insights and also to share and tell stories around their data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively use CSS, HTML and JavaScript to program pages from creative comps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 /CSS3 Knowledge is a huge plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Responsive development helpful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will develop core frontend components of a fast, scalable, complex web application (Haml, CoffeeScript, HTML5, SASS, CSS, JavaScript) using libraries and frameworks (e.g. Knockout JS, Angular JS, Ember JS, Batman JS, Closure). The sleek, beautiful results of your work make you an integral part of our product/engineering group as you define, design, and develop new features with a top-caliber team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years web development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in CSS, HTML with experience in Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML5, CSS3, and Responsive Design a strong plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works independently with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to research solutions and information independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in usability and accessibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please apply today for immediate consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-onward-itg-burlingame-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-onward-itg-burlingame-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Bump in La Jolla, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You will be part of a growing team to develop a cloud based SAAS application. As an applicant you should be well versed in multiple aspects of PHP Web Development techniques. Top candidates will have a high level of experience in OOPHP, MySQL, Javascript, HTML and CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full time position in La Jolla, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. in Computer Science with 2+ years of industry experience or equivalent experience regardless of education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced in HTML, JavaScript, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mid-Advanced PHP experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent debugging and testing skills, and cross-browser compatibility knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MySQL experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Highly Desirable&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of jQuery or similar JS framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AJAX, XML, JSON and Web Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile Team experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with OO PHP MVC/HMVC frameworks (Kohana 3.0+ preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating social networking products (FB Connect, twitter API) is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Personality Traits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated self-starter with a keen eye for design and layout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem solving and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to tackle challenging problems on a tight schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn new languages and technologies quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovative, enjoys challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commensurate with experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Benefits offered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;BUMP Network, Inc&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Located on the cliffs of La Jolla, California, BUMP offers an invigorating, positive working environment. Our team is composed of talented, innovative, and motivated individuals who share a commitment towards creating the world&amp;rsquo;s largest safety, communication, and membership network. At BUMP, every employee plays an integral role in the network&amp;rsquo;s success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are committed to hiring, promoting, and compensating employees based on their qualifications and demonstrated ability to perform job responsibilities. As an equal opportunity employer, BUMP promotes equal employment opportunity to all employees and applicants, without regard to age, race, color, national origin, physical or mental disability, gender, religion, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital or veteran status, condition of pregnancy, or any other legally protected characteristic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BUMP does not accept unsolicited agency resumes. We are not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-bump-la-jolla-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-bump-la-jolla-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Spendgo in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a motivated Sr. Web Developer who understands that great web-based applications are not just about the back-end or front-end, but truly a team effort to create a seamless elegant product. Every day we are disrupting the consumer-merchant-brand ecosystem like no one else has, using our patent pending technology to collect real-time itemized transaction data. This means we are constantly facing new challenges finding better ways to build intelligent Big Data applications and manage an ever expanding and interrelated data set. Our development team is rapidly growing and we’re looking for a super-star to get in on the ground floor and help build our cloud products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person who takes this position will play a key role in developing all of our web applications, portals, data systems and analytics for consumers, merchants and brands. You will be entrusted with the design and delivery of key features of web products, driving rapid iterations while keeping an eye on scale as we handle massive and multiple streams of data. You will be given the freedom and ownership to turn your ideas into great products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing UI and server side frameworks using SOA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of Java/J2EE, MySQL, Hibernate, REST, and Spring Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of open source technologies such as Apache, Tomcat, and MemCached&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of NoSQL databases such as MongoDB, Casandra, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of RDMS and implementing optimized data structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production level experience with display side languages and libraries. We use Jquery quite a bit, would be great if you did too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a continuous integration development environment using Agile Methodologies like Scrum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;San Francisco Office location with tons of free parking and close to public transportation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great Compensation: We offer competitive salaries and significant equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer paid Medical, Dental and Vision benefits for all employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many nerf weapons to defend yourself during spontaneous battles with the sales team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Topsy Labs, Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Topsy is looking for an exceptional web developer to join our front-end team to work on Topsy Pro, a leading social media analytics product. Topsy Pro is built on top of the Topsy indexing platform, which is the largest index of social data on the web.  Our platforms are accessible through REST &amp;amp; JSON, and we develop enterprise products that have modern consumer web sensibilities.  As part of the front-end team, you will be responsible for building product features that enable our customers to harness the insights provided by condensing the social web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement front-end capabilities in Topsy’s products: Topsy Pro Analytics &amp;amp; Topsy.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with backend engineers and product managers to define and implement feature sets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work across the front-end site stack, from interface design to implementation in CSS, Javascript &amp;amp; Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience writing Javascript, CSS, and HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong command of web standards, CSS-based design, cross-browser compatibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with Python and the Django Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a UNIX environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with REST and working with APIs, developing APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with product managers, back-end engineers and operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable foundation in interaction design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work through product ideas by fast prototyping and quick iterations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;DESIRED SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual-design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with building mobile applications and mobile UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. or higher in Computer science or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PHP, Python, Perl and other server-side languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-topsy-labs-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-topsy-labs-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer - LAMP at Elevano in Costa Mesa, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years PHP developer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP5 &amp;ndash; Candidate should be a top-noch developer, familiar with the latest features in PHP 5.3.X.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MySQL – Cutting edge database development expertise, words like &amp;lsquo;trigger&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;view&amp;rsquo; should be part of your vocabulary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XHTML/CSS/Javascript/AJAX &amp;ndash; Expert level Javascript/XHTML/CSS development will be necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 and jQuery experience preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Oriented Development / CS Background &amp;ndash; Ideal candidates should understand object oriented development, and apply OO concepts to everything they do. Formal CS background or experience preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead on a large B2C project/product that will become the primary internet presence of the company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prefer experience with high-volume transactional systems, such as eCommerce or order fulfillment, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead capacity on high profile applications with multi-sourced data models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science; advanced degree preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Services – Experience building modern web services (plus to have)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile App Development – IOS and Android (plus to have)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social App Development (plus to have)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We do not accept 3rd party agency resumes.  Unable to provide sponsorship at this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elevano is a premier provider of innovative Information Technology Solutions and Resources.  We offer a wealth of employment opportunities for technical professionals. You will be empowered to do the best job and achieve your professional goals.  Our goal is to match your talent to the best job.  Elevano is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elevano Consulting Inc.
Web: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.elevano.com&quot;&gt;http://www.elevano.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-lamp-elevano-costa-mesa-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-lamp-elevano-costa-mesa-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at FriendFinder Networks Inc. in Sunnyvale, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT US:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a leading Internet-based social networking and multimedia entertainment company operating several of the most heavily-visited websites in the world. We provide our customers with a wide variety of online products and services, appealing to members of diverse cultures and interest groups, so they can interact with each other and enjoy our content. Our sites’ services include social networking, online personals, live and recorded video, online chat rooms, instant messaging, photo and video sharing, blogs, message boards, email, and premium content websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Web Developer will be responsible for architecting, developing, and working on a wide array of projects written on object-oriented Perl/JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and update web content and code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather functional &amp;amp; technical requirements from stakeholders and technical users in order to plan releases and updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface with cross-functional teams in the development process from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate code to ensure that it is valid, properly structured, meets industry standards and is compatible with browsers, devices, or operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide recommendations for improvements to site architecture, design, and functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage bug tracking system and prioritize changes with business stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot and debug applications that occur outside of the regular release cycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science or related field or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Perl 5, and MySQL 5, minimum of 2+ years’ experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate knowledge of JavaScript, XSLT, HTML, CSS 2+ years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Object Oriented Programming and Service Oriented Architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with AJAX, CSS, DHTML, XHTML, JavaScript Frameworks, and mod-Perl in a LAMP environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of JavaScript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligence and a sense of humor to mix in well with a diverse group of bright engineers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Methodical in documenting and testing own code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be at least 21 years old&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be comfortable with adult content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;SKILLS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently and as a member of a cross functional team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High degree of honesty and integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline oriented and multi-tasking ability in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team-player, positive attitude and flexible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;BENEFITS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FriendFinder Networks Inc. and its subsidiaries offer a business casual work environment, flexible work hours, and a competitive salary.  The benefits** package includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) with a 4% match on year to date earnings with no vesting period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision and AFLAC Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Account for Healthcare and Dependent Care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life Insurance, LTD and AD&amp;amp;D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Time Off (PTO) and Holiday Pay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commuter Benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;529 Education Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition Reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Club Reimbursement*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complimentary Breakfast and Catered Lunches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;** Benefits vary depending on location and are subject to change without notice. Please check with Human Resources for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-friendfinder-networks-inc-sunnyvale-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-friendfinder-networks-inc-sunnyvale-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Ruby on Rails Developers at SocialChorus in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for a chance to do agile development? Do you want to immerse yourself in extreme programming using test driven development? Then SocialChorus is for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SocialChorus is forming a powerhouse of technology that measures social reach through paid and earned media through influencer distribution. Our technology stack is up to date with current standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On to our development practices. We are on Rails 3.2.8 with deployment on Heroku and test driving EVERYTHING with Rspec, Jasmine, and Selenium. Every Monday we have an internal planning meeting that includes the dev team along with our project manager to go over upcoming features, stories that need discussion, and story estimation (Pivotal Tracker). Mornings start with stand-ups to go over the previous day&amp;rsquo;s work, work for the current day, or any blockers anybody might have. Pair programming and green tests make the day fly by with the gratification of clean code without broken windows. Our analytics module runs in EC2, hitting nginx, aggregating all data into our sharded MongoDB database. Like to map/reduce over extremely large data sets? Sweet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great startup environment with a kegerator, ping pong table, Ruby Meetups every 3rd Thursday, Settlers of Catan, Bang!, Dominion, and poker tournaments! Food trucks every wednesday and friday too. Come join our team at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.socialchorus.com/company/jobs&quot;&gt;http://www.socialchorus.com/company/jobs&lt;/a&gt; or email jobs@socialchorus.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactoring&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debugging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintenance of successful social media SaaS application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Programming experience on SaaS platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have some experience with RoR and Front-end technologies (OO Javascript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with test-driven development (rspec and Test::Unit to Selenium and Jasmine)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About SocialChorus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SocialChorus helps brands find the people whose social influence matters most for your brand, then work with them in authentic ways to drive real marketing results . Our Influencer Relationship Management (IRM) software and services give brands the simplicity, speed, and efficiency they need to build enduring social relationships at global scale. As social influence grows, so does ROI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SocialChorus has offices in New York City and San Francisco, both of which are fostered by richly creative energy and hard-working team-oriented environments. We encourage a work hard, play hard attitude and value employees who thrive on collaboration, bring passion and enthusiasm for social media, and who are leaders both in and outside of the office.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-on-rails-developers-socialchorus-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-on-rails-developers-socialchorus-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior PHP Developer at Earthbound Media Group in Irvine, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Scope of Job&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EMG is seeking a Sr. PHP Developer to augment our progressive team of engineers. The position is for long term contract (6+ months) with intent to move to a permanent position within our company. The project we are hiring for could quite possibly be one of the coolest projects you have ever worked on. It combines front-end development with hardware integration within the entertainment industry. EMG will be using a true agile sprint planning process. This position is one among a project team of 4+ developers for this particular project. There will also be a mid-level PHP developer that you will work side-by-side with. No matter what level of engineer you are hired as, there is an expectation that you will teach and learn from your peers and teammates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EMG offers a wide array of technical projects to work on in various languages and platforms, each with a different challenge. Our environment is set up so that our developers can touch a little bit of everything for their own experience, and that also enables EMG to deliver high quality products for our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All employees of EMG must be positive with a “can do” attitude. The ability to understand risks and time/scope implications and be able to communicate those to your Director of Technology is required. There is not one person at EMG that does not have an entrepreneurial spirit. We work hard and play hard, together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The position requires the developer to work at EMG offices throughout this project’s duration on EMG supplied hardware. EMG offices are currently located in Culver City, CA. We will be moving to our new home towards the end of Q3 2012 which is at the Hercules Campus nearly 10 minutes from the current location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Candidate will have:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years overall professional software development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of PHP development experience (preferably recent experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with a relational database (preferably MySQL)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with design principles (patterns, cohesion/coupling, S.O.L.I.D.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile engineering practices (test driven development, continuous integration and pair programming, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional familiarity with object oriented development principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability (and enthusiasm) in mentoring less experienced developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Prefer candidates who additionally possess:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engineering web development, all layers, from database services to user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Oriented JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with eCommerce development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with high-volume web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the development, deployment, and enhancement of RESTful APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a medium or large corporate environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you meet the above qualifications, please forward your resume to resume@earthboundmediagroup.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-php-developer-earthbound-media-group-irvine-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-php-developer-earthbound-media-group-irvine-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Application Developer at Nutanix in San Jose, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for talented individuals who want to be part of an exciting startup that is building something new and ground-breaking. At Nutanix, you&amp;rsquo;ll find no shortage of challenging problems to work on &amp;ndash; changing the world is after all never easy! Not only will you be given surprising amounts of responsibility but you will work in a collegiate, collaborative environment that encourages the open exploration of ideas. We welcome big thinkers and budding entrepreneurs, unafraid to take on seemingly impossible challenges and interested in learning how to build a business along the way.
What We Do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nutanix is the first company to offer a radically simple compute and storage infrastructure for implementing enterprise-class virtualization without complex and expensive external network storage (SAN or NAS). Founded in 2009 by a team that built scalable systems such as Google File System and enterprise-class systems such as Oracle Database/Exadata, Nutanix has won the 2011 Best of VMworld Gold Award, been named to Gigaom&amp;rsquo;s Top 50 Cloud Innovators list, VentureWire&amp;rsquo;s most Innovative Tech Startups, CRN&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Storage Startups, and won the SearchStorage&amp;rsquo;s 2011 Product of the Year, among others. Nutanix is based in San Jose, California, and is backed by Lightspeed Venture Partners, Khosla Ventures, Goldman Sachs, Battery Ventures, and Blumberg Capital.
Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nutanix conducts its employment practices in a manner that treats each employee and applicant for employment on the basis of merit and experience, without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity, marital status, age, disability, veteran status, sexual orientation, national origin, or other classification protected by applicable law. In addition, consistent with Nutanix&amp;rsquo;s culture and business need, employees are expected to treat each other with respect and dignity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Current Openings:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web Application Developer &amp;ndash; Customer Portal and Salesforce Lead Developer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web Application Developer&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; At Nutanix, you&amp;rsquo;ll find no shortage of challenging problems to work on &amp;ndash; changing the world is, after all, never easy! Not only will you be given surprising amounts of responsibility, but you will work in a collegiate, collaborative environment that encourages the open exploration of ideas. We welcome big thinkers and budding entrepreneurs, unafraid to take on seemingly impossible challenges and interested in learning how to build a business along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Nutanix, you&amp;rsquo;ll find no shortage of challenging problems to work on &amp;ndash; changing the world is, after all, never easy! Not only will you be given surprising amounts of responsibility, but you will work in a collegiate, collaborative environment that encourages the open exploration of ideas. We welcome big thinkers and budding entrepreneurs, unafraid to take on seemingly impossible challenges and interested in learning how to build a business along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the design and development of the real-time web-based interfaces of the Customer Portal and Salesforce-based infrastructure for Nutanix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Nutanix customers, partners, SRE team and Engineering team to define and develop the layout and functionality of these portals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead development of test and validation infrastructure for the external interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, implement, and improve the Case Handling, KB, Discussion Forums, Training and Documentation, Licensing and Asset Tracking functions of our customer-facing support site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the internal pages and processes which are used by&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in design and development of our Partner Portal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with team to evolve and improve functionality of our Customer Portal services and Internal SFDC-based processes over time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of web development experience using Salesforce, successful development of a portfolio of Salesforce-based portal sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and hands-on experience with popular MVC frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Visualforce and Apex site development with Salesforce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Salesforce Sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Salesforce &amp;ldquo;Service Cloud&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of code management life cycle, and how to use the Salesforce sandbox for proper testing and code promotion to production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of Salesforce permissions structure and access controls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Knowledge of DNS and implementing DNS records for a Salesforce-based portal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Knowledge of DHTML/CSS/Javascript/jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Oriented Design (OOD) and Object Oriented Programming (OOP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in UX and UI principles and design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in portal authentication and SSO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web services experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills, problem solving skills, customer service and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Engineering (or equivalent technical degree and 6+ years work experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with search indexing for web portals and federated search (Apache Solr/Lucene)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile development methodology and experience working in a startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subversion/GIT experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development experience on relational and non relational databases (preferably MongoDB and MySQL)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business Intelligence tools experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Amazon Web Services and VMware Virtualization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Certification as a Salesforce Developer, Salesforce Administrator, or Salesforce Architect&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-nutanix-san-jose-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-nutanix-san-jose-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>