<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at AllData in Elk Grove, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Web Developer’s role is to build the operations end of the organization’s Web sites and keep them running smoothly. This includes designing, building, and implementing new Web pages and sites; integrating sites with back end applications; migrating legacy applications to the Web; and performing day-to-day administration of the organization’s Web portfolio. Use of a variety of Web development languages is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Strategy &amp;amp; Planning&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate is setting organizational Web development strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and communicate Web site usage and security policies and standards to all users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define Web site architecture and overall site structure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish policies and procedures for publishing Web pages and applications in conjunction with content creators.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Acquisition &amp;amp; Deployment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform cost-benefit analyses of proposed Web implementations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct research into current and emerging Web technologies and issues in support of Web development efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Operational Management&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install and configure HTTP servers and associated operating systems, and establish appropriate server directory trees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, recommend, and prioritize new Web features and applications in conjunction with business leaders and department managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee Web development projects, including intranets and extranets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, code, install, test, debug, and document Web applications using appropriate editors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Register Web servers and sites with domain name services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update Web pages to ensure site accuracy and currency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diagnose and troubleshoot problems with existing Web applications and sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with database administrator to design, develop, and update databases as they relate to Web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure security of all Web sites and related applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform periodic Web site audits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor and report on Web site traffic and performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and/or provide guidance to junior members of the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;ALLDATA® is the leading provider of automotive repair information and solutions to the professional automotive service industry. Thousands of professional repair and collision shops across North America depend on ALLDATA for service &amp;amp; repair information, shop management and customer relations solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-7 years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of Web technologies, protocols, and tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of Internet programming languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of application development methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with computer graphic and multimedia design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive experience with structuring, developing, and implementing interactive corporate Web sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in installing, upgrading, and maintaining Web servers and associated operating systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of database development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in gathering and analyzing business requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project management experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of the organization’s goals and objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML (including html5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript (jQuery a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic Design and Usability Experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-alldata-elk-grove-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-alldata-elk-grove-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at LinkedIn in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you dream in markup? Can you bend uncooperative browsers to your will using only a toothpick, some chewing gum, and a well placed &amp;lsquo;position: relative&amp;rsquo;? As soon as you finish a project, do you step back and think, &amp;lsquo;Now, how can I make this better?&amp;rsquo; We&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn is looking for web developers who are eager to tackle the challenges of a rapidly growing web application with millions of daily visitors. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for developers to help build rich, dynamic client-side interfaces using Javascript, leveraging new technologies like HTML5 and CSS3, to launch fast/scalable products for our 200+ million global users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our Linkedin Labs page which showcases products built on what we call &amp;lsquo;inDay&amp;rsquo; each month.  inDay is an innovation day where LinkedIn employees have no meetings and are encouraged to work on something not already on the roadmap to keep creative juices flowing. Here is a quick video to explain more about inDay: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9Ny_jFV4dTk
And to see the products created on inDay check out our labs: www.linkedinlabs.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Responsibility:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will own the front-end development for one or more of our products and collaborate with visual/interaction designers, engineers, and product managers to launch new products, iterate on existing features, and build a world-class user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will implement cutting-edge technologies and will be writing state-of-the-art code to keep LinkedIn at the cutting edge of current technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your specific expertise will be required to make efficient use of A/B testing frameworks, fast page load times, and efficient UI development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meet with colleagues including product managers and engineers assigned to your project(s).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3+ years experience with semantic HTML/XHTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing clean, unobtrusive Javascript/AJAX including experience with common libraries (YUI, jQuery, etc) and debugging tools (Firebug, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An encyclopedic knowledge of browser quirks and their remedies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating front-end code with server-side technology on a large-scale, dynamic website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of (and a passion for) current trends and best practices in front-end architecture, including performance, accessibility and usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and comfort with command-line applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree or equivalent experience required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JSP programming a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters degree preferred, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-linkedin-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-linkedin-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Volcom in Costa Mesa, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Volcom is looking for an experienced front end Web Developer that will be responsible for planning, developing, deploying and maintaining solutions using the latest tools and technologies. You will work with the Web team to develop applications that support and enhance the user experience on Volcom’s websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop websites that support the brand and e-commerce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create excellent user experiences using leading technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update old web applications using newest technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage web projects from beginning to finish (project planning, design/develop, execution)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four-year college degree or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience web application development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work well within a team environment and communicate with multiple departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Core skills required:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of HTML / CSS / JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a Javascript framework (i.e. jQuery).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of XML/JSON and web services, and integration with 3rd party systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object-oriented programming and modern practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with source control management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop and Illustrator experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desirables:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with 3rd-party web technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with Wordpress, ability to edit theme files, create plugins, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UX Design / Web design experience a major plus!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Volcom is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-volcom-costa-mesa-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-volcom-costa-mesa-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Application Developer at Blue Tangerine Solutions in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Ebates is the pioneer and leader of online cash back shopping. Ebates pays members cash back every time they shop online as well as provide them with the best coupons and deals online. Since the company&amp;rsquo;s 1998 inception, more than 12 million Ebates members have spent over $2.5 billion via Ebates.com and earned over $80 million in cash back (and growing).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ebates offers a casual but fast paced environment where creativity and effective teamwork and collaboration are rewarded. We are passionate about changing the way people shop online and providing the best possible customer experience &amp;ndash; not to mention cash back on every purchase, with no strings attached.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even after 12 years in business, the company is driving rapid growth and searching for the right developer to help our systems meet demand and satisfy our increasing number of customers.  The right candidate will have a passion for creating, coding and implementing scalable web designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Application Developer will be responsible for supporting and creating new pages, applications and widgets for the existing web site and infrastructure, as well as developing new technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate must display excellent written and oral communication skills with demonstrated interpersonal and organization abilities. A candidate for this position must be able to work in a varied, fast paced environment. Flexibility and tolerance is a necessity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience coding web pages for very high traffic, scalable and available consumer applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be an HTML, HTML5 and CSS wizard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely experienced with Javascript – JQuery in particular.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent with XML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be able to work with existing codebase and find out practical solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to constructively influence a distributed team with new design paradigms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in computer science, MIS, or related experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to create an HTML/CSS page that is a near exact replica of a JPEG or PSD design and that works across a larger set of browsers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a solid focus on page speed and a good understanding of basic principles (e.g., deferring javascript, sprites/css, compression).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of JSP, Velocity (and Velocity Template Engine) knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of scripting languages (PHP, Ruby, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AJAX (dojo, scriptaculous, prototype).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile (JQuery for Mobile, Sencha).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL, MySQL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;QA, UI design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing for Facebook Pages and iFrames.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile coding experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;App coding experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience with ecommerce or affiliates or online advertising a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in structured environment with increasing levels of responsibility and complexity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work additional hours as needed, especially around holidays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely hands on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a high growth start-up environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash, animation, video.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Benefits include Medical, Vision and Dental insurance, along with 401k. Equity provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Information About This Position:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No travel required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work at SOMA office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-blue-tangerine-solutions-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-blue-tangerine-solutions-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP Web Developer at QuinStreet in Foster City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You will be part of a team that’s very visible and is highly valued throughout the organization. You will contribute to the design and implementation of our major products and services. This will include but not limited to building the data access layer, writing APIs, developing modules to provide essential services such as implementing core methodology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PHP Web Developers are expected to work independently but also in collaboration with Web Producers and Technical Managers to innovate and create web applications. We like to work aggressively but also set realistic expectations in meeting our business and development needs. We use an “Agile style” development methodology, so you will be working on small teams and in short cycles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with PHP and MySQL to design, develop and debug Web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and deploy PHP implementation of core algorithms with a solid understanding of    coding best-practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate back-end services with PHP/JavaScript based front end needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the team to manage, optimize and customize multiple web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain technical documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree and/or 4+ years software development experience or equivalent, including Object Oriented design and PHP Development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with front-end scripting including: HTML, DHTML, JavaScript, CSS, AJAX.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with web application architecture and relational database design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of search engine optimization (SEO) and marketing (SEM)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the LAMP environment (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding and demonstrated adaptation of cross-platform, cross-browser compatibility  concerns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in building database-driven applications and Web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in PHP development frameworks is required. Previous experience with Code Igniter is a huge plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong presentation, communication, and collaboration skills, enabling effective interaction and knowledge transfer to teammates and other departments within the company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A high task load is expected. You should be able to work within tight deadlines while exhibiting exemplary time management and task prioritization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive attitude and professionalism in the workplace as well as great sense of humor is always appreciated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-web-developer-quinstreet-foster-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-web-developer-quinstreet-foster-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Pulsepoint in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is a highly independent self-starter with at least two-three years of experience and a great sense of humor. The User Experience and Creative Group is made up of a motivated group of close-knit professionals, including developers, information architects, Web designers and other creative types who work hard every day to provide an intuitive and innovative experience for the customer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like to laugh hard, live life harder, and desire to work in a dot-com start-up type environment that relies on collaboration and imagination, then we’d like to talk to you right away. Okay, there are a few other requirements we’re asking for — so take a look at the list below. If you have all, or most, of these qualifications, we’d like to hear from you right away!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What we’re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two to three years experience in web interface and layout design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree (or comparable work experience) and experience in a web-related environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate understanding of HTML/CSS, with direct experience optimizing design concepts around these technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio that displays an understanding of user-centered design (online portfolio preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to work closely with information architects, copywriters, developers and others to produce a team-driven end product that leads to a top-notch user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to deliver high quality work consistently and on time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An appreciation for the excellence that the above collaboration can produce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail, while also considering the big picture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Although production work is part of the daily responsibilities of this position, this designer will routinely be called upon to create cutting-edge designs that align with the brand of the site while enhancing the user experience. This position will include, but not be limited to, designing navigation, splash/landing pages and icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:Core Competencies:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong HTML, XHTML, DHTML, CSS, XML programming skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in JavaScript / Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Macromedia HomeSite or IDM UItraEdit, Adobe Photoshop / Image Ready, Adobe Illustrator, Macromedia Fireworks, Macromedia Dream Weaver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of interaction design and user-centered design methods &amp;amp; practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience collaborating with design and development teams on large-scale projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and track multiple tasks across multiple projects, under tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy working closely with others, respectful of other perspectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert conflict resolution skills and being able to negotiate with stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and manage multiple tasks across multiple projects, under tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized, self-directed, efficient and able to manage complex projects in a timely manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to switch gears quickly and be flexible to work on concurrent projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create clean, precise browser-compatible code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience with HTML, XHTML, DHTML, CSS, XML, RSS, JavaScript, AJAX, Flash and other related interactive technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years experience in e-commerce, retail merchandising/marketing, advertising, product development, e-commerce or related fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Website Localization Issues and Web Accessibility Standards a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with IBM Web Sphere, JSP, Swing, Struts would be a definite asset but not necessarily required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Marketing, Visual Communication, Graphic Arts, Computer Science or related area a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agency/Design Firm experience a big plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio of your best recent work will be reviewed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Onward ITG in Burlingame, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Excellent opportunity for an experienced Front End Web Developer in San Mateo, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our latest Web Developer position will be responsible for the development of complex sites and web applications or large components of our client&amp;rsquo;s web site. You&amp;rsquo;ll be architecting solutions from requirements gathering through execution and implementation for high profile clients in a range of different industries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain the latest next generation web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;developing high performance, responsive user interfaces for modeling, wrangling, processing and storing massive datasets and managing server clusters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;developing a user interface that plays a critical role in the companies user experience &amp;mdash; allowing users to navigate through data and visually manipulate massive data sets to gain new insights and also to share and tell stories around their data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively use CSS, HTML and JavaScript to program pages from creative comps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 /CSS3 Knowledge is a huge plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Responsive development helpful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will develop core frontend components of a fast, scalable, complex web application (Haml, CoffeeScript, HTML5, SASS, CSS, JavaScript) using libraries and frameworks (e.g. Knockout JS, Angular JS, Ember JS, Batman JS, Closure). The sleek, beautiful results of your work make you an integral part of our product/engineering group as you define, design, and develop new features with a top-caliber team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years web development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in CSS, HTML with experience in Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML5, CSS3, and Responsive Design a strong plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works independently with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to research solutions and information independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in usability and accessibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please apply today for immediate consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-onward-itg-burlingame-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-onward-itg-burlingame-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Bump in La Jolla, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You will be part of a growing team to develop a cloud based SAAS application. As an applicant you should be well versed in multiple aspects of PHP Web Development techniques. Top candidates will have a high level of experience in OOPHP, MySQL, Javascript, HTML and CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full time position in La Jolla, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. in Computer Science with 2+ years of industry experience or equivalent experience regardless of education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced in HTML, JavaScript, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mid-Advanced PHP experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent debugging and testing skills, and cross-browser compatibility knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MySQL experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Highly Desirable&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of jQuery or similar JS framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AJAX, XML, JSON and Web Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile Team experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with OO PHP MVC/HMVC frameworks (Kohana 3.0+ preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating social networking products (FB Connect, twitter API) is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Personality Traits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated self-starter with a keen eye for design and layout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem solving and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to tackle challenging problems on a tight schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn new languages and technologies quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovative, enjoys challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commensurate with experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Benefits offered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;BUMP Network, Inc&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Located on the cliffs of La Jolla, California, BUMP offers an invigorating, positive working environment. Our team is composed of talented, innovative, and motivated individuals who share a commitment towards creating the world&amp;rsquo;s largest safety, communication, and membership network. At BUMP, every employee plays an integral role in the network&amp;rsquo;s success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are committed to hiring, promoting, and compensating employees based on their qualifications and demonstrated ability to perform job responsibilities. As an equal opportunity employer, BUMP promotes equal employment opportunity to all employees and applicants, without regard to age, race, color, national origin, physical or mental disability, gender, religion, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital or veteran status, condition of pregnancy, or any other legally protected characteristic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BUMP does not accept unsolicited agency resumes. We are not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-bump-la-jolla-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-bump-la-jolla-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Spendgo in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a motivated Sr. Web Developer who understands that great web-based applications are not just about the back-end or front-end, but truly a team effort to create a seamless elegant product. Every day we are disrupting the consumer-merchant-brand ecosystem like no one else has, using our patent pending technology to collect real-time itemized transaction data. This means we are constantly facing new challenges finding better ways to build intelligent Big Data applications and manage an ever expanding and interrelated data set. Our development team is rapidly growing and we’re looking for a super-star to get in on the ground floor and help build our cloud products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person who takes this position will play a key role in developing all of our web applications, portals, data systems and analytics for consumers, merchants and brands. You will be entrusted with the design and delivery of key features of web products, driving rapid iterations while keeping an eye on scale as we handle massive and multiple streams of data. You will be given the freedom and ownership to turn your ideas into great products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing UI and server side frameworks using SOA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of Java/J2EE, MySQL, Hibernate, REST, and Spring Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of open source technologies such as Apache, Tomcat, and MemCached&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of NoSQL databases such as MongoDB, Casandra, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of RDMS and implementing optimized data structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production level experience with display side languages and libraries. We use Jquery quite a bit, would be great if you did too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a continuous integration development environment using Agile Methodologies like Scrum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;San Francisco Office location with tons of free parking and close to public transportation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great Compensation: We offer competitive salaries and significant equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer paid Medical, Dental and Vision benefits for all employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many nerf weapons to defend yourself during spontaneous battles with the sales team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Topsy Labs, Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Topsy is looking for an exceptional web developer to join our front-end team to work on Topsy Pro, a leading social media analytics product. Topsy Pro is built on top of the Topsy indexing platform, which is the largest index of social data on the web.  Our platforms are accessible through REST &amp;amp; JSON, and we develop enterprise products that have modern consumer web sensibilities.  As part of the front-end team, you will be responsible for building product features that enable our customers to harness the insights provided by condensing the social web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement front-end capabilities in Topsy’s products: Topsy Pro Analytics &amp;amp; Topsy.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with backend engineers and product managers to define and implement feature sets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work across the front-end site stack, from interface design to implementation in CSS, Javascript &amp;amp; Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience writing Javascript, CSS, and HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong command of web standards, CSS-based design, cross-browser compatibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with Python and the Django Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a UNIX environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with REST and working with APIs, developing APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with product managers, back-end engineers and operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable foundation in interaction design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work through product ideas by fast prototyping and quick iterations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;DESIRED SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual-design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with building mobile applications and mobile UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. or higher in Computer science or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PHP, Python, Perl and other server-side languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-topsy-labs-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-topsy-labs-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>