<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Product Designer at User Testing in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://UserTesting.com&quot;&gt;http://UserTesting.com&lt;/a&gt; is a fast-growing start-up in Mountain View (right off 101) in our 5th year of business.  We’re in the business of helping website managers answer one question: “WHY are people leaving my website without buying?”  We do that by recording ‘think-aloud’ videos of people using websites, so you can quickly see why they get stuck and frustrated.  We’ve become part of the website and mobile improvement process for companies like Google, Amazon, Facebook, Walmart, and Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for a smart and energetic Product Designer who&amp;rsquo;s all about design that is easy to use. From conception to sketches to iteration to production, be prepared to own and organize your work.  Ideal candidates will successfully take charge of entire features, pages, and apps.  Experience working with engineers is an absolute must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a STRONG preference for someone who can work on site at our office near Google in Mountain View.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll manage new products through their life-cycle, from design to implementation. Responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop mockups, wireframes, specs, and other guides for development for new features and products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web site design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with sales, marketing, engineering, and customer support to prioritize needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather and incorporate feedback from customers and internal teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage multiple projects and initiatives simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Our Ideal Candidate Has:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience as an online product designer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in the field of usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product development experience at a start up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with project management and productivity tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of delivering projects on time and on budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong teamwork and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of UserTesting.com and other usability tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product Management Certification or related degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What We Offer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IRA plan with matching contributions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid vacation and company holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gym membership reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid time off to work at a charity or nonprofit of your choice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll be working for the Chief Product Officer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;UserTesting.com is a profitable 35 person company and recently raised $3M to acclerate our growth. The product team is only four people including you so you&amp;rsquo;ll have a huge impact on our mission of making the web a better place.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-product-designer-user-testing-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-product-designer-user-testing-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Interface Designer at Hathway in San Luis Obispo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Hathway, we live and breathe the quality of work we produce and in the creative process we trust. We are looking for a creative leader with a stacked portfolio, a love of interface design and the desire to create amazing and innovative work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior User Interface Designer will lead the HATHWAY creative team and is responsible for creative vision, user experience, visual communication, graphic design and asset production. Responsibilities include website user interface design, mobile application design and digital campaign design along with some occasional branding and print projects. This individual is a versatile and multi-faceted pixel slayer with a keen understanding of web technologies and a mastery of design tools. We are seeking a conceptual thinker that shines in front of the computer AND in front of the client while also producing crazy, beautiful work on a deadline and within budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior User Interface Designer will contribute various forms of design and production support to the team as well as lead client interaction during the design phase. Among other things, you will:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspire and collaborate with your co-workers to produce inventive, thoughtful, outstanding work for clients (web interfaces, mobile apps, branding, and more&amp;hellip;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with your team to execute on the creative strategy for projects by creating viable design schemes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead all aspects of design and production for your team’s projects, focusing on innovation, quality, and usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand and work within project parameters: client goals and requirements, internal goals, usability, technical constraints, budget and schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate an understanding of industry trends and share your insights with the whole team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Applicant Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An amazing online portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of Adobe Photoshop &amp;amp; Adobe Illustrator and basic knowledge of the entire Master Suite. (Experience with Premier Pro, AfterEffects &amp;amp; Flash are a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of web and mobile design trends and technologies (knowledge of print applications and production process is a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and client management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive user interface design experience while living on the forefront of web design concepts (html5/css3, mobile web, native mobile, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Availability to work from our office in San Luis Obispo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Moving forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To apply for this position please email your resume and portfolio to jobs@wearehathway.com. If you knock our socks off, we&amp;rsquo;ll give you a call.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-interface-designer-hathway-san-luis-obispo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-interface-designer-hathway-san-luis-obispo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Interactive Designer at SolutionSet in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;SolutionSet’s Digital Practice is looking for a top-notch Senior Designer to join our team. As a Senior Designer, your responsibilities include the design and production of projects based on creative specifications provided by the Creative/Art Director and/or Project Manager. You will also collaborate with the various departments within the company to ensure a successful project and delivery of the creative goals. Senior Designers are expected to bring their sense of design and detail along with some personality to all projects they are assigned to while working within deadline-driven work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;WE’D LIKE TO MEET YOU IF YOU CAN:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Articulate Brand in an interactive medium&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show strong problem solving abilities in visual, written, and verbal forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate an understanding of how technology and design impact brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry multiple projects from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know the ins and outs of managing priorities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate a passion for the design in the interactive medium&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive in a deadline-driven environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;JOB BREAKDOWN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;60% Project work and creative development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20 % Pre-production development create redlines, style-guides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% Project level concept and strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;KEY AREAS OF RESPONSIBILITY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and extend visual concepts that align with creative strategies, architecture, and user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Senior Creatives and copywriters to refine and extend creative solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create cutting-edge interfaces for display, rich media, widgets, websites and other interactive mediums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to carry concepts to pre-production level quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6+ years of creative, advertising or interactive agency experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of graphic design principles such as typography, layout, color, composition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of User Experience artifacts such as sitemaps, wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of User Interface Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Web enhancement technologies such as Ajax and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of HTML development and testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of Adobe CS4&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of Pre-Production protocols and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design or Interactive Media related degree or diploma or equivalent experience in the interactive design field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have online portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please have good examples of your previous work to show while explaining the details involved in their design/production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT SOLUTIONSET&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SolutionSet is an award-winning digital consultancy built from the ground up to combine the thinking, creativity, and passion of a digital agency with the strategy, process, and engineering depth of a technology consultancy. We design and develop web, mobile, social and digital marketing solutions to help leading companies better engage and serve customers. SolutionSet clients include American Express, California Lottery, Cisco, Dell, Duke University,Intel, and TXU Energy. SolutionSet is a Hyper Marketing, Inc. company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SolutionSet is an equal opportunity employer and will not discriminate against any individual, employee, or application for employment on the basis of race, color, marital status, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, national origin, handicap, or any other legally protected status recognized by federal, state or local law. SolutionSet is committed to hiring veterans and military spouses.
SolutionSet offers a competitive salary and comprehensive benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interactive-designer-solutionset-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interactive-designer-solutionset-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at Barracuda Networks in Campbell, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Barracuda Networks is looking for an outstanding web and graphics designer to produce beautiful, usable interfaces for a brand new product offering. In addition to bringing product design innovation, you will be positioned to provide broad design and user interaction leadership across the company. This is a great opportunity to join a talented and fun team to bring exciting new technology to the market from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide design ideas and implantation guidance formobile device management web portal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrate a compelling simple vision for how customers will manage their products and services through usage scenarios provided by product management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promote our creative culture through educating, inspiring and developing the group’s skills and determination to execute great interactive work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead projects under the supervision of senior team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present creative concepts and capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create mockups and design graphics that demonstrate UI standards/best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident and capable of juggling multiple projects simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of web design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong graphics design skill ( with portfolio to match )&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand modern web technologies design principles &amp;ndash; working knowledge of how to translate wireframes into design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent graphics production skills (Photoshop or like)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front end web development experience a plus (HTML, CSS, Javascript, Ruby, PHP etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with developers to deliver a high quality product in an agile software development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you are interested, please send your resume to jobs@barracuda.com. Please place &amp;ldquo;Req 12-223 Web/Graphics Designer&quot;in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-barracuda-networks-campbell-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-barracuda-networks-campbell-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Interaction Designer at Leads360 in El Segundo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Leads360 is a market leading provider of cloud-based lead management and sales automation solutions proven to deliver smarter, more efficient lead distribution and sales processes for improved conversion rates. With unmatched expertise, drawn from a dedication to helping more than 5,000 clients automate and improve their lead distribution, response and conversion processes, Leads360 has become the platform of choice for organizations focused on improving customer acquisition practices and business performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leads360 is a three-time winner of the Los Angeles Business Journal Best Place to Work award, and we have a strong culture based on the principles that each of us act as owners; seek the truth; collaborate and listen; expect to be accountable; embrace change; obsess about making our clients successful, and value work/life balance. We offer lots of in-office perks, and a competitive benefits package to each team member.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leads360 is a privately held company, recently recognized as one of the fastest growing companies in North America by Deloitte and backed by financial investors Rustic Canyon Partners and Volition Capital. We are looking for qualified, energetic, innovative, team-players to help take the business and the solutions we offer to new heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead interaction design for projects, including gathering requirements and mapping the requirements into page flows and page designs. Create logical and easy-to-use navigation, page layout, and interaction design across multiple applications. Create both static wireframes and interactive high-fidelity wireframes.  Create content inventories and blueprints. Document user experience requirements.  Perform competitive analyses.  Contribute to ongoing process improvement, including best practices and standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For individual projects, lead information architecture and interaction design work, including gathering requirements and mapping the requirements into page flows and wireframes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and update page layout, page flow, site architecture, interaction design, and logic for application pages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with User Experience, Product Managers, Marketing, and business stakeholders on project requirements, along with the overall strategic direction and vision of the applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create design solutions that integrate business, product, and User Experience requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For some projects, act as the User Experience Project Lead, managing the project schedule and approvals for the User Experience team deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare all interaction design documents and write guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide input and support for user research and usability test plans.  Apply results of research to designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with members of the User Experience and Technology groups to develop leading-edge interactivity and functionality that can also be efficiently implemented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that user requirements are carefully balanced relative to the technical constraints and business requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create solutions designed to scale and grow over time, as the functionality and content matures and as user requirements evolve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide input and support for User Experience team members pertaining to architecture, navigation, and interaction design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write guidelines and document design decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create page templates, IDs, and names.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the development of style guides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the development of best practice standards, deliverable templates, and process improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 6 years performing interaction design and information architecture for large-scale, corporate web sites and web applications, with an emphasis on functional design and content integration (navigational elements, images, and text).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 2 years of B-to-B experience desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evidence of successful interaction design, including navigation, templates, and design patterns for complex applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Axure and Visio for creating page flows and wireframes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of Internet technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interaction design and visual composition skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the limits and constraints of design for the web and across different browsers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to integrate the requirements of different teams and business units and ability to negotiate to create a unified user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with project management, including setting schedules and delivering to those schedules.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS in Human-Computer Interaction, Design, Human Factors, or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide direction, leadership and collaboration in the creative process from conception to final production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extreme attention to detail and commitment to high-quality production standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proactive and innovative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work in a team environment with an iterative design process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation and Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work in a team environment with an iterative design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compensation based on experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 weeks of vacation and 8 company holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Medical/Dental/Vision Plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company-provided Life and Long-term Disability insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K with company matching contributions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock Options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What others have to say about us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Money talks &amp;ndash; Leads360 was recently featured on TechCrunch regarding our latest round of VC funding. &lt;a href=&quot;http://techcrunch.com/2012/02/03/lead-management-company-leads360-raises-15-million/&quot;&gt;http://techcrunch.com/2012/02/03/lead-management-company-leads360-raises-15-million/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deloitte&amp;rsquo;s Fast 500 list recognized Leads360 as one of the fastest growing technology companies in North America.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In 2012, Los Angeles Business Journal listed us as one of the &amp;lsquo;Best Places to Work in LA&amp;rsquo; for the third year in a row. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bestplacestoworkla.com/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;task=view&amp;amp;id=60&quot;&gt;http://www.bestplacestoworkla.com/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;task=view&amp;amp;id=60&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interaction-designer-leads360-el-segundo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interaction-designer-leads360-el-segundo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Petco in San Diego, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Position Purpose:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conceptualize, design, illustrate and/or produce all in-store graphics, both internal and external and to develop strategic branding guidelines for all related collateral.  Develop strategic designs for in-store graphics including logo development, campaigns, themes, vendor collateral, Petco messaging and marketing aesthetics.  Produce, pre-flight and archive all artwork and sign templates.  Create all support materials including informational brochures, pocket cards, action memos, and other special projects.  Coordinate all related production entities including in-house/outside digital imaging, photographers, printers and pre-press.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through previous background and experience, the candidate must demonstrate, with or without any accommodation, the ability to…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact professionally and effectively through verbal and written communication with all professional contacts with emphasis on company interests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independently prioritize and accomplish multiple tasks within established timeframes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze data to determine appropriate courses of action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work Environment:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of job duties are conducted while seated indoors with little or no exposure to hazards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Education/Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position requires a bachelor of fine arts/bachelor or arts degree with special emphasis on graphic and/or packaging design and/or 5-7 years design experience incorporating a minimum of 2-4 years experience in an senior-level packaging design position. Qualified applicants will have in-depth training on programs running on Macintosh OS platform including QuarkXpress, Adobe PhotoShop and Illustrator. Exceptional freehand drawing/sketching skills are required.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-petco-san-diego-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-petco-san-diego-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Designer at Lumos Labs in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;With 35+ million current users and hundreds of thousands of new additions every month, Lumosity&amp;rsquo;s creative team makes marketing campaigns and product features that are viewed by millions of people around the world. And we&amp;rsquo;re looking for a talented designer to help get our message out there. We want a visual communicator and problem-solver who knows digital advertising front to back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;YOU WILL&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with marketers, product managers, and engineers to conceptualize and execute designs for Lumosity&amp;rsquo;s merchandising, business, marketing or branding objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create multiple design solutions to solve creative marketing problems (both online and offline) while meeting business and communication objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create flash and marketing assets (including animations and banners) that clearly communicate with customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide production support for team members as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promote design thinking at Lumos Labs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;YOU HAVE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio featuring user-friendly web design and creative branding work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep knowledge of typography and grid systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Adobe skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Flash, HTML, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pixel-perfect attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to clearly articulate design decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good writing skills and an understanding of basic content strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of user-centered design and navigation structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Graphic Design, Interaction Design, or Communications Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-designer-lumos-labs-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-designer-lumos-labs-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at Womply in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Womply is looking for an exceptional designer to work closely with our CEO and Director of Product to set the creative direction for our consumer and merchant facing products. This role will include UX/UI, and Visual design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You must:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a deep understanding of fundamental visual and interactive design principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess a blend of visual, interaction, and user experience design capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to visualize, own and execute the creation of an experience from initial concept to final pixel perfect implementation. Collaboration with developers will be an important part of your role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have extensive experience designing beautiful, engaging user experiences for the web and mobile. Your portfolio should reflect this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain an unrelenting commitment to outstanding quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be self-motivated and can work independently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to create gorgeous visuals, ranging from content layouts to icons and illustrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have an expert eye for detail. Every pixel counts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a great communicator and play well with others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve built amazing products in the local or mobile space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience designing for sales, marketing, or advertising&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML, CSS, or applicable programming languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re a lover of Apple products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You live by the ways of the Honey Badger&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If this excites you, please introduce yourself with a brief paragraph explaining what makes you tick. Include a link to your portfolio which showcases your visual design skills and other relevant work that you’re proud of.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-womply-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-womply-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at KIXEYE in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;KIXEYE is currently looking for a kick-ass UX Designer. You’ll get to work with all our game teams, as well as help support our new platform. You’ll be responsible for requirements gathering and creating wireframes/flows to support our UI team in the creation of assets for all of our products. It also goes without saying that you need to fight for the user day in and day out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you get to do everyday:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide comprehensive designs for all our games’ new features, specifying layout, functionality, and flow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather design requirements from appropriate stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocate and lead UX discussions; achieve best-possible designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive design thinking and champion the UX vision across the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm, research, wireframe, design and refine user experiences within product requirements and deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other designers, program managers, and engineering teams, working to prioritize UX design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create wireframes, workflow diagrams, mockups and design specifications required for proper implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you bring to the role:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in applied UX design,  Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid portfolio demonstrating your UX skills with examples of process used on projects (please specify work done individually or with a team)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for UX and keeping current with recent usability trends and best of practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Balsamiq, Omnigraffle, Visio or other UX wireframing tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be comfortable with a motion driven process. UX design is highly iterative and includes multiple rounds of brainstorming and revisions to find the perfect solution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication skills with the ability to present and explain UX ideas and concepts effectively whether verbally, written or through visuals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open minded and collaborative approach to UX with the ability to take direction and constructive feedback and use it to create easy to use solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to produce in a fast paced environment with a dedication to iterate in pursuit of the best UX solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated worker with ability to prioritize and manage work load to meet critical project deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to grow your skill sets and broaden your experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sense of humor. Or, openness to the occasional, unsolicited dick/fart joke&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be an avid gamer! Live and breathe games!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Stuff that helps:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undergraduate degree or equivalent certificates in interaction design, industrial design, graphic design, or other UX design-related field; Master’s degree preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a game development team as a user interface designer, artist, or game designer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and presentation skills; ability to present design solutions for game UX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong project management skills; ability to manage schedules and identify project needs and priorities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of PC and console games; familiarity with MMO and shooter games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on familiarity with Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Art skills—not required, but nice to have&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on familiarity with HTML and CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-kixeye-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-kixeye-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web/Graphic Designer at j2 Global in Hollywood, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About j2 Global:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1995, j2 Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:JCOM) is an award winning, leading provider of cloud services to individuals and businesses around the world. j2 Global&amp;rsquo;s network spans 49 countries on six continents, supporting the company’s  more-than 11 million eFax customers and voice services customers. The Company provides Internet fax, voice, email and online backup solutions to a wide range of businesses, from sole proprietors to Fortune 500 companies. j2 Global markets its services principally under the brand names eFax®, Onebox®, eVoice®, FuseMail®, Campaigner®, KeepItSafe® and CampaignerCRM™.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2012 alone, j2 Global® has been recognized by Los Angeles Business Journal (“20 Biggest Telecommunications Firms,” “Most Profitable Companies,” and LA’s “Largest Public Companies”), as well as a repeat ranking in the InformationWeek 500, a prestigious global listing of the leading technology companies that includes many Fortune 500 companies. It’s brands have also been recognized as industry leaders, including eFax receiving an “Editor’s Choice” award from PC magazine. As of December 31, 2011, j2 Global had achieved 16 consecutive fiscal years of revenue growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Our Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast-paced and dynamic, j2 Global, Inc. is not your typical 9-to-5 work environment.  Operating from numerous international offices – including Hollywood, Ottawa, Dublin, and our emerging market in Tokyo, Australia, New Zealand – and supporting a plethora of time zones, j2 Global™ truly lives up to its name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The executive staff has an open door policy, inviting each member of the company – from directors and managers to entry-level positions and interns – to partake in casual conversation.  Employees are not just colleagues – they’re business partners, fostering an efficient and effective environment.  The inviting and energetic environment creates a world where differing opinions matter and collaboration leads to success.  From a small start-up in 1995 to an award-winning company recommended by Forbes, j2 Global, Inc. has grown by establishing an amazing company culture – one that will continue to foster ingenuity and invention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;j2 Global, Inc. is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Director of Creative Services the Sr. Web/Graphic Designer is as a key member of a dynamic in house Creative Team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating web sites, landing pages, HTML emails, banners, print pieces and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with Marketing and Creative Services departments to ensure adherence to corporate look-and-feel, and to company technical standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performing all work in a manner which leads to the ultimate goals of increased brand awareness and product sales while raising the bar creatively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates must be experienced with a proven track record of success. Have a strong portfolio that demonstrates his/her design skills as well as strong conceptual/strategic thinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;9+ years’ experience in developing and implementing creative campaigns/projects (design and/or copy) with an ad agency, interactive agency, or in-house creative department.  5+ years web experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct Response Marketing experience a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses expert knowledge of computers and the Internet—including both PC and Macintosh platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a command of the creative requirements of marketing communications including: advertising, print collateral, logo development, and interactive multimedia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess expertise in design for the web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational, time management, communication, and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website production work-flow skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with scheduling and organization of production tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good eye for design and photographic color correction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project management skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be self-motivated and the able to multi-task 2 to 5 projects simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work as part of a team, share ideas, offer and take constructive reviews, yet at the same time, work independently to assure your responsibilities are completed accurately and in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Driven to assume increasing levels of responsibility within a growing company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be deadline oriented with good organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent skills in Adobe CS3 apps such as Photoshop, Illustrator, Fireworks, Flash, Dreamweaver.  MYSQL, JavaScript, Flash/Action Script, Fireworks/Image Ready, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer experience necessary includes an understanding of HTML, CSS, PHP, XML.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education:  BA Degree in marketing, communications, graphic arts, advertising, interactive media, or related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-graphic-designer-j2-global-hollywood-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-graphic-designer-j2-global-hollywood-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>