<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. Visual Designer at Rovi Corporation in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Rovi, we connect people to the entertainment they love.  Our products and services power some of the most iconic entertainment and technology brands around the world including Comcast, Samsung, iTunes and Pandora. Rovi is headquartered in Santa Clara, California with over 1,800 employees worldwide working to create a better entertainment experience.  To learn more, watch The Rovi Story&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rovi Corporation is a global B2B leader focused on revolutionizing the digital entertainment landscape by delivering software and data solutions to connect people to the movies, music and television they enjoy – anytime, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;130 million viewers use our interactive program guide technologies through cable and satellite service provider offerings. Customers include: Comcast, Cox, Charter, Time Warner Cable, AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approximately 220 million consumer electronic (CE) devices use our CE-guide technologies including products by: Dell, LG, Motorola, Panasonic, Philips, Pioneer, RCA, Samsung, Siemens, and Sony&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rovi has information on over 3.6 million TV shows, 28 million tracks and 500,000 movie titles. Metadata customers include: Spotify, Shazaam, MOG, iTunes and Google.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rovi’s Cloud services are revolutionizing the consumer electronics industry and service providers space by helping them drive sales and consumption with advanced media search and discovery capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rovi Advertising Network reaches more than 40 million households globally and offers advertisers a platform to serve targeted interactive advertisements with high levels of engagement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Senior Visual Designer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Visual Designer will create and maintain visual elements for the various projects associated with (but not limited to) consumer web projects. You will work with the UX director and Product Managers to ensure the design is easy to use consumer friendly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You would be responsible for&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Line art illustration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logos, mastheads, and banners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brand and style guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing materials and emails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting in creation of design prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;We&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design SideReel.com as well as other Rovi consumer web properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work at a sustainable pace – roughly 9 to 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think “meow” can be a noun, verb, adjective, and a state of mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You should&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have experience working on a large consumer web site in the capacity of graphic or visual design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be an expert in the latest versions of graphic design software, including, but not limited to Adobe Photoshop/Fireworks/Illustrator/InDesign&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a solid understanding of web page optimization standards and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have a solid understanding of user-centered design principles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have experience creating and maintaining graphic specification documents&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience with developing graphics for web- and mobile-based applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be excited to work with a dynamic and collaborative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience working at a fast pace on multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be our flavor of crazy &amp;ndash; we enjoy working together and hope you will too!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You are especially intriguing if you have&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML and CSS, especially if it&amp;rsquo;s HTML 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Print production experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent time working within an agile team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;When applying, make sure to include a link to your design portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-visual-designer-rovi-corporation-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-visual-designer-rovi-corporation-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UI Designer at Sling Media, Inc. in Foster City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Sling Media is a digital lifestyle products company, focused on creating empowering entertainment experiences for consumers. Sling Media&amp;rsquo;s award winning Slingbox turns any Internet-connected PC, Mac, or mobile device into your home television allowing you to watch your TV virtually anywhere in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Senior UI Designer at Sling Media, you will inspire new consumer TV and Video experiences for the Television, Web and Mobile. You will bring strong interaction and Information Architecture (IA), creative vision and a clear user-focused point of view to design key user interfaces. You will brainstorm, storyboard, wireframe, and prototype to support a variety of products and experiences. You will be measured by your product and expected to be relentless in pursuit of elegance, simplicity and innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;General Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive interaction design background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to translate product requirements into detailed user flows/wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to manage workflows and liaise directly with PMs to evaluate requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross platform experience across web, iOS, Android and 10ft preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor/Master’s degree in graphic arts, interaction design, or a design related field is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-6 years related work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Critical Competencies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly proficient with Photoshop, Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with After Effects, Solidworks, Alias, or Rhino3D is a bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail is a mandatory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear communicator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent/hard worker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet deadlines and work under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Applicant must provide portfolio of relevant design work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-designer-sling-media-inc-foster-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-designer-sling-media-inc-foster-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Interactive Designer at Meredith Corporation in Culver City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Senior Interactive Designer works to reshape the advertising for the leading pharmaceutical-cosmetics brand, Allergan. From web, mobile and digital CRM to traditional collateral and motion graphics, this individual will play a key role in creating an entirely new brand program from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Partner closely with the writing team to concept and create compelling integrated campaigns.
Own responsibility for maintaining a consistent visual language across all communications
Oversee production and the development of client work
Partner with Creative Director; integrating feedback as required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;br/&gt;
All must be met to be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor Degree in Design, Advertising or New Media; or equivalent combination of experience and education&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5-7 years of professional design experience with at least 3 years of digital agency experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Specific Knowledge, Skills and Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio that demonstrates compelling design, typography and interactive experiences, strong conceptual thinking, and a track record of campaign work executed across a number of media types: web, mobile and traditional.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can problem solve and work under tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely versed in Photoshop and Illustrator primarily for screen devices (web, mobile etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have an understanding of print design and different printing techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of motion graphics is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on female oriented brands is big plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with minimal supervision and stay on task and on time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interactive-designer-meredith-corporation-culver-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interactive-designer-meredith-corporation-culver-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Yelp in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Yelp can be found everywhere &amp;ndash; from the window of your local pub to those nifty little iPhones. That red Yelp burst is unmistakable, all thanks to our design team. We are hiring a new designer to join us. This role will support our graphics, UI, and marketing needs across the company. If you are ready for your designs to be seen by millions, then send in your portfolio!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create icons and mockups for the website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build marketing materials, including posters, party graphics, mailers, and swag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design custom banner ads for the website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure consistent branding across the site and marketing collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide overall graphic and design support to the company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA or BFA with concentration in Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe CS5 Creative Suite (Illustrator,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop and InDesign. Knowledge of Fireworks a plus).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freehand illustration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to move fast, prioritize, and manage multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sense of humor!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include your Yelp url – understanding our brand is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please submit resumé, portfolio of recent work, and briefly tell us what your favorite website(s) are (and why you go gaga for them).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-yelp-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-yelp-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Delivery Agent in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the product development team in a graphic design capacity.  Majority of work is Production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in product development process for major network &amp;amp; cable entertainment brands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively and accurately manage creative assets and artwork used in merchandise development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the PD team to create presentation decks for clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute product ideas to brainstorm sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years’ experience with graphic t-shirt design is an absolute must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Calm under pressure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid Graphic Design skills to work with type, color, illustrations and photographs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized and can maintain a standardized naming convention across multiple GD platforms including Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and InDesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to recognize the appropriate aesthetic for each particular brand and create graphics accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meets deadlines and detail oriented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional attention to detail and ability to follow through on assignments and responsibilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of current celebrities, pop trends and entertainment media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in developing fan gear products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Top-notch skills in Photoshop, Excel and Power Point.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entertainment experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open to Creative feedback based on goals in an ever changing brand portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Licensed product experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not afraid of ambiguity and is a self-starter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-delivery-agent-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-delivery-agent-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr User Experience Designer at eMeter, a Siemens Business in Foster City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;eMeter, a Siemens Business is where high-tech and green-tech converge. Our mission is to provide robust, next-generation enterprise software and consumer applications that support innovative &amp;amp; clean energy technologies. Smart Meter technology is a high-demand, exciting space that enables leading utilities world-wide to address the energy information challenges they face as they deal with significant technology, regulatory, and innovation challenges. eMeter’s executive team is made up of seasoned thought leaders in the metering technology space and they have a proven record of success in this emerging market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have created a culture that fosters open communication, collaboration and innovation. So, if you want to work in a challenging environment that offers growth, opportunity and the chance to make a real difference, you need to see what eMeter has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity Statement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siemens is an Equal Opportunity and Affirmative Action Employer encouraging diversity in the workplace. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to their race, color, creed, religion, ancestry, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, disability, marital status, family responsibilities, pregnancy, genetic information, veteran or military status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to change the world, helping customers use energy and water more efficiently?  Do you want to become the utility industry expert on User Experience?  As a Senior UX Designer, you will work closely with product managers, the development staff, and other stakeholders to understand product vision and customer needs, gather requirements, and validate proposed designs with real customers. You will help drive the direction of the end-to-end experience for our software and mobile products and find opportunities for further research and improvement.  You will also work to define and implement standards and best practices across the product development team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is passionate about user experience and user-centered design, is eager to learn new methods and technologies, and is able to effectively evangelize user experience and usability best practices throughout the organization.  You are able to communicate your designs verbally and visually with poise and clarity.   You have a reputation as a great collaborator and facilitator, have experience relating to others from different disciplines and backgrounds, and can incorporate insights from many different perspectives into your work.  You like to make work fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define the user model and user interface for new and existing products and features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop high level and/or detailed storyboards, mockups, and prototypes to effectively communicate interaction and design ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gauge the usability of new and existing products, and making constructive suggestions for change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with our members, user experience researchers and others in the business to gain deep understanding of real world customer needs and business goals, and collect valuable feedback and insight in order to drive product direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act as an experience evangelist, advocating for our members and representing their needs and perspectives to the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with stakeholders, team members and customers in an agile user-centered design process to design features, write user stories, partner with UX researchers to validate designs through user research, and work with development teams to ensure correct implementation of your design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On occasion, speak publicly about user experience’s impact to the bottom-line of our enterprise customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Key Relationships&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills and Experiences&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8- 10 years as a user experience designer, with proven experience designing for consumer-facing web applications, e-Commerce sites or SaaS products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to process large volumes of data from many sources to synthesize clear problem sets and solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep experience with multiple UX design tools, such as Fireworks, Omnigraffle or Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working understanding of prevalent web technologies, including HTML, javascript, AJAX, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with user interface guidelines and best practices for major platforms (web browser, iOS, MacOS, Windows) and the benefits and tradeoffs of using various web and mobile technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create pixel-level mockups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in an agile product development environment a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for energy efficiency and green technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong passion for learning and a desire to help others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work as part of a highly collaborative team: able to listen effectively, respectful of others' perspectives and contributions, and able to both offer and accept feedback openly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think beyond what is asked for, act independently, and juggle multiple projects and competing priorities in a fast-paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Please Provide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume that lists your specific contributions to successful products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio, sites or pointers to products on which you&amp;rsquo;ve had direct impact&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-user-experience-designer-emeter-a-siemens-business-foster-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-user-experience-designer-emeter-a-siemens-business-foster-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UX Designer, Yammer Job at Microsoft in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Vision&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every day, we work on a product that is changing people&amp;rsquo;s lives at work. We believe that everyone deserves to use software that is useable, simple, and beautiful, whether they use it in their personal lives or for work. Yammer empowers employees to create a healthier, more transparent, more equal way of doing their jobs. To change more lives at more companies, we&amp;rsquo;re now a part of Microsoft, but we run independently &amp;ndash; and quickly &amp;ndash; in London and San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Gig&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help us lead the London edition of Yammer&amp;rsquo;s User Experience Team as chief user advocate. You&amp;rsquo;ll be a critical part of every London feature from conception to launch, working constantly with product management, research, engineering, and QA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need designers who are great communicators and problem solvers with dead-on interaction instincts, but who know how visual UI design can affect the experience. We need both concise wireframes, and flawless visuals, but we know that they are separate skills and not mutually exclusive to create the best experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the UX design process for product features that will be released in London&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice a highly efficient, iterative design process with light documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Negotiate and articulate the &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; of design decisions. You&amp;rsquo;ll need to convince, to disagree confidently, take and give straightforward criticism.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide interaction/visual specification with visual styling, wireframes, workflow diagrams, and interactive mockups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate frequently with the UX Team in San Francisco to keep consistency with the user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience (or comparable) at various companies designing great consumer facing or enterprise products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed and launched multiple products/major features/apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with cross-functional teams in a rapid paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of technology advantages and limitations required (i.e. JavaScript, CSS, HTML)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Illustrator, Fireworks, Omnigraffle or Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio online or in PDF format&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to demonstrate excellent use of typography, color, imagery, and graphic elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working remotely&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work experience with user research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide production ready files to engineers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The kind of people we&amp;rsquo;re eager to work with are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full of empathy for users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated more by shipping product than building a work of art&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited not daunted by the fact that designs will be validated by qualitative and quantitative research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-yammer-job-microsoft-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-yammer-job-microsoft-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer - Yammer (Mobile/Android) Job at Microsoft in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Social media has dramatically changed the way we share and connect with friends and family, and it will have an even more profound impact on the way companies operate. Yammer and Microsoft provide a secure, private social network for your company. Yammer empowers employees to be more productive and successful by enabling them to collaborate easily, make smarter decisions faster, and self-organize into teams to take on any business challenge. It is a way of working that naturally drives business alignment and agility, reduces cycle times, engages employees and improves relationships with customers and partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Vision&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know devices are the future; come help us design the future of great work software on Android-powered devices. We&amp;rsquo;re building a product that empowers employees to create a healthier, more transparent way of doing their jobs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Yammer team is located in San Francisco, and we maintain the intensity, pragmatism, and velocity of a startup. We release product weekly and projects last weeks, not years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Gig&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team is structured around designers who are flexible, but who specialize in either visual/UI or interaction/UX. Our UI designers translate wireframes into pixel-perfect, typographically beautiful, development-ready visuals. Your visual designs and ideas are an integral part of what makes a feature stick. You&amp;rsquo;ll be part of feature project teams from the beginning until launch, working side-by-side with a product manager, UX designer, researcher, engineering team, and QA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years’ experience working, preferably at more than one past company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of Android’s User Interface Guidelines through completed design work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to demonstrate excellent use of typography, color, imagery, and graphic elements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to negotiate and articulate the &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; of design decisions. You&amp;rsquo;ll need to convince, to disagree confidently, take and give straightforward criticism.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise working daily in Photoshop, Illustrator, or Fireworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide visual specification and production ready files to engineers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio online or in PDF format&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;The kind of people we&amp;rsquo;re eager to work with are:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full of empathy for users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated more by shipping product than building a work of art&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited that their designs will be validated by qualitative and quantitative research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiastic and possibly a little bit weird&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eager to move to a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-yammer-mobile-android-job-microsoft-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-yammer-mobile-android-job-microsoft-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UIDesigner, Desk.com at Salesforce in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salesforce.com&lt;/strong&gt; transformed the enterprise software market with cloud computing. We’ve launched business apps and platforms that are as easy to use as Amazon.com and as social as Facebook. Recognized as the world’s most innovative company and the third fastest-growing technology company by Forbes and for the third consecutive year in 2011 selected as one of the &amp;ldquo;Best Places to Work&amp;rdquo; by FORTUNE magazine, we now have our sights set on the next generation of cloud computing. Our technology teams are the brains behind visionary technologies like the Force.com platform, and enterprise social collaboration tools like Salesforce Chatter and the AppExchange marketplace. With more than 7,000 employees, the first enterprise cloud computing company to exceed $2.0B in annual revenue run rate, and more than 100,000 customers worldwide, we are proud to contribute to the success of companies of all sizes and industries, around the globe. If you&amp;rsquo;re passionate about innovation, come help revolutionize how companies collaborate and communicate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desk.com&lt;/strong&gt; is a fast-paced startup inside Salesforce.com, which means you get the best of both worlds: small teams, fun projects, and fast execution backed by the vast resources of a publicly traded company. We have the cool vibe of a startup and the dependability of an established player. We are headquartered in San Francisco and have really cool offices south of Market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a highly-motivated Sr. UI Designer with a strong understanding of design, to contribute in shaping the user interface of our product and strengthening our online presence across web, tablet, and mobile devices. We drive our product by the user experience, and need someone with the skills who can keep up and push the vision forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will work directly with other members of the product team to build experiences that reinforce the Desk.com brand and help wow our customers. You will get to work in an exciting and engaging agile startup-like environment where you will be encouraged to expand your skills, test your creative boundaries, share new ideas, and most importantly – have fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, iterate, and refine UI and UX concepts for the company’s core products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with product managers, front-end engineers, and other UI designers to insure we maintain a high-quality user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively with your team to meet the demands of our customers, while at the same time continuing to innovate far beyond the competition. .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required/Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are a master of your craft and tools. As a designer you are expected to have a dominating control over Photoshop, as well as create satisfying interfaces boasting user-centered design principles for our core applications. Bonus for a dribbble or other online portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You get excited to work with some of the coolest clients on the web on a product that people love using. With customers like 37signals, Rdio, Square, Pandora, many more, we’re building software that real companies are using and we need you to contribute to our evolution. You must be excited about your role! Anybody can build something that’s “good”, but true passion breeds “incredible.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You like to deliver real results. So, you’ve got some design and prototyping chops but do you have the ability to bring your work to life? This is a great opportunity to expand your front-end skills, and learn from an exceptionally talented team. You’ll need to be able to build those great experiences with HTML, CSS, and Javascript. Bonus if terms like HAML, CoffeeScript, and AngularJS not only make sense to you, but excite you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On occasion, you will have to receive feedback from our customers &amp;ndash; so excellent written and oral communication skills are a must!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-uidesigner-desk-com-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-uidesigner-desk-com-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Principal Product Designer at Salesforce in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an exceptional designer to help lead the design of our products into 2013. This individual should be able to flow effortlessly from high-level strategy to the tiniest details of a design infrastructure, and help grow a solid team of designers in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience / Skills Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master of design and communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Adobe CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to successfully manage all aspects of a project from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be self-motivated, a good communicator, comfortable following direction, and able to balance great design with meeting short deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to produce results independently as well as collaboratively in a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Icon design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytic / Infographic design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile App design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing social products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with pattern libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on various web, mobile and tablet application interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create designs, icons and layouts that adhere to and extend the app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate discussions into leading app designs and layouts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate detailed specs of final designs that allow devs to build accurately&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with devs to deliver polished final product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evangelize new interface guidelines and design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor new members of design staff during onboarding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive in a highly collaborative, fast-paced, agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Top talent from around the world join Salesforce for its “change the world” mentality; the opportunity to excel in a performance-driven, fast-paced, and competitive atmosphere; the chance to be surrounded by peers and leaders that inspire, motivate, and innovate and a corporate philosophy that incorporates community involvement into its fabric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1999, Salesforce.com is the enterprise cloud computing leader. Our social and mobile cloud technologies — including our flagship sales and CRM applications — help companies connect with customers, partners, and employees in entirely new ways. With more than 100,000 customers worldwide, we are proud to contribute to the success of companies of all sizes and industries, around the globe. If you&amp;rsquo;re passionate about innovation, come help revolutionize how companies collaborate and communicate with customers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-product-designer-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-product-designer-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>