<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feeds/ca-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at Scribd in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Scribd is looking for a UX Designer to join our growing Product &amp;amp; Design team to improve existing web and mobile products and build new ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scribd is changing the way people discover and share information. Every day millions of people visit Scribd to read, share, and publish written works. If you&amp;rsquo;re excited by this challenge, we want you. As an important member of a small and agile team, you will be responsible for architecting the user experience for Scribd’s applications. Other responsibilities will include contributing with visual designs, helping streamline the product development process, and conducting usability tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who You Are&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a team oriented individual who enjoys working with product, design, and engineering teams. You enjoy collaboration and appreciate the exchange of ideas and concepts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are passionate about software products and obsess over their usability, and with improving people’s interaction with these. You have extreme attention to detail and are meticulous about how you communicate and document your designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You care deeply about your work and how it will impact millions of users daily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product/design team to define strategy and goals, design site architecture and navigation, and map out user experience in support of business requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Derive detailed use cases, interaction flows, wireframes, and specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and manage work to adhere to critical project timelines in a fast-paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with engineering teams during the development process to ensure designs are properly implemented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish consistent interactions and appearance across all web and mobile products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct regular usability tests for your projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with visual designers to produce pixel-perfect mockups and final artwork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of dedicated experience in UX architecture, interaction design, information architecture, or similar field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience as a member of a cross-functional team where you were part of designing, shipping, and revising more than one customer-facing web, mobile or software product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong comprehension of user-centered design principles, current design, and interaction trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of opportunities and constraints of current and new UI languages, devices, and technologies as they pertain to visual design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and spoken communication skills; comfort presenting cohesive design approaches to non-design audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in Graphic Design, Human-Computer Interaction or related field, or equivalent combination of education and experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Photoshop, Illustrator, and/or other visual design tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual design skills are a plus. An understanding and appreciation for innovative use of typography, color, and layout for digital media would be welcome in this role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of CSS/HTML at the code level to determine how code affects design and vice versa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please submit your portfolio when you apply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To apply: Please send your cover letter and resume with the subject &amp;ldquo;Your name &amp;ndash; UX Designer &amp;ndash; via Scribd.com&amp;rdquo; to jobs@scribd.com.
Permalink to this post&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:35:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-scribd-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-scribd-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Lucky Brand Jeans in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucky Brand is true blue American. Born and bred in Los Angeles, Lucky shipped its first pair of vintage-inspired jeans in 1990 and quickly became known as a pioneer and innovator in the world of modern denim. Synonymous with the easy Southern California lifestyle and the fearless American spirit, Lucky Brand creates great fitting, good quality, distinctively Lucky jeans and fashion that works with the American lifestyle. Our collections are carried at better department and specialty stores and over 200 of our company-owned stores across the U.S.A., as well as online at LuckyBrand.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rooted in Americana, Lucky Brand is inspired by active Californian types like surfers, cowboys, artists, musicians, and photographers, as well as anyone who embodies our fun-loving, friendly vibe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Graphic Designer will be responsible for producing graphic designs that reflect the design direction of Lucky Brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take conceptual direction from the design director and create original graphics which accurately reflect the Lucky Brand style and maintain the standard of quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take ownership of a project and lead it from concept to production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects at the same time while meeting assigned deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with various departments and vendors both domestically and overseas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform other duties as required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very strong sense of type, image and color. Strong hand lettering ability and excellent illustration skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level proficiency in MAC OS, Adobe PhotoShop and Adobe Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to take creative direction and also provide creative inputs to others when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in the development, creation, and production of original designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient knowledge of screenprinting and embellishment techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational skills. Capable of working in a fast paced, demanding work environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to juggle shifting priorities and meet deadlines while maintaining a high level of accuracy and quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player with a positive attitude and excellent interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to follow directions, manage multiple tasks and meet deadlines under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:35:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-lucky-brand-jeans-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-lucky-brand-jeans-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Designer at Shutterfly in Redwood City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About The Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a senior designer for join our internal design team in our fast growing photo gifts category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must have 3-5 years of experience in graphic design, designing outstanding work (packaging + product design a plus, but not a must). you must have an amazing portfolio that shows your love of typography, layout and illustration skills. you must have a passion for trends, and be able totranslate these trends into designs that respond to our business needs for the relevant product. you must be able to design in a wide variety of styles and have a strong attention to detail. you must be able to listen, adapt and incorporate feedback. you must be able to relentlessly collaborate and at the same time work independently on several different projects at once. you must be adept at giving and receiving critiques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Cire Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;proficiency in adobe creative suite required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Bonus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And as a bonus, you have a great sense of humor and can introduce us to new design techniques and music.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:35:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-shutterfly-redwood-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-shutterfly-redwood-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile/Web UI Designer at mSpot in Palo Alto, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This is a key position in our creative services team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with a multi-disciplinary design team for user experience planning and development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help generate elegant &amp;amp; innovative design solutions for complex cutting edge mobile &amp;amp; web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for documenting applications with wireframes and comps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help design and run usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid graphic design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid Knowledge of OmniGraffle, Visio or equivalent tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of UI/UX best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable adapting and problem solving in a fast paced team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Note:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position is for a full time position (no contractors please)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position is on-site only (Palo Alto)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:35:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-ui-designer-mspot-palo-alto-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-ui-designer-mspot-palo-alto-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead UX Designer/Developer at UniversityNow, Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;UniversityNow is building the most accessible and affordable accredited university in the world.  Backed by leading technology and education investors, we are transforming an existing accredited online university to our custom adaptive learning platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for the right people to join our UX/UI team. You are fun, fearless and fast. You think about your life as a series of design problems. You have skills in interaction, experience, and visual design and love building things as much as imagining them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;framework and screen-level interaction design of web and mobile apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;design communication through sketches, wireframes, prototypes, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;user research, feedback, metrics, and usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate on UX design and strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate on Visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate on front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;NEED TO HAVE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA or BS in Interaction/UX Design or professional equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years working in web applications or mobile apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;familiarity with CSS &amp;amp; JavaScript frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience working with developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;NICE TO HAVE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience with agile or lean methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in tight collaboration with others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience pairing with designers and/or developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in HTML/CSS/JS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS, Android experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visual design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;copywriting experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;background in education, learning design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additionally …&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;We are looking for team members who&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leave their ego at the door&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive on collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acknowledge and broker creative differences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always seek to better understand and serve our students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share the drive to reform higher education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate and promote an elegant visual design aesthetic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are or seek to be Lean, Agile, and Balanced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know when to obsess and when to move on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;You’ll need to show us&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong passion for learning and a desire to help others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to listen effectively, to offer and accept feedback openly and work as part of a highly collaborative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High quality portfolio in consumer web and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly deliver strong design during rapid iterative processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of design fundamentals and principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some knowledge of front-end programming and mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;You should enjoy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing your work before it’s “done”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing in the browser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactoring your markup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilizing metrics in design decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning about and addressing people’s goals and frustrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping your co-workers become better designers and makers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;WANT TO KNOW MORE?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to use your skills in support of a worthwhile mission and get paid for it, let’s talk. Diversity is important to us, so we’re looking for people from ALL backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We pay our staff competitively with cash and equity.  Our benefit package includes Medical, Dental, Vision, 529 College Savings Plan, Flexible Spending Accounts, Life Insurance, Adoption Assistance, Paid Holidays, Unlimited Vacation and Snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:35:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-ux-designer-developer-universitynow-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-ux-designer-developer-universitynow-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>