<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Experience Designer at Concur in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Concur (NASDAQ: CNQR) is a leading provider of cloud and mobile-based integrated travel and expense management solutions. With over 400+MM in revenues, Concur is trusted by thousands of companies in more than 100 countries and reaches millions of people worldwide. Concur helps organizations and their employees control costs and save time. TripIt, a Webby award-winning travel service and the leading mobile travel organizer from Concur®, makes it easy for millions of travelers to manage and share their trips no matter where they book. Travelers simply forward their travel confirmation emails to TripIt and a master itinerary is automatically created that combines all their travel plans. Concur and TripIt offer an open platform that integrates mobile and web services, content, and technology from third-party developers, suppliers, travel management companies and customers. Together, Concur and TripIt bring order to the chaos for both managed and unmanaged travel, and make life better for business travelers globally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The TripIt team has built a service unlike any that have come before it in the online travel space. Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to take it to the next level, and to do that we need you. You are the type of designer that is driven by the challenge of solving unique UI/UX problems in a compressed timeframe while balancing the needs of the business and the constraints of the medium. You will report directly to the Principal Designer and will work alongside TripIt&amp;rsquo;s product managers and engineers. You will be responsible for providing design leadership for all components of the TripIt service &amp;ndash; from web pages, to emails, to mobile screens, and printed itineraries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading design throughout the entire product lifecycle, from initial explorations through final design deliverables, user interface elements, and prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Producing prototypes that employ jQuery, HTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translating usability and field research findings into design improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicating design strategy and rationale to key stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with engineers to deliver polished final product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributing to a culture of innovation and teamwork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pushing the boundaries of what’s possible to create better experiences for people using TripIt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education, Experience &amp;amp; Training required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong visual and UX design skills: attention to detail down to the pixel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work fast.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of current web technologies (CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, social media, iPhone apps).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skill and proven ability to work with cross-functional teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in Graphic Design, Digital Media Design, HCI or related field, or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least five years experience as a key member of a UI/UX team through the product development cycle of several successfully launched web, mobile and/or software applications (as opposed to layout and decorative design).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;More about the TripIt Business Unit:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TripIt&amp;rsquo;s web and mobile service is praised by travelers and industry notables, including TechCrunch, the New York Times, the Wall Street Journal and by thousands of bloggers worldwide. We’ve been called “absolutely awesome”, “addictive” and “a seriously powerful travel tool.” Just search Google or Twitter for TripIt and see for yourself. We’re located in spacious new offices in the sunny Mission District in San Francisco, close to BART and several MUNI lines. Our refrigerator is stocked with drinks and we’ve got a great courtyard for BBQs too. We’re a hard-working team of 45 people and growing. We value creativity, collaborative thinking, new ideas and open communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Value Competencies:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays passion for &amp;amp; responsibility to the customer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hires, develops &amp;amp; rewards great people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays leadership through innovation in everything you do&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays a passion for what you do and a drive to improve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays a relentless commitment to win&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays personal &amp;amp; corporate integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EEO:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concur is an Equal Opportunity Employer and applies this policy to all applicants and employees. We are committed to hiring and valuing a global diverse work team. (M/F/D/V)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concur is a dynamic, growing and fast-paced organization.  As such, successful employees are able to work in a fast-paced environment, managing multiple priorities often times under tight deadlines.  This typically requires working a 40+ hour work week to accomplish performance objectives.  With that, Concur offers flexibility as to the specific working hours that may be required or available depending on your role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concur is a SaaS company.  Employees must be technically savvy with the ability to use the computer/keyboard and telephone to conduct business.  The ability to creatively problem solve to our core value of ‘Leadership through innovation in everything we do’.   Many positions within Concur are customer facing so written, verbal and interpersonal communications skills are required for a majority of opportunities with Concur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confidentiality and our core value ‘Personal and corporate integrity’ are critical components being that Concur is a publicly traded company and working towards building a great, enduring company.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-concur-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-concur-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Tween Brands in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Primary Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides graphic design services for a diverse range of projects including Tablet and Smart Phone applications; web, email, print content; image and photographic development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takes responsibility for meeting agreed project timelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to manage multiple projects simultaneously and be comfortable in taking the lead role as well as being a project contributor.  Anticipates or identifies potential production problems, proposes solutions and implements solutions as necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and deploys promotional tools for IOS and Android platforms using Adobe CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completes projects using the corporate style guide.  Contributes to the development of corporate style guide as necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stays abreast of graphic design industry trends and changes and recommends new strategies and activities to keep our content, look and execution in line with industry best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops and maintains templates in a variety of formats include Marketo (html), Adobe PDF and Word.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Complexity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requires a thorough understanding of web design, multimedia tools, imaging, and printing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requires high proficiency in desktop publishing software (Adobe Creative Suite CS5+, Macromedia/Adobe Flash, Audio/Video presentation software)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requires excellent design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education / Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree in Graphic Design, Art, or equivalent is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 6 years of experience in desktop publishing, layout, and graphic design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to clearly communicate verbally and in writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of typography and design concepts is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform keyboarding or mouse-driven computer input for at least 6 to 8 hours per day is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to sit at workstation for extended periods of time is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-tween-brands-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-tween-brands-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface (UI) Designer at Liftopia in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our products are nothing without easy-to-use and straight-forward interfaces that get out of people&amp;rsquo;s way and help users achieve their goals (in this case, getting out to the slopes!). We&amp;rsquo;re looking to expand our product/design team by adding a designer who believes usability is an important component to badass online experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role requires a mix of user interface and visual design skills. You will be working on multiple web and mobile products- a mix of enterprise, mobile and consumer/e-commerce applications. This is not a position meant for specialist visual designers or pure information architects.  If you believe usability &amp;amp; delight goes beyond (but still works closely with) visual aesthetics, this may very well be the perfect role for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An online portfolio is required to apply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on web and/or mobile applications in the consumer space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design background with expert knowledge of page hierarchy, typography, color theory, and branding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience developing and designing: wireframes, mockups, site maps, storyboards, task flows, design specifications, and/or landing pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You find little touches of personality in interfaces delightful and make an effort to bring that kind of &amp;lsquo;human&amp;rsquo; feel to your work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexibility in learning new ways of doing and thinking through problems; comfortable with testing to validate theories and ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within, manage and extend design styleguides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full understanding of modern web standards and the design implications of CSS-based layout are also required. Must know how HTML/CSS/JS make your designs possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in web design tools (ie: Fireworks, Photoshop, llustrator, Balsamiq, Omnigraffle, Axure, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to drive design concepts and present early stage sketches &amp;amp; wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable in a fast-paced, rapidly-growing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess a self-motivated, &amp;ldquo;git &amp;lsquo;er done&amp;rdquo; work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years minimum experience designing interfaces that incorporate &amp;amp; extend a brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PLUSES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototyping code abilities (HTML, CSS, light JS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enterprise user interface design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;IS LIFTOPIA A GOOD FIT FOR YOU?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the typical startup/tech industry benefits (like unlimited vacation, health insurance, bonus pool, flexible schedule, stock options, and so on), Liftopia would be a great fit if you identify with any (or all!) of the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You want to work with equally motivated and smart people to create Awesome Stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continued learning via workshops, conferences, classes, etc is important to you. We want to support you in your desire &amp;amp; effort to grow and remain relevant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company culture &amp;ndash; like grabbing beers after work or kayaking with teammates on Liftopia Days &amp;ndash; appeals and is important to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy snow and even skiing/snowboarding/snowshoeing/kite-skiing/snow-camping/cat-skiing/alpine-touring/heli-skiing/snowmobiling/crosscountry-skiing/sledding/tubing/luging OR you&amp;rsquo;re curious to learn (many of us are first-time skiers/snowboarders!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work is about much more than a paycheck. So much time is spent working; it should be enjoyable, you should be continuing to grow, and you should be able to find satisfaction in what you produce.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT LIFTOPIA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Liftopia we’re building tools that will ignite a movement in the ski industry, bringing innovative changes that benefit both resorts and those who love snow. Our site allows people to book lift tickets months in advance at the best prices for their favorite and new resorts. It helps resorts grow revenue through advance purchase tickets and reach a new demographics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Liftopia is a rapidly-growing, venture-backed company that is already the largest seller of lift tickets online. Our team is the driving force behind our success. We are united by our passion for changing the industry for good and ensuring the success of our product. You belong here if this is something that raises your eyebrows (in a good way).You will join and enhance our already motivated and energetic team. You will be asked to accomplish things you’ve never done before. You will be able to reap the benefits of seeing tangible results of your effort. You will make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-ui-designer-liftopia-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-ui-designer-liftopia-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience (UX) Designer at Liftopia in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You: Motivated &amp;amp; talented designer with a knack for creating easy-to-use &amp;amp; clean web apps. You believe communication is the key to good working relationships and helping others understand your vision. You desire a role where you will have a tangible and meaningful impact on the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role requires a mix of UX design, visual design and basic prototyping skills (HTML, CSS, some JS). You will be working on multiple web and mobile products- a mix of enterprise, mobile and consumer/e-commerce applications. This is not a position meant for specialist visual designers or pure information architects.  If you are open to learning from data &amp;amp; qualitative findings and incorporating those into your work, this may very well be the perfect role for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience working within an interactive or UX agency environment with a variety of clients is desired. Enterprise and/or mobile experience is a huge plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online portfolio with sample workflow designs and projects from start to finish (a link is required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to drive design concepts and present early stage sketches &amp;amp; wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience developing and designing: wireframes, mockups, site maps, storyboards, task flows, design specifications, and/or landing pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design background with expert knowledge of page hierarchy, typography, color theory, and branding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open to learning new ways of doing and thinking through problems; comfortable with testing to validate theories and ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within and manage a design styleguide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in full Adobe CS suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full understanding of modern web standards and the design implications of CSS-based layout are also required. Must know how HTML/CSS/JS make your designs possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with usability testing and incorporating findings to designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable in a fast-paced, rapidly-growing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess a self-motivated, driven work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years minimum experience designing a mix of brand elements and user experience design flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;IS LIFTOPIA A GOOD FIT FOR YOU?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the typical startup/tech industry benefits (like unlimited vacation, health insurance, bonus pool, flexible schedule, stock options, and so on), Liftopia would be a great fit if you identify with any (or all!) of the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You want to work with equally motivated and smart people to create Awesome Stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continued learning via workshops, conferences, classes, etc is important to you. We want to support you in your desire &amp;amp; effort to grow and remain relevant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company culture &amp;ndash; like grabbing beers after work or kayaking with teammates on Liftopia Days &amp;ndash; appeals and is important to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy snow and even skiing/snowboarding/snowshoeing/kite-skiing/snow-camping/cat-skiing/alpine-touring/heli-skiing/snowmobiling/crosscountry-skiing/sledding/tubing/luging OR you&amp;rsquo;re curious to learn (many of us are first-time skiers/snowboarders!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work is about much more than a paycheck. So much time is spent working; it should be enjoyable, you should be continuing to grow, and you should be able to find satisfaction in what you produce.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT LIFTOPIA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Liftopia we’re building tools that will ignite a movement in the ski industry, bringing innovative changes that benefit both resorts and those who love snow. Our site allows people to book lift tickets months in advance at the best prices for their favorite and new resorts. It helps resorts grow revenue through advance purchase tickets and reach a new demographics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Liftopia is a rapidly-growing, venture-backed company that is already the largest seller of lift tickets online. Our team is the driving force behind our success. We are united by our passion for changing the industry for good and ensuring the success of our product. You belong here if this is something that raises your eyebrows (in a good way).You will join and enhance our already motivated and energetic team. You will be asked to accomplish things you’ve never done before. You will be able to reap the benefits of seeing tangible results of your effort. You will make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-ux-designer-liftopia-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-ux-designer-liftopia-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UX Designer at The Climate Corporation in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Climate Corporation’s mission is to help all the world’s people and businesses manage and adapt to climate change. To achieve our mission, we have built a unique technology platform to enable, for the first time, the real-time pricing and purchasing of customizable weather insurance. Managing over 200 TB of data, including 34 trillion+ weather simulation data points, 150 billion soil type observations, and more than 3 million daily weather measurements, we are one of the largest users of Amazon Web Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Climate Corporation is focused on the enormous challenge and opportunity of protecting the $3 trillion global agriculture industry from the financial impact of adverse weather – the cause of over 90 percent of crop loss – with fully automated weather insurance products. We are also building web and mobile applications that unleash the power of our unique data and analyses to help farmers manage their daily work with field-level weather and crop insights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At The Climate Corporation, leaving a mark on the world is in our DNA; we want to make a lasting and meaningful real-world impact. We relish big problems because they are the most interesting to tackle, the most rewarding, and typically, the most valuable to solve. We also thrive on finding the possible in the impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are the best at what you do, you like solving interesting problems, and you are looking for like-minded people dedicated to having a major impact on the world, we are eager to talk with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our video about what it’s like to work at The Climate Corporation: goo.gl/GsY2y&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being an inspiration for small to medium design/UX teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentoring team members and sharing best practices in areas of design, UX, management, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruiting and growing the team to support company needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitating and guiding a cross-discipline design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping the team dream up and recognize great ideas, and then execute on them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping distribute and prioritize design requests/needs from across the company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with the team to shape design process to work with internal teams efficiently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With marketing, helping the team manage and evolve our visual brand identity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help the team work with vendors effectively (when appropriate)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product and engineering teams not just to design amazing products, but to ship amazing products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads production of prototypes for usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to the design of TCC&amp;rsquo;s internal and customer-facing products and services on the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocates for an optimal customer experience through efficient information and visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production of art assets such as buttons and photos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists in creating and iterating wireframe designs for existing and new products and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists in developing creative interactive concepts that directly address customer and business needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to wireframes, prototypes, comps, design specifications and demos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports usability process by creating and evolving wireframes that are responsive to customer feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to branding and information design for third-party technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 7 years of web design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years managing a design and/or UX team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to date with latest design tools and trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;U.S. citizenship or permanent resident status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a high-energy startup or an enterprise class software *company is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in mobile, tablet user experience is a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience with user centered design concepts and strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great understanding of information architecture and usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prototype in Axure or HTML/CSS/JavaScript and any other prototyping tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very competent in Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Keynote and other design tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding written and verbal communication skills, and ability to present work to executives and large groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to juggle multiple projects and tasks concurrently and handle project/situational changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently and with a team Bachelors Degree in Design or similar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Portfolio:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to your portfolio please provide a link to your best pieces and explain why you think they are your best pieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What We Offer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team is composed of some of the most brilliant interdisciplinary minds in the industry. Climatology Specialists, Big Data Engineers, Mathematicians, Front end Application Engineers and more work together to create the most forward thinking technology in the industry. The environment is extremely engaging and fast-paced, with dozens of specialties coming together to provide the best product and experience possible for our customers.  As Mark Twain said, “A great deal has been said about the weather, but very little has been done about it.” Our goal is to change that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary, excellent benefits, and some of the best perks in the industry, including:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous stock options. Our success is your success.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Catered lunch 5 days a week from a varied array of San Francisco eateries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Endless snacks and company-paid dinner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“3-On 1-Off” Sprints. That means that 25% of your time is spent working on your own innovations for the company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company sponsored outings, including go-kart races, kayaking, holiday yacht parties, and sporting events, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An always-stocked kegerator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energetic idea-driven work environment with an exciting culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exciting world-changing opportunity &amp;ndash; we are solving problems that have a massive impact on the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A driven, talented team that aims to make a large-scale impact through an innovative technology platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-the-climate-corporation-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-the-climate-corporation-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Experience Designer at MarketLive in Pleasanton, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you love designing winning software products that customers love? Do you like working with smart, motivated and fun team members (a few of which are the furry four-legged type)? If so, then read on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MarketLive is looking for a passionate Senior User Experience Designer to lead the design and development of MarketLive’s leading e-commerce applications and platform. You will engage with MarketLive users to understand their businesses and workflows, and use that as the basis for developing product requirements, and translating those requirements into exceptional user experiences and user interface design for the products we build. You’ll work with senior management in defining our product design strategy, partner with customers and product managers to iterate UX/UI design requirements, develop wireframes and prototypes that illustrate your design, participate on our engineering scrum teams to guide design throughout the development process, and deliver optimal end user experiences based on best practices in application usability. Most importantly, you’ll help create products that our customers will love to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You could be a great fit with MarketLive’s Product team if you enjoy…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with internal and external customers to define product UX/UI design requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with Product Managers and Software Engineers to build consensus around your design requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing functional product specifications, which may include (but are not limited to) flow diagrams, wireframes with detailed annotations, and prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partnering with Quality Assurance to test and validate that your design specifications have been delivered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluating and developing tools and processes to improve the product development UX/UI design process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with a fun team (including dogs) in a beautiful, casual work environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Experience &amp;amp; Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 3-5 years of experience as a software User Experience and/or User Interface Designer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience eliciting, defining, and documenting requirements and translating them into UX/UI design for a successful software application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to create comprehensive functional and UX/UI design requirements for software products. Should be able to provide examples.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating detailed flowcharts, wireframes, and other interaction design documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with agile/scrum development methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think quickly, assimilate complex issues and clearly articulate ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with tight deadlines in fast-paced environments with minimal supervision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player with demonstrated leadership and presentation / communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;U.S. work authorization is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Experience &amp;amp; Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in enterprise software/software as a service (SaaS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with eCommerce, Mobile, Tablet, Order Management and/or Call Center software applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in B2B or B2C e-commerce, retail or related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in HCI, Information Science, or other design disciplines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of user research and usability testing principles and practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with rich internet application (RIA) technologies such as Ajax &amp;amp; jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Axure RP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing software UI prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-marketlive-pleasanton-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-marketlive-pleasanton-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UI Designer at Salesforce in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Salesforce.com transformed the enterprise software market with cloud computing. We’ve launched business apps and platforms that are as easy to use as Amazon.com and as social as Facebook. Recognized as the world’s most innovative company and the third fastest-growing technology company by Forbes and for the third consecutive year in 2011 selected as one of the &amp;ldquo;Best Places to Work&amp;rdquo; by FORTUNE magazine, we now have our sights set on the next generation of cloud computing. Our technology teams are the brains behind visionary technologies like the Force.com platform, and enterprise social collaboration tools like Salesforce Chatter and the AppExchange marketplace. With more than 7,000 employees, the first enterprise cloud computing company to exceed $2.0B in annual revenue run rate, and more than 100,000 customers worldwide, we are proud to contribute to the success of companies of all sizes and industries, around the globe. If you&amp;rsquo;re passionate about innovation, come help revolutionize how companies collaborate and communicate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Desk.com is a fast-paced startup inside Salesforce.com, which means you get the best of both worlds: small teams, fun projects, and fast execution backed by the vast resources of a publicly traded company. We have the cool vibe of a startup and the dependability of an established player. We are headquartered in San Francisco and have really cool offices south of Market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a highly-motivated Sr. UI Designer with a strong understanding of design, to contribute in shaping the user interface of our product and strengthening our online presence across web, tablet, and mobile devices. We drive our product by the user experience, and need someone with the skills who can keep up and push the vision forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will work directly with other members of the product team to build experiences that reinforce the Desk.com brand and help wow our customers. You will get to work in an exciting and engaging agile startup-like environment where you will be encouraged to expand your skills, test your creative boundaries, share new ideas, and most importantly – have fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, iterate, and refine UI and UX concepts for the company’s core products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with product managers, front-end engineers, and other UI designers to insure we maintain a high-quality user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively with your team to meet the demands of our customers, while at the same time continuing to innovate far beyond the competition. .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required/Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are a master of your craft and tools. As a designer you are expected to have a dominating control over Photoshop, as well as create satisfying interfaces boasting user-centered design principles for our core applications. Bonus for a dribbble or other online portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You get excited to work with some of the coolest clients on the web on a product that people love using. With customers like 37signals, Rdio, Square, Pandora, many more, we’re building software that real companies are using and we need you to contribute to our evolution. You must be excited about your role! Anybody can build something that’s “good”, but true passion breeds “incredible.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You like to deliver real results. So, you’ve got some design and prototyping chops but do you have the ability to bring your work to life? This is a great opportunity to expand your front-end skills, and learn from an exceptionally talented team. You’ll need to be able to build those great experiences with HTML, CSS, and Javascript. Bonus if terms like HAML, CoffeeScript, and AngularJS not only make sense to you, but excite you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On occasion, you will have to receive feedback from our customers &amp;ndash; so excellent written and oral communication skills are a must!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-designer-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-designer-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Product Designer UI/UX Designer at AlwaysOnVacation, Inc. in San Ramon, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;AlwaysOnVacation is looking for a Product Designer to join their global User Experience Group to help drive the conceptual direction for the visual language for 16 international AlwaysOnVacation sites. This visual designer will contribute to a strategic direction that promotes a delightful, engaging, and highly usable site that drives high-percentage user conversions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AlwaysOnVacation is looking for someone with the talent and skills to create innovative visual components, and define visual languages for our users, as well as the ability to participate throughout the product development process, working closely with user researchers, product managers, interaction designers, front-end developers, and other team members to help shape the visual language for our web experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, the right candidate will have a deep understanding of user-centered design and user experience methods and processes, and will have graduated from a university known for producing world-class digital experience designers. The candidate must be a strategic, independent, self-motivated, creative professional, capable of adapting quickly to a fast-paced environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applying advanced graphic design processes to create high quality visual experiences to ensure optimal visual hierarchy, discoverability, and delight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create visual interface guidelines and specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with interaction designers to design and observe usability studies, and use these to inform future designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Producing creative visual designs, including imagery, iconography, colors, kinetics, and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functioning as custodian of the visual style guide and branding philosophy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in industrial design, visual arts, Human Factors, HCI, or related area from an institution known for producing world-class visual designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience as a visual designer on a larger User Experience Design team participating in the visual design for several successfully launched web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must have examples they can show that demonstrate strategic creative thinking and be able to articulate why those chose the way they did to meet strategic objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be process driven, demonstrate strong visual design skills, careful attention to detail, and have a deep understanding of user-centered design principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have solid grasp of graphic and web design principles and good understanding of current web technologies (HTML5, DHTML, CSS3).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to produce highly structured artifacts in Adobe Photoshop, which can be leveraged by Front-end development engineers to easily produce presentation-layer code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to collaborate actively as part of a multi-disciplinary team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have excellent interpersonal and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be organized, able to act independently, and able to switch rapidly between different projects in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works well under pressure and able to meet aggressive deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-designer-ui-ux-designer-alwaysonvacation-inc-san-ramon-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-designer-ui-ux-designer-alwaysonvacation-inc-san-ramon-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Principal Product Designer at Salesforce in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an exceptional designer to help lead the design of our products into 2013. This individual should be able to flow effortlessly from high-level strategy to the tiniest details of a design infrastructure, and help grow a solid team of designers in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience / Skills Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master of design and communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Adobe CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to successfully manage all aspects of a project from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be self-motivated, a good communicator, comfortable following direction, and able to balance great design with meeting short deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to produce results independently as well as collaboratively in a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Icon design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytic / Infographic design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile App design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing social products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with pattern libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on various web, mobile and tablet application interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create designs, icons and layouts that adhere to and extend the app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate discussions into leading app designs and layouts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate detailed specs of final designs that allow devs to build accurately&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with devs to deliver polished final product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evangelize new interface guidelines and design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor new members of design staff during onboarding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive in a highly collaborative, fast-paced, agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Top talent from around the world join Salesforce for its “change the world” mentality; the opportunity to excel in a performance-driven, fast-paced, and competitive atmosphere; the chance to be surrounded by peers and leaders that inspire, motivate, and innovate and a corporate philosophy that incorporates community involvement into its fabric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1999, Salesforce.com is the enterprise cloud computing leader. Our social and mobile cloud technologies — including our flagship sales and CRM applications — help companies connect with customers, partners, and employees in entirely new ways. With more than 100,000 customers worldwide, we are proud to contribute to the success of companies of all sizes and industries, around the globe. If you&amp;rsquo;re passionate about innovation, come help revolutionize how companies collaborate and communicate with customers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-product-designer-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-product-designer-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at Intuit in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine a career where your creative inspiration can fuel BIG innovation.  Year-over-year, Intuit has been recognized on Fortune&amp;rsquo;s “100 Best Companies to Work For” and at the top of Fortune World’s “Most Admired Software Companies.”  Immerse yourself in our award winning culture while creating breakthrough solutions that change the financial lives of more than 50 million personal users, seven million small businesses, and over 1,800 financial institutions and their millions of customers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Combining organic growth with strategic partnerships, Intuit is expanding its social, mobile, and global footprint with products and services that are revolutionizing the industry.  Our entrepreneurial employees have brought more than 250 innovations to market &amp;mdash; from QuickBooks®, Quicken®, and TurboTax®, to GoPayment, Mint.com, Intuit Healthcare Solutions, big data, cloud (SaaS, PaaS) and mobile apps.  The breadth and depth of these customer-driven innovations mean limitless opportunities for you to turn your ingenious ideas into reality at Intuit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intuit&amp;rsquo;s Employee Management Solutions Division (EMS), a division of the Small Business Group, is the small business payroll leader with over 1 million customers (more than any other payroll provider).  We make it easy for small businesses to confidently pay employees while keeping more money in their pockets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CHECK OUT WHAT IT IS LIKE TO WORK IN THE SMALL BUSINESS GROUP&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8xe6x8dLesc&amp;amp;feature=related&quot;&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8xe6x8dLesc&amp;amp;feature=related&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come join the &amp;ldquo;Employee Management Services Team&amp;rdquo; as an &amp;ldquo;Interaction Designer&amp;rdquo;. If you are interested in building beautiful, emotionally engaging products that delight customers this is the place for you! We build products that help small businesses take care of their employees. We put our customers’ needs at the heart of everything we do and we have a blast inventing new ways of solving customer pain points and building experiences that surprise and delight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops professional expertise while learning the key aspects of the job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applies company processes to resolve a variety of routine issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works on problems with limited to moderate scope ( feature level or small projects)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Normally receives general instructions and mentoring on routine work and detailed instructions for new assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For projects of low to moderate complexity Assists in: Discover phase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Input for XD research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive audits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;External trends analysis Define phase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interaction design goals and principles; input to delight goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interaction design process, schedule, milestones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personas, user scenarios/stories, storyboards Delivers: Design phase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple concepts and iterations around user interaction models and workflows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wireframes, screen flows, prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentations for communicating any of the above Deliver phase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI Specs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assurance that delivery matches specs (e.g. identifying deviations, owning Interaction design bugs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appropriate trade-off recommendations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Discover what it’s like to be part of a team that rewards taking risks and trying new things. It’s time to love what you do! Check out all of our career opportunities at: http://jobs.intuit.com.  Intuit is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be yourself. Be Intuit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-intuit-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-intuit-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>