<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at THE OUTDOOR RECREATION GROUP in Redlands, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Use your years of graphic design experience to create and/or coordinate the development of a wide range of digital and printed materials requiring expert knowledge of specialized, multi-faceted design concepts and media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize, plan, design, and produce a wide range of specialized graphic and/or illustrative material, maintaining company branding standards and adhering to established guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with other departments to ascertain needs and develop graphic directions, concepts, and specifications for assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan production schedules for the various steps in the design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select appropriate production media and materials such as ink and paper; inspect proofs for accuracy and adherence to appropriate production standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical advice and guidance to other departments on design and technical graphics issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in group sessions and meetings on a project basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurately maintain digital files and records&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May provide technical computer support and install software programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor other department staff; may supervise and/or lead other design staff and/or student employees on special projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Arts in graphic design or related studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of directly related experience including expert knowledge of principles and practices of graphic art and design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to independently visualize and provide design solutions from concept to completion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create and produce graphic materials using a range of media or provide detailed specifications to external vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to compile and prepare schedules and work plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with all external graphic design, printing, publication, and associated resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience supervising and training assigned staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated mastery of graphic layout and photographic requirements and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of printing and/or reproduction processes and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated proficiency with Mac OS and Microsoft Windows platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of skills with Adobe Creative Suite including but not limited to Photoshop, InDesign, and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of effective web design including user interface for mobile and desktop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Microsoft Office Suite, specifically PowerPoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Portfolio Submission:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only candidates who submit samples by PDF or URL viewable at no less than 720x1080 will be considered for this position. Samples must show a full range of design work as described below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Layout work including multi-page publications, brochures, flyers, and advertising samples (InDesign)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vector work including logos, illustrations, and typography samples (Illustrator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raster work including photo editing, compositing, and blending (Photoshop)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design including user interface, banners, social media, or e-mail blasts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other illustration work including drawing, painting, and mixed media (Handwork)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our passion for improving quality of life through geography is at the heart of everything we do. Esri’s geographic information system (GIS) technology inspires and enables governments, universities, and businesses worldwide to save money, lives, and our environment through a deeper understanding of the changing world around them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carefully managed growth and zero debt give Esri stability that is uncommon in today&amp;rsquo;s volatile business world. Privately held, we offer exceptional benefits, competitive salaries, 401(k) and profit-sharing programs, opportunities for personal and professional growth, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more and apply online at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.esri.com/careers&quot;&gt;http://www.esri.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;. Esri is an equal opportunity employer (EOE) supporting diversity in the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-the-outdoor-recreation-group-redlands-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-the-outdoor-recreation-group-redlands-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at Ancestry.com in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be responsible for all phases of user experience design, from concept to iterative improvements, ensuring that design and interaction blend with business, customer and technical requirements into a crescendo of your design brilliance. In short, you must be legally authorized to kick some design ass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a creative individual with great problem-solving skills and a passionate attention to detail. You wield Photoshop (or Illustrator or Fireworks) like Tiger Woods wields a 9-iron: generating lots of options and getting the design to lay down in just the right spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Make Your Mom Proud&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have 2.5 million subscribers who use our site to enrich their understanding of themselves and their place in history by researching their family. They use our site for a combined 5 million hours a week. Come and make an impact by designing a fabulous experience for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;In Your Wheelhouse:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating taskflows, wireframes, prototypes, annotated mocks, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awesome at synthesizing product requirements, technical constraints, user research and web analytics into efficient user scenarios and design solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love soliciting additional insights by sharing your design work with customers, other designers, and project stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working within and contributing to company design standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know how to nurture great relationships with coders to ensure that new features are implemented according to your wickedly good specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Our Baseline Needs:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of relevant industry experience designing for consumer-focused online interaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Human Computer Interaction, Graphic Design or related discipline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in the use of design tools to craft great user experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A thorough understanding of interaction/user-centric design and proven visual design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication, interpersonal skills working with remote teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latent jet-setter DNA: We have a main office in Utah which you&amp;rsquo;ll visit for 1-2 days every couple months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bottom line:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Show us a phenomenal, knock-our-socks-off online portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Working for Ancestry.com&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancestry.com is a profitable, growing company with a positive, high-energy environment. Together, our dedicated teams are harnessing the power of technology and using it to simplify the way people connect with their families and their unique legacies.  Our work environment is fast-paced and challenging, but also extremely exciting. You’ll work with a team of passionate, engaged individuals. We offer excellent benefits and a competitive compensation package. For additional information, regarding our benefits and career information, please visit our website at http://ancestry.com/careers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancestry.com Inc. is interested in you and we are dedicated to building a diverse workforce with equal opportunities for employment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancestry.com is not accepting unsolicited assistance from search firms for this employment opportunity. All resumes submitted by search firms to any employee at Ancestry.com via-email, the Internet or in any form and/or method without a valid written search agreement in place for this position will be deemed the sole property of Ancestry.com. No fee will be paid in the event the candidate is hired by Ancestry.com as a result of the referral or through other means.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-ancestry-com-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-ancestry-com-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at Rosetta in San Luis Obispo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is looking for a Designer who has a passion for the web and application interface. You’re a usability junkie. Face it, bad design makes your skin crawl &amp;ndash; beautiful design puts a smile on your face. You sweat every pixel, but still understand the big picture. Your creative experience and inspiration extend beyond the digital realm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who We Are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is a consulting-centered interactive agency engineered to transform marketing for the connected world. We are focused on helping progressive marketers drive material business impact by translating deep consumer insights into personally relevant brand experiences across touch points and over time. Our differentiated capabilities and structure have enabled us to become a market leader, operating as an independent brand in the Publicis Groupe of global agencies. Rosetta is ranked by Ad Age among the top U.S. digital agencies and was recently named the #1 Agency to Watch in Ad Age’s Agency A-List.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for executing solid designs that speak to creative and art direction provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works well as a team member of a large account, understanding how a team operates and what is expected in critiques and team meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists Art Director in necessary research and preparation of presentation materials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An online portfolio is required to apply for this position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Graphic Design or related experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 years experience creating online/interactive designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional skills in programs required for your discipline; Flash, Photoshop, Dreamweaver, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is an equal opportunity employer M/F/V/D&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-rosetta-san-luis-obispo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-rosetta-san-luis-obispo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Visual Designer at Coupa in San Mateo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you want to work for a company that has been named one of The Wall Street Journal top 50 startups and one of the 25 top start ups to bet your career on by Business Insider?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coupa is building a world-class company of experienced professionals. We are looking for a Visual Designer who will join our product team and work on design and delivery of new products from concept generation to completion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define visual design principles and language for Coupa web and mobile products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create visually pleasing and delightful interface elements and pages for existing and new features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop visual design prototypes, mockups and comps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enforce consistent visual language for web and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help build UX and Visual Style Guide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with designers, PM and Development to deliver the final product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy working in a fast paced agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on designer that can create exciting results on their own&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can address customer needs by promoting ease of use and beauty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love reaching out to customers to understand their needs and expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep an eye on latest UX and Visual trends and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can recommend improvements for the user experience and visual language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have design experience with mobile and mobile apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can effectively communicate with developers to implement and realize the design vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a portfolio to show your work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Coupa offers a very comprehensive and competitive benefit package that includes company paid health insurance, stock options, 401(k), FSA, a very generous PTO plan along with a creative and exciting place to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested, please contact Natalie Cedeno, Director of Human Resources for additional information or assistance at careers@coupa.com or 650-539-3872.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/visual-designer-coupa-san-mateo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/visual-designer-coupa-san-mateo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface Designer at Linea Photosharing LLC in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re a talented designer with a passion for both web and mobile interfaces. You&amp;rsquo;re extremely passionate about designing and using web apps, websites, and mobile apps. You&amp;rsquo;re always exploring the latest and greatest. You keep a portfolio or blog of new design patterns and interesting UI treatments, which you usually explore in your next project. You abide by Steve Krug&amp;rsquo;s philosophy of minimizing thinking in interfaces, thus creating simple solutions to complex questions. As a designer, you love to discuss and critically dissect your work and the work of your peers because you believe the best designer is one that improves with feedback. Above all, you can describe your work as efficient, inspired,  and beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each day you&amp;rsquo;ll work with both the Product and Engineering teams to create beautiful interfaces that reach users around the world. A large part of your job will be to conceptualize and design original ideas that bring simplicity and ease of use to complex design issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate requirements into concepts and elegant user experience design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create interaction models, user task flows, screen designs, and UI details that promote ease of use and optimize the user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other designers as needed, and work independently to see a project through&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with Design Research to inform and improve interfaces and workflows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visualize complex sets of data in ways that are easy to comprehend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Engineering to guide final implementation of design concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be working from our San Francisco office located at mid-market in the Twitter building (9th and Market).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing consumer and/or commercial web application interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record and a passion for designing compelling user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid intuition of best practices and tools used in user-centered interaction design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong visual design skills, including an eye for good typography, composition, and use of color&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluid ability to design in Photoshop, OmniGraffle, and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in creating various prototype methods and knowledge of best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multitask, prioritize projects, and communicate progress and expected milestones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation with the larger professional design community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with front-end web technologies (HTML, CSS, JS) and an understanding of how they play into interaction design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We pay special attention to those that are looking to create new experiences, not just re-purpose the old. Special consideration will be given to those that show entrepreneurial spirit, are looking to mold the organization, and help create a better agile development environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates should have solid communication skills and the ability to both provide competitive and well-informed arguments, but at the same time be able to listen to strategic business, design and user needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-designer-linea-photosharing-llc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-designer-linea-photosharing-llc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead Experience Designer at Yahoo! Inc. in Santa Monica, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Yahoo! is focused on making the world&amp;rsquo;s daily habits more inspiring and entertaining. By creating highly personalized experiences for our users, we keep people connected to what matters most to them, across devices and around the globe. In turn, we create value for advertisers by connecting them with the audiences that build their businesses. Yahoo! is headquartered in Sunnyvale, Calif., and has offices located throughout the Americas, Asia Pacific (APAC) and the Europe, Middle East and Africa (EMEA) regions. For more information, visit the pressroom (&lt;a href=&quot;http://pressroom.yahoo.net&quot;&gt;http://pressroom.yahoo.net&lt;/a&gt;) or the company&amp;rsquo;s blog (yodel.yahoo.com).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience Designer, Y! News&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yahoo! is looking for an exceptional Experience Designer to join the Yahoo! News Design team. This team&amp;rsquo;s charter is to define and design the user experience across a variety of editorial and content initiatives – from baseline research to full execution and production. We have a collaborative, innovative culture, where you will be working closely with other experience designers, user experience researchers, prototypers, product managers and technologists to define the Yahoo! News user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for someone with the talent to create elegant designs, the skills to participate throughout the product development process, and the passion to help us create innovative experiences for our users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The candidate must be a strategic, independent, self-motivated, creative professional, capable of adapting quickly to a fast-paced environment. This is an active hands-on role that will require a designer who can solve visual and interaction design challenges but is also capable of taking active design direction. The candidate should also have excellent communication skills and be able to articulate their ideas to designers, product managers and developers. The candidate must have an extremely developed sense of design and impeccable attention to detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Producing innovative yet intuitive design solutions that address complex consumer, editorial and marketing needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rapidly developing pixel-accurate visual mockups, final design assets and functional spec documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with the Engineering and QA teams to support UX implementation efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must demonstrate outstanding talent, creativity and design sensibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of designing consumer focused, media rich web UX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of the user-centered design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience visualizing complex data sets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently as well as in cross-functional groups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to thrive in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert-level proficiency in Photoshop. Advanced level skills in Illustrator. Also desired, but not required: experience with Omnigraffle and InDesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of mobile trends and technologies, focused on smart phones and tablets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BFA or BA degree in design related studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML/CSS prototyping skills a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;LI-US&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-experience-designer-yahoo%21-inc-santa-monica-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-experience-designer-yahoo%21-inc-santa-monica-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Mobile Designer at StubHub in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Since its inception 10 years ago, StubHub has built the world’s largest ticket marketplace and our year-over-year growth remains impressive. We are now turning our eyes towards the next 10 years and are looking for a few talented individuals to bring their passion and experience to meet the next set of challenges (among other things, building a social commerce marketplace for fans of sports and music).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop intuitive, usable, and engaging interactions and visual designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create holistic end-to-end experiences and ecosystems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiate and respond to ideas for innovation/improvements based on research, analysis, and competitive reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide strategic thinking and leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceive, manage, and lead project design from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify user needs, business requirements, and business opportunties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantiate design approach with analysis &amp;amp; projections for improvements in key metrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create design deliverables such as specifications, process flows, wireframes, and mock-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with user experience researchers to develop user research and usability tests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with cross-functional teams as well as the greater UX team throughout the design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate harmoniously with multiple stakeholders to synthesize and incorporate feedback appropriately with equanimity and a user-centered focus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Procure buy-in with stakeholders early and often&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During implementation phase respond to day-to-day questions from developers, product managers &amp;amp; project managers. Also work with QA to identify, document, and verify bug fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be comfortable sketching or quickly mocking up and communicating design ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level skills in Photoshop, Fireworks and other associated design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rock solid skills in graphic design, with an eye for typography, palette development, intuitive layout, and a pixel-level attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Native app design for both iPhone and Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Javascript capabilities (i.e., what can be done on mobile with AJAX and emerging mobile JS libraries)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML 5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with international audiences a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years experience as an interaction or hybrid designer (Masters degree counts as 1 year)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s or higher degree in Interaction Design, Human-Computer Interaction, Cognitive Science or related field. Masters degree preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of user experience design for mobile and the web, technology trends, demonstrable design skills, and ability to show relevant work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in agile methodology and working closely with the immediate scrum team on a day-to-day basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;E-Commerce experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid grasp of web design principles and a good understanding of front-end web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability delivering high quality designs to customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to communicate your design vision and defend your design decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A team player who can easily adapt in a rapidly changing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to coordinate, prioritize, and accomplish multiple tasks in a fast-paced atmosphere with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills and presentation skills, including the ability to communicate effectively in small and large groups and to senior executives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a self starter that can create schedules and define scope of work even when there are no clear requirements and direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability delivering high quality designs to customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelors Degree or Equivalent&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-designer-stubhub-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-designer-stubhub-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Visual Designer at TuneIn in Palo Alto, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Visual Designer is responsible for designing and implementing a variety of marketing campaigns and materials to represent the TuneIn brand. The ideal candidate will have a broad portfolio and experience creating a coherent, consistent design system across media (web, mobile, print) and disciplines (advertising, marketing, guerilla/non-traditional). The role requires strong project management, communication and collaboration skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide design direction for the TuneIn brand across media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help create, define and maintain visual campaign style guides and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with the marketing team to develop and execute marketing campaigns and projects including email marketing, site merchandising, digital and print advertising, partner marketing materials, and brand assets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage a team of creative contractors to help with design and production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As the company grows, recruit, develop, and lead an in-house creative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA degree in graphic design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of related experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative talent across a range of media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with current design software tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong project management, organizational and time management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborative, team-oriented work style&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing others and demonstrated leadership potential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrives in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-visual-designer-tunein-palo-alto-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-visual-designer-tunein-palo-alto-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Motrr in Santa Cruz, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We believe in designing and building products that elevate the way people connect with each other and with the world around us. Our first offering, Galileo, is an iOS controlled robotic platform that adds a new dimension of control and motion to smartphone cameras. We began our journey on Kickstarter where our project became one of the most successfully funded in the design category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Motrr is one of several companies part of a tech incubator in the hills of beautiful Santa Cruz. We are a talented team with extensive mechanical design, product design and software development experience. We design and build our hardware and software in house. Our ambitions are growing and so is our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a talented and passionate graphic designer to help us grow motrr into a globally recognizable brand. You should be able to work autonomously and within our UX team to carry out our vision. You would play a key role in designing and creating graphic elements for:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS and Android apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;website and developer portal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;social media sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;product packaging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate conceptual ideas into elegant, intuitive, and engaging experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated and enthusiastic, as well as being well organized and accountable for your work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible approach to your work and excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever software works for you, works for us&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is a senior in college or a recent college graduate who fits our needs and is looking for an amazing internship/job opportunity. We need to hire asap. We offer competitive pay and benefits that are commensurate with your experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about us here &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/449163977/galileo-your-ios-in-motion&quot;&gt;http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/449163977/galileo-your-ios-in-motion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are confident that you could be a strong candidate for this position, we would love to hear from you. Please include a brief cover letter, your resume, and a link to your online portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-motrr-santa-cruz-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-motrr-santa-cruz-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Interaction Designer at Intuit in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine a career where your creative inspiration can fuel BIG innovation.  Year-over-year, Intuit has been recognized on Fortune&amp;rsquo;s “100 Best Companies to Work For” and at the top of Fortune World’s “Most Admired Software Companies.”  Immerse yourself in our award winning culture while creating breakthrough solutions that change the financial lives of more than 50 million personal users, seven million small businesses, and over 1,800 financial institutions and their millions of customers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Combining organic growth with strategic partnerships, Intuit is expanding its social, mobile, and global footprint with products and services that are revolutionizing the industry.  Our entrepreneurial employees have brought more than 250 innovations to market &amp;mdash; from QuickBooks®, Quicken®, and TurboTax®, to GoPayment, Mint.com, Intuit Healthcare Solutions, big data, cloud (SaaS, PaaS) and mobile apps.  The breadth and depth of these customer-driven innovations mean limitless opportunities for you to turn your ingenious ideas into reality at Intuit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intuit&amp;rsquo;s Employee Management Solutions Division (EMS), a division of the Small Business Group, is the small business payroll leader with over 1 million customers (more than any other payroll provider).  We make it easy for small businesses to confidently pay employees while keeping more money in their pockets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;CHECK OUT WHAT IT IS LIKE TO WORK IN THE SMALL BUSINESS GROUP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8xe6x8dLesc&amp;amp;feature=related&quot;&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8xe6x8dLesc&amp;amp;feature=related&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come join the Employee Management Team as a Senior Interaction Designer. We design delightful and engaging products that help small businesses manage their employees and grow their businesses without having to worry about things like taxes and compliance laws. Are you passionate about helping entrepreneurs do what they love? Come join us on our quest to simplify employee management and help small businesses grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply strategic thinking to design and deliver innovative end-to-end user experiences that optimize among user needs, business goals, and technological realities across web &amp;amp; mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take ideas and concepts, and visualize them in such that they are communicated effectively and compellingly for internal leaders, partners and customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turn visions into concepts and translate those concepts into designs that illustrate simplicity, despite complexity of the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directly responsible for delivering User Experience visions, UI specifications, wireframes and prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate effectively with researchers, product management, development, marketing, and other team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use facilitative leadership skills to drive to the best outcome for stakeholders, resulting in others learning from you, and inspiring others to want to work with you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in and foster the Intuit Experience Design Community and mentor junior members of the design team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four-year degree in Human Computer Interaction, graphic design, or other relevant field. Graduate degree a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of interface design experience in delivering high-volume, high-profile or award-winning web sites or products; preferably experience with SaaS and mobile products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge and experience with driving and applying user-centered design processes while working collaboratively with customers, along with cross-functional teams including engineering, product management, and user research. Seasoned in Agile development processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in a variety of methods to convey ideas and concepts (e.g. storyboards, wireframes, prototypes, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record in setting a vision for great customer experiences, inspiring others to get behind the vision, and ultimately delivering products and services that are known for their delightful experience and ease of use&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective communicator, presenter, and negotiator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized, self-directed, efficient and able to manage multiple and complex projects in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with design tools such as Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, but skilled in creating &amp;lsquo;lo-fi&amp;rsquo; prototypes to share with users in a fast, iterative manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with web and mobile technologies and their impact on the feasibility of design solutions; hands-on expertise with HTML, CSS, AJAX, DoJo, Flash, and/or Flex a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for creating products that resonate on an emotional level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong online portfolio available for viewing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Discover what it’s like to be part of a team that rewards taking risks and trying new things. It’s time to love what you do! Check out all of our career opportunities at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://jobs.intuit.com&quot;&gt;http://jobs.intuit.com&lt;/a&gt;.  Intuit is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interaction-designer-intuit-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interaction-designer-intuit-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>