<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Pulsepoint in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager leads interactive marketing and Web development projects, oversees creative and technical project teams, interacts with business managers and is responsible for producing projects on time and on budget. The PM also contributes strategic and operational insight on client accounts to promote project efficiency and success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the creation, maintenance and delivery of detailed project plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies and scopes client requirements and deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create goals and milestones that correlate to billable events within a project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies, documents, and manages scope or deliverable change requests required whether initiated internally or by the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and maintains activity and progress reports for internal and external customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates daily tasks and assigns project resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracks all budget-related information, including billable hours and project expenses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the success of the project while remaining within the scoped time and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages and helps ensure client satisfaction in partnership with the internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Properly notifies the internal team of any risks, weaknesses or opportunities that could impact the success of the project, escalating to upper management as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plans for and controls quality by reviewing items before delivery to client; monitoring and enhancing internal and external deliverables/documents; working with internal teams on needed revisions/enhancements, and involving the Quality Assurance team at key project junctures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates and participates in periodic project and program reviews and strategy meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in and completes training and professional development as detailed within department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an understanding of the client’s operating environment and internal processes and procedures that may affect the project’s success; serves as point of contact for clients as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the use of best practices and apply lessons learned from previous projects; share lessons learned with other project management team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of relevant experience managing projects (preferably * 2-4 years within an interactive, advertising or marketing agency environment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management principles, methods and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of financial concepts and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to demonstrate experience with professional services processes and tools including workflow development and management, milestone management and quality assurance practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of technical and creative design and development principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing resources, budgets and project timing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience analyzing complex data reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in MS Project, and the entire MS Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business analysis and requirements gathering skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director, Digital Programming at Red Bull North America, Inc. in Santa Monica, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Drawing on parent company Red Bull&amp;rsquo;s quarter century heritage, Red Bull Media House (RBMH) creates compelling, entertaining and authentic content across film, television, print and digital. Red Bull Media House is a key driver in highly coveted young male demographic across all platforms and is widely recognized as an authority by both its target audience, industry media and influencers.  Red Bull Media House tells one cohesive story that lets all of its parts work together in concert, allowing consumers to see and connect the dots, no matter what screen or medium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PURPOSE OF THIS JOB&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Red Bull Media House has an opening for a world-class Director of Digital Programming. The ideal candidate will own the editorialization, distribution and monetization of Red Bull owned media properties across all relevant digital channels and device platforms, the expansion of the Red Bull digital channel ecosystem and the development of new digital media products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and execute editorial and programming strategies for Red Bull media properties including Red Bull TV, Red Bull Signature Series, Red Bull Gaming and Red Bull Soundstage with a focus on rapid audience growth, cross-platform experiences and revenue generation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and develop Red Bull owned web sites, social networks (e.g. Facebook, Twitter, Instagram), digital media channels (e.g. YouTube, Hulu, Xbox Live) and consumer device applications (e.g. on iPhone/iPad, Android, Windows and Xbox).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance audience research, forecasting, editorial and marketing planning to continuously improve the quality and relevance of our media products, drive audience growth and maximize revenue opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and bring to market new content formats, interactive user experiences and digital products to further strengthen Red Bull owned media properties and create new online platforms that enable self-propelling scenes within the Red Bull core playgrounds in sports, culture, music and gaming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;MAJOR ACTIVITIES TO ENSURE ACHIEVEMENT OF KEY RESULTS AND DELIVERABLES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and execute digital programming strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the creation and execution of editorial plans for all digital media products and oversee the integrated execution across all relevant digital channels and screens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with the Distribution department to develop new marketing and syndication partnerships that expand viewership of our digital media properties and open up new revenue sources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop programing, marketing and monetization strategies for the launch of a new Internet based TV product and secure digital content, distribution and marketing partnerships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a framework for structured monetization of Red Bull media products across digital channels and device platforms through subscription, sponsorship and advertising models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build out a durable digital channel and device platform ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and expand an integrated system of owned web sites and applications, social networks and media channels to provide customers with seamless media experiences through the channels and devices of their choice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Editorialize Red Bull playgrounds in action sports, motor sports, music and gaming within dedicated content channels on redbull.com with customized experiences for all relevant screen formats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grow and strengthen Red Bull communities through innovative content strategies for social anchor platforms Facebook and Twitter, emerging channels like Instagram and innovative social features within our own properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Develop a world-class Internet based TV and video distribution system through the integration of our own video and TV applications with leading OTT platforms including YouTube, Hulu, xBox and Roku&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advance audience research, forecasting, editorial and marketing planning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop audience segmentation, modeling and forecasting techniques and apply against all Red Bull digital media products to maximize audience growth across channels and device platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently monitor consumer needs and behaviors to optimize editorial calendars, programing schedules and distribution plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the planning and implementation of sophisticated monitoring capabilities across all Red Bull owned and operated web sites, applications and digital channels to better understand user behavior, optimize SEO, allow for advertising inventory management and provide insight for sponsors and advertising partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring to market new digital media products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create new and innovative media products by blending digital video, gaming and interactive formats with real-world consumer experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with the Red Bull Marketing, Brand and Product Innovation teams on the development of new digital platforms that will enable self-propelling scenes within the Red Bull core playgrounds in sports, culture, music and gaming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, test and bring to market new advertising formats and subscription models that are optimized for RBMH digital media and product offerings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;KEY RESULTS AND DELIVERABLES (WHAT DOES SUCCESS LOOK LIKE)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and bring to market new digital media products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Achieve ambitious audience growth, engagement and revenue targets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anticipate new digital business opportunities and articulate to company leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit, manage and mentor high-performing editorial and programming teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become a leading advocate of the Red Bull Media House mission and products with the media, entertainment and technology industries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flawless follow-through; all deadlines met&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 + years experience in developing digital marketing, advertising and/or media software products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong programing and editorial background; hands-on experience with running consumer focused content portal or video site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of online advertising formats, platforms, tools and processes, experiences with publisher tools preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional team leadership skills, ability to build positive relationships and work cross-functionally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track record of cross-functional collaboration in a variety of organizational environments &amp;amp; cultures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication skills, including written, verbal and presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound strategic thinking and analytical capabilities with an emphasis on reading and interpreting data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong planning, prioritization and project management competencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel 25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Live and represent the Red Bull Brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree, MBA a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-digital-programming-red-bull-north-america-inc-santa-monica-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-digital-programming-red-bull-north-america-inc-santa-monica-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at R/GA in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a Creative Director, you are responsible for creative strategy and general direction of the work. In collaboration with the team and designers, the Creative Director ensures the quality of the concept and the work produced, in addition to presenting work to the client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Creative Director also assists in managing the department and helps ensure the growth of individuals in the Visual Design Department. We are looking for a strong strategic and conceptual thinker who can present their ideas clearly to the team. More specifically, someone who knows how to look at corporate brands from fresh angles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified people have 8+ years of design experience in web, advertising and typography.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An in-depth understanding of HTML, and the capabilities of web browsers are essential, and knowledge of Photoshop, Illustrator, and Flash is required.  After Effects, Maya experience is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely strong leader with the ability to manage multiple clients and projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience in Graphic Design, team management and client facing experience. Working knowledge of Interaction Design, technology, usability and experience design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is responsible for strong conceptual and strategic directions and clearly presents those ideas to the team and the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Builds strong relationships with multi-levels of marketing clients. Assists clients with deepening their knowledge of interactive marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong client managing skills, works directly with the clients, directing the users experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral, written, and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversees Art Director providing feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-r-ga-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-r-ga-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director of UI/UX at GREE International in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The GREE Design team is looking for an experienced Director of Game UX/UI to join our fun, brilliant and diverse team.  You will work with the Head of Design, and all team members leading by example, and helping to define better process, and generate better output from the Game UX/UI Design team. You will also work with an incredibly talented group of artists, product managers, and engineers to help fuel innovation via user centric practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work to support and grow best UX practices with the Game UX group and embedding this into all product teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct regular output of Game UI group assets for quality and promptness including contract and external workforce.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track and consistently improve output from Design group, by helping to facilitate change where needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and iterate on robust processes, and management of projects across team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute personally and via team to well thought out, clear, and polished products, providing an engaging and delightful user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor team members, introducing them to new techniques, design patterns, and user research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3+ years of team leadership, and 6+ years of design/art experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent and diverse portfolio of UX / UI for Games, Apps, Prototypes or otherwise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work in games, and some mobile experience, or deep understanding of mobile space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading a product design team in a rapid development process, working alongside product managers, and engineers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for pushing innovation in mobile gaming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work under pressure in a timely manner without sacrificing quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Illustrator, Photoshop, and standard tools of the trade.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical understanding of HTML5/CSS, and/or other web/native code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prototype ideas via interactive mocks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some fluency in Japanese.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being a game nerd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-ui-ux-gree-international-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-ui-ux-gree-international-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Producer/ Project Manager at Leap Motion in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Leap Motion is looking for highly organized Interactive Producer/ Project Manager to manage projects across multiple digital channels including web, ecommerce, social, and email. The Producer can effectively manage internal cross functional teams and external vendors to balance longer-term creative and strategic programs with day-to-day tactical projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages and leads digital creative and production projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the timely execution and delivery of creative projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates digital creative project progress across the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates cross-functional teams in order to ensure completion of digital creative projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrates up-to-date project management expertise and applies this to the development, execution, and improvement of project action plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years experience as a producer or project manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing website development, mobile sites, apps, and social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well versed in front end development technology (HTML, CSS, Javascript) and understands back end development and integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing QA process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of site usability and information architecture principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing scope, schedule, issues, risks, and resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-producer-project-manager-leap-motion-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-producer-project-manager-leap-motion-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director, Interactive - Education at Apple in Santa Clara Valley, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a member of the graphic design team, the Art Director designs marketing and communication content for the Education market, and appearing primarily on apple.com, and in email communications. They work under the limited direction of an Associate Creative Director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position requires a proven track record of graphic design for the web, particularly in the marketing of major brands; a strong knowledge of interactive creative development processes; and experience developing creative solutions with a relatively high level of autonomy. The ideal candidate will have an interest in how technology can be used as an educational tool both inside and outside of the classroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven, superior ability to develop innovative and on-strategy designs which are highly resolved from a formal perspective, and which meet the objectives of the assignment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently executes on the assignment, as well as creates inspiring design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven ability to solve problems conceptually in collaboration with the broader interactive team, including writers, other designers, information architects, and developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate effectively with creative and project management staff, engendering trust and respect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good at presenting and “selling” the worth of creative ideas, to influence decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent skills with design software used in the design process, including, but not limited to, Illustrator and Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent ability to art direct photographers and illustrators as necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scope of Duties and Responsibilities Include: Accountable for successful conception and execution of visual creative direction on assigned projects for the Education market that successfully pushes the Apple brand forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regularly reviews creative work with the group’s senior creative staff to get feedback on direction, and to ensure the work is aligned with other activities in the group.  Serves as a resource to, and periodically supervises the work of, senior designers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BA or BFA in Graphic Design or other related design discipline, with a minimum 5 to 7 years relevant (preferably agency) experience specializing in visual design for the web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in advertising, marketing, corporate identity, brand management, sales promotion and/or new media communication. Expertise in developing creative solutions in a variety of campaigns, across a broad range of problems and media, including advertising, graphic design, Corporate ID, interactive, and collateral.  Solid knowledge of the requirements of the creative process including typical time and resources needed to produce with efficiency quality work on time, and to specification.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-interactive-education-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-interactive-education-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Salesforce in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Salesforce.com is looking for an amazing designer/art director with a solid history of creating impressive interactive/offline experiences and campaigns. You can conceive of engaging ideas that help propel a client’s brand and result in visually stunning award winning creative solutions. You must have an exceptional portfolio and a solid broadcast reel is a huge plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The AD:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Art Director has a unique understanding for strategy and a talent for creative development. He/She is able to manage and inspire a team, as well as work independently. Some jobs will require you to direct a team of people to produce your ideas and visions, while others will require hands-on art direction and design. The AD is able to work collaboratively with other creatives and the ECD, CD’s and ACD’s to arrive at solid concepts and then own those ideas through to completion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must have experience working in a web design or advertising agency environment. We are looking for you to have work involving websites, advertising, social networking and mobile, to name a few. You have a solid understanding of, if not hands-on experience, with multi-media interactive platforms and tools like Flash, video, 3D, coding and scripting, CS4, etc. You are experienced in working with designers, producers, videographers, action scripters, coders and animators to achieve high production values in the work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Areas of Responsibility:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works in creative team, typically including an art director or senior art director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for understanding the client’s business and industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in all necessary internal and external meetings – client briefings, status, team briefings, brainstorming sessions and presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with team to deliver excellent work for every aspect of a project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages multiple projects for various clients and works with project management to meet all deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively identifies and pursues opportunities on behalf of the client that go beyond the obvious or accepted solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presents and sells work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides rationale for the team’s aesthetic and strategic thinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for having a point of view and for expressing it well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepares for all internal and external presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains strong, proactive relationship with all members of the creative, as well as members of the client team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is aware and respectful of everyone’s role and contribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates with all team members about all current and future work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attends meetings – punctual and prepared.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentors, trains and inspires less experienced Art Directors/Designers and other team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates regularly with the ACD and Creative Director about Client issues, team dynamics, workloads, new opportunities, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in building a strong, profitable and respected discipline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works to stay current with and employ appropriate new technologies and opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to all new business pitches whenever necessary and with a sense of urgency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in building a collaborative, inspiring and fun culture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in English, Liberal Arts, Humanities or other relevant disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years experience in an advertising agency or design shop or other professional environment including considerable writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have an established portfolio which displays long-term client relationships, integrated campaigns, and compelling and effective writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong conceptual and compositional skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with corporate branding, and a clear understanding of marketing strategies and concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong presentation skills, and outstanding communication and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interpret creative direction, and a willingness to learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for the medium and a familiarity with its possibilities are essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with current advertising and design trends, and practical knowledge of Internet and multimedia technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penchant for detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Coordinator at Trinet Internet Solutions Inc. in Irvine, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trinet is a full-service web firm with expert capabilities in web strategy consulting, interactive marketing, creative and design services, web development, and web campaign management services. Basically, we are all about developing great websites and applications that allow our clients to breathe new life into their communication efforts and increase revenue or contributions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We not only work to help businesses achieve success online, but we also help many non-profits and faith based ministries as they work to meet the physical and spiritual needs of people both around the world and here at home.  Some of the organizations we have done work for include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coca Cola&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;World Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harvest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IMAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Billy Graham Evangelistic Organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toyota Racing Development (TRD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on the Family&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samaritan&amp;rsquo;s Purse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cisco / Linksys&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Red Cross, and many more…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a full-time, entry level &lt;strong&gt;Project Coordinator&lt;/strong&gt; for our corporate office in &lt;strong&gt;Irvine, CA&lt;/strong&gt;.  The selected candidate will be a motivated, career focused team player with a desire to work in a growing small to medium sized company.  This is a great entry level position for someone interested in a career in Project/Operations Management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directing programmers and graphic designers in building/maintaining websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taking Meeting Minutes and reporting on action items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scheduling meetings and preparing materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting Project Managers through engagements with clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online, phone, email, webex communication with clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracking time and intricate details of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friendly and good attitude with customers and internal staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoys being involved in a cutting edge, Internet industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional writing ability (able to provide samples)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to delegate and follow up to ensure progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong judgment, analytical and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years working in some sort of customer service role where maintaining client relationships was a primary accountability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of experience working with websites/online marketing (building your own, managing client websites, managing depepartment websites, etc.) strong preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate working knowledge of MS Office Suite, specifically PPT, Excel and Word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Certifications/internships surrounding Operations Management, Business Analysis, Project Management will be favorably considered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-year degree is strongly preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Irvine, California, United States&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Type&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full-Time/Regular&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-coordinator-trinet-internet-solutions-inc.-irvine-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-coordinator-trinet-internet-solutions-inc.-irvine-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Project Manager at Huge in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Senior Project Manager&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Project Managers should have 6-8+ years experience managing large-scale interactive projects from discovery and design to technical development and implementation. Extensive experience in an agency environment working with and implementing both project management and online best practices on and across large-scale engagements are a critical component of this role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, the Senior Project Manager must be attuned to value the details as well as be able to understand and drive towards the big picture. Analytical and quick thinking in a fast-paced environment are essential. The Senior Project Manager is an enthusiastic problem solver and thrives on being engaged at all levels of the project. As the key point of contact for both the Client and the project team, the Senior Project Manager plays a pivotal role in the success of any major engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for developing overall project management strategy and working with discipline leads and project teams to execute on plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor day-to-day activities of the project team and ensure work is progressing as planned. Work with project team and actively be involved in the work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage schedules, budgets, assets, and overall project organization to ensure requirements and project deliverables dates are clearly communicated, understood and executed upon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work across several projects with one or more junior project manager(s) or as the primary Project Manager on a large-scale engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively and efficiently plan and prioritize all deliverables and resources working across project(s) based on scope of work and project goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively monitor project risks and scope creep to foresee/identify potential problems and proactively identify solutions to address them in advance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently identify needs that Clients may not recognize and ensure approaches and solutions are linked to objectives and future needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently manage client expectations, ensure delivery of the highest quality service, and solicit and act on client feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and document project status and strategic recommendations to clients, team members and senior HUGE management on a regular basis; escalate issues accordingly via the appropriate channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively identify opportunities and deliver improvements; evangelize the HUGE project management methodology and project processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with project team leads to present work as well as participate in new business presentation opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the training/mentoring of junior project managers on HUGE project management methodologies and best practices as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree and at least 6-8+ years of experience in interactive project management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written, presentation, and interpersonal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to motivate, support and understand different project teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding and awareness of product development and experience tying product goals to business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail and focus on task completion is critical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the development of large-scale websites and a strong understanding of associated web development technologies and third party applications and platforms is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile and social media/community experience an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencies in MS Office, MS Project, bug tracking, wiki and other related project management and common communications tools is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PMP and other project management certifications are a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;HUGE is an equal opportunity employer (EOE). We strongly support diversity in the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-huge-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-huge-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Huge in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Project Manager&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager is responsible for the management and delivery of mid to large-scale interactive website design/development projects. The Project Manager works with the Engagement Director to ensure that the project team is poised to meet the objectives and goals of each project on-time and on-budget as well as champion quality and integrity of the end result. Project Managers must have 3-5 years experience managing interactive projects from discovery and design to technical development and implementation. Experience in an agency environment is key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager is an enthusiastic problem solver and thrives on being engaged at all levels of the project. As the key point of contact for both the Client and the project team, the Project Manager plays a pivotal role in the success of an engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for developing and managing the project plan and working with discipline leads and project teams to execute on plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor day-to-day activities of the project team and ensure work is progressing as planned. Work with project team and be actively involved in all aspects of the work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage schedules, budgets, assets, and overall project organization to ensure requirements and project deliverables dates are clearly communicated, understood and executed upon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively and efficiently plan and prioritize all deliverables and resources working across project(s) based on scope of work and project goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively monitor project risks and scope creep to foresee/identify potential problems and proactively identify solutions to address them in advance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently identify needs that Clients may not recognize and ensure approaches and solutions are linked to objectives and future needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently manage client expectations, ensure delivery of the highest quality service, and solicit and act on client feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and document project status and strategic recommendations to clients, team members and senior HUGE management on a regular basis; escalate issues accordingly via the appropriate channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively identify opportunities and deliver improvements; follow HUGE project management methodology and project processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with project team leads to present work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree and at least 3-5+ years of experience in interactive project management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written, presentation, and interpersonal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work with and support cross-functional project teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand and document project requirements and dependencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of business and functional requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail and focus on task completion is critical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the design and development websites and an understanding of web technologies and third party applications and platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile and social media/community experience an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencies in MS Office, MS Project, bug tracking, wiki and other related project management and common communications tools is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;HUGE is an equal opportunity employer (EOE). We strongly support diversity in the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-huge-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-huge-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>