<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Design / Art Director at The Oya Group in Los Gatos, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Oya Group is seeking an experienced Designer/Art Director to join our creative team in Los Gatos as our in-house design lead. We’re an established Silicon Valley design, branding, and strategic marketing agency, and are looking for an energetic addition to our team. The position will be demanding but also rewarding for your design portfolio. Candidates should be well versed in traditional print and branding as well as web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a dog-friendly office and have a sweet black lab with big brown eyes, named Rain, who will gaze at you intently until you scratch behind her ears. And, you’ll want to. She’s relentlessly cute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About You:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve got a myriad of projects in your bulging portfolio, from brand development, web design, print and a generous helping of interactive experience. You’re proud of your work but take constructive feedback well. You&amp;rsquo;re all about getting your hands dirty, rolling up your sleeves, and taking creative ideas from concept to completion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re all about the details. Creative problem solving and process comes as naturally to you as monarchs to Monterey. Your finished product is technically flawless and ready to deliver to the client, web developer, or printer. You are a sucker for a pair of “big brown eyes”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Driving designs from concept to print/launch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with project managers, vendors, and senior creative team to create solutions for design problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present concepts to client and provide sound rationale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on projects ranging from identity design to web to presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage file iterations and design process with client budget, timeline, and requirements in mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years professional experience in print and web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Design, preferably from an accredited art school&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid design portfolio with examples of relevant work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of applications including Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talent and ability to sketch to illustrate visual concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work well in a fast-paced environment, with high volume project turn around&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be organized and pay attention to details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous agency experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to design high-end executive presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working knowledge of CSS, and HTML would be awesome&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video experience would put you over the top&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for learning about new technology and design trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a good sense of humor, professional behavior, and friendly attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Start Date&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now? — How about Now? If you’d love to work in a small studio environment, with friendly staff and international brands, then send us your resume now!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/design-art-director-the-oya-group-los-gatos-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/design-art-director-the-oya-group-los-gatos-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Project Manager at ScrollMotion in San Diego, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor day-to-day activities of the project team and ensure work is progressing as planned, as well as being actively involved in the work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage schedules, budgets, assets, and overall project organization to ensure requirements and project deliverables dates are clearly communicated, understood and executed upon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work across several projects as the primary Project Manager on a large-scale engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively and efficiently plan and prioritize all deliverables and resources working across project(s) based on scope of work and project goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively monitor project risks and scope creep to foresee/identify potential problems and proactively identify solutions to address them in advance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently identify needs that Clients may not recognize and ensure approaches and solutions are linked to objectives and future needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently manage client expectations, ensure delivery of the highest quality service, and solicit and act on client feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and document project status and strategic recommendations to clients, team members and senior ScrollMotion management on a regular basis; escalate issues accordingly via the appropriate channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with project team leads to present work as well as participate in new business presentation opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience in project management or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior project management experience at a web firm, interactive agency, or software development company is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written, presentation, and interpersonal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of both theoretical and practical aspects of project management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience applying project management techniques and using project management software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding and awareness of product development and experience tying product goals to business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail and focus on task completion is critical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile and social media/community experience an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencies in MS Office, MS Project, bug tracking, wiki and other related project management and common communications tools is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PMP and other project management certifications are a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-scrollmotion-san-diego-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-scrollmotion-san-diego-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Support Manager at ServiceNow in San Diego, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Join the hottest name in enterprise software today! ServiceNow, one of the fastest growing publicly held SaaS and Cloud Companies, is transforming and reinventing the way large corporations are managing their IT. Established in 2004, ServiceNow develops and delivers a comprehensive suite of cloud-based services for enterprise IT management. You are invited to be part of the success – join our team of dedicated professionals and grow your career with us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ServiceNow is currently seeking a Technical Support Manager. The successful candidate will manage our growing Technical Support team. This includes providing leadership to the team&amp;rsquo;s technical staff, interfacing with Development on customer impacting enhancements and fixes, recruiting and development of support staff, development of key team metrics, development and implementation of technical support inactivates and development of cross functional effort within customer support for new releases. The successful candidate will also have responsibility for leading efforts in developing and implementing world class technical support services, knowledge base content, best practices and methodologies to deliver unsurpassed service and support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading efforts to develop to build Technical Support SME teams including development of architecture, strategies, objectives and metrics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive the highest levels of performance from each team through coaching, training and performance metrics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership in developing and implementing service best practices that deliver world class customer satisfaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading by example to cultivate and maintain a culture built on teamwork and collaboration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managed major outages and dissatisfaction issues for customer accounts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishing and leading a team of professionals to deliver service and support that will result in the highest possible levels of customer satisfaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A well-developed set of leadership, coaching, and organizational skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to adapt to an extremely fast-paced and ever changing environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent time management skills with the ability to routinely multitask from the tactical to the strategic activities in a fast paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-developed skills in written and oral communications,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 6 years technical support and service management experience with a minimum of 3-4 years in supervisory role is required. Prefer experience working in a web based service and technology environment where web based support programs and tools were a key component to service delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/BA in Computer Science, Software Engineering, Electrical Engineering or related field or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ServiceNow enterprise IT Service Management platform combines ITIL process support and SaaS delivery to provide a flexible, intuitive and self-managing application in the cloud. Founded in 2004, ServiceNow has a forward thinking business model and leading edge technologies. According to the 2010 Inc. 500 list, ServiceNow is one of the ten fastest growing software companies. For more information, please visit ServiceNow or Demo.Servicenow.com to checkout a fully functional instance of our software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Work Environment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a dynamic and rapidly growing software company with a strong sense of dedication to our customers. We work hard but try not to take ourselves too seriously. This is a very collaborative and inclusive work environment where individuals strong on aptitude and attitude will have an opportunity to grow their professional careers through working with some of the most advanced technology and talented developers in the business. We provide competitive compensation, generous benefits, and a professional, yet relaxed atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-manager-servicenow-san-diego-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-manager-servicenow-san-diego-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Project Manager at International Consulting Group Inc. in Silicon Valley, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;International Consulting Group Marketing (www.icgmarcom.com), located in Silicon Valley, is seeking a well-qualified Web Project Manager consultant for our leading High Tech client.
Location:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onsite at Client HQ – with some offsite flexibility. Silicon Valley/ South S.F. Bay Area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;W-2, Depending on experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duration:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Targeting a minimum of 1 year with potential to extend. Fulltime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Project Manager consultant will engage, collaborate with and support stakeholders across a key corporate division with web strategies, integrated web marketing projects, and ongoing measurement and analysis. The consultant will advise, manage and coordinate production of a wide range of Web/Online projects and deliverables. Key responsibility includes effective cross-functional teamwork with product marketing, marketing communications, demand generation, web content providers, web content strategists, editorial, web design, web development, development, and QA to develop, manage and publish a wide range of short-term and long-term web initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of generalist web project management experience or combined with an SEO or Web Producer background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record successfully managing a wide variety of web projects, maintenance/updates, and deliverables concurrently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid working knowledge and/or expertise with SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound understanding and/or expertise with UX/UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in Web production and web development processes and activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web content management, optimization, and publishing exposure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to effectively utilize design and content/editing resources to develop page mock-ups for coordination with web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SiteCatalyst or similar web analytics tool for analyzing online metrics/measurements, reporting, presentations, and providing ongoing recommendations and optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in high tech, F500 company environment, and/or large cross-functional teams ideal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor Degree in marketing, communications, or equivalent web/interactive coursework/certifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please submit your relevant cover letter/email text including “Web Project Manager”, and WORD-version Resume to: applicants@icgmarcom.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that no phone calls can be accepted. Only local-S.F. Bay Area candidates will be considered.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-project-manager-international-consulting-group-inc-silicon-valley-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-project-manager-international-consulting-group-inc-silicon-valley-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Eveo, Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager will manage all aspects of digital program development including interactive projects and web and mobile applications.  The ideal candidate will not only be able to deliver projects on time and on budget, but meet client requirements in a way that demonstrates solid project management skills and strong understanding of software and web development processes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own and manage all aspects of project development throughout the entire lifecycle of projects including budgets, timelines, resource management and work quality, based on business requirements defined by the Account team in conjunction with client stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with cross-functional teams within the organization to build and deliver high-quality work, on time and on budget, that meets and exceeds client expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate project status to internal teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mediate issues and proactively problem solve with both internal stakeholders and external clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track budget expenditures and report status, escalating any issues to Account Managers and Project Management leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively monitor project risks and scope creep to foresee/identify potential problems and proactively identify solutions to address them in advance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forecast and estimate new projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and navigate the medical and legal approval process common to large pharma companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simultaneously manage multiple large scale engagements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with Account teams to establish and maintain strong client partnerships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Knowledge, Skills &amp;amp; Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum years of experience:2+ years of experience in an interactive agency or software development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education: 4 year degree strongly preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of project management methodology including the ability to identify and resolve issues, manage risk, develop work plans and run team meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of software development, web technologies, web development processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to lead groups and small teams that include both technical and non-technical staff to successful outcomes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written and interpersonal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive agency experience- experience in the healthcare sector a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in the MS Office suite of applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Authorized to work in the US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local candidates preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Desired Attributes:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile application experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing Motion Graphics, Video and/or Animation projects a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical experience in software or web development a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Eveo Communication Group, Inc. is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. Applicants are considered for all positions without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability, sexual orientation, ancestry, marital or veteran status.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-eveo-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-eveo-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Pulsepoint in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager leads interactive marketing and Web development projects, oversees creative and technical project teams, interacts with business managers and is responsible for producing projects on time and on budget. The PM also contributes strategic and operational insight on client accounts to promote project efficiency and success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the creation, maintenance and delivery of detailed project plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies and scopes client requirements and deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create goals and milestones that correlate to billable events within a project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies, documents, and manages scope or deliverable change requests required whether initiated internally or by the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and maintains activity and progress reports for internal and external customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates daily tasks and assigns project resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracks all budget-related information, including billable hours and project expenses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the success of the project while remaining within the scoped time and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages and helps ensure client satisfaction in partnership with the internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Properly notifies the internal team of any risks, weaknesses or opportunities that could impact the success of the project, escalating to upper management as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plans for and controls quality by reviewing items before delivery to client; monitoring and enhancing internal and external deliverables/documents; working with internal teams on needed revisions/enhancements, and involving the Quality Assurance team at key project junctures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates and participates in periodic project and program reviews and strategy meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in and completes training and professional development as detailed within department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an understanding of the client&amp;rsquo;s operating environment and internal processes and procedures that may affect the project&amp;rsquo;s success; serves as point of contact for clients as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the use of best practices and apply lessons learned from previous projects; share lessons learned with other project management team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of relevant experience managing projects (preferably * 2-4 years within an interactive, advertising or marketing agency environment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management principles, methods and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of financial concepts and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to demonstrate experience with professional services processes and tools including workflow development and management, milestone management and quality assurance practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of technical and creative design and development principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing resources, budgets and project timing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience analyzing complex data reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in MS Project, and the entire MS Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business analysis and requirements gathering skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Pulsepoint in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager leads interactive marketing and Web development projects, oversees creative and technical project teams, interacts with business managers and is responsible for producing projects on time and on budget. The PM also contributes strategic and operational insight on client accounts to promote project efficiency and success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the creation, maintenance and delivery of detailed project plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies and scopes client requirements and deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create goals and milestones that correlate to billable events within a project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies, documents, and manages scope or deliverable change requests required whether initiated internally or by the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and maintains activity and progress reports for internal and external customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates daily tasks and assigns project resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracks all budget-related information, including billable hours and project expenses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the success of the project while remaining within the scoped time and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages and helps ensure client satisfaction in partnership with the internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Properly notifies the internal team of any risks, weaknesses or opportunities that could impact the success of the project, escalating to upper management as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plans for and controls quality by reviewing items before delivery to client; monitoring and enhancing internal and external deliverables/documents; working with internal teams on needed revisions/enhancements, and involving the Quality Assurance team at key project junctures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates and participates in periodic project and program reviews and strategy meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in and completes training and professional development as detailed within department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an understanding of the client’s operating environment and internal processes and procedures that may affect the project’s success; serves as point of contact for clients as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the use of best practices and apply lessons learned from previous projects; share lessons learned with other project management team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of relevant experience managing projects (preferably * 2-4 years within an interactive, advertising or marketing agency environment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management principles, methods and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of financial concepts and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to demonstrate experience with professional services processes and tools including workflow development and management, milestone management and quality assurance practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of technical and creative design and development principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing resources, budgets and project timing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience analyzing complex data reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in MS Project, and the entire MS Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business analysis and requirements gathering skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director, Digital Programming at Red Bull North America, Inc. in Santa Monica, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Drawing on parent company Red Bull&amp;rsquo;s quarter century heritage, Red Bull Media House (RBMH) creates compelling, entertaining and authentic content across film, television, print and digital. Red Bull Media House is a key driver in highly coveted young male demographic across all platforms and is widely recognized as an authority by both its target audience, industry media and influencers.  Red Bull Media House tells one cohesive story that lets all of its parts work together in concert, allowing consumers to see and connect the dots, no matter what screen or medium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PURPOSE OF THIS JOB&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Red Bull Media House has an opening for a world-class Director of Digital Programming. The ideal candidate will own the editorialization, distribution and monetization of Red Bull owned media properties across all relevant digital channels and device platforms, the expansion of the Red Bull digital channel ecosystem and the development of new digital media products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and execute editorial and programming strategies for Red Bull media properties including Red Bull TV, Red Bull Signature Series, Red Bull Gaming and Red Bull Soundstage with a focus on rapid audience growth, cross-platform experiences and revenue generation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and develop Red Bull owned web sites, social networks (e.g. Facebook, Twitter, Instagram), digital media channels (e.g. YouTube, Hulu, Xbox Live) and consumer device applications (e.g. on iPhone/iPad, Android, Windows and Xbox).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance audience research, forecasting, editorial and marketing planning to continuously improve the quality and relevance of our media products, drive audience growth and maximize revenue opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and bring to market new content formats, interactive user experiences and digital products to further strengthen Red Bull owned media properties and create new online platforms that enable self-propelling scenes within the Red Bull core playgrounds in sports, culture, music and gaming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;MAJOR ACTIVITIES TO ENSURE ACHIEVEMENT OF KEY RESULTS AND DELIVERABLES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and execute digital programming strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the creation and execution of editorial plans for all digital media products and oversee the integrated execution across all relevant digital channels and screens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with the Distribution department to develop new marketing and syndication partnerships that expand viewership of our digital media properties and open up new revenue sources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop programing, marketing and monetization strategies for the launch of a new Internet based TV product and secure digital content, distribution and marketing partnerships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a framework for structured monetization of Red Bull media products across digital channels and device platforms through subscription, sponsorship and advertising models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build out a durable digital channel and device platform ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and expand an integrated system of owned web sites and applications, social networks and media channels to provide customers with seamless media experiences through the channels and devices of their choice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Editorialize Red Bull playgrounds in action sports, motor sports, music and gaming within dedicated content channels on redbull.com with customized experiences for all relevant screen formats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grow and strengthen Red Bull communities through innovative content strategies for social anchor platforms Facebook and Twitter, emerging channels like Instagram and innovative social features within our own properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Develop a world-class Internet based TV and video distribution system through the integration of our own video and TV applications with leading OTT platforms including YouTube, Hulu, xBox and Roku&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advance audience research, forecasting, editorial and marketing planning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop audience segmentation, modeling and forecasting techniques and apply against all Red Bull digital media products to maximize audience growth across channels and device platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently monitor consumer needs and behaviors to optimize editorial calendars, programing schedules and distribution plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the planning and implementation of sophisticated monitoring capabilities across all Red Bull owned and operated web sites, applications and digital channels to better understand user behavior, optimize SEO, allow for advertising inventory management and provide insight for sponsors and advertising partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring to market new digital media products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create new and innovative media products by blending digital video, gaming and interactive formats with real-world consumer experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with the Red Bull Marketing, Brand and Product Innovation teams on the development of new digital platforms that will enable self-propelling scenes within the Red Bull core playgrounds in sports, culture, music and gaming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, test and bring to market new advertising formats and subscription models that are optimized for RBMH digital media and product offerings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;KEY RESULTS AND DELIVERABLES (WHAT DOES SUCCESS LOOK LIKE)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and bring to market new digital media products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Achieve ambitious audience growth, engagement and revenue targets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anticipate new digital business opportunities and articulate to company leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit, manage and mentor high-performing editorial and programming teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become a leading advocate of the Red Bull Media House mission and products with the media, entertainment and technology industries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flawless follow-through; all deadlines met&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 + years experience in developing digital marketing, advertising and/or media software products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong programing and editorial background; hands-on experience with running consumer focused content portal or video site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of online advertising formats, platforms, tools and processes, experiences with publisher tools preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional team leadership skills, ability to build positive relationships and work cross-functionally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track record of cross-functional collaboration in a variety of organizational environments &amp;amp; cultures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication skills, including written, verbal and presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound strategic thinking and analytical capabilities with an emphasis on reading and interpreting data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong planning, prioritization and project management competencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel 25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Live and represent the Red Bull Brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree, MBA a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-digital-programming-red-bull-north-america-inc-santa-monica-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-digital-programming-red-bull-north-america-inc-santa-monica-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at R/GA in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a Creative Director, you are responsible for creative strategy and general direction of the work. In collaboration with the team and designers, the Creative Director ensures the quality of the concept and the work produced, in addition to presenting work to the client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Creative Director also assists in managing the department and helps ensure the growth of individuals in the Visual Design Department. We are looking for a strong strategic and conceptual thinker who can present their ideas clearly to the team. More specifically, someone who knows how to look at corporate brands from fresh angles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified people have 8+ years of design experience in web, advertising and typography.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An in-depth understanding of HTML, and the capabilities of web browsers are essential, and knowledge of Photoshop, Illustrator, and Flash is required.  After Effects, Maya experience is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely strong leader with the ability to manage multiple clients and projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience in Graphic Design, team management and client facing experience. Working knowledge of Interaction Design, technology, usability and experience design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is responsible for strong conceptual and strategic directions and clearly presents those ideas to the team and the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Builds strong relationships with multi-levels of marketing clients. Assists clients with deepening their knowledge of interactive marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong client managing skills, works directly with the clients, directing the users experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral, written, and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversees Art Director providing feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-r-ga-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-r-ga-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director of UI/UX at GREE International in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The GREE Design team is looking for an experienced Director of Game UX/UI to join our fun, brilliant and diverse team.  You will work with the Head of Design, and all team members leading by example, and helping to define better process, and generate better output from the Game UX/UI Design team. You will also work with an incredibly talented group of artists, product managers, and engineers to help fuel innovation via user centric practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work to support and grow best UX practices with the Game UX group and embedding this into all product teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct regular output of Game UI group assets for quality and promptness including contract and external workforce.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track and consistently improve output from Design group, by helping to facilitate change where needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and iterate on robust processes, and management of projects across team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute personally and via team to well thought out, clear, and polished products, providing an engaging and delightful user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor team members, introducing them to new techniques, design patterns, and user research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3+ years of team leadership, and 6+ years of design/art experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent and diverse portfolio of UX / UI for Games, Apps, Prototypes or otherwise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work in games, and some mobile experience, or deep understanding of mobile space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading a product design team in a rapid development process, working alongside product managers, and engineers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for pushing innovation in mobile gaming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work under pressure in a timely manner without sacrificing quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Illustrator, Photoshop, and standard tools of the trade.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical understanding of HTML5/CSS, and/or other web/native code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prototype ideas via interactive mocks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some fluency in Japanese.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being a game nerd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-ui-ux-gree-international-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-ui-ux-gree-international-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>