<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Director, Product Marketing at Castlight Health in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As Castlight’s Director of Product Marketing focused on employee communications, you are responsible for leading a critical element of Castlight’s value to employers – employee health care consumerism engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Castlight’s employee communications practice rigorously determines the right frequency, form, and content of employee communications to turn employees into engaged consumers of health care. You lead Castlight’s team focused on creating and executing direct-to-employee communications in all media to drive Castlight registration and return usage for Castlight’s employer customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years of experience designing and executing employee benefits communications with a minimum of 3 years of direct team management experience in this capacity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful track record of working with employee benefits teams to identify and initiate new employee communications opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively with Castlight’s customers in a consultative fashion, up to and including leading large communications workshops and influencing senior management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent management, personnel development, and mentoring skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and respect for the role of the employee in the business of health care, as well as a keen interest and expertise in employee behavior change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talent for communicating ideas in compelling ways that influence others; excellent writing ability and eye for effective design elements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise working in both offline and on-line communications channels, including the latest digital technologies including social media, enterprise social media, mobile, interactive web, video, and SMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with ambiguity and making decisions on the fly when needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working at a leading employee benefits consulting firm preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance degree preferred; BA/BS required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all – intellectual horsepower, with an eager curiosity and demonstrated ability to learn quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead Castlight’s team working with the country’s largest and most innovative employers to plan, design, execute, and measure multi-channel communications campaigns for health care consumerism in general and Castlight’s product in particular.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directly manage Castlight 4-6 Castlight Product Marketing Managers plus 3rd party communications consultants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate expertise in direct marketing and employee benefits communications with a broad understanding of health care consumerism and extensive knowledge of Castlight’s services and operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help champion Castlight’s company wide strategic efforts to drive employee engagement &amp;ndash; both registration and return usage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-product-marketing-castlight-health-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-product-marketing-castlight-health-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director, Technical Development &amp; Delivery at Scripps Networks in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Scripps Networks Interactive is seeking a Director, Technical Development &amp;amp; Delivery for a new digital video initiative. The initiative will be a data-driven video-distribution ecosystem that will allow SNI to syndicate high-quality video content across a large number of sites, mobile applications, and other connected experiences. It will include a branded destination website that promises to bring &amp;ldquo;life&amp;rsquo;s best, all in one place&amp;rdquo; and deliver an experience that conveys the professional, authentic, and authoritative quality of the content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Technical Development Director owns solution delivery and is ultimately responsible for development project leadership, management, quality, and timely / cost-effective delivery. The Senior Delivery Manager has to work effectively with upper management and multiple stakeholders and to apply customer relationship management practices, including the identification of appropriate, mutually agreed objectives. He/she must also be able to lead technical individual (Developers, QAs), provide input to functional design and architecture, track and resolve technical issues during build and test phases, and overall to successfully develop and deliver technical solutions. He/She will undertake the overall responsibility for the development and delivery of new and/or existing applications while working with the product managers, technical architecture, and the development/QA team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide overall development leadership, and direct teams in the delivery of high-quality products on time and within budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for managing the entire SDLC process for software products and/or projects in Agile environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for continuously monitoring the overall progress of projects and having a risk assessment and mitigation plan in place for further communication to senior management team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead development team in requirements analysis, features scoping and backlog scheduling for multiple intermediate milestones until the final delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead development team in accurately projecting efforts, resource requirements, risks, constraints in project management related activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement standards &amp;amp; best practices for software development and ensure process compliance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directly and indirectly manage the work effort of Scripps development team and 3rd party vendors, in the delivery of assigned projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for analyzing resource requirements, recruitment and succession planning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for training and mentoring of the development team and monitoring their performance throughout the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for keeping self and the development team updated on latest trends in tools &amp;amp; technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish and maintain relationships with business clients to ensure that their needs are articulated in business and technological terms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with business and technology leaders to develop and manage the software development roadmap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage business requirements and scope on a technical level, and coordinate between cross-functional teams to ensure product adherence to business requirements and architectural direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as initial escalation point within the delivery team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to think strategically about business objectives and synthesize a broad range of requirements from business development, licensing, legal, marketing, operational, technical, user experience to develop functional specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience establishing technical delivery management best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful experience with hiring and mentoring technical members of the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills. Strong analytical and quantitative skills; strong bias towards data-based decision making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nimbleness and comfort with ambiguity; comfort responding quickly to rapidly evolving opportunities and situations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong bias for action; ability to juggle multiple priorities and create a sense of urgency in a fast-paced, dynamic environment. Willingness to roll up the sleeves and do whatever is necessary to meet team goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to lead cross-functional teams through influence versus direct management; excellent interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management disciplines &amp;ndash; scope, schedule, budget, risk, andIssue management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with multiple delivery methodologies (e.g., Waterfall, RUP, Agile/SCRUM).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to lead by influence up, down, and across an organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of management or project lead experience required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10+ years of web, e-commerce or mobile software development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-technical-development-and-delivery-scripps-networks-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-technical-development-and-delivery-scripps-networks-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Art Director at Liquid error: private method `gsub' called for nil:NilClass in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our client, a global hybrid production company’s Los Angeles office is looking to permanently hire a senior level Digital Art Director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Deliverables:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Installations and other media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The Job:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your job will be split between art directing projects (supported by our client’s Creative Director) and leading pitch work. They are team-oriented and there is always a project team with you, whether it’s a pitch or a project. You will team up with our client’s developers, creative directors, producers, directors and animators to keep delivering some of the world’s finest creative work out of their LA offices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a true digital art director with a strong knowledge and understanding of digital and traditional communication, excel when presenting ideas to top agency teams – and, of course, you have a fine-tuned aesthetic. Lastly, you have hands-on skills in design, and know your way around code, animation, and film production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please apply for this position through our Online Registration System.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We appreciate your interest but due to time constraints we can only contact candidates in consideration. Creative Niche is dedicated to matching outstanding communication, design and interactive professionals with the right companies. If you are not contacted for the current role(s) for which you have applied, please be confident that your application will be electronically filed for future searches.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-art-director-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-art-director-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Director at KQED Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Associate Director, Foundation and Government Support is responsible for researching, identifying, soliciting, securing and stewarding philanthropic grants in support of two to three assigned content areas at KQED, with a current focus on KQED News and KQED Education. The Associate Director will raise funds for projects within these content areas across multiple platforms, including public television, radio, and interactive media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working closely with the Director, Foundation and Government Support, this position helps to provide leadership to the Foundation and Government Support team, which includes advising and mentoring the Project Supervisor/s, Project Manager/s and Development Associate; and serving as a key liaison with content staff across different departments at KQED. The Director will look to the Associate Director to help shape strategy, build departmental capacity, track workflow and foster a truly collaborative culture of teamwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate for this position will have a passion for public media, and especially news and public affairs topics; as well as a deep understanding of education practice, methodologies and issues in the education community and field at large. Interest in and enthusiasm for all of KQED’s work is essential, as fundraising for projects beyond designated content areas may be assigned at a future time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Accountabilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FUNDRAISING. Identifies and develops funding relationships with local, regional and national foundations and government sources of support through formal grant inquiries, proposals, reports and other written correspondence; telephone calls and email updates; events (hosted by KQED or other); and meetings with funders that will usually include one or more additional KQED colleagues. For KQED News, this includes fundraising for specific news programming across media platforms (radio, television, online, mobile) and reporting around topic areas such as community health, governance, immigration and more. For KQED Education, this includes raising funds (a) to produce standards-aligned digital learning objects, (b) to distribute these resources via KQED.org and other web-based platforms, and &amp;copy; to train educators on use of educational media and digital media production tools in the classroom and other formal/informal learning environments. 65%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;COLLABORATION. Works with the Director, Foundation and Government Support on departmental planning and funding strategies; manages the workplan for the Foundation and Government Support team; coordinates crediting of foundation and government donors. Also works collaboratively across the broader Development Division and with content/production staff (including Senior Executive Producers, Executive Producers, Producers, Web Producers, Outreach Managers, and Production Managers) and Finance to oversee and manage all tasks associated with creating, executing and maintaining a strategy to raise the necessary funds for budgeted projects within designated content areas. 10%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LIAISON. Serves as an important liaison between KQED content/production staff and Development with a particular focus on news, education and other related projects in need of funding. This includes attending cross-division content meetings, and meeting regularly with television, radio, interactive and education content creators to keep informed about current and upcoming projects, as well as the development of station-wide initiatives. 10%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GRANT COMPLIANCE. Complies with reporting requirements for grants and communicates in a timely and effective manner on the progress and outcome of funded projects and activities—both internally (to the Development Division, and Finance and Legal Departments) and externally (to funders). 10%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Represents KQED at community and industry-related events. 2.5%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other essential duties as required TBD. 2.5%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of five years fundraising experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with local, regional and/or national private and corporate foundation community required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superb writing skills; ability to compose, edit and proof correspondence, reports, proposals, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to persuasively communicate with and diplomatically respond to present and potential funders, staff, community contacts, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interact productively with people at all levels and to work well in a team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple, simultaneous projects and deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly adept at proactively researching and accessing information about funders and funding opportunities, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with word processing, spreadsheet and development database software required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-director-kqed-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-director-kqed-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Art Director at American Constitution Society in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Fi is a boutique-minded agency, with full-service digital offerings that span the world. Our clients, such as HTC, Porsche and Google, come to Fi because while being lean, we also think big and bold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal Senior Art Director candidate comes from a small agency back-ground, where he/she has been a hands-on leader and artistic force for both the clients and the company. The Art Director is involved in most creative under-takings, from project conception to design prototyping to design execution. He/she is expertly skilled in defining and executing design styles based on client strategy, brand, and creative guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate has strong experience creating and managing design directions and materials. The daily work includes brainstorming new concepts, nailing down guidelines for artistic direction, making quick directional design mock-ups, leading and coaching the designers, ensuring adherence to our quality guidelines, and signing off on designs before delivery. The Art Director reports directly to the Creative Director and has daily communication with the CD on all creative matters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Main Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading the design input to RFP responses, executing design directions, managing the design process, induce design genius, and signing off on final designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively inspiring the team and the client through ideas, designs and quality mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for pixel-perfect visual appearance and design style of our projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seeing and communicating the artistic vision to the team and the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recognizing and acquiring new design talent for the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing, mentoring and coaching the design team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teaching and implementing Fi Quality as a standard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Giving daily feedback and direction to the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being the CDs steady support for creative input and design execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Key Experience and Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience defining and driving the design process and direction of both small and large interactive projects for Web and other digital media (interactive design agency or advertising agency a must)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert proficiency in multiple types of design software, including Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and designing interactive campaigns across multiple platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong on-line portfolio, showcasing expertly executed ranges of design skills and styles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Driven to lead the design team and propel Fi forward&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good insight into current web design trends and related creative spaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Immaculate attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, both written and oral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage and mentor designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural leadership abilities and affinity for building report, internally and externally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-american-constitution-society-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-american-constitution-society-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director Of Technology - Digital Products at FX in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Director, Technology, Digital Products (FX Networks – Los Angeles, CA 90064) Supporting FX Networks, FXNetworks.com is a multi-platform interactive entertainment, information and community destination that provides an extended experience to viewers featuring original content and digital experiences for FX originals, acquired movies and FXM. The Director of Technology, Digital Products will work with multi-disciplinary teams to innovate, plan and deliver technology projects on time and within budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with internal business units and external vendors to architect and implement highly-technical infrastructure solutions for the FX Networks suite of digital properties. As the key technical position within the group, the Director is charged with innovating and developing solutions for both consumer facing experiences and key infrastructure components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with Content, Products and Platforms and Social teams to improve performance across web, hand-held devices, connected devices and social services. Develops strategies to scale services to meet demand, API management and database systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage project status from a technical perspective by creating and maintaining project plans, time-lines and budgets, overseeing development by external agencies Position requires a deep passion for working on the latest technologies and services, collaborating with our internal team, business units, external vendors and technology partners to drive new experiences for FX viewers. Position works closely with Vice President to identify emerging technology to support digital infrastructure or consumer facing services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Project Management&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideates, plans, executes and successfully delivers on concurrent technology projects overseeing external vendors and working with internal business units&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides leadership in developing business requirements and is the technology leader at the network defining architecture for web, hand-held devices and connected platforms. Leads technology focused team meetings and participates in product meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracks and monitors project status, escalates unresolved technology issues to senior management as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops project plans and estimates in collaboration with internal teams and external vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops and maintains technical contingency from an operations and security perspective&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures quality of project deliverables by vendors from a technical perspective&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads efforts to improve technology development and project management Technology Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop requirements and functional specifications for complex infrastructure projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a solid understanding of FXNetworks.com infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify opportunities to leverage new products or platforms improving performance, functionality or consumer user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Fox is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-technology-digital-products-fx-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-technology-digital-products-fx-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>eMedia Art Director at Patagonia, Inc in Ventura, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;General Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The eMedia Art Director is responsible for taking a variety of projects from concept stage through completion in a high-energy environment. S/he works directly for and under the supervision of the eMedia Creative Director to further the Company’s graphic design aesthetic in eMedia. S/he is responsible for directing the U/X for eMedia projects and directing the efforts of production artists, illustrators, photographers and all other designers and design support personnel in order to ensure that all designs are produced for optimum performance on the web. S/he works closely with web developers and other technicians to insure that all projects run effectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for collaborating on ideas with the creative team to drive a variety of projects from concept to execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based on the target audience and defined user scenarios for all eMedia projects, develop and maintain the graphic design style that effectively communicates to the end user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the Creative Director and the Managing Producer to assure that all projects are completed on time and meet pre-determined milestones and objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Posses excellent time-management skills to meet development timelines while working on concurrent projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manager two in house web designers as well as select and manage outside creative freelancers and agencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor all of the Company’s web sites in order to identify areas of improvement. Work closely with the eMedia Creative Director, eMedia Development Director, and the Managing Producer to provide the most effective design in conjunction with programming guidelines; taking into account style guides, performance metrics and programming best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the eMedia Creative Manager to constantly evolve the Company’s eMedia design aesthetic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct consistent thorough reviews of new sites, competitors, and industry trends and recommend suggestions to the eMedia Creative Director in regards to graphic design and user interface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Physical Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to sit for extended periods of time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to look at a computer screen for extended periods of time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to maintain a composed and professional demeanor within a flexible and (at times noisy) work environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to travel utilizing various transportation methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years web design experience ideally within an agency or other service-oriented environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA, BFA, or greater degree in Graphic Design/Advertising (or other visual art).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive/online portfolio demonstrating solid on-brand understanding and executions as well as dynamic, out-of-the-box thinking and work for client projects in any/all of the following: print advertising, online advertising, email, direct mail,interactive,product websites/landing pages, Facebook applications, mobile apps, and events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of general marketing and advertising principles with regards to the incorporation/presentation of individual brands, products, and company business identity within design efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of designing intuitive site functionality, interaction, site architecture, user interfaces, and navigation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage creative projects effectively while maintaining priorities, deadlines and deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to effectively explain concepts and the design rationale behind your work to “non-creative others” including account managers, external partners, and clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to produce sketches, wireframes and information architecture diagrams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the user experience reflects customer needs and business goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong typography/layout skills and strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of web standards and preparing output for online development and interactive environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience commissioning photography or illustration and/or working with outside vendors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level experience with Adobe Creative Suite and Microsoft Office applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work well under pressure and deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in the Outdoor or Action Sports industry a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Employee Conduct:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the responsibility of every employee to contribute to a positive work environment through cooperative and professional interactions with co-workers, customers and vendors.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/emedia-art-director-patagonia-inc-ventura-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/emedia-art-director-patagonia-inc-ventura-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director of Product Management at AlwaysOnVacation, Inc in San Ramon, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;AlwaysOnVacation, Inc. is an established, venture backed online travel company dedicated to the distribution and marketing of vacation rental accommodations on the Internet. Based in San Ramon, California, with operations also in Ogden, Utah and New Delhi, India, we are seeking an experienced and talented Product Manager professional with a track record of delivering innovative consumer products to assume ownership of the company’s product development efforts. The Product Manager will work closely with the company co-founders to help define the product strategy and execute the roadmap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A passion to create innovative products is an absolute must. The product manager will play a vital role in shaping our online, social, mobile, and tablet based travel products.  Our platform is fully localized for 16 global markets and languages worldwide; our software is also accessible through our 60 plus global distribution network partners.  The ideal candidate will also have substantial experience in a fast-paced, deadline-driven development environment, where high visibility and strategically importance are opportunities.  An unfailing passion and capacity for advocating on behalf of our customers is also an absolute must because this role will directly impact the experience of millions of travelers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Product Manager is responsible for defining, prioritizing, planning, and driving the execution of the vision for the existing and future product lines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take charge of delivering an innovative consumer travel product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and manage product requirements, product strategies, roadmaps, project plans, and product specifications in collaboration with internal teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop all process flows, screen designs, data flow diagrams, and any other documentation that may be necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the design/build/test/release process end-to-end through consideration of market research, business requirements, customer feedback, and usability study findings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a team of Product Managers, in conjunction with the Product Marketing team and the travel industry, to assure consistency between travelers’ and travel suppliers ‘ perspectives of display an booking workflow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive integration with social media platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balance workload across multiple time zones to guarantee design quality in every deliverable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage multiple projects simultaneously in an agile development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred experience in travel or other consumer websites that required complex user interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in Product Development or Product Management. (Be prepared to tell us about the products you&amp;rsquo;ve developed!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in a high-tech industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in an entrepreneurial or startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with highly interactive UIs and web 2.0 design sensibilities and technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent visual design skills as well as interaction design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in user interface design, especially in social and e-commerce based UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience producing user-interface changes that increase conversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of visual design principles as they apply to web, mobile and desktop user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in best practices for web, mobile, and tablet design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience with common software development practices and the ability to grasp complex systems and speak about user work flow with developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with development team on complex projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work collaboratively within a team environment of other business systems analysts and cross functional peers to support deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to execute with very little or no direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven ability to follow through with multiple concurrent tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical, problem-solving, negotiation, task and project management, and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work in a team within a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to learn quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A problem-solving attitude. The ability to attack a problem from both an engineering and an end-user perspective&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-product-management-alwaysonvacation-inc-san-ramon-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-product-management-alwaysonvacation-inc-san-ramon-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Engagement Director at Huge in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Engagement Director is responsible for providing both strategic and tactical leadership across multi-million dollar engagement while still keeping their finger on the pulse of day-to-day project activities with a focus on meeting deliverable requirements, assuring overall quality of deliverables and ensuring overall customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Engagement Director is able to identify a client’s business needs and work with both the client and Huge cross-disciplinary teams to understand, define, and build effective and innovative solutions that generate measurable results. The Engagement Director is as much a leader as they are a communicator and mentor. The ability to read between the lines and hear what is not being said is at the core of this role and an ability to solicit information and facilitate its transfer consistently and correctly across the various project communication channels is a key skill of any successful Engagement Director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for overall account management, account growth, and leadership of cross-functional teams to develop approaches and targets that meet the business goals of our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for developing overall engagement strategy and working with discipline leads and project teams to execute on plans, involving people at optimal levels to maximize utilization targets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expand contacts with key client executives and maintain strong post-engagement relationships introducing new opportunities accordingly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage account profitability by developing and negotiating statements of work, ensuring work is delivered on budget, and invoicing clients according to the proper terms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently identify needs client may not recognize and ensure that approaches and solutions are linked to objectives and future needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently manage client expectations, ensure delivery of the highest quality service, and solicit and act on client feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively and efficiently plan and prioritize all deliverables and resources working across the account based on engagement strategy and work contracted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the training/mentoring of Project Managers on Huge project management methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resolve team conflicts as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong presentation, verbal and written skills as well as proven ability to develop well-written documents and presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in strategic development of new business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8-10 years related experience in a client services organization, preferably on projects with top tier consulting firms or interactive agencies (including web, mobile, video, brand, and strategic consulting projects)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of interactive experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to manage long term, multi-million dollar engagements with multiple project tracks and teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interact with clients of all levels and industry backgrounds, from the CEO to administrative support staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firm understanding of project management processes and methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of web development and design lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to manage and set client expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding and awareness of product development and experience tying product goals to business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of web development technologies, technology vendors and third party offerings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of satisfied large scale clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage and mentor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MBA Preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local candidates are encouraged to apply&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Huge is an equal opportunity employer (EOE). We strongly support diversity in the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/engagement-director-huge-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/engagement-director-huge-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Director Web Marketing at Good Technology in Sunnyvale, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Good Technology, we secure enterprise information and applications on today’s most popular mobile devices—such as iPhone, iPad, and Android—protecting both company and personal data. An exceptional user experience enhances productivity, whenever and wherever people want or need access. Mobile is on fire. So are we. Join us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Director of Web &amp;amp; eMarketing must have the chops to handle all things digital for a fast- growing business in the wild world of mobile technology. This senior leader will be responsible for leading the strategy, planning, development, and implementation of Good.com and all customer-facing web sites and online communities. In addition, the Senior Director will drive expansion of Good’s online presence by leveraging social media, mobile applications, and other methods to increase the company’s visibility. The web must be a well-oiled machine that serves as an effective and engaging “hub” for customer and prospect engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILTIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the strategy, concept development, execution, and management of the company&amp;rsquo;s Web presence, based on strategic initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide the leadership, vision, and direction for all Web-based activities, focusing on demand generation and engagement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan, manage, develop, and deploy any needed Web Services and mobile applications needed for Good.com and related properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct regular usability testing and continuously improve the site based on real world feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with our demand generation, events and marketing communications teams to deliver world-class web marketing programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive reporting and analysis to ensure Good.com is delivering on business objectives and deepen customer engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage a team of web production and community management resources as well as agency partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and manage an environment that allows for global growth and scale, including responsibility for the company’s Content Management System, translation management, and other tools needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the company is optimizing its Web presence for Search (SEO, SEM)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+10 years of progressively advancing Web experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+5 years of direct team management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+5 years of previous web site management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise of web technology, strategy, usability, content, interactive marketing, search, and social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talented thinker with proven ability to execute and deliver new concepts and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborative leadership experience working across diverse functions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience tracking, measuring, and reporting on all things Web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Budget and vendor (agency) management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree plus proven professional skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;LI-DN1&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-director-web-marketing-good-technology-sunnyvale-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-director-web-marketing-good-technology-sunnyvale-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>