<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Salesforce in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Salesforce.com is looking for an amazing designer/art director with a solid history of creating impressive interactive/offline experiences and campaigns. You can conceive of engaging ideas that help propel a client’s brand and result in visually stunning award winning creative solutions. You must have an exceptional portfolio and a solid broadcast reel is a huge plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The AD:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Art Director has a unique understanding for strategy and a talent for creative development. He/She is able to manage and inspire a team, as well as work independently. Some jobs will require you to direct a team of people to produce your ideas and visions, while others will require hands-on art direction and design. The AD is able to work collaboratively with other creatives and the ECD, CD’s and ACD’s to arrive at solid concepts and then own those ideas through to completion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must have experience working in a web design or advertising agency environment. We are looking for you to have work involving websites, advertising, social networking and mobile, to name a few. You have a solid understanding of, if not hands-on experience, with multi-media interactive platforms and tools like Flash, video, 3D, coding and scripting, CS4, etc. You are experienced in working with designers, producers, videographers, action scripters, coders and animators to achieve high production values in the work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Areas of Responsibility:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works in creative team, typically including an art director or senior art director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for understanding the client’s business and industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in all necessary internal and external meetings – client briefings, status, team briefings, brainstorming sessions and presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with team to deliver excellent work for every aspect of a project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages multiple projects for various clients and works with project management to meet all deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively identifies and pursues opportunities on behalf of the client that go beyond the obvious or accepted solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presents and sells work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides rationale for the team’s aesthetic and strategic thinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for having a point of view and for expressing it well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepares for all internal and external presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains strong, proactive relationship with all members of the creative, as well as members of the client team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is aware and respectful of everyone’s role and contribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates with all team members about all current and future work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attends meetings – punctual and prepared.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentors, trains and inspires less experienced Art Directors/Designers and other team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates regularly with the ACD and Creative Director about Client issues, team dynamics, workloads, new opportunities, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in building a strong, profitable and respected discipline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works to stay current with and employ appropriate new technologies and opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to all new business pitches whenever necessary and with a sense of urgency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in building a collaborative, inspiring and fun culture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in English, Liberal Arts, Humanities or other relevant disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years experience in an advertising agency or design shop or other professional environment including considerable writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have an established portfolio which displays long-term client relationships, integrated campaigns, and compelling and effective writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong conceptual and compositional skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with corporate branding, and a clear understanding of marketing strategies and concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong presentation skills, and outstanding communication and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interpret creative direction, and a willingness to learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for the medium and a familiarity with its possibilities are essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with current advertising and design trends, and practical knowledge of Internet and multimedia technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penchant for detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-salesforce-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Coordinator at Trinet Internet Solutions Inc. in Irvine, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trinet is a full-service web firm with expert capabilities in web strategy consulting, interactive marketing, creative and design services, web development, and web campaign management services. Basically, we are all about developing great websites and applications that allow our clients to breathe new life into their communication efforts and increase revenue or contributions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We not only work to help businesses achieve success online, but we also help many non-profits and faith based ministries as they work to meet the physical and spiritual needs of people both around the world and here at home.  Some of the organizations we have done work for include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coca Cola&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;World Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harvest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IMAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Billy Graham Evangelistic Organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toyota Racing Development (TRD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on the Family&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samaritan&amp;rsquo;s Purse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cisco / Linksys&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Red Cross, and many more…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a full-time, entry level &lt;strong&gt;Project Coordinator&lt;/strong&gt; for our corporate office in &lt;strong&gt;Irvine, CA&lt;/strong&gt;.  The selected candidate will be a motivated, career focused team player with a desire to work in a growing small to medium sized company.  This is a great entry level position for someone interested in a career in Project/Operations Management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directing programmers and graphic designers in building/maintaining websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taking Meeting Minutes and reporting on action items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scheduling meetings and preparing materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting Project Managers through engagements with clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online, phone, email, webex communication with clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracking time and intricate details of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friendly and good attitude with customers and internal staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoys being involved in a cutting edge, Internet industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional writing ability (able to provide samples)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to delegate and follow up to ensure progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong judgment, analytical and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years working in some sort of customer service role where maintaining client relationships was a primary accountability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of experience working with websites/online marketing (building your own, managing client websites, managing depepartment websites, etc.) strong preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate working knowledge of MS Office Suite, specifically PPT, Excel and Word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Certifications/internships surrounding Operations Management, Business Analysis, Project Management will be favorably considered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-year degree is strongly preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Irvine, California, United States&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Type&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full-Time/Regular&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-coordinator-trinet-internet-solutions-inc.-irvine-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-coordinator-trinet-internet-solutions-inc.-irvine-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Project Manager at Huge in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Senior Project Manager&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Project Managers should have 6-8+ years experience managing large-scale interactive projects from discovery and design to technical development and implementation. Extensive experience in an agency environment working with and implementing both project management and online best practices on and across large-scale engagements are a critical component of this role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, the Senior Project Manager must be attuned to value the details as well as be able to understand and drive towards the big picture. Analytical and quick thinking in a fast-paced environment are essential. The Senior Project Manager is an enthusiastic problem solver and thrives on being engaged at all levels of the project. As the key point of contact for both the Client and the project team, the Senior Project Manager plays a pivotal role in the success of any major engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for developing overall project management strategy and working with discipline leads and project teams to execute on plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor day-to-day activities of the project team and ensure work is progressing as planned. Work with project team and actively be involved in the work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage schedules, budgets, assets, and overall project organization to ensure requirements and project deliverables dates are clearly communicated, understood and executed upon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work across several projects with one or more junior project manager(s) or as the primary Project Manager on a large-scale engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively and efficiently plan and prioritize all deliverables and resources working across project(s) based on scope of work and project goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively monitor project risks and scope creep to foresee/identify potential problems and proactively identify solutions to address them in advance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently identify needs that Clients may not recognize and ensure approaches and solutions are linked to objectives and future needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently manage client expectations, ensure delivery of the highest quality service, and solicit and act on client feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and document project status and strategic recommendations to clients, team members and senior HUGE management on a regular basis; escalate issues accordingly via the appropriate channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively identify opportunities and deliver improvements; evangelize the HUGE project management methodology and project processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with project team leads to present work as well as participate in new business presentation opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the training/mentoring of junior project managers on HUGE project management methodologies and best practices as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree and at least 6-8+ years of experience in interactive project management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written, presentation, and interpersonal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to motivate, support and understand different project teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding and awareness of product development and experience tying product goals to business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail and focus on task completion is critical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the development of large-scale websites and a strong understanding of associated web development technologies and third party applications and platforms is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile and social media/community experience an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencies in MS Office, MS Project, bug tracking, wiki and other related project management and common communications tools is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PMP and other project management certifications are a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;HUGE is an equal opportunity employer (EOE). We strongly support diversity in the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-huge-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-huge-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Huge in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Project Manager&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager is responsible for the management and delivery of mid to large-scale interactive website design/development projects. The Project Manager works with the Engagement Director to ensure that the project team is poised to meet the objectives and goals of each project on-time and on-budget as well as champion quality and integrity of the end result. Project Managers must have 3-5 years experience managing interactive projects from discovery and design to technical development and implementation. Experience in an agency environment is key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager is an enthusiastic problem solver and thrives on being engaged at all levels of the project. As the key point of contact for both the Client and the project team, the Project Manager plays a pivotal role in the success of an engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for developing and managing the project plan and working with discipline leads and project teams to execute on plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor day-to-day activities of the project team and ensure work is progressing as planned. Work with project team and be actively involved in all aspects of the work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage schedules, budgets, assets, and overall project organization to ensure requirements and project deliverables dates are clearly communicated, understood and executed upon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively and efficiently plan and prioritize all deliverables and resources working across project(s) based on scope of work and project goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively monitor project risks and scope creep to foresee/identify potential problems and proactively identify solutions to address them in advance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently identify needs that Clients may not recognize and ensure approaches and solutions are linked to objectives and future needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently manage client expectations, ensure delivery of the highest quality service, and solicit and act on client feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and document project status and strategic recommendations to clients, team members and senior HUGE management on a regular basis; escalate issues accordingly via the appropriate channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively identify opportunities and deliver improvements; follow HUGE project management methodology and project processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with project team leads to present work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree and at least 3-5+ years of experience in interactive project management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written, presentation, and interpersonal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work with and support cross-functional project teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand and document project requirements and dependencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of business and functional requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail and focus on task completion is critical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the design and development websites and an understanding of web technologies and third party applications and platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile and social media/community experience an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencies in MS Office, MS Project, bug tracking, wiki and other related project management and common communications tools is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;HUGE is an equal opportunity employer (EOE). We strongly support diversity in the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-huge-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-huge-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Concur in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Concur (NASDAQ: CNQR) is the leading provider of travel and expense management solutions. As a Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) provider, Concur’s easy-to-use Web-based and mobile solutions help companies and their employees control costs and save time. By driving innovation in the travel and expense industry, Concur is on a mission to create The Perfect Business Trip for both the individual traveler and enterprise organizations.  In 2011, Forbes ranked Concur the #1 Most Innovative Growth Company. Powering evolution in travel technology, the Concur Connect platform enables the entire travel and expense ecosystem of customers, suppliers and solution partners to access and extend Concur’s T&amp;amp;E cloud. Concur is trusted by thousands of companies in more than 100 countries and reaches millions of employees worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join the marketing team as Art Director (AD) and help TripIt&amp;rsquo;s more than 7 million users across the globe easily organize and share their travel plans.  The AD will set a strong, clear creative vision for all marketing communications, keeping the brand consistent and expressed in fresh ways. The AD reports to the Sr. Director of Consumer Marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this is a strategic role, it is also a hands-on position.  The AD will be expected to translate marketing objectives and strategies for Concur’s Traveler Services business unit into creative strategies and design – and direct others (contractors, agencies) to achieve the same. Key deliverables include but aren’t limited to brand system templates (stationery, business cards, PPT, etc.), interactive communications, print collateral, online and offline advertising, videos, and event materials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AD will also take on the role of creative influencer, working closely with the Traveler Services product design team and the Concur corporate marketing team to ensure company-wide brand consistency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TripIt has a very powerful story to tell and will require a creative leader with vision, passion for great design, and collaborative skills to bring that story to life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as creative thought leader and primary hands-on producer for the Traveler Services business unit; ensure that the creative execution supports the creative brief, brand and business strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and direct any creative agencies, contract graphic designers, or production artists; set world-class quality standards in all creative deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the development, evolution, and implementation of TripIt brand; create style guide documentation and visual standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop synergistic, effective working relationships with internal partners and outside agencies to help ensure global brand consistency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring fresh ideas and approaches to design.  Challenge traditional ways of thinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently deliver a high quality end product.  Review all work for quality, brand consistency, and standards of design excellence; ensure materials have been copy-edited and proof-read before being finalized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure management and archival of graphic assets, such as source files and templates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain up-to-date knowledge of design trends and production techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be aware of, and comply with, all corporate policies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Education, Experience &amp;amp; Training required:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College degree in Design (or comparable experience); strong, comprehensive graphic design portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10+ years of graphic design and art direction experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to pass a background check&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with creative development for the consumer markets in the online sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relationship builder; partners cross-functionally and works effectively with various levels of the organization; team player with the presence to inspire and coalesce varying points of view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovative, solution-based thinker who proactively identifies opportunities and is motivated by challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mature management presence, sound judgment, and a sense of humor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to communicate effectively; strong presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive attitude and the ability to respond well to critical feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to develop both print and interactive communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Adobe Creative Suite 5 at the design and production level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PowerPoint design expertise is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Value Competencies:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays passion for &amp;amp; responsibility to the customer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hires, develops &amp;amp; rewards great people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays leadership through innovation in everything you do&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays a passion for what you do and a drive to improve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays a relentless commitment to win&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays personal &amp;amp; corporate integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;EEO:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concur is an Equal Opportunity Employer and applies this policy to all applicants and employees. We are committed to hiring and valuing a global diverse work team. (M/F/D/V)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concur is a dynamic, growing and fast-paced organization.  As such, successful employees are able to work in a fast-paced environment, managing multiple priorities often times under tight deadlines.  This typically requires working a 40+ hour work week to accomplish performance objectives.  With that, Concur offers flexibility as to the specific working hours that may be required or available depending on your role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concur is a SaaS company.  Employees must be technically savvy with the ability to use the computer/keyboard and telephone to conduct business.  The ability to creatively problem solve to our core value of ‘Leadership through innovation in everything we do’.   Many positions within Concur are customer facing so written, verbal and interpersonal communications skills are required for a majority of opportunities with Concur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confidentiality and our core value ‘Personal and corporate integrity’ are critical components being that Concur is a publicly traded company and working towards building a great, enduring company.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-concur-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-concur-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Director at Siteworx, Inc in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Technical Director &lt;/strong&gt;is an integral part of a cross-functional team and serves as the project lead in the management, coordinating, and scheduling of Web projects from inception to completion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves as a consultant to clients on all project issues including web and application design and development, collaborative models and software methodologies, andÂ budget recommendations and negotiations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates organization methods and tools specific to individual projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads project team to ensure deadlines are met, and within budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides project team with guidance as required to ensure progress is sustained and project goals are fulfilled&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicates and controls project scope, schedules, assignments, and open issues both with the internal team and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages project finances; monitors and controls expenses and communicates variances with management and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Predicts issues/risks and consults with clients and team leads to find creative solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exercises authority to make decisions and resolve disputes; escalates issues to Director of Project Management when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively leads and facilitates project meetings and presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages support contracts and issue tracking for clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acts as the project expert retaining and communicating all project history&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports the development of Account Management programs and processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client facing experience necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CMS preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Web practices and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Broad understanding of software development methodologies is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience with industry standard project management tools including Microsoft Project, time tracking, and budget tracking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical, planning, problem solving, and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic negotiation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of managing multiple tasks in a fast paced, high volume environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;About Siteworx, Inc.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteworx is an award-winning interactive agency with deep roots in agile design, Web content management (WCM) and systems integration. For more than a decade, we’ve tapped an uncommon blend of technology and design know-how to discover, create and deploy best in class Web and mobile experiences that deliver business results. Siteworx was recently named to the IMA&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Agencies of 2011 and has been recognized among KMWorld&amp;rsquo;s 100 Companies that Matter in Knowledge Management for the last three consecutive years. Headquartered in Reston, Virginia, Siteworx maintains full-service offices in San Francisco, CA, Atlanta, GA, Chicago, IL, Raleigh, NC, Rochester, NY and New York, NY. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.siteworx.com/&quot;&gt;www.siteworx.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteworx employees are a unique mix of creative and technical individuals whose skill and dedication have won acclaim and loyalty from our many high profile clients. We are passionate about our work and about our lives, and our culture emphasizes the need to balance them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteworx offers competitive salary and benefits including health, dental and life insurance; 401k plan with employer contribution; vacation, holiday and sick leave; and education reimbursement plan. EOE/M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-director-siteworx-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-director-siteworx-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director, Copywriting at Resource in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Chief Creative Officer, the Creative Director, Copy is responsible for creative leadership and management of the Creative Department on the respective Team. The Creative Director is highly conceptual – both visually and verbally, is a fearless leader who possess a spirit for methodology and innovation, while at the same time remarkably business savvy. The Creative Director is responsible for representing Resource’s thought leadership, methodologies and capabilities to existing and potential clients. The Creative Director also works closely with internal leadership across disciplines to ensure their team’s infrastructure is compatible with the workload it supports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Essential Job Functions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core leadership and development of Creative Talent (Design, Interaction Design and Copywriters) under respective Practice Group&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept creation and development, evaluates the appropriateness of voice and tone and look and feel for a brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ownership of copy and message continuity, establishing voice and tone throughout projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core creative direction in shaping strategic vision and experience for all client work and responsible for documenting and sharing the Creative POV through formal channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate an environment of inspiration, innovation and turn opportunities into actionable results. Expertise in Interactive Marketing and eRetail is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Client Delivery&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with peers across disciplines to ensure talent and staffing levels are compatible with existing and projected workload. This may include leadership of an Offering team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective and persuasive communicator with clients. Owns relationship with client on behalf of creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultimately responsible for the integrity of the solutions created by the team. Strong leadership qualities are critical to leading and mentoring the team to take calculated risks
in the pursuit of innovation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Business Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works closely with Studio leadership to identify and cultivate new opportunities through participation in annual client planning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for assembly and leadership of new business pursuit teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s Degree in Marketing, English, Communications or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10+ years experience in leading a team of Design and Content talent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years experience in Interactive Marketing and brand communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documented examples of shaping and leading creative vision of commerce, site, social, promotional and online advertising campaign executions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience in building relationships with Information Architecture, Technology, Strategy and Project Management partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of user interface design, development of brand voice and tone, and examples of prototype creation to illustrate
a high-level concept&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and ability to contribute to analysis of web performance metrics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Travel Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position may require up to 40% travel to and from current or potential client sites, conferences, seminars and/or training sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please Note:&lt;/em&gt; This job description is not intended to be a complete list of all responsibilities, duties or skills and due
to the changing nature of the job is subject to review and change at any time, with or without notice.  This position
is exempt based on the FLSA laws.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-copywriting-resource-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-copywriting-resource-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Project Manager at Rosetta in San Luis Obispo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Associate Project Manager&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is looking for an Associate Project Manager to drive cross-functional project teams, project budgets and project schedules. Individuals in this role have considerable client exposure and must demonstrate the ability to work on both business and technology projects with companies across a broad range of industries. The Associate Project Manager must have considerable experience in a fast-paced, dynamic environment and demonstrate a degree of project ownership and accountability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who We Are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is a consulting-centered interactive agency engineered to transform marketing for the connected world. We are focused on helping progressive marketers drive material business impact by translating deep consumer insights into personally relevant brand experiences across touch points and over time. Our differentiated capabilities and structure have enabled us to become a market leader, operating as an independent brand in the Publicis Groupe of global agencies. Rosetta is ranked by Ad Age among the top U.S. digital agencies and was recently named the #1 Agency to Watch in Ad Ageâ€™s Agency A- List.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role will be responsible for leading and designing projects, communicating with clients/internal teams, directing creative brainstorming sessions and, most importantly, promoting a culture of fun and excellence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and management of project timelines and project plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assurance that projects achieve desired business and technical objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of internal project team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identification and mitigation of project risks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validation and presentation of project deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of project financials, with a focus on optimizing efficiency and project margin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishment of close working relationships with client project team and internal development managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2-3 years of project management experience in a technology organization or professional services company working on mid-sized projects with 5+ team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, organization, interpersonal and writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to multi-task and interact with a large number of customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business process planning and implementation planning experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS in communications, business or technology-related field (or commensurate experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience with the MS Office suite, including MS Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in web design and interactive technology preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is an equal opportunity employer M/F/V/D&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-project-manager-rosetta-san-luis-obispo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-project-manager-rosetta-san-luis-obispo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>