<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. Front-End Developer at Onward ITG in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Onward ITG has partnered with a a large enterprise organization in search of a Senior Front End Developer.  This person will have the opportunity to work on one of the largest eCommerce sites being built, in a highly innovative and creative environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Project Scope&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front End development for Item Page as part of team member of Front End Migration Item page  team using Agile Scrum methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take direction from the Item Page Product Owner and Scrum Master for development tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in Daily scrums, Sprint planning meetings and Sprint review meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be able to independently lead all front-end/client-side architecture for client’s website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the features support in different browsers and different environments like desktop, tablets, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in responsive design and multiple grids for multiple devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to implement polling and pushing and should be able to criticize pros and cons of using each technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in using templating frameworks like node.js is plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be able to build front-end code as reusable components and code for optimal site performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-onward-itg-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-onward-itg-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Front-End/Web Developer at Sungard AS in San Ramon, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our Vision is to be the IT solutions provider of choice to ensure the availability of our customers’ business operations.   Do you want to make a difference in one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading IT services companies? SunGard Availability Services offers careers that combine the independence of working in a small entrepreneurial environment with the depth of resources of a Fortune 500 technology company.
At SunGard Availability Services, we provide operations support to organizations that need to ensure business viability by keeping mission critical information and applications up and running. With the recent launch of our Enterprise Cloud Services, SunGard continues to invest in new technologies to stay in the foreground of technology innovations that solve business challenges.
Unlike other companies that offer individual technology services, SunGard Availability Services is focused on providing responsive and integrated disaster recovery, managed services, IT consulting and business continuity management software solutions, to help organizations keep critical technology and applications available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At SunGard Availability Services, we know that people our people are our greatest assets; we work hard to develop our employees and rely on them to make wise choices. The result is a challenging and rewarding work environment that fosters growth and encourages professional development. That’s why over 3000 dedicated professionals chose SunGard Availability Services as their place of employment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SunGard is looking for an experienced and passionate Front End Web Developer to join our development team. We are looking for candidates who eagerly explore new technologies and trends, and are masters of their craft. Candidates must be able to code valid and accessible HTML5 and CSS2+3, use or write the latest JavaScript tools, and create forward-thinking user experiences on the web. Candidates should be able to recognize the use of JavaScript libraries as a convenience, but are knowledgeable in core JavaScript enough to be capable of working without them, have a high degree of attention to detail in all aspects of your work, and have experience working on rich interactive websites or applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive the design and implementation of critical customer facing web applications that will be offered on SunGard’s next generation web site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product management to understand and influence the product features and requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with User Experience (UX) to produce functional prototypes showcasing the latest UI/UX ideas, translate UX designs into pixel perfect HTML/CSS/JavaScript using the latest web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop responsive web interfaces that leverage AJAX for passing information between the browser and the server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow best practices for data validation, and preventing cross site scripting attacks (XSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore new technologies/industry trends and technical innovation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be an effective team-player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop exemplary code for highly available systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seven (7) or more years of relevant experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with current web development standards (HTML5, CSS, AJAX, JSON, JavaScript, REST) is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with JavaScript and toolkits such as JQuery, Backbone.js, and Twitter Bootstrap, X-editable etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on multiple projects using Agile development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for code quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. in Computer Science or equivalent (M.S. preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About SunGard Availability Services&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SunGard Availability Services provides IT Operations support to IT departments that need to ensure business viability by keeping mission critical information and applications up and running. Unlike other companies that offer individual technology services, SunGard is focused on providing responsive and integrated disaster recovery, managed services, IT consulting and business continuity management software solutions, to help organizations keep people and information connected.
At SunGard Availability Services, we know that people are our greatest assets; we work hard to develop our employees and rely on them to take initiative and make wise choices. The result is a challenging and rewarding work environment that fosters growth and encourages professional development.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-web-developer-sungard-as-san-ramon-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-web-developer-sungard-as-san-ramon-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Moboom in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a member of our User Interface Development Team your main responsibility will be to create, develop, and maintain our web applications. You will work with server side developers to create new functionality and evolve product architecture, turning rough concepts into practical, visually appealing applications. You should be passionate about unobtrusive Javascript and standards compliant HTML and CSS and committed to writing readable, efficient, scalable, and maintainable code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong development skills, including object oriented JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, JSON, XML, Handlebars, LESS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Backbone.js, JQuery, Bootstrap, Underscore, Vanilla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of MVC, Object Oriented software development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong user experience and visual design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AJAX techniques and technologies, and a polished style, in regards to web application look-and-feel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-directed and capable of working in a fast paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree and/or at least five years Web development experience or equivalent is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working knowledge of industry standard visual design tools (Visio, Photoshop, Illustrator), personal information management software, and usability testing and user research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Salary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commensurate with experience &amp;amp; market value&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-moboom-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-moboom-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Application Developer at Proteus Digital Health in Redwood City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Want to help build the future of digital health?   This position is responsible for developing the customer facing UIs for our Digital Health Applications on both desktop and mobile browsers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will work in a small, fast-moving lean product development team with UX, commercial and product management focusing on cutting edge digital health solutions that leverage Proteus Digital Health’s core technology and digital health platform.  You will be challenged to define the most effective application architecture and design with a focus on optimizing UI’s for responsive performance on multiple mobile device formats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Supervisory Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially, you are expected to be able to work independently to deliver finished applications and over time will likely have the opportunity to lead small teams of application developers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building single page MVC apps using Dojo, Backbone, Spine, Ember, Knockout, Angular, or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building responsive Mobile Web Apps using Dojo, SenchaTouch, JQMobile or similar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building secure front ends to REST API&amp;rsquo;s using oauth, XSS/CSRF protections, and secure local storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing SVG based graphing frameworks tools such as Dojo, Sencha, and D3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing automated web UI tests using tools such as Mocha, Selenium, Geb, WebTest or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with agile processes including test driven development and continuous deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice To Have :&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Coffeescript / Live Script&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accustomed to working on multiple projects simultaneously to a high standard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for the Internet, World Wide Web and Web Design / Development and Mobile Applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong desire to break new frontiers in the emerging field of Digital Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building certified web applications in a regulated industry such as Finance or Healthcare&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and/or Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years of commercial and / or non-commercial work or a very strong portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer Science Degree or Equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Language Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation skills. Excellent communication skills (verbal and written).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to read, analyze, and interpret complex documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write presentations and other documents using original or innovative techniques or style.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-application-developer-proteus-digital-health-redwood-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-application-developer-proteus-digital-health-redwood-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Front-End Engineer / Web Developer at QuinStreet, Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you possess a craving for constant challenge and delight in conquering new frontiers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We seek a talented and focused Senior Front End Engineer to navigate the exciting terrain of improving and extending the web interface of Eventbrite. Our team works at a fast pace on an awesome product that is constantly evolving and improving so we&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who can pick things up quickly. Your job will be dynamic, interesting, challenging and fun. We have a great team overall and a friendly, outgoing engineering department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain site-wide XHTML, CSS and Javascript code and coding standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate and work across teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product and Design to understand goals, use cases, and flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engineering and QA to deliver high quality implementations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize your trained eye for UI and design to make pleasing, efficient, and robust iterations on our site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level coding skills in XHTML, CSS, Javascript, DHTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced AJAX knowledge including detailed knowledge of available libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of all browser types and their various idiosyncracies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in UI conceptualization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interact with and communicate effectively across multiple teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multitasking skills, as you will be working on several projects at once&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently while also participate actively in an Agile/SCRUM environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in a LAMP development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years at a consumer-facing web company in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nice to have: Experience with a client-side MVC like Backbone.js and knowledge of a Javascript testing framework such as Jasmine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A BS or equivalent degree in one or more disciplines ranging from graphic design to computer science&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-engineer-web-developer-quinstreet-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-engineer-web-developer-quinstreet-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer / Front-End Developer at GENWI in Palo Alto, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;GENWI (Generation Wireless) helps content publishers to create engaging apps with a revolutionary cloud-based mobile content management system. The GENWI mobile Content Management System (mCMS) gives publishers a quick and easy way to repurpose their content to create engaging apps once and then deliver native and HTML5 apps to multiple devices. Today, there are over 1,500 apps powered by GENWI including those from Conde Nast, The Hollywood Reporter, IndiaTimes, Forbes, and PBS Kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2010, GENWI is a privately held firm based in the Bay Area. For more information, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://genwi.com&quot;&gt;http://genwi.com&lt;/a&gt; or follow us on Twitter @genwi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obtain project requirements from UI designers and product managers and build efficient, clean and modular code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take ownership and test code for robustness, usability, reliability and most importantly, end-user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist the technical team in improving and maintaining the development and release environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the product manager/designer to develop strong and consistent branding elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest and implement design decisions and evolve new features that scale well&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strictly comply with deadlines and deliver under minimum supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own the design and branding elements for a host of GENWI products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to react quickly and work non-standard work hours as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in HTML, XHTML, HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adept in CSS/CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop/Illustrator experience is a must&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascripting is a must. Other scripting language experiences a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Webtool kit experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design sensibilities with ability to deliver great creatives, images, icons, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SVN a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please submit your portfolio, resume, and cover letter. Wow us with your application however you choose. Unique projects (not just academic assignments or work collaborations) often catch our eye.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-front-end-developer-genwi-palo-alto-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-front-end-developer-genwi-palo-alto-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Inflection in Redwood City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Inflection is on the hunt for a passionate Front End Developer that lives on the edge of technology and design! If you’re excited by the idea of building great features on a fast paced agile team, creating applications that will be used by tens of millions of users a month, and working with over 14 billion records (AKA, “big data”), we’d love to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve got moxie.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love building websites using emerging technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You keep up with all the latest Javascript libraries and exciting developments within the Javascript community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re best at crafting HTML/CSS code, but have an aesthetic eye for design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You thrive on testing new ideas across millions of users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re not afraid to work with some of the most skilled engineers in the Silicon Valley&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You believe the work day should be dynamic, ever-evolving, and filled with free food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re flexible (mentally&amp;mdash;we have a yoga-free interview process).&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re excited about bringing the worlds of engineering and design together&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your eye for detail ensures our sites stay pretty, clean, and well maintained&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You like seeing features come to fruition and are able to jump into a project at any point in its lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You thrive within our data-driven design culture, and can quickly react to changes and new feature requirements driven by our user analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re hip to the latest requirements for cross-browser compatibility and page optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You know your stuff:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very familiar with HTML5 and care about the semantic cleanliness of your markup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident with CSS and Sass with the ability to leverage new features via progressive enhancement; creating reusable selectors puts a smile on your face&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong with Javascript and excited about libraries such as jQuery, Backbone and Require&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love implementing responsive design and bring a mobile-first approach to your code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve worked with some form of version management system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intuitive and excellent visual eye&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know your browsers and the limitations and abilities of each&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Brownie Points!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robust portfolio with up-to-date code samples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve worked with XSLT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love working with dual Thunderbolt display monitors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love contributing to the vision of your product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy working in an agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You believe that work and fun can, in fact, coexist:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bored employees make boring products. At Inflection, there&amp;rsquo;s no such thing. We run big websites with millions of users, but we&amp;rsquo;re allergic to the sterile and cold corporate culture. Work and life should definitely be buddies, so we&amp;rsquo;re serious about cultivating a fab work environment. To wit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conveniently located off 101 in Redwood Shores, with free Caltrain access through company sponsored GO Pass and a shuttle from both Hillsdale and San Carlos Caltrain stations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business goals celebrated with Major Milestone Trips and frequent Friday Happy Hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company sponsored catered lunch daily&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A start up&amp;rsquo;s pantry of complimentary beverages and snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company subsidized gym membership at nearby Pacific Athletic Club&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High energy team with great mix of experienced entrepreneurs, talented engineers, and successful Silicon Valley veterans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Culture of acting with integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation including equity options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive benefits package including medical/dental coverage, 401K, and life insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-inflection-redwood-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-inflection-redwood-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at ZehnerGroup in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We have an immediate 3-month contract on-site with one of our clients. There is opportunity to extend the contract or make a full-time offer with the right candidate full-time in our Los Angeles office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills we are seeking&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web standards compliant,valid HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional Javascript/jQuery skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile/iPhone/iPad UI Experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eCommerce experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating with an MVC web framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Must be available to work on-site in Los Angeles or willing to relocate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No recruiters please&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About ZehnerGroup:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through strategy, design, and technology innovation ZehnerGroup builds startups and transforms established organizations. Headquartered in Los Angeles, we pride ourselves in clean, usable interfaces backed by scalable technology solutions. By harnessing the power of ZGLabs (Strategy) and ZGInteractive, we offer a complete solution driven by the intersection of business and user goals. Our client list includes some of the most dynamic and successful leaders in their industries. The common thread throughout is an entrepreneurial spirit that pushes boundaries and continually strives for innovation and a competitive advantage.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-zehnergroup-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-zehnergroup-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UI Developer at SoftPros,Inc. in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills, Education and Experience Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of web development (UI) experience in a corporate environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to lead a small team of UX professionals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience as either a Information Architect, Interaction Designer, or Visual Designer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good leadership and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on large, complex sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience translating user research into design decisions and specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of UI and UX principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of advanced JavaScript principles and techniques including OO, Client Side MVC, Templates, AJAX, Single Page Architecture, Design Patterns, and Dependency Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to produce flawless work in a fast paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently or in a group&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects at one time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail-oriented and comfortable in a fast-pace environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate technical concepts to technical and non-technical audience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior track record leading Front end framework/design/development methodologies in 2 or 3 major SDLC initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with design tools such as Visio, Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-developer-softpros-inc-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-developer-softpros-inc-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. Front-End Developer at StackSocial in Venice, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About StackSocial:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What: StackSocial powers digital commerce across the web with an online marketplace of over 200,000 active members.  Our digital commerce platform provides web publishers a simple and effective way to generate additional revenue by organically weaving flash sales on relevant digital products &amp;amp; tech gear into the reader’s daily experience by channeling the StackSocial storefront directly into each publisher’s site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where: Founded in 2011, StackSocial was accelerated at Amplify.LA and is now headquartered right across from the beach in soulful Venice, California.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why: We&amp;rsquo;re changing the way web publishers engage and monetize their audiences.  Publishers hold a captive, passionate fan base; yet most aren&amp;rsquo;t able to engage with their fans via ecommerce, email marketing, and site registration.  StackSocial changes this by enabling publishers to offer sales on hand-picked, trending products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who: We’re a team of entrepreneurs who previously worked at companies like Meebo, Klout, Yahoo!, PopSugar, and our own entrepreneurial ventures. We’re backed by a group of top-tier investors including Draper Associates, 500 Startups, Siemer Ventures, Paige Craig, EchoVC, and others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you’ll do:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Breathe Life into Ideas. Help us revolutionize digital commerce to change the way people discover and buy products on the web.  Take product insights and business needs and translate them into elegant and efficient user experiences. Solve challenging issues to understand what features our users want before they even ask for it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play Well with Others. You are a great software engineer in general; know a few languages, and especially javascript, html5, css3 inside and out. Can possibly overlap a little with the backend guys…knows a little about ruby/python/php or similar, along with a selection of web frameworks. Knows MVC, and understands its use-cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Impress our customers. Constantly advocate for the best customer experience possible while balancing design and business objectives. Demonstrate deep understanding of customer interactions to transform complex design requirements into intuitive interface.  Create world-class customer experiences and beautiful visuals that support and reinforce StackSocial’s vision, brand, and business objectives across all platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About You:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Key Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Event and OO JavaScript, AJAX, CSS3, HTML4/5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design to production &amp;ndash; all in a days work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to bend existing web technologies to your will&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JQuery is great, but you don’t need it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands UX and design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to debug any cross-browser/cross-domain issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frameworks: You can build your own and hack the internals of others'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong grasp of CS fundamentals and design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong familiarity with Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sense of urgency and thrives in an incredibly fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Big pluses:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building for large-scale ecommerce site(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience at a top-tier start-up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits + Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary + Bonus: Competitive base + potential bonus based on experience and performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity: Generous equity stake for the right candidate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dream Setup: Whatever equipment you need to be at your best, up to $3000.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Super Flex Time: Run errands as needed, just get your stuff done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Food/Drinks: We’ll stock the cabinets and the fridge for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hack Days: Two days per quarter to work on any Company-related project you want.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Location: Our office is across from the Beach…take a jog anytime to clear your mind!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send an email and cover letter to josh@stacksocial.com with links to all applicable pages that you have (i.e. your portfolio, blog, LinkedIn, twitter, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-stacksocial-venice-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-stacksocial-venice-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>