<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Nest in Palo Alto, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and update nest.com, nest.com/works, support.nest.com, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize and show off the latest and greatest in HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help deliver best of breed blog posts on a regular basis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop tests and standards for the web properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills and experience needed:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with front end web engineering (JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3/SCSS, AJAX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with backend tools and languages (Ruby, Python, Middleman, Yeoman, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable using the best practices of version control (GitHub/Git)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with nuances between Mobile Safari and other WebKit based mobile browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to both guide and expand upon given designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knows when to use a library, and when it is better to role your own code for a particular interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can make HTML, CSS, and JS sing and dance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to employ graceful fallbacks for older browsers (especially IE)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to communicate technical topics to non-technical people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-broomfield-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-broomfield-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End/UI Developer at EVault, A Seagate Company in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;EVault, A Seagate Company, is a fast-growing industry leader in network-based data backup and recovery solutions.  We’ve been providing data protection and professional-grade storage solutions to small and mid-size businesses since 1997. Our technology platform is stable, secure, and optimized for WAN data transfer, and our recovery capabilities are ultra-reliable. We back it all with a rock-solid data center infrastructure and the industry&amp;rsquo;s highest quality customer service, while encouraging innovation and creativity by providing a casual and friendly work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EVault is led by a team of storage industry veterans with a compelling vision and a proven track record. We also benefit from the backing and expertise of our parent company, Seagate—the largest storage company in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a UI Developer with the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with development team to quickly understand requirements and come up with a solution proposal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write excellent design and functional documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate design and architecture to cross functional teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and development of wireframes and flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in conducting performance testing of application and GUI components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishing and maintaining high performance GUI web delivery function&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selection and implementation of appropriate tools, templates, libraries and standards for the creation of quality GUI components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with management/leadership/architect to set design direction and guide accordingly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review and evaluate designs and project activities against product goals and requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Knowledge and Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience developing appealing browser-based interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with Javascript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development experience with AJAX, HTML5, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of responsive web design, graceful degradation, and progressive enhancement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience translating wireframes to fully functional code that is modular and re-usable.Experience using a range of open source technologies and contributing to an open source project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;EVault, A Seagate Company, is an Equal Opportunity Employer committed to a diverse workforce.^&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-evault-a-seagate-company-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-evault-a-seagate-company-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer Internship at Plantronics in Santa Cruz, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Working at Plantronics gives you the rare opportunity to make a difference and feel valued, respected and supported, both personally and professionally. You&amp;rsquo;ll find the ideal blend of a casual, fun, friendly atmosphere with a strong commitment to the company&amp;rsquo;s success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since 1961 Plantronics (NYSE: PLT) people have been bringing sound innovation to the world.  We are a world leader in personal audio communications for professionals and consumers. Our reputation for excellence is built on innovative products, a people-centered workplace and strong ethics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Headquartered in Santa Cruz, California, Plantronics and its Clarity division have offices in 20 countries, including facilities in Mexico, China, and Europe.  Plantronics offers a generous mix of health, financial and lifestyle benefits as well as career development opportunities to its associates.  Discover Plantronics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PEOPLE-PLACE-PURPOSE-POTENTIAL&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Development team within the Digital Marketing department is looking for someone to assist with the development of our next generation product comparison and product search features.  The project involves analyzing product specifications and organizing them into groups as well as transforming them into terms that a visitor might find useful when searching on Plantronics.com.  Analysis of current best practices in the areas of product comparison and search will also be performed.* The work products to be delivered at the end of the project are a design document for each of the features, and if time allows, a working prototype based on findings from the best practice research that incorporate the specifications and related transformations from the product catalog.  This will require working closely with the Web Development and Production teams within Digital Marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This role requires knowledge of core web technologies such as HTML, JavaScript, and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional knowledge in PHP or JSP technologies is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be enrolled in an U.S. accredited higher educational institution on a full-time basis and in good academic standing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Plantronics is an Affirmative Action/Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To all recruitment agencies: Plantronics does not accept agency resumes. Please do not forward resumes to our jobs alias, Plantronics employees or any other company location. Plantronics is not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-internship-plantronics-santa-cruz-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-internship-plantronics-santa-cruz-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web App UI Developer at Bluenose Analytics in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bluenose Analytics is building a CRM for the subscription economy by creating value from the intersection of product usage and CRM data.  Our initial analytics application gives SaaS vendors an &amp;ldquo;early warning system&amp;rdquo; of reports and alerts to drive better trial conversions, prevent churn and grow recurring revenue.  For example, SaaS users with declining product usage might be at risk to renew their subscription.  Bluenose spots these patterns and alerts the vendor before it&amp;rsquo;s too late. We are backed by top-­-tier venture investors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Success in this role means:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delighting users with an intuitive user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taming complex data and make interaction a joy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iteration is your middle name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to learn more about Big Data and analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seeking and ingesting frequent customer feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead UX responsibilities for new product development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design mock-ups and novel user interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate them to working, production code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm new features and models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make  enterprise  software  look  and  feel  like  it  rightfully  belongs  next  to  the latest consumer application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years making browser-based magic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5, CSS3, jQuery (and all their buddies) are your best friends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience of popular web app frameworks is most excellent (RoR, Groovy on Grails)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-directed, motivated, passionate when it comes to user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile development a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to define an early-stage start-up culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-app-ui-developer-bluenose-analytics-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-app-ui-developer-bluenose-analytics-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at BEAR Data Solutions in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bear Data Solutions is named as one of the fastest growing companies by Inc. magazine in 2010 continues to grow and evolve as a successful IT solutions and services provider. The BEAR Data Team is a group of highly experienced and talented professionals who are passionate about delivering five star service and solutions to their clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our customer is seeking a FrontEnd Developer with 5 years of web development experience and extensive knowledge in JavaScript Frameworks/Toolkits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop Client side applications using HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, communicate and debug short and long term Front End Solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in defining systems architecture from a scripting, efficiency, caching, and client-side performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of web development experience, preferably in media and entertainment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge in coding native JavaScript, HTML4/5, and CSS2/3 in non-WYSIWYG editors (e.g. Eclipse)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in JavaScript Frameworks/Toolkits (e.g. jQuery, YUI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in live data applications using AJAX/JSONP with JSON/XML/HTML content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to debug and analyse JavaScript/CSS/http requests using updated tools and methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the principles of object-oriented programming and design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in cross-browser/fullback solutions and implementing future proof solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in page speed optimizations such as browser cache, media asset preloading, efficient JavaScript processing techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of version control concepts and tools, particularly SVN, with branching and merging (or equivalent) knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of web standards and IA/UI best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resourcefulness in troubleshooting complex problems, finding available internal solutions, as well as developing new solutions based on external sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably knowledge in any CMS environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands Agile or other project development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multitask and manage multiple complex initiatives simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For more information, please visit us at www.beardatasolutions.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send resume to resumes@bdata.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-bear-data-solutions-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-bear-data-solutions-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Jr. Web &amp; Mobile Developer at Ghost Group in Newport Beach, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re an awesome, Orange County based, IT company with a fun atmosphere to work in.We have a lot of new projects starting that you would be working on, providing you with a lot of hands on experience.
Check us out at http://legalmarijuanadispensary.com/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for motivated Computer Science majors at major Universities to join our team!
10-25 hours per week, $15/hour. You&amp;rsquo;ll gain a lot of experience and get to work in a great environment!
You will be working out of our brand new office in Newport Beach&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to Develop Real Web Applications in PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to Develop on the Android &amp;amp; iOS mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn internet marketing and search engine optimization from our experts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Prerequisites:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good working knowledge of HTML5/CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to analyze and use Google analytic data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux system administration (Lite)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Majoring in Computer Science at a major university (UCI, Chapman, UCLA, USC etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Must be friendly to medical marijuana and mmj patients
Knowledge of Joomla, Drupal or other CMS systems a plus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please provide us with your resume as well as either a demo of sites you&amp;rsquo;ve built, github
account, or even code examples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-web-and-mobile-developer-ghost-group-newport-beach-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-web-and-mobile-developer-ghost-group-newport-beach-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at ClearCapital.com, Inc. in Roseville, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clear Capital® is a rapidly growing, privately-held company located near Lake Tahoe in the mountain resort town of Truckee, Calif. Cultivating the highest levels of customer ethics, we serve as a trusted partner for customers across the mortgage and lending industries. We use the most progressive technologies available and human, hands-on analytics to deliver highly accurate and reliable valuation tools. This unique combination of customer ethics and progressive technology makes Clear Capital the ideal choice for people seeking a high trust and high tech work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a passionate front-end web developer with strong HTML, CSS, and JavaScript experience. Please include a portfolio of your work and any code samples you feel are a good representation of your skill when you apply.  In this role, you will be responsible for developing rich web user interfaces that integrate with back-end components and result in web solutions that people want to use. You will be part of a team that works on various web-based applications and ultimately contribute to a high-quality user experience. As a front end developer, you will work with the application development team to implement a presentation layer which delivers information from the application layer for further processing and display it in a variety of formats. A passion for new technologies and a drive to find better ways to implement user interfaces is key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop rich web user interfaces that integrate with back-end components using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop successful user interfaces that are standards-compliant, cross-browser compatible, and performance optimized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build well-formed user interfaces based on direction from the design team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain a repository of common and reusable code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain documentation for front end code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act as a support resource for back end developers using pre-built front end components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with development leads to ensure consistent and correct integration with back end code and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritize workload to meet deadlines for assignments in the code release schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop own insights through independent analysis and communicate actionable recommendations based on insights&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement presentation layer components that are backed by data from defined application layer interfaces when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Job Related Skills and Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of five (5) years experience building user interfaces for large, complex template-based websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level front end development using HTML, CSS, object-oriented JavaScript, and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience developing Ajax style web applications and MVC frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with web development and object-oriented software engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competency in developing standards-compliant user interfaces accessible via the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to create clean and reusable code libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to develop cross-browser compatible user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize requirements into development tasks and execute&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to translate design documents into semantic code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using graphic applications like Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, or Fireworks for web graphic preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using web development tools such as Firebug, Developer Toolbar, or DebugBar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a team environment on large-scale projects and working within a local development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational, communication, and interaction skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to adapt to change quickly, self manage, and work on multiple projects simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interest in how and where the web is consumed, from desktop to mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relentless self learner who thrives in a fast-paced and highly-interactive environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in computer science or related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using HTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity of database and server-side scripting languages such as SQL and ColdFusion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development supporting tools like Subversion and Jira&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience integrating 3rd party APIs such as Google Maps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;At Clear Capital, we have an underlying philosophy that guides our efforts: Go wherever it leads, and do whatever it takes to help clients find their optimal solution. This philosophy guides how we create and deliver products, and how we interact with our clients, vendors and each other. We offer an exciting fast-paced work environment, challenging and rewarding careers, and competitive compensation and benefits. Relocation assistance is available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary commensurate with experience&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-clearcapital-com-inc-roseville-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-clearcapital-com-inc-roseville-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI/ Front-End Web Developer at myTAG Inc in San Jose, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are offering an exciting full-time employment opportunity to join a fully funded technology start-up located in San Jose, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About The Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this position you will be the front end developer.  You will assume various roles such as translating the design renderings to pixel perfect code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will work with the creative director to create web and mobile GUI&amp;rsquo;s for myTAG customers. Projects are highly varied to allow you to engage in something new every few days. Each project provides a new problem-solving opportunity and depending on its requirements may incorporate new third party technologies. If you enjoy creating smart and user friendly web apps and thrive in a fast paced environment,  this position is for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web layout integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web interface design implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build web apps with JavaScript, CSS, XHTML, HTML5,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate apps with web services, such as payment gateways, e-signatures, emails, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take projects from concept through development cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of HTML5, XHTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In depth knowledge of converting graphic design to HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to write cross-browser compatible code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a current portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In depth knowledge of cross browser development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile and responsive web development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hand coding javascript and jquery experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in computer science or related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with minimal supervision and perform well under pressure to meet project milestones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to Detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work onsite full time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of MVC Architecture, LAMP structure,  with frameworks such as Codeigniter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with Git or SVN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examples of iconography and current web interface samples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legal residency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience Breakdown&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years Jquery and javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We offer many employment incentives including stock options, equity sharing, and upward mobility within the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are qualified and interested, please email your cover letter, resume including compensation history and portfolio or work examples to our ZipRecruiter Account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About myTAG Inc:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stealth start-up company located in San Jose, CA&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-front-end-web-developer-mytag-inc-san-jose-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-front-end-web-developer-mytag-inc-san-jose-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Sony Computer Entertainment of America Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Sony Computer Entertainment America&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Developer Services and Support Group&amp;rdquo; provides a range of services (technical support, software development and consultancy) that support the development of PlayStation products by both SCEA and its partners throughout North America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Developer Services and Support Group is looking for a full-time staff member to join our infrastructure development team immediately, reporting to the team lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SCEA Developer Services and Support Group implements web-based services to enable the highest quality of support for PlayStation developers and facilitate internal collaborative software development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an individual with agile skills and proven front-end experience developing web applications to join our team in improving and expanding our existing services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skills/Experience
Applicants should have at least two years of professional experience developing web applications in a team setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The following skills are essential:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong HTML5, JavaScript, and CSS skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of experience implementing rich client-side interaction for web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with emerging methods, web standards, and open source tech used in web site development (examples: jQuery, client-side MVC such as backbone.js)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using test-driven design/development (TDD) for front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;The following skills would be highly advantageous:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with pair-programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training in Scrum or experience applying Scrum on the job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP development skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience applying server-side MVC frameworks (eg Symfony) on the job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competence with SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing with a MongoDB, Cassandra, or similar data store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Secure coding practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Sony Computer Entertainment America (SCEA) is home to the PlayStation&amp;reg; family of products, including the PlayStation&amp;reg;3 (PS3™), PlayStation&amp;reg; Vita (PS Vita), PlayStation&amp;reg; Mobile and PlayStation&amp;reg;Network. Founded in 1994, SCEA has grown into a leading global computer entertainment brand and continues to redefine interactive consumer entertainment. Since the original PlayStation&amp;reg; first revolutionized the world of gaming, SCEA has repeatedly set the benchmark for innovation in home and portable entertainment through amazing gameplay experiences that inspire people across the world. Based in Foster City, CA, SCEA serves as headquarters for all North American operations and employs over 2,104 people in offices located in Foster City, CA, San Diego, CA, Santa Monica, CA and Bend, OR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is SCEA&amp;rsquo;s policy to provide equal employment opportunity for all applicants and employees. SCEA does not unlawfully discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, gender, gender identity, marital status, age, disability, veteran status, sexual orientation, national origin, or any other category protected by applicable federal and state law.  SCEA also makes reasonable accommodations for disabled applicants and employees.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-sony-computer-entertainment-of-america-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-sony-computer-entertainment-of-america-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>HTML/CSS Developer at The Phelps Group in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Phelps, an integrated marketing communications agency in Santa Monica, is seeking a full time, in-house web developer to take on multiple responsibilities within our organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Candidates should have the following experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 to 2 years of hands-on web development experience (examples of past work/projects will be required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of HTML and CSS coding best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Photoshop, Fireworks, and other graphics optimization software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of coding websites and HTML emails for consistent appearance across multiple browsers, platforms, and devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and experience with quality assurance processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firm grasp of working within a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage one’s own time and project responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to effectively communicate with other members of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great attitude, and the desire to expand one’s skill set and abilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Campaign Monitor ESP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with other ESP platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Litmus email testing platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/html-css-developer-the-phelps-group-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/html-css-developer-the-phelps-group-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>