<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feeds/ca-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at UniversityNow, Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;UniversityNow is building the most accessible and affordable accredited university in the world.  Backed by leading technology and education investors, we are transforming an existing accredited online university to our custom adaptive learning platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for the right people to join our UX/UI team. You are fun, fearless and fast. You think about your life as a series of design problems. You have skills in interaction, experience, and visual design and love building things as much as imagining them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design screen-level interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement HTML/CSS/JS/Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate on UX design and strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate on Visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate on front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;NEED TO HAVE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 years working in web applications or mobile apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of CSS &amp;amp; JavaScript frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;NICE TO HAVE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience with agile or lean methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in tight collaboration with others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience pairing with designers and/or developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;familiarity with Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS, Android experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visual design/production experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;interaction / UX design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;background in education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additionally …&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;We are looking for team members who&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leave their ego at the door&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive on collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acknowledge and broker creative differences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always seek to better understand and serve our students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share the drive to reform higher education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate and promote an elegant visual design aesthetic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are or seek to be Lean, Agile, and Balanced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know when to obsess and when to move on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;You’ll need to show us&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong passion for learning and a desire to help others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to listen effectively, to offer and accept feedback openly and work as part of a highly collaborative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High quality portfolio in consumer web and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly deliver strong design during rapid iterative processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of design fundamentals and principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some knowledge of front-end programming and mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;You should enjoy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing your work before it’s “done”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing in the browser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactoring your markup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilizing metrics in design decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning about and addressing people’s goals and frustrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping your co-workers become better designers and makers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;WANT TO KNOW MORE?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to use your skills in support of a worthwhile mission and get paid for it, let’s talk. Diversity is important to us, so we’re looking for people from ALL backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We pay our staff competitively with cash and equity.  Our benefit package includes Medical, Dental, Vision, 529 College Savings Plan, Flexible Spending Accounts, Life Insurance, Adoption Assistance, Paid Holidays, Unlimited Vacation and Snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:35:37 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-universitynow-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-universitynow-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Odopod in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a rock star front-end web developer to join the team through the beginning of February 2013. We are working on a large-scale responsive design project that is pushing the envelope for one of the most respected consumer brands in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve complex engineering problems quickly and smartly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write code and assist with asset production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clearly articulate ideas and recommendations on development solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a strong voice in application architecture, investigating solutions and finding ways to innovate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Live and breath HTML, CSS, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep expertise with supporting web standards technologies, including jQuery, Bootstrap and libraries, LESS, SASS, DocPad, Grunt, Mustache&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prefer experience with responsive design, grid systems, deferred loading schemes, jank-free animation rendering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience working on large teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approach technical challenges with an open mind and desire to innovate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appreciate great design and thrive in a creative environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicative and clear under tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have strong personal organization and attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE&amp;rsquo;RE ODOPOD, a new kind of agency – one that thinks like a start-up, understands brands like an agency, and creates products and services like an innovation firm. We’re located in Hayes Valley, San Francisco. We work with bold, forward-looking brands like Sony, Google, Coca-Cola, Tesla Motors, PlayStation, the International Watch Company (IWC), and Sling Media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn more about us at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.odopod.com&quot;&gt;http://www.odopod.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please, no phone calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include a link to your online portfolio and PDF of your resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must live in the San Francisco area or be willing to move here&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:35:37 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-odopod-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-odopod-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Front-End Developer at Venables Bell & Partners in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a front-end web developer to translate creative concepts into online advertising, interactive web experiences and animations. Candidate must be adaptive, self-motivated, detail oriented, organized, an excellent communicator and have a minimum of one year of experience in front-end web development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Candidate must be&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quick to adapt to changing technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovative, easygoing and hardworking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to manage multiple projects in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to collaborate effectively with other staff members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ year(s) experience as a front-end web developer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, CSS, JavaScript, structured data formats like XML, JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite to create assets for interactive and web projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with version control/source control systems like Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to haves&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash/ActionScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with backend programming concepts using PHP &amp;amp; MySQL or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:35:37 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-front-end-developer-venables-bell-%26-partners-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-front-end-developer-venables-bell-%26-partners-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>