<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End Web Developer at Spendgo in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a motivated Front End Web Developer who understands that great web-based applications are not just about the back-end or front-end, but truly a team effort to create a seamless elegant product. Every day we are disrupting the consumer-merchant-brand ecosystem like no one else has, using our patent pending technology to collect real-time itemized transaction data. This means we are constantly facing new challenges finding better ways to build intelligent Big Data applications and manage an ever expanding and interrelated data set. Our development team is rapidly growing and we’re looking for a super-star to get in on the ground floor and help build our cloud products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person who takes this position will play a key role in developing all of our web applications, portals, and analytics reports for consumers, merchants and brands. You will be entrusted with the design and delivery of key features of web products, and you ideas and input will be welcomed and expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with, developing and building highly interaction Web 2.0 UI’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptionally strong in HTML, HTML5, JavaScript, UI design patterns, and solving cross-browser UI issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Java/J2EE and Spring MVC Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of open source technologies such as Apache, Tomcat, and MemCached&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of NoSQL databases such as MongoDB, Casandra, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of RDMS and implementing optimized data structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production level experience with display side languages and libraries. We use Jquery quite a bit, would be great if you did too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a continuous integration development environment using Agile Methodologies like Scrum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have worked on server side technologies like Spring, Hibernate and RDBMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;San Francisco Office location with tons of free parking and close to public transportation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great Compensation: We offer competitive salaries and significant equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer paid Medical, Dental and Vision benefits for all employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many nerf weapons to defend yourself during spontaneous battles with the sales team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Lead Web Developer at xOverTime in Sunnyvale, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Front-End Lead Web Developer will be responsible for designing and implementing the large scale JavaScript application running in the browser and will co-ordinate with the lead for the back-end server to design appropriate web APIs to support the user interface. This role reports to our Technical Founder and VP of Development to build the company’s cloud-based web application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/CS and 5-7 years of industry experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in JavaScript, HTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for user interface design and the overall user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong desire to build an application from scratch with a small team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven project experience building single page web applications using a MVC style design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Angular.js or Backbone.js is a major plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Committed to test driven development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current with latest HTML5 features being implemented by the leading browsers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A preferred candidate will enjoy applying new technologies to push the boundaries of usability and interface design (e.g. CSS3, SVG and Canvas).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of node.js for the server application framework is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with mongoDB is desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you are qualified, please send your resume to careers@xovertime.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-lead-web-developer-xovertime-sunnyvale-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-lead-web-developer-xovertime-sunnyvale-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front end Developer at Pulsepoint in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an experienced Front-End Developer to join our User Experience Team. The ideal candidate should be able to quickly hand-code clean HTML and CSS from Comps and Wireframes. You will report to the Manager of Front-end Development. You will take on new development initiatives and platform enhancements on Grainger.com focusing on front-end development and client-side interactions using HTML, XHTML, CSS, XML, JavaScript, and other related interactive technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Major responsibilities and duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate and maintain front-end code (HTML / CSS / JavaScript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working to improve site performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain reusable code libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurately estimating and tracking your time across multiple simultaneous projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a team of developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn and adapt to new software/hardware technology and incorporate into production process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;collaborating on new design concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Core Competencies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert HTML, XHTML, DHTML, CSS, XML programming skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create clean, precise browser-compatible code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in JavaScript / Dojo / jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Adobe Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of interaction design and user-centered design methods &amp;amp; practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience collaborating with design and development teams on large-scale projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and track multiple tasks across multiple projects, under tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy working closely with others, and respectful of other perspectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert conflict resolution skills and being able to negotiate with stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to switch gears quickly and be flexible to work on concurrent projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the Agile development methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Education and Experience&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 2 to 3 years experience of hands-on web development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience Web Accessibility Standards a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Broad Vision, Hybris, JSP, Swing, Struts a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Marketing, Visual Communication, Graphic Arts, Computer Science or related area a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-pulsepoint-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End Developer at GumGum in Santa Monica, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Reaching millions of consumers as they actively view images across hundreds of premium websites, GumGum serves contextually relevant ads that yield far higher engagement than those of traditional display advertising units. In addition to helping advertisers reach highly targeted audiences in a brand-safe environment, GumGum gives publishers a new way to earn revenue by overlaying interactive ad units on the photos within their sites. Founded in 2007, GumGum is headquartered in Santa Monica, California. Investors include GRP Partners, First Round Capital, New Enterprise Associates and Crosscut Ventures. For more information, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gumgum.com&quot;&gt;http://www.gumgum.com&lt;/a&gt; or call (310) 260-9666.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and implement static and rich-media In-Image ad creatives using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, and Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test appearance and functionality of ad creatives on multiple desktop and mobile platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support and troubleshoot issues with existing campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with graphic designers, account managers, and ad operations teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid foundation in front-end development skills, e.g. HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience ensuring consistency across popular web browsers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of responsive design concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest and experience in web and mobile advertising is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communications skills and &amp;ldquo;customer service attitude&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock options, 401k, medical/dental&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix-style vacation policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Located in hotbed of tech startups blocks from the beach!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-gumgum-santa-monica-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-gumgum-santa-monica-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End Developer at art.com in Emeryville, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Front End Developer works within Creative Services as a member of the web production team translating e-mail, landing page designs and website updates to HTML for internal clients. Major responsibilities include mentoring junior level developers, HTML/CSS/email coding, acting as a liaison between technical and non-technical stakeholders, and some UX design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work as a part of the HTML/CSS coding team reporting to the Web Production Manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in mentoring junior developers and contractors on a day-to-day basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage external creative services agencies on a project-by-project basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurately translate Photoshop comps to web and e-mail ready HTML according to specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize graphics for web usage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform quality assurance testing of e-mails and landing pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide UX and interactive design input that creatively and successfully addresses business objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish solid relationships within the art.com Engineering department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act as a liaison between Creative Services and Engineering teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undergraduate degree &amp;ndash; and preferably additional qualifications in Creative design (Diploma / Degree in Applied Arts / Design)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-4 years of work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills across a variety of disciplines (i.e.: can flawlessly converse with technical and non-technical individuals alike)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good performance in a Creative / Web Production role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience managing junior level developers, contractors, and external creative services agencies is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript and jQuery knowledge and experience preferred (familiarity implementing scripts as well as hand-coded JS or jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of email coding best practices &amp;ndash; expert knowledge of table-based coding practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of web browser irregularities and Internet Explorer 7.0+ debugging experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be very conversant with design tools such as Adobe PhotoShop and DreamWeaver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be highly organized, goal oriented and extremely attentive to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Flash a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work under tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven team player as well as independent achiever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A voracious appetite for internet knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-art.com-emeryville-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-art.com-emeryville-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End Web Developer at Spendgo in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a motivated Front End Web Developer who understands that great web-based applications are not just about the back-end or front-end, but truly a team effort to create a seamless elegant product. Every day we are disrupting the consumer-merchant-brand ecosystem like no one else has, using our patent pending technology to collect real-time itemized transaction data. This means we are constantly facing new challenges finding better ways to build intelligent Big Data applications and manage an ever expanding and interrelated data set. Our development team is rapidly growing and we’re looking for a super-star to get in on the ground floor and help build our cloud products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person who takes this position will play a key role in developing all of our web applications, portals, and analytics reports for consumers, merchants and brands. You will be entrusted with the design and delivery of key features of web products, and you ideas and input will be welcomed and expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with, developing and building highly interaction Web 2.0 UI’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptionally strong in HTML, HTML5, JavaScript, UI design patterns, and solving cross-browser UI issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Java/J2EE and Spring MVC Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of open source technologies such as Apache, Tomcat, and MemCached&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of NoSQL databases such as MongoDB, Casandra, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of RDMS and implementing optimized data structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production level experience with display side languages and libraries. We use Jquery quite a bit, would be great if you did too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a continuous integration development environment using Agile Methodologies like Scrum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have worked on server side technologies like Spring, Hibernate and RDBMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;San Francisco Office location with tons of free parking and close to public transportation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great Compensation: We offer competitive salaries and significant equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer paid Medical, Dental and Vision benefits for all employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many nerf weapons to defend yourself during spontaneous battles with the sales team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End Developer at HotStudio in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Hot Studio is a leading experience design company with offices in San Francisco and New York. Dedicated to creating elegant solutions for complex design challenges, we collaborate with business leaders, innovative organizations, and emerging companies to create breakthrough products and services that have global reach and local impact. Our clients include Cisco, Dow Jones, Warner Music Group, Palm, Gap, eBay, Zinio, Ancestry.com, SFMOMA, and California Academy of Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Articulate the level of effort and timing of projects to producers/project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share technical considerations with visual designers and UX designers to support the creation of accurate design comps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take the lead in translating design comps into HTML, CSS and JavaScript files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the design team to produce prototypes that help illustrate concepts to the team and to clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the senior web application developer to integrate back end code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create multiple design options within a set period of time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document best practices and code standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to author advanced HTML, CSS and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of browser/platform compatibility issues and techniques for front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Web UI debugging tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of requirements for back-end integration with PHP or similar technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with bug tracking and version control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Photoshop and web image production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mac and Windows proficient&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate effectively with information architects and programmers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of both waterfall and Agile development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for and experience with video a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please include a link to your portfolio in your resume&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot Studio is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-hotstudio-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-hotstudio-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Demandforce in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Demandforce is looking for an outstanding front-end developer with a positive can-do attitude. The position will work from the San Francisco office, in an energy-filled startup environment, with a motivated team that is getting results and having fun. This role will be a key asset in the future growth of the company. The position reports to the Corporate Marketing Manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new customer facing web applications to increase online conversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think creatively about how to take the corporate website to the next level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own core processes with stakeholders for landing page and micro site development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement reporting and analytics on an ongoing basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push the boundaries with JQuery, Prototype (optional), or other JS platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute reporting and code cleanup responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operate in a pseudo-agile development environment leveraging GIT repositories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve upon corporate content management system (Crown Peak)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement and report on main website and landing pages testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own high and low level integration efforts with Marketo and Salesforce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure cross browser compatibility, including mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support all marketing efforts on corporate website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have 3+ years relevant work experience in a front-end development roll.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge working with jQuery, JavaScript, and other front end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of CMS technology such as Crown Peak (SAAS), WordPress, Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to quickly think on your feet while working in an agile friendly environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of HTML5 and CSS3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the DOM, cross-browser issues, and how to resolve them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Photoshop to turn designs into working hi-fidelity web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to easily learn and work with someone else’s code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of A/B and multivariate testing tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of analytics packages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Salesforce and Marketo a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/MS in Information Systems, Computer Science or a related field, or equivalent work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are looking for high caliber, positive individuals to join our team as we continue to build on our great momentum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Demandforce&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demandforce, Inc., a leading online marketing and communication software service from Intuit Inc. (Nasdaq:INTU), helps local businesses thrive in the Internet economy using email communications, text messaging and online services. Demandforce combines an award winning communication platform with best-in-class reputation and networking tools into one powerful web-based application that seamlessly integrates with existing workflow systems to help build businesses a strong online reputation and leverage local network marketing. Founded in 2003, Demandforce has collected over 1.6 Million consumer reviews, which are published across the Web, and has generated over 1.5 Billion dollars for its clients. Through the Demandforce Network, its end clients are connected to over 30 Million local consumers. For more information on how you can utilize Demandforce for your business, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.demandforce.com&quot;&gt;http://www.demandforce.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-demandforce-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-demandforce-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer/Front-End Engineer at AppFolio in Goleta, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to build software that matters? Do you want to work with a brilliant engineering team that really cares that users love their software?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AppFolio is a fast growing and funded startup in Santa Barbara, CA that is focused on building exciting web-based business applications that customers rave about. We take pride in finding new ways to delight our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will join our engineering team to design and build user interfaces that are used millions of times each month and help to make people&amp;rsquo;s lives a little bit better. Although all our engineers work across the entire development stack, we are looking to hire specialists specifically in the front-end who can provide expert level guidance to our team and stay on top of emerging technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;We are looking for people with expert-level proficiency in:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML(5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS(3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript (and libraries like jQuery, Modernizr, Backbone, Underscore, etc..)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-browser support and progressive enhancement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Inspector/Firebug including the JavaScript debugger and web console&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Expert-level proficiency means:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You follow industry leaders and the latest w3 specs to stay on the cutting edge of new technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve downloaded and installed nightly builds of Chrome, Webkit, and Firefox just to try out new features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don’t just use JavaScript libraries, you know how they work. You’ve probably submitted patches to popular libraries or even built your own.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML semantics is important to you; you’d never have a hard time deciding between using a &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;div&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo; and a &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;ul&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a solid understanding of CSS selector specificity and you don’t resort to just adding another ID to make one rule trump another.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;If you have one or more of the skills below, even better:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Ruby on Rails or similar MVC application framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SASS, Compass, CoffeeScript or other language preprocessors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-front-end-engineer-appfolio-goleta-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-front-end-engineer-appfolio-goleta-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer/Developer at Pandora in Oakland, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Pandora we have a single mission: To play only the music you&amp;rsquo;ll love. (Okay, we&amp;rsquo;ve added comedy as well – so we&amp;rsquo;re also up for playing some jokes you&amp;rsquo;ll love). To do this, it takes lots and lots of smart, self-motivated, and passionate people. Our teams are innovating in everything we do — from our playlists, to our ad services, to making Pandora available everywhere. All of that is in the service of building the best product we can, so that you can simply enjoy the music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a terrific opportunity for a talented, inspired, self-motivated, and responsible graphic designer to work on creative advertising projects at Pandora. In this position you will report into the creative team, working with many different disciplines, to execute on advertising projects. This position will require traditional digital graphic design skills, along with HTML/CSS development skills. To bring to life ad campaigns, from the custom level to the standard campaign. Delivering engaging experiences across web, mobile and tablet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile/Web/Tablet Advertising Design &amp;ndash;  creative design and production of custom ad experiences and standard ad campaigns (banners, wallpapers, custom digital sites)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Authoring of HTML and CSS, to build functional, interactive experiences across all platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Juggle an array of ongoing client projects, ability to meet deadlines and communicate clearly across the team and across other teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to conceptualize creative, solve visual problems with inadequate assets to meet project goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a strong portfolio that demonstrates experience in digital creative (web/mobile/tablet)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years of relevant experience, including web/mobile design/HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA or BFA in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Adobe Suite skills (photoshop, illustrator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Experience coding HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of JQuery/Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Engineer/Developer teams to bring front end to life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash experience a plus but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in rich media toolkits and ad builders is a plus but not a requirement, training can be provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-developer-pandora-oakland-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-developer-pandora-oakland-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>