<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Brighter.com in Santa Monica, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a talented front-end web developer to build web sites for brighterla.com.  Ideal candidates will have a can-do attitude, passion for technology, extensive HTML/CSS development experience, and will be able to get up to speed quickly in a fast moving agile development environment.  This will be a contract to hire position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a team environment, from making pixel perfect sites that meet the design requirements to integrating code with the back-end development team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of Photoshop; able to cutup comps from the design team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of CSS inheritance and how to use it to your advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good ideology for managing maintainable, scalable and cross-browser code across large sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with source control principles and comfortable with Subversion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of IE quirks and how to address them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with jQuery, Google Maps API and/or other JavaScript libraries a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML5 and mobile experience a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-brighter-com-santa-monica-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-brighter-com-santa-monica-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at NCLUSIVE, inc. in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of PHP &amp;amp; MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of back-end content management systems, PHP, and MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong education with HTML, CSS, JQUERY, and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great understanding of content management and eCommerce development, including Wordpress and Magento&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Linux, Unix, Apache, and terminal commands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and education with SEO best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adapt to the ever-changing trends in website design and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate transferrable HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript coding with an understanding of back-end integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-End Mobile Website Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform digital maintenance on an ongoing basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop websites and provide ongoing maintenance with content management systems and eCommerce websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate third-party coding using API development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with members of the front-end design and development teams to create a unified and focused brand strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About NCLUSIVE, inc.:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NCLUSIVE, inc (NCLUSIVEinc.com) is a digital and creative consulting firm with offices in Los Angeles and Atlanta. Our team specializes in brand creation, web development, and digital engagement. Working with some of the most recognizable companies, athletes, and talent, NCLUSIVE, inc&amp;rsquo;s core principal is to convert ideas into realities. The foundation of NCLUSIVE, inc. is based on a steadfast attention to detail down to the very last pixel. Our customer-focused approach gives us the ability to engage with our clients, achieving their objectives in each stage of their unique business cycle. From the creative lab to our evolving marketing strategies, the all-encompassing NCLUSIVE, inc. team is dedicated to creating and sustaining lifelong relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While our team is growing rapidly, we are constantly on the search for ambitious individuals to join the NCLUSIVE movement. Our core philosophy is built on taking an idea and making it a reality. Our creative process is an integral component to our success, and we consider ourselves more of a family than coworkers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Clients:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paris Hilton (ParisHilton.com)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yolanda Foster (Yolanda.com)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CJ Spiller (CJspiller.com)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John Wall (Johnwall2.com)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gigi Hadid (Gigihadid.com)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jon Taffer (JonTaffer.com)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-nclusive-inc-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-nclusive-inc-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Wallaby Financial Inc. in Pasadena, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Wallaby has one mission: To simplify people&amp;rsquo;s lives and help them save money by providing automation and intelligence for everyday payments. Our founders have extensive payments and data experience. We’re building the team to take on established players and change how people think about paying. As part of that effort, we’re seeking a software engineer who is comfortable with both front-end layouts and back-end controllers to build out our consumer-facing web offerings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are an agile shop and make extensive use of Ruby, Padrino, Bootstrap, ember.js, Coffeescript, and RESTful APIs alongside the usual HTML5 and CSS. You&amp;rsquo;ll be tasked with driving the development of Wallaby&amp;rsquo;s responsive user experience, and with organizing the code into manageable modules that can be reused and expanded upon as we grow. If you want to disrupt the payment system that everyone uses every day and have a blast doing it, send us your resume!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our headquarters are nestled in Old Town Pasadena just blocks from the 210 Freeway and LA’s Metro Gold Line providing easy access to all parts of Los Angeles. Old Town features more than 80 bars and restaurants for every meal of the day and our building includes a beer garden downstairs. We furnish the office with extensive snacks and caffeine in all its forms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wallaby Financial is a venture-backed startup whose investors include Peter Thiel’s Founders Fund FF Angel, WI Harper Group, Quotidian Ventures, Karlin Ventures and a great group of angels. We are committed to the success of both Wallaby and each of our employees and your career goals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-wallaby-financial-inc-pasadena-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-wallaby-financial-inc-pasadena-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at PlayHaven in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Front End Developer to work on the PlayHaven Dashboard. You will engineer new platform features into our Front End, enabling game developers to easily market to their players.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years software development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of CSS/JS/HTML5 with jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of object-oriented principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast-learning and adaptable to new code-bases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General familiarity with current trends in front-end tools and frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to see a project from spec to pixel-perfect implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Driven to find the right people/things that can unblock your blockers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Plus:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real test-driven development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of WebDriver or other browser automation tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Server-side (Python) experience or interest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you done Agile before?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we offer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free lunches every day and plenty of snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salaries and awesome paid-for medical, dental and vision benefits plus a 401(k)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited vacation (and we require a minimum of 2 weeks!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Epic ping pong and FIFA battles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A transparent work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A developer community that inspires and works with you to change mobile gaming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-playhaven-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-playhaven-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Nest in Palo Alto, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and update nest.com, nest.com/works, support.nest.com, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize and show off the latest and greatest in HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help deliver best of breed blog posts on a regular basis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop tests and standards for the web properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills and experience needed:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with front end web engineering (JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3/SCSS, AJAX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with backend tools and languages (Ruby, Python, Middleman, Yeoman, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable using the best practices of version control (GitHub/Git)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with nuances between Mobile Safari and other WebKit based mobile browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to both guide and expand upon given designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knows when to use a library, and when it is better to role your own code for a particular interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can make HTML, CSS, and JS sing and dance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to employ graceful fallbacks for older browsers (especially IE)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to communicate technical topics to non-technical people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-broomfield-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-broomfield-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End/UI Developer at EVault, A Seagate Company in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;EVault, A Seagate Company, is a fast-growing industry leader in network-based data backup and recovery solutions.  We’ve been providing data protection and professional-grade storage solutions to small and mid-size businesses since 1997. Our technology platform is stable, secure, and optimized for WAN data transfer, and our recovery capabilities are ultra-reliable. We back it all with a rock-solid data center infrastructure and the industry&amp;rsquo;s highest quality customer service, while encouraging innovation and creativity by providing a casual and friendly work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EVault is led by a team of storage industry veterans with a compelling vision and a proven track record. We also benefit from the backing and expertise of our parent company, Seagate—the largest storage company in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a UI Developer with the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with development team to quickly understand requirements and come up with a solution proposal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write excellent design and functional documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate design and architecture to cross functional teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and development of wireframes and flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in conducting performance testing of application and GUI components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishing and maintaining high performance GUI web delivery function&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selection and implementation of appropriate tools, templates, libraries and standards for the creation of quality GUI components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with management/leadership/architect to set design direction and guide accordingly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review and evaluate designs and project activities against product goals and requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Knowledge and Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience developing appealing browser-based interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with Javascript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development experience with AJAX, HTML5, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of responsive web design, graceful degradation, and progressive enhancement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience translating wireframes to fully functional code that is modular and re-usable.Experience using a range of open source technologies and contributing to an open source project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;EVault, A Seagate Company, is an Equal Opportunity Employer committed to a diverse workforce.^&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-evault-a-seagate-company-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-evault-a-seagate-company-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer Internship at Plantronics in Santa Cruz, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Working at Plantronics gives you the rare opportunity to make a difference and feel valued, respected and supported, both personally and professionally. You&amp;rsquo;ll find the ideal blend of a casual, fun, friendly atmosphere with a strong commitment to the company&amp;rsquo;s success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since 1961 Plantronics (NYSE: PLT) people have been bringing sound innovation to the world.  We are a world leader in personal audio communications for professionals and consumers. Our reputation for excellence is built on innovative products, a people-centered workplace and strong ethics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Headquartered in Santa Cruz, California, Plantronics and its Clarity division have offices in 20 countries, including facilities in Mexico, China, and Europe.  Plantronics offers a generous mix of health, financial and lifestyle benefits as well as career development opportunities to its associates.  Discover Plantronics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PEOPLE-PLACE-PURPOSE-POTENTIAL&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Development team within the Digital Marketing department is looking for someone to assist with the development of our next generation product comparison and product search features.  The project involves analyzing product specifications and organizing them into groups as well as transforming them into terms that a visitor might find useful when searching on Plantronics.com.  Analysis of current best practices in the areas of product comparison and search will also be performed.* The work products to be delivered at the end of the project are a design document for each of the features, and if time allows, a working prototype based on findings from the best practice research that incorporate the specifications and related transformations from the product catalog.  This will require working closely with the Web Development and Production teams within Digital Marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This role requires knowledge of core web technologies such as HTML, JavaScript, and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional knowledge in PHP or JSP technologies is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be enrolled in an U.S. accredited higher educational institution on a full-time basis and in good academic standing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Plantronics is an Affirmative Action/Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To all recruitment agencies: Plantronics does not accept agency resumes. Please do not forward resumes to our jobs alias, Plantronics employees or any other company location. Plantronics is not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-internship-plantronics-santa-cruz-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-internship-plantronics-santa-cruz-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web App UI Developer at Bluenose Analytics in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bluenose Analytics is building a CRM for the subscription economy by creating value from the intersection of product usage and CRM data.  Our initial analytics application gives SaaS vendors an &amp;ldquo;early warning system&amp;rdquo; of reports and alerts to drive better trial conversions, prevent churn and grow recurring revenue.  For example, SaaS users with declining product usage might be at risk to renew their subscription.  Bluenose spots these patterns and alerts the vendor before it&amp;rsquo;s too late. We are backed by top-­-tier venture investors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Success in this role means:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delighting users with an intuitive user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taming complex data and make interaction a joy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iteration is your middle name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to learn more about Big Data and analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seeking and ingesting frequent customer feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead UX responsibilities for new product development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design mock-ups and novel user interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate them to working, production code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm new features and models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make  enterprise  software  look  and  feel  like  it  rightfully  belongs  next  to  the latest consumer application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years making browser-based magic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5, CSS3, jQuery (and all their buddies) are your best friends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience of popular web app frameworks is most excellent (RoR, Groovy on Grails)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-directed, motivated, passionate when it comes to user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile development a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to define an early-stage start-up culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-app-ui-developer-bluenose-analytics-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-app-ui-developer-bluenose-analytics-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at BEAR Data Solutions in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bear Data Solutions is named as one of the fastest growing companies by Inc. magazine in 2010 continues to grow and evolve as a successful IT solutions and services provider. The BEAR Data Team is a group of highly experienced and talented professionals who are passionate about delivering five star service and solutions to their clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our customer is seeking a FrontEnd Developer with 5 years of web development experience and extensive knowledge in JavaScript Frameworks/Toolkits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop Client side applications using HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, communicate and debug short and long term Front End Solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in defining systems architecture from a scripting, efficiency, caching, and client-side performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of web development experience, preferably in media and entertainment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge in coding native JavaScript, HTML4/5, and CSS2/3 in non-WYSIWYG editors (e.g. Eclipse)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in JavaScript Frameworks/Toolkits (e.g. jQuery, YUI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in live data applications using AJAX/JSONP with JSON/XML/HTML content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to debug and analyse JavaScript/CSS/http requests using updated tools and methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the principles of object-oriented programming and design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in cross-browser/fullback solutions and implementing future proof solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in page speed optimizations such as browser cache, media asset preloading, efficient JavaScript processing techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of version control concepts and tools, particularly SVN, with branching and merging (or equivalent) knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of web standards and IA/UI best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resourcefulness in troubleshooting complex problems, finding available internal solutions, as well as developing new solutions based on external sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably knowledge in any CMS environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands Agile or other project development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multitask and manage multiple complex initiatives simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For more information, please visit us at www.beardatasolutions.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send resume to resumes@bdata.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-bear-data-solutions-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-bear-data-solutions-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Jr. Web &amp; Mobile Developer at Ghost Group in Newport Beach, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re an awesome, Orange County based, IT company with a fun atmosphere to work in.We have a lot of new projects starting that you would be working on, providing you with a lot of hands on experience.
Check us out at http://legalmarijuanadispensary.com/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for motivated Computer Science majors at major Universities to join our team!
10-25 hours per week, $15/hour. You&amp;rsquo;ll gain a lot of experience and get to work in a great environment!
You will be working out of our brand new office in Newport Beach&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to Develop Real Web Applications in PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to Develop on the Android &amp;amp; iOS mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn internet marketing and search engine optimization from our experts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Prerequisites:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good working knowledge of HTML5/CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to analyze and use Google analytic data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux system administration (Lite)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Majoring in Computer Science at a major university (UCI, Chapman, UCLA, USC etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Must be friendly to medical marijuana and mmj patients
Knowledge of Joomla, Drupal or other CMS systems a plus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please provide us with your resume as well as either a demo of sites you&amp;rsquo;ve built, github
account, or even code examples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-web-and-mobile-developer-ghost-group-newport-beach-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-web-and-mobile-developer-ghost-group-newport-beach-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>