<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End Web Developer at Spendgo in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a motivated Front End Web Developer who understands that great web-based applications are not just about the back-end or front-end, but truly a team effort to create a seamless elegant product. Every day we are disrupting the consumer-merchant-brand ecosystem like no one else has, using our patent pending technology to collect real-time itemized transaction data. This means we are constantly facing new challenges finding better ways to build intelligent Big Data applications and manage an ever expanding and interrelated data set. Our development team is rapidly growing and we’re looking for a super-star to get in on the ground floor and help build our cloud products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person who takes this position will play a key role in developing all of our web applications, portals, and analytics reports for consumers, merchants and brands. You will be entrusted with the design and delivery of key features of web products, and you ideas and input will be welcomed and expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with, developing and building highly interaction Web 2.0 UI’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptionally strong in HTML, HTML5, JavaScript, UI design patterns, and solving cross-browser UI issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Java/J2EE and Spring MVC Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of open source technologies such as Apache, Tomcat, and MemCached&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of NoSQL databases such as MongoDB, Casandra, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of RDMS and implementing optimized data structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production level experience with display side languages and libraries. We use Jquery quite a bit, would be great if you did too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a continuous integration development environment using Agile Methodologies like Scrum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have worked on server side technologies like Spring, Hibernate and RDBMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;San Francisco Office location with tons of free parking and close to public transportation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great Compensation: We offer competitive salaries and significant equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer paid Medical, Dental and Vision benefits for all employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many nerf weapons to defend yourself during spontaneous battles with the sales team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-spendgo-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End Developer at HotStudio in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Hot Studio is a leading experience design company with offices in San Francisco and New York. Dedicated to creating elegant solutions for complex design challenges, we collaborate with business leaders, innovative organizations, and emerging companies to create breakthrough products and services that have global reach and local impact. Our clients include Cisco, Dow Jones, Warner Music Group, Palm, Gap, eBay, Zinio, Ancestry.com, SFMOMA, and California Academy of Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Articulate the level of effort and timing of projects to producers/project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share technical considerations with visual designers and UX designers to support the creation of accurate design comps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take the lead in translating design comps into HTML, CSS and JavaScript files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the design team to produce prototypes that help illustrate concepts to the team and to clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the senior web application developer to integrate back end code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create multiple design options within a set period of time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document best practices and code standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to author advanced HTML, CSS and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of browser/platform compatibility issues and techniques for front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Web UI debugging tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of requirements for back-end integration with PHP or similar technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with bug tracking and version control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Photoshop and web image production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mac and Windows proficient&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate effectively with information architects and programmers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of both waterfall and Agile development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for and experience with video a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please include a link to your portfolio in your resume&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot Studio is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-hotstudio-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-hotstudio-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Demandforce in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Demandforce is looking for an outstanding front-end developer with a positive can-do attitude. The position will work from the San Francisco office, in an energy-filled startup environment, with a motivated team that is getting results and having fun. This role will be a key asset in the future growth of the company. The position reports to the Corporate Marketing Manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new customer facing web applications to increase online conversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think creatively about how to take the corporate website to the next level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own core processes with stakeholders for landing page and micro site development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement reporting and analytics on an ongoing basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push the boundaries with JQuery, Prototype (optional), or other JS platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute reporting and code cleanup responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operate in a pseudo-agile development environment leveraging GIT repositories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve upon corporate content management system (Crown Peak)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement and report on main website and landing pages testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own high and low level integration efforts with Marketo and Salesforce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure cross browser compatibility, including mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support all marketing efforts on corporate website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have 3+ years relevant work experience in a front-end development roll.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge working with jQuery, JavaScript, and other front end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of CMS technology such as Crown Peak (SAAS), WordPress, Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to quickly think on your feet while working in an agile friendly environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of HTML5 and CSS3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the DOM, cross-browser issues, and how to resolve them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Photoshop to turn designs into working hi-fidelity web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to easily learn and work with someone else’s code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of A/B and multivariate testing tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of analytics packages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Salesforce and Marketo a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/MS in Information Systems, Computer Science or a related field, or equivalent work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are looking for high caliber, positive individuals to join our team as we continue to build on our great momentum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Demandforce&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demandforce, Inc., a leading online marketing and communication software service from Intuit Inc. (Nasdaq:INTU), helps local businesses thrive in the Internet economy using email communications, text messaging and online services. Demandforce combines an award winning communication platform with best-in-class reputation and networking tools into one powerful web-based application that seamlessly integrates with existing workflow systems to help build businesses a strong online reputation and leverage local network marketing. Founded in 2003, Demandforce has collected over 1.6 Million consumer reviews, which are published across the Web, and has generated over 1.5 Billion dollars for its clients. Through the Demandforce Network, its end clients are connected to over 30 Million local consumers. For more information on how you can utilize Demandforce for your business, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.demandforce.com&quot;&gt;http://www.demandforce.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-demandforce-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-demandforce-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer/Front-End Engineer at AppFolio in Goleta, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to build software that matters? Do you want to work with a brilliant engineering team that really cares that users love their software?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AppFolio is a fast growing and funded startup in Santa Barbara, CA that is focused on building exciting web-based business applications that customers rave about. We take pride in finding new ways to delight our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will join our engineering team to design and build user interfaces that are used millions of times each month and help to make people&amp;rsquo;s lives a little bit better. Although all our engineers work across the entire development stack, we are looking to hire specialists specifically in the front-end who can provide expert level guidance to our team and stay on top of emerging technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;We are looking for people with expert-level proficiency in:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML(5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS(3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript (and libraries like jQuery, Modernizr, Backbone, Underscore, etc..)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-browser support and progressive enhancement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Inspector/Firebug including the JavaScript debugger and web console&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Expert-level proficiency means:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You follow industry leaders and the latest w3 specs to stay on the cutting edge of new technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve downloaded and installed nightly builds of Chrome, Webkit, and Firefox just to try out new features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don’t just use JavaScript libraries, you know how they work. You’ve probably submitted patches to popular libraries or even built your own.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML semantics is important to you; you’d never have a hard time deciding between using a &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;div&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo; and a &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;ul&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a solid understanding of CSS selector specificity and you don’t resort to just adding another ID to make one rule trump another.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;If you have one or more of the skills below, even better:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Ruby on Rails or similar MVC application framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SASS, Compass, CoffeeScript or other language preprocessors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-front-end-engineer-appfolio-goleta-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-front-end-engineer-appfolio-goleta-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer/Developer at Pandora in Oakland, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Pandora we have a single mission: To play only the music you&amp;rsquo;ll love. (Okay, we&amp;rsquo;ve added comedy as well – so we&amp;rsquo;re also up for playing some jokes you&amp;rsquo;ll love). To do this, it takes lots and lots of smart, self-motivated, and passionate people. Our teams are innovating in everything we do — from our playlists, to our ad services, to making Pandora available everywhere. All of that is in the service of building the best product we can, so that you can simply enjoy the music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a terrific opportunity for a talented, inspired, self-motivated, and responsible graphic designer to work on creative advertising projects at Pandora. In this position you will report into the creative team, working with many different disciplines, to execute on advertising projects. This position will require traditional digital graphic design skills, along with HTML/CSS development skills. To bring to life ad campaigns, from the custom level to the standard campaign. Delivering engaging experiences across web, mobile and tablet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile/Web/Tablet Advertising Design &amp;ndash;  creative design and production of custom ad experiences and standard ad campaigns (banners, wallpapers, custom digital sites)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Authoring of HTML and CSS, to build functional, interactive experiences across all platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Juggle an array of ongoing client projects, ability to meet deadlines and communicate clearly across the team and across other teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to conceptualize creative, solve visual problems with inadequate assets to meet project goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a strong portfolio that demonstrates experience in digital creative (web/mobile/tablet)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years of relevant experience, including web/mobile design/HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA or BFA in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Adobe Suite skills (photoshop, illustrator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Experience coding HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of JQuery/Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Engineer/Developer teams to bring front end to life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash experience a plus but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in rich media toolkits and ad builders is a plus but not a requirement, training can be provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-developer-pandora-oakland-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-developer-pandora-oakland-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Front-End Web Developer at Balsam Brands in Redwood City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do your eyes sparkle after making a website design come to life? Are you passionate about coding and structuring and just LOVE the fast-paced nature of this industry? If so, you might be interested in joining one of the fastest-growing online retail companies in America &amp;mdash;the high-energy passionate environment of Balsam Brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our new web developer will work closely with our E-Commerce UX, Design, and Development teams to transform mock-ups into cross-platform pixel-perfect web interfaces&amp;mdash;achieving well executed, high-performing, scalable, and easily maintained results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within a fun team environment: Development, Design, UX, SEO, and Managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver high quality HTML/CSS code for web content (e.g. E-Commerce site designs, web pages, web content, blogs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create code based on mock-ups from Photoshop and other design applications (e.g. PowerPoint)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize, QA, and debug existing HTML/CSS web content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce and optimize image assets (e.g. compression, splicing, sprites, other techniques)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct thorough cross-browser and cross-device testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop from within E-Commerce platforms, Wordpress, and various other platforms as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue to improve UI/Front-end development skills and stay up-to-date on HTML/CSS trends and technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage with the team on your progress and participate in status calls/meetings as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest and present overviews of best practices, relevant and effective current and new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in coding cross-browser and cross-device HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with HTML5/CSS3 and latest development technologies and concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with W3 standards and using cross-platform testing and debugging tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience with Javascript/Jquery/XML/AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the relationship and interactions between HTML and other scripting languages/technologies (e.g. Javascript, PHP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Photoshop skills&amp;mdash;can navigate software, edit, manipulate, splice, and optimize easily&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to learn and work from within any CMS and E-Commerce platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great &amp;ldquo;work-around&amp;rdquo; skills&amp;mdash;able to provide solutions to platforms and CMS environment limitations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with SEO and its relationship with web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire and ability to thrive in a fast-paced, growing, dynamic environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn new technologies quickly and independently, and committed to continually learning new things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills&amp;mdash;verbal and written&amp;mdash;with a wide range of colleagues from different backgrounds, including non-technical business managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very strong organization skills and keen attention to detail (not satisfied until everything is just right)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage time effectively and efficiently, and meet project deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work collaboratively with remote and offshore teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Computer Science, relevant experience, or really cool dropout story&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years professional/relevant experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List of at least 3 projects to showcase relevant skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Assets:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with E-Commerce sites and industry trends (e.g. cross-selling, mobile shopping)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing for an E-Commerce website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the E-Commerce platform Volusion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript/JQuery/AJAX coding skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP coding skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordpress development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excel skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Balsam Brands:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Balsam Brands manages a collection of branded online businesses that sell specialty products.  Balsam Brands has successfully rolled out brands such as Balsam Hill (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.balsamhill.com&quot;&gt;http://www.balsamhill.com&lt;/a&gt;) and Backyard Ocean (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.backyardocean.com&quot;&gt;http://www.backyardocean.com&lt;/a&gt;).  With a proven track record for growth in new markets, Balsam Brands presents a unique opportunity to those who are seeking to have a meaningful impact in a fast-paced, high-energy environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PTO, Medical, Dental &amp;amp; Vision Insurance, 401K, Flex Spending, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Contact:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send cover letter and resumé to jobs@balsambrands.com . Please include your favorite vacation destination on your cover letter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-front-end-web-developer-balsam-brands-redwood-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-front-end-web-developer-balsam-brands-redwood-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Developer at awe.sm in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Why us: help solve hard problems that create real value for business&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearly every website, mobile app, or marketing campaign has a social layer now, but too few companies make use of the incredibly valuable social data generated each day by their own users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;awe.sm has built a powerful platform that captures these data, connects them to real business goals, and enables our customers to harness the results to create value through our growing toolset, robust APIs, and integrations with leading 3rd-party tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve proven the value of our technology to a growing number of real customers – from startups to the Fortune 500, and now we&amp;rsquo;re ready to grow our team, our capabilities, and the reach of our platform. Our goal is to help our customers harness the rich intent and effectiveness data from social interactions to build more compelling applications, produce more relevant content, and market more effectively – anywhere social is driving value, awe.sm can help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the job: turning Big Data into Great Info&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are collecting enormous amounts of data, and are constantly coming up with new things we can do with it. Your job is to take the power of our APIs and focus it down into clear, easy-to-understand interfaces that help our customers see what&amp;rsquo;s going on and make use of that information to meet their goals. You&amp;rsquo;ll be extending our GUI as well as knocking out prototypes that demonstrate to customers all the ways they can use the data our platform can provide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want you to think creatively and come up with novel, illuminating interfaces that make the value of our data more obvious, easier, and more fun to use. We&amp;rsquo;re not going to be handing you a PSD and telling you to get all the pixels lined up; we&amp;rsquo;re going to be explaining a problem and looking to you for a solution that nobody&amp;rsquo;s tried before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who you are: excited just from the job description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need an experienced developer with a proven track record of getting things done on the web. We&amp;rsquo;re also looking for someone deeply interested in user interface design and the presentation of information. Ideally you&amp;rsquo;ll have built something in this area already, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just a side project. We want somebody who uses JavaScript for more than form validation, and knows more than just jQuery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of all we&amp;rsquo;re looking for honest enthusiasm: does the idea of building big new things and having to learn a lot to get them done fill you with a burning desire to get started right away? Then you&amp;rsquo;re the person we need. We want somebody who has big ideas and the technical chops to bring them to life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the company&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;awe.sm works with hundreds of customers large and small, from startups like Zaarly, StockTwits, and Topspin Media to not-so-startups like Groupon, Zynga, and Gilt Groupe. We’re backed by leading VC firms and are expanding from a team of 5 to 10–15. The salary is competitive and comes with a generous stock option plan as well as full health, dental and vision coverage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a technology-driven business, we are creating an engineering-driven organization. Personal development is one of our highest company priorities, and we believe that technical development is essential to a strong engineering culture. That translates into code reviews and tech talks to promote learning and assigning projects in ways that help team-members explore their interests first-hand. We hope this will be your favorite job, but we doubt it will be your last and we want every member of our team to walk away from this experience better equipped to pursue their own goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the tech&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our current front-end code is mostly in PHP using the Zend Framework (we like MVC, but are not big fans of Ruby on Rails). We want somebody unafraid of learning new languages and APIs to get things done. Our user interface is HTML5 with a lot of Javascript for visualizations. You&amp;rsquo;ll probably be pleased to hear that we do not support IE 6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a close-knit team. It should go without saying since we&amp;rsquo;re a startup, but we work flexible hours in casual dress. We mostly work out of our offices on the 6th floor of the US Bank building in the Mission, featuring truly awesome views. We value our ability to concentrate, so we&amp;rsquo;re a pretty quiet room and everyone&amp;rsquo;s got headphones, but our IRC room is always active, with both technical arguments and the latest YouTube videos. We eat lunch together every day, and socialize after work regularly. We are increasingly good at throwing surprise birthday parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Buzzwords:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Must-haves:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML (including HTML5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript (actual knowledge of the language, not just jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Nice-to-haves (in order of niceness):&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MVC framework (especially Zend Framework)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook and Twitter APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SVG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-developer-awe-sm-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-developer-awe-sm-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Google in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a member of the Help Center Front End team, you live on the front lines of support.google.com and build features used by millions of people every day. The work is challenging, fast paced and always changing. Strong analytical skills, unwavering commitment to quality, collaborative work ethic and cutting edge coding skills are all necessary. You should live and breathe the fundamentals of JavaScript (not just jQuery), CSS, and HTML and use these technologies to build elegant and responsive web applications. Google aims to provide a best-in-class support experience so our customers can get the most out of Google products. Translating business requirements into engineering and UX requirements, you frequently act as consultant, advisor, and product manager to teams seeking to improve their online help presence. You play a key role in building next-generation customer support and education services at Google&amp;rsquo;s scale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, develop and maintain critical components of the help center platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in an on-call rotation for off-hours emergency escalations and outages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advise and collaborate effectively with cross-functional business partners on feature design and work closely with back end engineering teams on feature development and deployment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fulfill several requests and responsibilities simultaneously while delivering on tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a champion for both our internal clients (editorial staff, product support teams) and external users (advertisers, consumers, general public).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS or MS in Computer Science or related technical field (In lieu of degree, 4 years relevant work experience).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technically strong in front end web developing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Area&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When our millions of advertisers and publishers are happy, so are we! As small business experts, we help get local entrepreneurs on the map, and deliver a beautifully simple, intuitive experience that enables customers to grow their businesses with us. By spotting and analyzing customer needs and trends, our innovative teams of strategists, account developers and customer support specialists work together on scalable solutions for each business, no matter its age or size.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-google-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-google-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End Developer at Third Eye Consulting Services &amp; Solutions LLC. in Cupertino, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Third Eye is looking for a creative, talented front end developer with an eye for quality and detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Must have the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong HTML and HTML5 expertise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in CSS and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross browser development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of advanced JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using JQuery and other JS frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web application development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Strong pluses:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiemce with frameworks like ext.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JSP development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This is a FULL time position with Third Eye where the compensation package includes bonuses and full medical benefits. Highly skilled contractors can also be considered on a C2C basis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-third-eye-consulting-services-%26-solutions-llc-cupertino-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-third-eye-consulting-services-%26-solutions-llc-cupertino-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Engineer / FrontEndDeveloper at Hearsay Social in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for someone who knows what makes a website look and behave well and also has the random set of skills to actually
make it happen. Someone who is so OCD that she even wants her code to look pretty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for someone who understands that there are living, breathing people at the other end of the tube. They’re impatient.
They read very little. Sometimes they use ancient devices that you wouldn’t touch with a 10 foot pole, but hey they’re your guests and you’re open-minded so you accommodate them. If they can’t figure something out, it&amp;rsquo;s not their fault; it&amp;rsquo;s your fault for building a confusing application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a designer you believe less is more. You deconstruct a page to its most crucial elements (after figuring out what the most crucial elements are). You show and don’t tell. You realize that we are building a business application and not (thank God) a consumer daily deal site. As such, our site should be timelessly elegant without being trendy. You are consistently consistent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a developer you want every page to load in a snap. You know that all those &lt;strong&gt;HTTP requests&lt;/strong&gt; cause the browser to chug-a-lug so you use &lt;strong&gt;CSS3 for the bling and kiss the PNGs goodbye&lt;/strong&gt;. You have a visceral reaction to any text that’s part of an image (excepting, of course, logos) because you know it isn&amp;rsquo;t scalable or translatable. Your markup is clean and semantic. You know the difference between &lt;strong&gt;display block, inline and inline-block&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can do &lt;strong&gt;Javascript&lt;/strong&gt;. You know what it’s good for but you also know when not to use it. You prefer the &lt;strong&gt;acronym XHR to the misnomer AJAX because it should really be called AJAJ&lt;/strong&gt;. You like to experiment with new paradigms like Backbone but ultimately know it’s just one of many different implementations; it’s the thing you’re implementing that’s important not the technology that gets you there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You secretly know that front end development is harder than back end development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You tell us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-engineer-frontenddeveloper-hearsay-social-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-engineer-frontenddeveloper-hearsay-social-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>