<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Android Developer at Deluxe Entertainment in Burbank, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Division Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deluxe Digital Distribution provides turnkey video management and distribution solutions for online retailers, device manufacturers, video operators, and other IP-based solutions providers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a Lead Android Developer with 8+ years of Software Development Experience to work out of our Burbank, or San Diego, CA facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the design and development of our best-in-class Android clients for mobile and tablet devices for millions of users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Owning and driving both personal and team level goals from discovery to completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Member of architecture team responsible for approving client architecture as well as client/server integration points and APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be self-directed in a fast paced, growing organization with the ability to balance multiple customers, priorities, and objectives simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guiding and mentoring junior to mid-level developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a leader of and enforce Agile principles within the product development team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of relevant software development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of Android development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of video formats, playback, streaming, UI frameworks, and developing for multiple screen sizes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing and/or interfacing with WS APIs (SOAP/REST/JSON)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in building video playback applications on Android.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and passion for developing usable client SDKs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communicator who is passionate about quality, supportability, extensibility, and simple design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on iOS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One or more published Android apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Digital Rights Management (DRM) including PlayReady, OMA, WMDRM, AES&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile principles and practices such as TDD, Continuous Integration, daily Scrums, and sprint/release planning and execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We offer competitive pay and benefits program, including: medical, dental &amp;amp; vision coverage, vacation &amp;amp; sick leave, 401(k), company health screenings and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To view other open positions and for more information on our company, please visit our website at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bydeluxe.com&quot;&gt;http://www.bydeluxe.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deluxe is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-android-developer-deluxe-entertainment-burbank-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-android-developer-deluxe-entertainment-burbank-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Technical Customer Service Advisor at Apple in Sacramento, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Apple, we believe in hard work, a fun environment, and the kind of creativity and innovation that only comes about when talented people from diverse backgrounds approach problems from varying perspectives. We believe each customer interaction is an opportunity to delight, impress, engage and inspire. We focus on all the small details to have the biggest impact!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A driving passion for new and innovative technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Owns a computer and peripheral devices like iPods, cell phones, PDA’s, etc., and has personal experience with troubleshooting them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the Mac platform, Apple software, and Mac OS X.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable navigating through unfamiliar software applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Broad understanding of computing technology including: hardware components, data storage, operating systems, software applications, common peripheral devices, and external connectivity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Internet services and network configurations including broadband, dial-up, and wired or wireless home networks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approaches unknowns with a systematic and analytical process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seeks technical challenges and enjoys finding answers unassisted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sales experience in a technical field, discussing the specifications and benefits of various products with potential customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in retail, technical support, help desk support, or customer service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adaptive interaction with people of diverse technical proficiency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An active listener and excellent verbal communicator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An excitement and passion for the company and product you are representing and the ability to share this passion with your customer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The responsibilities of the Technical Customer Service Support Advisor includes the following: &amp;ndash; Provide unparalleled customer service and enrichment to the digital lifestyles primarily for our iOS customers. &amp;ndash; Delight our customers by listening attentively to their needs, reaching agreement about their issue and driving it to a resolution. &amp;ndash; Troubleshoot simple to complex issues, adapting to a variety of skill levels through a positive, analytical, and informative approach. &amp;ndash; Educate customers about Apple’s support options, online tools, and self-help or tutorial training resources. &amp;ndash; Communicate positively with team members, customers, and other partners – always remembering, that you represent the Apple brand. Oh yeah &amp;ndash; and have fun! After all, this is Apple. Technical Consultants that support our Apple customers are the best of the best of the best. Are you one of them?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-technical-customer-service-advisor-apple-sacramento-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-technical-customer-service-advisor-apple-sacramento-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at A2Z Development Center, Inc. in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Music is looking for a talented iOS developer to join us in revolutionizing the digital music customer experience. Come join our small San Francisco-based team and help us take our iOS app to the next level. We love beautiful apps and we like to ship often. We have a strong focus on quality, so we like continuous integration and use automated test frameworks extensively. At Amazon Music, our environment frees up developers to do what they do best: to innovate and implement. We love to work with smart people who have a strong sense of ownership and a strong engineering mindset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science, or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years iOS development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of Objective-C, Xcode and Unix development experience in a shipping iOS application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ Industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MS in Computer Science.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing, deploying and supporting iOS applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven ability to learn and adapt to new, complex development environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superb analytical skills, excellent communication, strong team ethic, and attention to details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Amazon Music San Francisco, part of the Amazon.com, Inc. group of companies, is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-a2z-development-center-inc-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-a2z-development-center-inc-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr iOS Programmer at Insomniac Games, Inc. in Burbank, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Insomniac Games is looking for a Sr iOS programmer to work with the Outernauts team! Surprise! This sounds just like our other posting – except with this position – we expect you to be at a senior level of knowledge and skill. We are looking to you to help design and implement new game features, optimize for memory and performance, and provide tools for content creators. We are also looking for you to write server and database code to support new features. Read on if this sounds like the spot you have been waiting for!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities include the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintenance and development of server and client code for game features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimization of existing code for performance and memory. Provide useful analysis of game performance problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of technology to improve security, data protection, and to prevent hacking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of server and client code related to payment gateways, financial transactions, and transaction security.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintenance and development of server deployment scripts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintenance and development of application instance monitoring software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diagnosing and debugging problems with client performance, load time, and connection problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintenance and development of tools for content creators.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, implementation, and maintenance of User Interface systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of performant, reusable and clean code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical input/guidance to other programmers; mentor programmers as appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research prospective solutions and provide assistance in establishing the technical direction of the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties may be assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional skills needed for this position include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to adhere to existing coding practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently, trouble-shoot problems, and provide solutions proactively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and/or Experience needed for this position:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree from a four-year college or university. Six to eight years related experience and/or training; or equivalent combination of education and experience. Degree in Computer Science is favorable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert command of C++ or ActionScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of iOS and Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like an exciting opportunity, then we look forward to hearing from you. Please use the link below, and apply directly to the position. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-ios-programmer-insomniac-games-inc-burbank-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-ios-programmer-insomniac-games-inc-burbank-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at UberConference in Pleasanton, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;UberConference is a new visual audio conferencing service with a visual interface that took home first prize in the Battlefield competition at TechCrunch Disrupt.  Funded with $18M from Google Ventures and Andreessen Horowitz, UberConference solves the most common problems faced in teleconferencing including making a conference easy to join, knowing who is participating, knowing who is speaking, and making advanced features easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write gorgeous and optimized code for the iOS platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect, build, iterate and manage our set of mobile applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner closely with our design team to produce an application that flows seamlessly and works intuitively with our users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our mobile team is fairly small and self-directed so each person is responsible for at least one critical part of a project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particulars of experience are not as important to us as generally being a smart person. Smart people learn quickly so use the bullet points below as a guideline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience releasing at least one application into the App Store.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building applications in memory- and network-constrained scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency with Objective-C and Cocoa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cutting-edge iOS technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong framework outside of iOS is always a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ÜberConference is working on the future of communications and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for great people to join us. We&amp;rsquo;re a small team, obsessed with elegant design and efficient solutions to big problems. Our office is fast-paced, loud and crazy. We like making things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% paid Medical, Dental and Vision Plan for you and your dependents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday Weekly Socials and a Company Game Room complete with a game consoles, a ping pong and a beer pong table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cell Phone, Home Internet and Gym reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free healthy as well as unhealthy snacks and drinks are available in the kitchen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose your setup (monitor, laptop, mouse, keyboard etc…)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iPad for all new employees and your very own company jacket!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-uberconference-pleasanton-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-uberconference-pleasanton-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer (Contract) at GoPro in Cardiff-by-the-Sea, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;GoPro makes the world’s most versatile cameras, enabling people to capture immersive and engaging photo and video content during their favorite activities. GoPro’s HERO lines of wearable and gear mountable cameras are used collectively by more consumers, professional athletes, and video production professionals than any other camera in the world. Based in San Mateo, California, GoPro’s products are sold in over 100 countries worldwide and at GoPro.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GoPro offers a fun and fast-paced work environment with passionate and motivated people who have a drive to learn, innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GoPro is seeking a top tier candidate for the iOS Developer contract role. This role will contribute to the exceptionally programming skills to develop highly innovative, consumer based mobile products. The iOS developer will make disciplined use of source control and bug tracking systems. In addition, the role will participate in software code reviews to ensure the creation of high quality, compact and elegant code. The ideal candidate will have familiarity with XML, JSON and REST-based API’s and exceptional communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute exceptional programming skills to develop highly innovative consumer-based mobile products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make disciplined use of source control and bug tracking systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unit-test developed code for usability, general reliability and elegance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in software code reviews to ensure the creation of high quality, compact code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in code development from requirements throughout the deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other engineers, managers, and executive team to define, design and ship new features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Mathematics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong CS fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of commercial experience in developing applications for the iPhone and iPad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Objective-C and developing native iOS apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with XML, JSON and REST-based APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Webkit and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of MVC, OOP, memory management and threading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven successful track record showing an aptitude for engineering and product sense&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication (written and verbal) skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly learn and apply new technologies and methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess the passion to design, build and polish innovative applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;GoPro is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-contract-gopro-cardiff-by-the-sea-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-contract-gopro-cardiff-by-the-sea-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at GREE in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The GREE Game Studio develops AAA games for the iOS and Android platforms.  The Studio builds games natively using the advantages of each operating system. To date, the Studio’s published titles have all been in iTunes top 10 Free-to-Play apps (both in terms of downloads and revenue).  Our game portfolio includes:  Crime City, Modern War, Kingdom of Age, and Zombie Jombie.  We have many new games in production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Job:  iOS Developer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Studio builds addictive games, enjoyed by millions.  Our games push iOS devices to their limits, squeezing every drop out of memory and performance.  Our developers support stunning graphics and are required to innovate intelligent solutions to complex engineering challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code in Objective-C primarily and develop features that uses the iPhone SDK, such as in-app purchase and animations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and implement scalable, reliable, and maintainable technologies for our gaming platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate closely with engineering, product, graphics, and game design teams to define our next generation games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated fluency in a compiled language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Objective-C, ideally through some commercial experience (Mac OS X and/or iPhone), a university course, or independent iPhone application development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Objective-C or cocos2d is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;WORKING ENVIRONMENT PERKS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Convenient to public transportation, across from ATT Ballpark (SOMA)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subsided commuter/parking support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macbook Pros, 27'&amp;lsquo; Monitors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health, Dental and Vision coverage with top providers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snacked-filled kitchen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free catered lunches and dinners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smartphone or Tablet reimbursement program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Japanese language lessons&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted gym memberships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-gree-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-gree-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior iOS Developer at HireUp in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Lead iOS development position building a card loyalty program from the ground up. Opportunity to work for a public company on a small team in a satellite office with a casual start-up environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualified candidates will have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One or more native apps published on the App Store
Passion for mobile development and user experience design
Respect for the iOS HIG (unless you have a better solution)
Solid knowledge of recent iOS additions (and deprecations)
Comfort in working fast with a small team with a lot of responsibility
Desire to grow your skills and acquire new ones&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Employee Type:  Full-Time Employee
Experience Required:    0 Years
Degree Required:    Not Specified
Travel Required:    Not Specified&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Detailed Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;N/A&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum Pay:    Not Specified
Average Bonus:  Not Specified
Average Commission:     Not Specified
Other Compensation:     Not Specified&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-hireup-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-hireup-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>OSX and iOS Developer at AnchorFree Inc in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a strong Mac OS X developer, with experience in Cocoa and new features of Leopard and Snow Leopard. The candidate should have proficiency with Mac OS X development internals, multi-threaded programming, networking programming and some Socket programming experience. Should be able to Debug and Profile a Cocoa application. Experience with background process development such as Launch Agent daemons is a plus.  Experience working with VPN clients is a strong plus. In this role you will work in the client side team and provide your expertise in developing next generation client for our famous product Hotspot Shield.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be tasked with helping formulate our technology presence on the Mac platforms as well as the migration and integration of current MS based applications onto the Mac platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing, developing and testing of new software products as well as supporting existing, released products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be working closely with other members of the development staff to extend the core functionality, to power new products and take existing products to the next level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Potentially porting MAC client to mobile platforms (iPhone, Android, and others)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science/Computer Engineering or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of development experience on the Mac platform, using Cocoa and/or Carbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with Mac OS X internals (file handling, memory management, http communications, TCP, Cocoa Framework, Foundation)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in Macintosh development tools XCode 3 and later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled objected-oriented analysis, design and implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to complete code with minimum supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A track record of delivering quality bug free code on schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferable Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-side HTTP proxies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML, XML, JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Virtual private networks, SSL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-side privacy and/or security management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web content parsing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS / mobile development work to develop applications for iPhone and iPad, Android, and other mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation and Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent employee stock option plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation assistance available&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free food and drinks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foosball, Small gym and showers, Pool table, Table Tennis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FREE Medical, Dental and Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easy Access to Caltrain and Light Rail (free pass)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Laptop and Monitor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee discounts on HP, Apple and Verizon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About AnchorFree:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AnchorFree enables millions of users with security, privacy, and freedom. AnchorFree’s Hotspot Shield is the world’s most popular consumer VPN (virtual private network).  It has taken off through a grass roots movement of Internet users interested in a free and simply way to stay secure and private online. AnchorFree provides free privacy protection and secure encrypted browsing for main stream consumers.  In regions where many sites are censored; AnchorFree enables access to all sites, democratizing the Internet, and proliferating freedom of information.   Millions of users in emerging regions use AnchorFree as an enabler to get to Google, Facebook, YouTube, Skype and many other sites/services that are censored.  AnchorFree enables users with secure and private browsers across computers, laptops, phones and tablets.  AnchorFree’s Hotspot Shield has been downloaded more than 60 million times, and is addressing a market of 1.5 billion internet users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to driving positive revenue and user growth, AnchorFree is making a major impact on the world by enabling access to all information online, breaking down borders, and proliferating user privacy.  The AnchorFree founders won the INC Magazine 30 Under 30 Award in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/osx-and-ios-developer-anchorfree-inc-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/osx-and-ios-developer-anchorfree-inc-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at UberConference in Pleasanton, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ÜberConference took home first prize in the Battlefield competition at TechCrunch Distrupt. A free audio conferencing service with a visual interface, ÜberConference solves the most common problems faced in teleconferencing including making a conference easy to join, knowing who is participating, knowing who is speaking, and making advanced features easy to use. Recent updates include Evernote integration, instant conferences and in-conference chat. ÜberConference is available on the web, with mobile versions coming soon. (This is where you come in)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write gorgeous and optimized code for the iOS platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect, build, iterate and manage our set of mobile applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner closely with our design team to produce an application that flows seamlessly and works intuitively with our users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our mobile team is fairly small and self-directed so each person is responsible for at least one critical part of a project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particulars of experience are not as important to us as generally being a smart person. Smart people learn quickly so use the bullet points below as a guideline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience releasing at least one application into the App Store.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building applications in memory- and network-constrained scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency with Objective-C and Cocoa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cutting-edge iOS technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong framework outside of iOS is always a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ÜberConference is working on the future of communications and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for great people to join us. We&amp;rsquo;re a small team, obsessed with elegant design and efficient solutions to big problems. Our office is fast-paced, loud and crazy. We like making things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% paid Medical, Dental and Vision Plan for you and your dependents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday Weekly Socials and a Company Game Room complete with a game consoles, a ping pong and a beer pong table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cell Phone, Home Internet and Gym reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free healthy as well as unhealthy snacks and drinks are available in the kitchen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose your setup (monitor, laptop, mouse, keyboard etc…)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iPad for all new employees and your very own company jacket!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-uberconference-pleasanton-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-uberconference-pleasanton-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>