<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web/Mobile Developer at Cashcall in Anaheim, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CashCall’s Mortgage Division, a growing Mortgage lending company in Anaheim, is currently seeking Senior Web/Mobile Designer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this role, you’ll formulate concepts and work with Design, Product, and Engineering teams to bring these websites or features to production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With strong attention to detail and a savvy knowledge of web standards, trends and usability, you’ll help us improve our overall user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect, Design and Support new interfaces/experiences with other Cash Call online and mobile entities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work in a team environment, and follow brand guidelines and take design direction with positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide continuous competitive research, leverage industry resources and market trends and liaise with marketing and business stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the user experience optimization of all existing online properties, mobile, email, social media, and other new technology, using business analytics and company initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with QC and usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirement:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing and building products and features on mobile and web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for people-centered design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML/CSS knowledge including a familiarity of Frameworks, Grids, and Responsive Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert UI/UX Design skills and understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to stay current with web trends and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to support a project from concept to wire-frames to rapid prototyping in HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication, interpersonal, multitasking and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to solve problems and meet deadlines with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to analyze statistics and understand online funnel and conversion reports, in order to identify opportunities to improve user experience and conversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated and organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Javascript and the jQuery frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of CSS preprocessors like SASS and LESS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Git and Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to create a strong visual identity and document it accordingly to facilitate design guidelines to other offices around the world, while being sensitive about the differences between cultures and mental models.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and able to work independently but within a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in UI/UX Design and strong knowledge of current web standards, technologies, and trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years front-end development experience using HTML/CSS/JS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in computer science or mortgage lending experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-mobile-developer-cashcall-anaheim-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-mobile-developer-cashcall-anaheim-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Lead/ Manager- Android at Trulia in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Engineering gets respect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use the phrase &amp;lsquo;we&amp;rsquo;re a tech company that does Real Estate&amp;rsquo; to emphasize how important engineering is to the company.  Engineering is the department that drives our apps, tools, data, and interfaces forward. This attitude comes not only from the Engineers, but from our CEO and other top management. They believe in us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have awesome problems to solve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The housing market provides a fantastic blend of problems.  We need creative people to help us combine the data about every address in America with the soft side of helping people find a home that makes them feel safe, happy, and comfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stability is wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re that rare company that holds the culture of its startup roots, while blending in the sanity of a regular work schedule with an emphasis on work/life/family balance. It’s like this because we worked hard to make it this way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you’ll work on:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll be technical lead of the team responsible for all of Trulia’s Android application development. This includes top rated phone and tablet apps in the main Google app store and even a few apps for Kindle. These apps are used by millions of consumers and real estate professionals each day, so the work you do will have huge impact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll contribute to Trulia’s awesome, employee-centric team, managing the team of developers who work on the core android experience, and mentoring developers across all teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll join forces with other engineering leads to achieve great things, including coordination projects across all display methods, bottom-up performance changes, enumerating and prioritizing engineering goals, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Who are you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have senior level technical chops, working in a professional coding environment for over five years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve been working directly with Android for at least 3 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You understand how to manage several apps that are always in progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve demonstrated success innovating with Engineering, Product and Design teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy motivating and mentoring talented engineers, helping them navigate tough tradeoffs between functionality, complexity and time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You live to break down and solving complex problems by creating practical, maintainable, and scalable solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re a great person that willingly collaborates, listens, and cares about treating people fairly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your work commands a top ranking in the app stores&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll work with:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We currently have 3 apps in Google Play and 2 for Kindle Fire. We use the standard Android framework with ActionBarSherlock and Android support library for UI consistency and device accessibility. We start with great user experience, ensure app stability, and focus on performance and code readability. We use ANT with Jenkins for our continuous integration. We release frequently and are working with Robolectric and Android uiautomator for testing. We use Git, and are nurturing a code review culture. We are always looking for new performance tools and optimization techniques to enhance our apps. If there&amp;rsquo;s something that&amp;rsquo;s a good idea for the team, we&amp;rsquo;ll do our best to implement it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How we work:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The engineering team is about a hundred people, and we break into small teams of 2-4 to focus on specific projects.  We release often, with new features always under development and a strong focus on user experience. Our local QA team writes automation tests and does hand testing of your features, working with you to ensure that only high quality code gets to production. Organizationally, we&amp;rsquo;re pretty flat, though you&amp;rsquo;ll have a mentor with whom you&amp;rsquo;ll have weekly 1-on-1 meetings, to review code, exchange ideas, and ensure we&amp;rsquo;re doing everything we can for you to thrive in your role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;lsquo;Innovation Week&amp;rsquo; every quarter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;People you&amp;rsquo;re happy to see every day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocked Kitchens and two kegerators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penthouse roof deck&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All IDEs welcome&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aeron chairs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to work directly with large OEMs and Google developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great benefits (untracked time off, variety of health plans, 401k match)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-lead-manager-android-trulia-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-lead-manager-android-trulia-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Engineering - iOS at Flinja in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Flinja.com is a website dedicated to connecting students and alumni through jobs.  Flinja provides students and alumni in their college network a safe place to hire each other through a secure third-party payment system. On Flinja, both students and alumni can post a service, write and read reviews on each other, and create a work profile for the world to see. Hiring parties can hire vetted students from specific universities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Distill the service experience for both our users and our Flinja&amp;rsquo;s into something effortless, responsive and accessible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement flows and mockups as provided by the UX and design teams, while intelligently and creatively “filling in the gaps” not necessarily covered by rough prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze usage patterns, funnels and economic metrics to produce the perfect product for all of our users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience shipping one or more Objective-C native iOS apps, ideally currently available on the App Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong CS fundamentals gained through Bachelor’s degree in CS, Math or related discipline or equivalent industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal projects that show an aptitude for engineering and product sense&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in areas outside of their usual comfort zone and get things done quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using Ruby-on-Rails in a production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience scaling high traffic websites (architecture/database/memcache/CDN)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with server administration and Amazon Web Services (EC2/S3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salaries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vacation days &amp;amp; time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental, &amp;amp; vision insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life &amp;amp; disability coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company dinners &amp;amp; happy hour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Much more&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;HIGHLY RECOMMEND REGISTERING on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flinja.com&quot;&gt;http://www.flinja.com&lt;/a&gt; and posting a service to understand how the site functions. Questions will be asked during the interview process that pertain to this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flinja FB page shown here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.facebook.com/theflinja?fref=ts&quot;&gt;http://www.facebook.com/theflinja?fref=ts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/engineering-ios-flinja-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/engineering-ios-flinja-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Grubwithus in Venice, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Grubwithus is revolutionizing our social networks, taking our online relationships offline. Created by two-friends who wanted to ease the post-college friend-making process, Grubwithus is a site that allows users to meet awesome people over tasting menus at top restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join what Paul Graham and WIRED have called “A square on the periodic table – a company that seems almost organically preordained, like Twitter and Facebook.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;iOS DEVELOPER POSITION&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building iOS applications (please provide links to apps in the App Store that you have worked on)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building an iOS app that has a server API it needs to communicate with&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of computer science fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Good to Haves&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good UI / UX skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with testing iOS apps (automated tests as well as process for beta testing with users)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-grubwithus-venice-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-grubwithus-venice-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Android Developer at Skout in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;SKOUT is an exciting, Andreessen Horowitz funded start-up company. We are a location-based social networking start-up and the leader in people discovery. Our mobile applications help our millions of users meet others in their immediate vicinity. We are a small company delivering big things and are looking for great people to help define the future of our company and the industry. We are building the future platform for meeting new people and discovering what’s going on around you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skout is seeking a Senior Android developer to join our mobile team in San Francisco and help shape the future of our Android applications. You will work within a small team, being part of the full product cycle making decisions and building software that changes the way millions of people use their mobile. The ideal candidate will be comfortable in a fluid start-up environment and will bring an energetic, fun and creative approach to their work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute best-in-class programming skills to develop highly innovative, maintainable Android code to be installed on millions of devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually offer thought-leadership and dependable execution ability in a high-paced environment characterized by ongoing iteration and product pushes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a key role in backend development, troubleshoot and help shape the architecture of new features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recent Android development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience building fast growing web or mobile products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience utilizing Android frameworks to help create user interfaces that are fast and intuitive to use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the Android market place and app device/OS compatibility on Android.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with mobile advertising and 3rd party SDK integration is a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS or MS in Computer Science or related field preferred, top-tier schools preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using version control repositories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with agile/scrum development process and code reviews.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-android-developer-skout-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-android-developer-skout-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead Android Developer at Jawbone in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Jawbone currently seeks an experienced and highly creative Mobile Software Developer with a strong background in delivering unique solutions with at least one of the dominant mobile platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be thinking, what will a software developer like me do at a company like Jawbone…they build headsets? Simply put &amp;ndash; you will be instrumental in shaping the next phase of mobile communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be working in a highly collaborative environment, with our world-class engineering team. You will design, implement and deploy the infrastructure components at the heart of Jawbone&amp;rsquo;s software services. “Good enough” is simply not in Jawbone&amp;rsquo;s DNA as we are maniacally focused on creating products that just work. Read no further if you do not have a passion for creating products that delight consumers because they are functionally sublime, not to mention aesthetically beautiful. You only live once so make it count for something special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and implement mobile applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide and adhere to best-practices for mobile application development, develop/maintain mobile applications, tools, and re-usable components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather functional requirements to generate technical design specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in self-starting side projects contributing to Jawbone’s product offerings and growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of total development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years of experience developing mobile applications for Android, Blackberry, and/or iPhone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of Object Oriented programming and data structures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing code for multitasking operating systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of end-to-end SW development tool chains and environments for the different Mobile Application Development environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Desired Skills and Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and organizational skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and problem solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with disciplined software release build/deploy processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple overlapping projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently with minimal supervision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated by continuous learning and development, dedicated to delivering exceptional solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Travel may be required for this position but is held to the minimum possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more than a decade, Jawbone has developed human-centered wearable technology and audio devices unparalleled in their technical innovation, ease-of-use and sophistication of design. A 2010 IDSA Design of the Decade winner, the company is the creator of the award-winning and best-selling Jawbone ERA and ICON Bluetooth® headsets; NoiseAssassin® technology, the world&amp;rsquo;s first and only military-grade noise-eliminating technology; and the JAMBOX and BIG JAMBOX wireless speakers and speakerphones. Jawbone’s approach to lifestyle tracking is unique, with over 110 patents filed related to UP and its wearable technology manufacturing processes. Jawbone is privately held and headquartered in San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jawbone is an equal opportunity employer, offers an exciting opportunity for qualified career-motivated professionals. We provide competitive compensation, stock options and the chance to work with talented people in a winning, successful, and pleasant environment. We offer many premium benefits including 401(k), medical, dental, life insurance, Paid Time Off and much more&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-android-developer-jawbone-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-android-developer-jawbone-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior iOS Developer at Skout in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;SKOUT is an exciting, Andreessen Horowitz funded start-up company. We are a location-based social networking start-up and the leader in people discovery. Our mobile applications help our millions of users meet others in their immediate vicinity. We are a small company delivering big things and are looking for great people to help define the future of our company and the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are building the future platform for meeting new people and discovering what’s going on around you.Skout is seeking an iOS developer to join our mobile team and help shape the future of our iOS applications. You will work within our small iOS team, being part of the full product cycle making decisions and building software that changes the way millions of people use their mobile. The ideal candidate will be comfortable in a fluid start-up environment and will bring an energetic, fun and creative approach to their work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute best-in-class programming skills to develop highly innovative, maintainable iOS code to be installed on millions of devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually offer thought-leadership and dependable execution ability in a high-paced. environment characterized by ongoing iteration and product pushes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take responsibility of architecting reusable code and libraries for our iOS applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recent iOS development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience building fast growing web or mobile products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Cocoa/UIKit frameworks and the iPhone SDK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience submitting application in iTunes connect with previous approved products in iTunes App Store.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable in a small, intense and high-growth start-up environment is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS or MS in Computer Science or related field preferred, top-tier schools preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using version control repositories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with agile/scrum development process and code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-skout-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-skout-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at Jawbone in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Jawbone currently seeks an experienced and highly creative Mobile Software Developer with a strong background in delivering unique solutions with at least one of the dominant mobile platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be thinking, what will a software developer like me do at a company like Jawbone…they build headsets? Simply put &amp;ndash; you will be instrumental in shaping the next phase of mobile communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be working in a highly collaborative environment, with our world-class engineering team. You will design, implement and deploy the infrastructure components at the heart of Jawbone&amp;rsquo;s software services. “Good enough” is simply not in Jawbone&amp;rsquo;s DNA as we are maniacally focused on creating products that just work. Read no further if you do not have a passion for creating products that delight consumers because they are functionally sublime, not to mention aesthetically beautiful. You only live once so make it count for something special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and implement mobile applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide and adhere to best-practices for mobile application development, develop/maintain mobile applications, tools, and re-usable components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather functional requirements to generate technical design specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in self-starting side projects contributing to Jawbone’s product offerings and growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of total development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years of experience developing mobile applications for Android, Blackberry, and/or iPhone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of Object Oriented programming and data structures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing code for multitasking operating systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of end-to-end SW development tool chains and environments for the different Mobile Application Development environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Desired Skills and Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and organizational skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and problem solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with disciplined software release build/deploy processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple overlapping projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently with minimal supervision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated by continuous learning and development, dedicated to delivering exceptional solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Travel may be required for this position but is held to the minimum possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more than a decade, Jawbone has developed human-centered wearable technology and audio devices unparalleled in their technical innovation, ease-of-use and sophistication of design. A 2010 IDSA Design of the Decade winner, the company is the creator of the award-winning and best-selling Jawbone ERA and ICON Bluetooth® headsets; NoiseAssassin® technology, the world&amp;rsquo;s first and only military-grade noise-eliminating technology; and the JAMBOX and BIG JAMBOX wireless speakers and speakerphones. Jawbone’s approach to lifestyle tracking is unique, with over 110 patents filed related to UP and its wearable technology manufacturing processes. Jawbone is privately held and headquartered in San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jawbone is an equal opportunity employer, offers an exciting opportunity for qualified career-motivated professionals. We provide competitive compensation, stock options and the chance to work with talented people in a winning, successful, and pleasant environment. We offer many premium benefits including 401(k), medical, dental, life insurance, Paid Time Off and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-jawbone-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-jawbone-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at Grubwithus in Venice, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Grubwithus is revolutionizing our social networks, taking our online relationships offline. Created by two-friends who wanted to ease the post-college friend-making process, Grubwithus is a site that allows users to meet awesome people over tasting menus at top restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join what Paul Graham and WIRED have called “A square on the periodic table – a company that seems almost organically preordained, like Twitter and Facebook.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ANDROID DEVELOPER POSITION&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building Android applications (please provide links to apps in the App Store that you have worked on)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building an Android app that has a server API it needs to communicate with&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of computer science fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Good to Haves&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good UI / UX skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with testing Android apps (automated tests as well as process for beta testing with users)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-grubwithus-venice-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-grubwithus-venice-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Web Developer at Moovweb in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Moovweb offers products and services that help our customers quickly take advantage of the mobile revolution. Our cloud-based platform offers the flexibility and power to deliver incredible mobile customer experiences while at the same time leveraging existing web investments. Super fast design and delivery. No expensive recoding. No synchronization headaches. No scaling issues. The Moovweb platform has served billions of mobile page views for an amazing set of customers. We power mobile websites, apps, and tablet solutions for Walmart, Macy&amp;rsquo;s, Under Armour, Sharpie, 1-800-FLOWERS.COM, Chico&amp;rsquo;s, Ross-Simons, John Deere, Cox Communications, The American Cancer Society, Lending Tree, Accenture, TicketWeb, Vitacost, Golfsmith and dozens of other businesses. We&amp;rsquo;re based in San Francisco, are profitable and growing fast. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.moovweb.com/&quot;&gt;http://www.moovweb.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is part of the Technical Services group, which is responsible for working directly with clients to adapt their existing desktop websites for the mobile, tablet, and app form factors. The Mobile Web Developer rapidly builds and launches client websites across a variety of verticals and industries. Working in a small, high octane group with some of the best and most experienced web developers out there, this role requires a combination of web development, design, and time and client management skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master the features, functionality, and best practices of the Moovweb platform and web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with our clients to create mobile versions of their desktop websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively manage multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate activities with internal Engineering and Operations teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively contribute to our group knowledge base&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well versed in HTML, CSS, and web standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript, AJAX, and DOM scripting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled at debugging web pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good design sensibilities and awareness of UX best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux command line&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby or Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git or other version control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SCSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XPath&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with external clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS or Android development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object-oriented programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer Science degree or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-developer-moovweb-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-developer-moovweb-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>