<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at GREE in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The GREE Game Studio develops AAA games for the iOS and Android platforms.  The Studio builds games natively using the advantages of each operating system. To date, the Studio’s published titles have all been in iTunes top 10 Free-to-Play apps (both in terms of downloads and revenue).  Our game portfolio includes:  Crime City, Modern War, Kingdom of Age, and Zombie Jombie.  We have many new games in production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Job:  iOS Developer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Studio builds addictive games, enjoyed by millions.  Our games push iOS devices to their limits, squeezing every drop out of memory and performance.  Our developers support stunning graphics and are required to innovate intelligent solutions to complex engineering challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code in Objective-C primarily and develop features that uses the iPhone SDK, such as in-app purchase and animations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and implement scalable, reliable, and maintainable technologies for our gaming platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate closely with engineering, product, graphics, and game design teams to define our next generation games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated fluency in a compiled language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Objective-C, ideally through some commercial experience (Mac OS X and/or iPhone), a university course, or independent iPhone application development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Objective-C or cocos2d is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;WORKING ENVIRONMENT PERKS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Convenient to public transportation, across from ATT Ballpark (SOMA)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subsided commuter/parking support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macbook Pros, 27'&amp;lsquo; Monitors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health, Dental and Vision coverage with top providers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snacked-filled kitchen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free catered lunches and dinners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smartphone or Tablet reimbursement program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Japanese language lessons&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted gym memberships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-gree-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-gree-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior iOS Developer at HireUp in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Lead iOS development position building a card loyalty program from the ground up. Opportunity to work for a public company on a small team in a satellite office with a casual start-up environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualified candidates will have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One or more native apps published on the App Store
Passion for mobile development and user experience design
Respect for the iOS HIG (unless you have a better solution)
Solid knowledge of recent iOS additions (and deprecations)
Comfort in working fast with a small team with a lot of responsibility
Desire to grow your skills and acquire new ones&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Employee Type:  Full-Time Employee
Experience Required:    0 Years
Degree Required:    Not Specified
Travel Required:    Not Specified&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Detailed Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;N/A&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum Pay:    Not Specified
Average Bonus:  Not Specified
Average Commission:     Not Specified
Other Compensation:     Not Specified&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-hireup-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-hireup-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>OSX and iOS Developer at AnchorFree Inc in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a strong Mac OS X developer, with experience in Cocoa and new features of Leopard and Snow Leopard. The candidate should have proficiency with Mac OS X development internals, multi-threaded programming, networking programming and some Socket programming experience. Should be able to Debug and Profile a Cocoa application. Experience with background process development such as Launch Agent daemons is a plus.  Experience working with VPN clients is a strong plus. In this role you will work in the client side team and provide your expertise in developing next generation client for our famous product Hotspot Shield.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be tasked with helping formulate our technology presence on the Mac platforms as well as the migration and integration of current MS based applications onto the Mac platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing, developing and testing of new software products as well as supporting existing, released products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be working closely with other members of the development staff to extend the core functionality, to power new products and take existing products to the next level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Potentially porting MAC client to mobile platforms (iPhone, Android, and others)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science/Computer Engineering or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of development experience on the Mac platform, using Cocoa and/or Carbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with Mac OS X internals (file handling, memory management, http communications, TCP, Cocoa Framework, Foundation)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in Macintosh development tools XCode 3 and later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled objected-oriented analysis, design and implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to complete code with minimum supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A track record of delivering quality bug free code on schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferable Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-side HTTP proxies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML, XML, JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Virtual private networks, SSL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-side privacy and/or security management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web content parsing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS / mobile development work to develop applications for iPhone and iPad, Android, and other mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation and Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent employee stock option plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation assistance available&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free food and drinks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foosball, Small gym and showers, Pool table, Table Tennis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FREE Medical, Dental and Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easy Access to Caltrain and Light Rail (free pass)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Laptop and Monitor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee discounts on HP, Apple and Verizon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About AnchorFree:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AnchorFree enables millions of users with security, privacy, and freedom. AnchorFree’s Hotspot Shield is the world’s most popular consumer VPN (virtual private network).  It has taken off through a grass roots movement of Internet users interested in a free and simply way to stay secure and private online. AnchorFree provides free privacy protection and secure encrypted browsing for main stream consumers.  In regions where many sites are censored; AnchorFree enables access to all sites, democratizing the Internet, and proliferating freedom of information.   Millions of users in emerging regions use AnchorFree as an enabler to get to Google, Facebook, YouTube, Skype and many other sites/services that are censored.  AnchorFree enables users with secure and private browsers across computers, laptops, phones and tablets.  AnchorFree’s Hotspot Shield has been downloaded more than 60 million times, and is addressing a market of 1.5 billion internet users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to driving positive revenue and user growth, AnchorFree is making a major impact on the world by enabling access to all information online, breaking down borders, and proliferating user privacy.  The AnchorFree founders won the INC Magazine 30 Under 30 Award in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/osx-and-ios-developer-anchorfree-inc-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/osx-and-ios-developer-anchorfree-inc-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at UberConference in Pleasanton, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ÜberConference took home first prize in the Battlefield competition at TechCrunch Distrupt. A free audio conferencing service with a visual interface, ÜberConference solves the most common problems faced in teleconferencing including making a conference easy to join, knowing who is participating, knowing who is speaking, and making advanced features easy to use. Recent updates include Evernote integration, instant conferences and in-conference chat. ÜberConference is available on the web, with mobile versions coming soon. (This is where you come in)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write gorgeous and optimized code for the iOS platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect, build, iterate and manage our set of mobile applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner closely with our design team to produce an application that flows seamlessly and works intuitively with our users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our mobile team is fairly small and self-directed so each person is responsible for at least one critical part of a project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particulars of experience are not as important to us as generally being a smart person. Smart people learn quickly so use the bullet points below as a guideline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience releasing at least one application into the App Store.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building applications in memory- and network-constrained scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency with Objective-C and Cocoa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cutting-edge iOS technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong framework outside of iOS is always a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ÜberConference is working on the future of communications and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for great people to join us. We&amp;rsquo;re a small team, obsessed with elegant design and efficient solutions to big problems. Our office is fast-paced, loud and crazy. We like making things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% paid Medical, Dental and Vision Plan for you and your dependents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday Weekly Socials and a Company Game Room complete with a game consoles, a ping pong and a beer pong table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cell Phone, Home Internet and Gym reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free healthy as well as unhealthy snacks and drinks are available in the kitchen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose your setup (monitor, laptop, mouse, keyboard etc…)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iPad for all new employees and your very own company jacket!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-uberconference-pleasanton-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-uberconference-pleasanton-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS App Compatibility QA at Apple in Santa Clara Valley, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, great ideas have a way of becoming great products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there&amp;rsquo;s no telling what you could accomplish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a great position where you can delve into the intricate details of virtually every aspect of iOS and could make a significant impact on an amazing product at the same time. The iOS Binary Compatibility team is looking for a curious, tenacious individual with great debugging, analytical, and development skills. Your primary responsibility is to ensure that 3rd party applications for the iPad, iPhone and iPod Touch continue to work with future releases of iOS. You will do this with engineering tools, creating processes and debugging issues in 3rd party apps and related frameworks. This position is cross-functional in nature. You will be working with a wide range of teams including software engineering, developer relations and developer tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Root cause analysis of issues found in existing and future releases of iOS software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop new and improve existing debugging tools and processes * Identify areas suitable for automation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide assistance and feedback to cross-functional teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become an iOS expert with a breadth of understanding of many frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C, Objective-C or C++ programming skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of at least one debugging tools (gdb, lldb, Visual Studio debugger, valgrind, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Breadth of knowledge in technical areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability and desire to quickly understand new frameworks and APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development experience with Cocoa, or at least one of Win32, Java, and Macintosh Toolbox/Carbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the iOS or MacOS SDKs, especially the Objective-C runtime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Apple toolchain, including Xcode, gdb, lldb and dtrace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with performance analysis a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS app development with apps on the AppStore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-app-compatibility-qa-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-app-compatibility-qa-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at M.ploy Ventures in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You will be working within a small and tightly focused team of experts, and while expectations are big, the egos are not. This is a company of technology and game enthusiasts; we all love what we do, take pride in our work, and have a good time while doing it. You should feel similarly and expect nothing less from your position at Blue Shell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own our Android technology stack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help us create great UI for strategy and simulation games on touch devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with top-notch visual and game designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expect a custom, high-performance backend purpose built for your client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grow into greater responsibility as the company expands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;We believe:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Less is better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Android devices are a platform like no other.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion is a competitive advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Preference given to candidates with relevant shipped products, ideally games. Demos, code samples or even gameplay videos are always appreciated and count for a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time position at our office in SOMA, San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-m-ploy-ventures-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-m-ploy-ventures-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior iOS Developer at Rovi Corporation in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Rovi, we connect people to the entertainment they love. Our products and services power some of the most iconic entertainment and technology brands around the world including Comcast, Samsung, iTunes and Pandora. Rovi is headquartered in Santa Clara, California with over 1,800 employees worldwide working to create a better entertainment experience. To learn more, watch The Rovi Story&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rovi Corporation is a global B2B leader focused on revolutionizing the digital entertainment landscape by delivering software and data solutions to connect people to the movies, music and television they enjoy – anytime, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;130 million viewers use our interactive program guide technologies through cable and satellite service provider offerings. Customers include: Comcast, Cox, Charter, Time Warner Cable, AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approximately 220 million consumer electronic (CE) devices use our CE-guide technologies including products by: Dell, LG, Motorola, Panasonic, Philips, Pioneer, RCA, Samsung, Siemens, and Sony&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rovi has information on over 3.6 million TV shows, 28 million tracks and 500,000 movie titles. Metadata customers include: Spotify, Shazaam, MOG, iTunes and Google.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rovi’s Cloud services are revolutionizing the consumer electronics industry and service providers space by helping them drive sales and consumption with advanced media search and discovery capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rovi Advertising Network reaches more than 40 million households globally and offers advertisers a platform to serve targeted interactive advertisements with high levels of engagement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SideReel team is building the best online experience in the world of television and video. We’re a highly collaborative team—the developers drive the architecture. We handle over a million users a day, deal with big data, and solve cool problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SideReel is looking for a developer to lead the expansion of our mobile applications. You should love working in a fast-paced agile environment and have a passion for TV and entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You would be responsible for&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading the development of our iOS mobile apps both as a technical lead and as a mentor to junior developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with the product owner and designers to flesh out user stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You should&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know the ins and outs of iOS development, at least 3 years experience developing mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have developed and shipped an iOS app from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience implementing user stories in a fast-paced agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be excited to be the tech lead of a small mobile development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You are especially intriguing if you&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have developed applications for iPad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have developed applications that stream video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy bacon or Fakin' Bacon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-rovi-corporation-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-rovi-corporation-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Software Eng, App Compatibility at Apple in Santa Clara Valley, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, great ideas have a way of becoming great products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there&amp;rsquo;s no telling what you could accomplish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a great position where you can delve into the intricate details of virtually every aspect of iOS and could make a significant impact on an amazing product at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iOS Binary Compatibility team is looking for a curious, tenacious individual with great debugging, analytical, and development skills. Your primary responsibility is to ensure that 3rd party applications for the iPad, iPhone and iPod Touch continue to work with future releases of iOS. You will do this with engineering tools, creating processes and debugging issues in 3rd party apps and related frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is cross-functional in nature. You will be working with a wide range of teams including software engineering, developer relations and developer tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Root cause analysis of issues found in existing and future releases of iOS software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop new and improve existing debugging tools and processes * Identify areas suitable for automation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide assistance and feedback to cross-functional teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become an iOS expert with a breadth of understanding of many frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C, Objective-C or C++ programming skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of at least one debugging tools (gdb, lldb, Visual Studio debugger, valgrind, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Breadth of knowledge in technical areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability and desire to quickly understand new frameworks and APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development experience with Cocoa, or at least one of Win32, Java, and Macintosh Toolbox/Carbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the iOS or MacOS SDKs, especially the Objective-C runtime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Apple toolchain, including Xcode, gdb, lldb and dtrace * Experience with performance analysis a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS app development with apps on the AppStore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-software-eng-app-compatibility-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-software-eng-app-compatibility-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior iOS Developer at Abbott/Adams, Inc in San Jose, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;RiteSite does not check this information for accuracy or for consistency with the posting below. We require and convey it so that you can check. We recommend that you always investigate and exercise caution regarding all employment activity on the Internet and elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client, a leader in their industry, is seeking a Senior iOS Developer in CA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in design activity, and implement flows and mockups as requested by the UX design team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze usage patterns, feedback and business metrics to produce the perfect product for all of our users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience shipping one or more Objective-C native iOS apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree in CS, Math or related discipline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of MVC, OOP, memory management and threading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with XML, JSON and REST-based APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UX design experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with server administration and web services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This is an outstanding direct hire opportunity offering excellent pay and benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-abbott-adams-inc-san-jose-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-abbott-adams-inc-san-jose-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at Trailer Park in Hollywood, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Trailer Park&amp;rsquo;s Mobile division is on the cutting-edge of creating interactive experiences on mobile devices. We concept, design and develop mobile websites, mobile applications and mobile marketing campaigns for movie studios, television networks and brands. We are looking for a passionate, hard-working, and talented Android developer to develop applications for phones, tablets and Google TV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and code using best practices for Android applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with QA to ensure outstanding products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate with existing modules and work with external APIs to manage data handling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with 3rd party APIs such as Facebook, Twitter, Linkedin, and others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with User Interface Designers to optimize usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with deployment team to deliver applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Android SDK, JSON , XML, and RESTful services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of OOP techniques and Design Patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with front-end technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building production software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio of previous Apps in the Android marketplace a MUST!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating mobile apps with web services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge/Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have excellent communication skills, both verbal and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works collaboratively and proactively on multi-functional teams. Open to feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently communicates using appropriate methods for the situation and audience in a clear, concise and professional manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Remarks:  Management has the right to add or change duties and job requirements at any time.  In addition, the employer may consider whether the individual applying for or holding the position is qualified.  There are two steps involved in this determination.  The first concern whether the applicant or current employee satisfies the prerequisites for the position.  The second step involves whether or not the person can perform the essential job functions with or without reasonable accommodation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-trailer-park-hollywood-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-trailer-park-hollywood-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>