<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Apple in Santa Clara Valley, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Apple is looking for an experienced iOS developer with a passion for delivering great new apps iPhone and iPad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong object-oriented programming and design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In depth understanding of Objective-C design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience with UIKit, CoreAnimation, and the iOS SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong UI development skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for quality and attention to interface details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The individual must be self motivated, an excellent problem solver and a fast learner. Very strong technical skills and demonstrated experience in writing commercial grade apps for iOS is a must. The candidate will work with talented engineers in a fast paced, technically demanding environment to deliver new features. &amp;ndash; Experience developing apps driven by XML or JSON web services &amp;ndash; Knowledge of C and C++ &amp;ndash; Experience writing multi-threaded, asynchronous code. GCD experience a plus. &amp;ndash; Strong debugging and performance testing with GDB and Instruments&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in computer science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Mobile Web Developer at Aetna in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This is a rare opportunity to help shape the future of Healthcare and drive innovation throughout Healthcare IT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Web Developer will provide development &amp;amp; technical integration support across web environments in support of marketing &amp;amp; sales initiatives in the emerging Healthcare IT industry. This role will also develop &amp;amp; deliver web solutions designed by top firms across the country for Aetnas Emerging Business division.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidate must have strong leadership, communication and technical skills as well as the ability to work well in a team environment. The ability to handle aggressive timelines is a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recognized as an expert and a leader throughout the IT community. Utilizes in-depth knowledge of the organizations tactical and strategic business objectives, the enterprise technological environment, the organization structure, strategic technological opportunities and requirements. As an individual contributor, this position has no direct line management responsibilities but is a major contributor to the success of mission critical, complex, typically large, often enterprise-wide major architecture projects and innovations. Participates with and provides expert technical consultation to senior IT management strategic planning groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The highest level of education desired for candidates in this position is a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;FUNCTIONAL EXPERIENCES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Functional &amp;ndash; Information Technology/Application development/7-10 Years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technology/Developing Competitive Technology and Architecture/MASTERY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;DESIRED SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technology/Promoting Emerging Technology/ADVANCED&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL JOB INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead web development projects delivering configurable/customizable solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate solution design and assembly based on design provided by UX team(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with marketing, product design &amp;amp; development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the maintenance of product and integrated solution documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other web development teams supporting web product roadmaps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Personal Characteristics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership, communication and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in fast paced cross functional team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated and comfortable making day to day decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a do whatever it takes attitude: delivery first, polish later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Skills Required&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of key web technologies (HTML5, CSS3, PhoneGap, Javascript, JQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JSON, ReST and Web APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with commercial web design and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of scrum processes and agile technical practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with customers to elicit technical requirements and objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Edge, etc) a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Apache Jackrabbit or Adobe CQ a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Degree and Positions Held&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-6 years in web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MS/BS in Computer Science or related field (Masters a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held previous role on web product team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior work in Healthcare industry desirable though not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please note that benefit eligibility may vary by position. Click here to review the benefits associated with this position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aetna does not permit the use of tobacco related products or drugs in the workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-web-developer-aetna-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-web-developer-aetna-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Web Consultant at Moovweb in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This position is part of the Professional Services group responsible for working directly with clients and partners to adapt existing desktop websites for the mobile, tablet, and app form factors. The Mobile Web Consultant rapidly builds and launches client websites and apps across a variety of verticals and industries. Working in a small, high-octane group with some of the best and most experienced mobile web consultants out there, this role requires a combination of web &amp;amp; app development, design, and time &amp;amp; client management skills. Occasional-to-often travel may be required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master the features, functionality, and best practices of the Moovweb mobile platform for web and app development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with our clients and partners to create mobile and app versions of their desktop websites in a rapid fashion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively manage multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather requirements and drive the project plan for on-going software releases and updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with clients' product managers and architects to ensure solutions meet customers' needs and business goals, keeping all parties up to date on progress and any issues that are encountered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate activities with internal Engineering and Operations teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively contribute to our group knowledge base&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-facing, confident, and savvy individual who can represent Moovweb effectively and honorably with our clients' business and technical teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated problem-solving skills with anecdotes from previous work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer Science degree or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable of both Android and iOS development platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in HTML, CSS, and web standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript and AJAX scripting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled at debugging web pages and mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good design sensibilities and awareness of UX best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in or with large system integrators such as TCS, CSC, and Accenture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior assignments as a technical trainer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux command line&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby or Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git version control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SCSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XPath&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object-oriented programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Moovweb&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moovweb is a software company transforming post-PC web development in a radically better model. Our technology is innovative, disruptive and just plain cool. Our cloud-based platform is global, high performance and reliable. Our customers include some of the biggest brands on the planet that rely on us to deliver millions of mobile page views every day. We have patents pending on website virtualization and transformation, two concepts we invented. And our development environment is simple, sophisticated and very powerful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll be joining an elite group of marketers, developers, consultants and sales people who are intensely focused on building a great company. We hire the best and brightest; people that are passionate about collaborating with our customers to deliver something special; something unique. Our people are sharp, dedicated and just plain fun. We’re based in downtown San Francisco and you’ll work from our office with the rest of the team.  We offer competitive salary, generous equity, healthcare, 401(K), lots of food, a computer setup of your choice, and other fun benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-consultant-moovweb-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-consultant-moovweb-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Developer (Android &amp; iOS) at NexGen Poker in Santa Monica, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;NexGen was founded by two serial entrepreneurs that have been very successful in their past startups which were in the web advertising area. Anticipating the law changes in CA to allow online poker and using their experience and numerous contacts they initiated the online poker room idea with an Indian casino partner on the order of 2 years ago. During 2012, the back-end technology for the company was developed by a single person who has extensive experience in the online poker industry. Benefitting from this experience, the current system has been shown to be efficient, fast and scalable to a level that can easily handle the anticipated load of players in CA online poker community ($1B) industry) and eventually a very opportunistic ($35B) global industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;NexGen&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Developer &amp;ndash; Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced architect of mobile and web games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands technology trade-offs for development platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has directed game developers on either mobile or web platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop against a variety of web architectures and services (HTTP, SOAP, REST, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing project within a version control system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have excellent problem solving skills and love technical challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be self-motivated and able to multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Android development experience using cross platform tools. i.e. creating one code base that can be compiled for both Android and iOS on same platform a plus, e.g. use of LiveCode, Marmalade, Corona&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to take initiative to be productive and efficient&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work independently and within a team, depending on the situation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requires hands-on architecting, designing, and coding new features on IOS and/or Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate with team members in design reviews and code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ yrs of development experience in IOS and/or Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ yrs of object oriented design, data structures, design patterns and problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;NexGen Poker Gaming Product Details &amp;ndash; Desktop (PC &amp;amp; Mac), Web &amp;amp; Mobile (Android &amp;amp; iOS)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re developing a legal, regulated online poker system. At this time we have a working core system that can play all the games and is well on its way to being fully compliant with the regulatory requirements that will be in place when legislation passes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The online poker system that will be the focus of our development has several components:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The core set of services that will run all the games and provide the game results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The game play client that will be a downloadable PC program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile versions of the game play client for Web, Android and iOS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The database and back-end reporting capability for company support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company website portal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We currently have demonstrated a complete core system with a demo game play client to our interested parties (regulators and investors). In this demonstration we have shown that not only does the system work, but that it has profound and unique scalability and performance characteristics that will put us in the forefront of being able to provide the top system in this market. We will also be pursuing strategic partnerships to provide this system to other regulated environments both domestic and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-developer-nexgen-poker-santa-monica-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-developer-nexgen-poker-santa-monica-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at FunnelHub in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an iOS developer who is a quick learner, who is passionate for creating exciting and intuitive software. We want someone who would like to push the platform to its limits, with implementation approaches transcending even Apple&amp;rsquo;s first-party apps. We have locations in San Mateo and San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are an exciting well-funded startup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would be working with Design and Product teams to create beautiful interfaces that facilitate what users want to do. You are care about details and believe that a task isn&amp;rsquo;t complete until everything is just right. Caring about users and believing the little things matter is more important than experience, but practice implementing user interfaces and iOS applications is a plus. You know Objective-C and Cocoa Touch well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Objective-C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functional knowledge of the iOS SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examples of iOS applications you wrote, released or unreleased&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with client-server applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Services integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Media integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-funnelhub-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-funnelhub-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Deluxe Entertainment in Burbank, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Deluxe Media is a leading supplier of DVD, Blu-ray, BD Live, and digital distribution post production services, including subtitling and localization, theatrical dubbing services, video compression, encoding, authoring, menu design, bonus content production, audio, and network services. Deluxe Media is a global company with presence in 5 countries. Our clients include the major Hollywood studios as well as a growing number of on-line retailers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iOS Developer will develop iOS applications as part of the mobile application development team. Individual will be responsible for design, implementation, release, and maintenance of applications. Development will include new features and applications for Hollywood movie titles, enhancing and supporting both the connected Blu-ray and electronic distribution experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In many cases, the candidate will be the sole person responsible for the design and development of applications. As such, this requires a level of responsibility to achieve a reliable end product with superb attention to detail and time management skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate must be able to find clever ways to solve problems, design around system limitations, and meet shortened schedules as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capture and/or translate functional requirements into software design documentation as necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and develop applications across iOS devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordination with creative personnel to ensure correct delivery of application resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordination with project management personnel, provide estimates of application development tasks, and on-going development progress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technical Qualifications (iOS)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Objective-C with a track record of deployed apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version control tools and concepts (Subversion preferred).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with media rich applications using image, audio, video, and animation. (Knowledge of AVFoundation, Core Image, and Core Animation a plus.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with 3D graphics and animation, particularly use of Open GL ES 2.0.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with localization of applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with integration of HTTP web services (REST), and XML/JSON document exchanges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Open GL ES 2.0.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Unity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with COCOS2D.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to scale rapidly developed projects into re-usable frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with app store submission process and enterprise distribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS degree or higher in Computer Science and/or Electrical Engineering. Master’s degree preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years software development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate, in both oral and written form, effectively to upper level management and peer engineers internally, and externally to customers with various backgrounds either technical staff or marketing personnel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must learn and process information quickly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to effectively document all processes, designs, and data flows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide technical leadership and support to management, peers, developers, and third parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid troubleshooting, problem solving and analytical skills, and the ability to reach innovative options quickly required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work well under pressure and tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good discipline to meet the requirements for production support and make commitments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexibility to work extended hours and/or weekends to meet project deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re an independent thinker with a high level of ingenuity and the above qualifications, then we&amp;rsquo;d like you to join our team!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NO PHONE CALLS OR DROP OFFS PLEASE. EOE M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-deluxe-entertainment-burbank-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-deluxe-entertainment-burbank-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Accessories Engineering Project Manager at Apple in Santa Clara Valley, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The iOS Accessories group is looking for an Engineering Project Manager (EPM) to lead the design and development of Apple-branded accessories for iPad, iPod and iPhone &amp;ndash; a multi-hundred-million-dollar business that sits alongside the enormous iPad, iPod and iPhone businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The EPM will be responsible for:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining communication within the development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining project schedules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-functional organization, communication, and management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating meetings and documenting action items and progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel to support manufacturing builds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reporting and presenting to senior management on project status and schedules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Engineering Project Manager&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iOS Accessories group is looking for an Engineering Project Manager (EPM) to lead the design and development of Apple-branded accessories for iPad, iPod and iPhone &amp;ndash; a multi-hundred-million-dollar business that sits alongside the enormous iPad, iPod and iPhone businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EPMs are responsible for managing and communicating project definition, development milestones, project schedules, and project status in the development of new products. An EPM must be able to prioritize issues and track the details as well as be in touch with the big picture issues. EPMs must be fearless organizers who are ready to work with the highly skilled hardware, software, mechanical design and industrial design teams to identify and resolve potential risks to the schedule and risks to the quality of the product. Success is defined in terms of the quality and timeliness of the pre-production builds and the start of mass production. EPMs need to have a strong understanding of development and manufacturing processes &amp;ndash; from part design to circuit board manufacturing to production line bring-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for someone who is flexible and can respond quickly, energetically, and enthusiastically to changes. Cross-functional communication skills and experience are essential. The EPM will interact with all engineering design disciplines plus safety, reliability, marketing, packaging, manufacturing, component engineering, and other resources inside and outside Apple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The EPM will be responsible for:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining communication within the development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining project schedules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-functional organization, communication, and management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating meetings and documenting action items and progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel to support manufacturing builds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reporting and presenting to senior management on project status and schedules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Required Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS ME/EE/CE degree or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years in consumer products and/or other product development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of project management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong technical background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong track record of shipping products and managing them through the entire product life cycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with off shore manufacturers and travel to manufacturing sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational and management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, both verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Some international travel is required, approximately 20%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS ME/EE/CE degree or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-accessories-engineering-project-manager-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-accessories-engineering-project-manager-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at AgreeYa Solutions in San Mateo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;AtHoc, a VC-backed company founded in 1999, is the pioneer and recognized market leader in next-generation emergency communications software for the security and safety market. Fundamental to our mission at AtHoc is the development of innovative products used for the critical endeavor of saving lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking dedicated, bright and highly motivated team players who want to make a difference and share in our accomplishments and passion. We provide a culture that encourages different perspectives and new ways of thinking toward a common, aligned goal and shared vision: to bring innovative solutions to market and advance the safety, security, and protection of people and property around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join a principled customer-focused team that is transforming an industry and has earned the trust of hundreds of customers and millions of users within the U.S. military, federal government, homeland security agencies, healthcare, fortune 500 companies and higher education institutions. At AtHoc, we recognize that the talent and drive of our people is a vital key to our continued success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information on AtHoc, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.athoc.com&quot;&gt;http://www.athoc.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Roles and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop new Android app projects and provide ongoing support throughout the product lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create new, exciting features and push code to millions of AtHoc users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your ear to the ground, helping us define and analyze industry best practices and important developments in the mobile space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating documentation for your code and high/low level documentation for various projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working individually and as a team member&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience and Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of the full Android app development lifecycle (Project setup, development, SDK, marketplace distribution, after-submission support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Published and maintained at least one app in the Android marketplace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience targeting devices with a variety of screen sizes (including tablets)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of Android app state management (background + foreground), memory management, multi-threading and security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong MVC/object-oriented programming skills (Encapsulation, Polymorphism, Inheritance)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience of basic data structures such as: linked lists, doubly linked lists, binary trees, arrays, lists, hash tables, and general knowledge about computer science, such as stacks, heaps, operators, and various algorithms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 8 years of programming experience and minimum 2 years of Android application development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/MS in Computer Science or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Personal Competencies/Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sincere passion for mobile devices and emerging technologies with a track record of execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work as part of a highly efficient and organized team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to apply a systematic, disciplined, and analytical approach to problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess a &amp;ldquo;can do&amp;rdquo; attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;AgreeYa’s IT Staffing Services helps businesses rapidly respond to changing requirements and scale to meet changing business and technology demands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AgreeYa Solutions provides high quality staffing services for information technology projects for companies throughout the world; from emerging business ventures to Fortune 500 companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AgreeYa provides the right talent ‐ at the right time – to enable our customers to meet their IT staffing needs. Our service offerings include Temporary Staffing, Contract‐to‐Hire, and Managed Staffing. Our consultants provide the skills and expertise to support Infrastructure Management, Packaged Software Solutions, Custom Application Development, and Product Development efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team screens and interviews all candidates to determine their technical capabilities, the relevance of their experience for a specific role, and cultural fit within our customers' organizations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AgreeYa’s consultants fill all Information Technology roles for our customers, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project Managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business Analysts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical/Functional Consultants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software Developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network Administrators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;System Administrators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database Administrators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Certified Security Professionals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software Testers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trainers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical Writers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AML Compliance Analysts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;AgreeYa’s consultants bring technical skills across all technology platforms and toolsets; from leading edge technologies to legacy systems tools. Our focus is to find the best technologists to help our clients achieve their goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AgreeYa is an equal access/equal opportunity employer and does not discriminate on the basis of age, color, disability, marital status, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, veteran status or any other classification prescribed by applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-agreeya-solutions-san-mateo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-agreeya-solutions-san-mateo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Product Marketing Manager, Web and Mobile Measurement at Quantcast in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Quantcast is looking for an experienced marketer to manage all product marketing activities for Quantcast Measure, Quantcast’s leading audience measurement service and our rapidly expanding mobile offering.  This role reports to the Director of Product Marketing and is responsible for supporting new launches and ongoing product adoption and usage.  Key focus areas include product positioning and packaging, go-to-market strategy, customer communications and industry thought leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as the marketing owner for the launch of new online and mobile measurement features and the ongoing commercialization the Quantcast Measure cross-platform solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with other marketers and cross-functional departments to ensure product communications and launch activities are coordinated and reflect our competitive advantage and benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support Quantcast’s publisher sales team by producing sales presentations, product collateral, case studies and trainings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set and maintain goals and metrics for measuring marketing’s impact on the measurement adoption and communicate results to key stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage ongoing customer communication activities for Quantcast Measure, including in-product messaging and communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze the market and relevant competitive set to ensure the company’s positioning is differentiated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with other marketing functions to inform product related content and relevant POVs throughout industry marketing activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct formal presentations and group discussions on products and trainings to sales, client services and operations teams when necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree required.  MBA, or similar advanced degree is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years experience working in a product marketing capacity and within the digital advertising or mobile space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of audience measurement and the mobile app market and the current industry platforms and leading companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated success in driving and establishing consistent product messaging and packaging across cross-functional teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with launching new digital advertising products and demonstrating impact to sales and/or company goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong informal leadership and project management skills and proven experience leading complex cross-functional projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and writing skills and strong executional judgment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Quantcast&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quantcast measures and organizes the world&amp;rsquo;s audiences in real-time so advertisers can connect with the people who matter most to them. Named one of The 10  San Francisco Tech Companies You Wish You Worked for by Wired, the company is used by the world&amp;rsquo;s leading media agencies, hundreds of major marketers and millions of global web destinations including thousands of the world&amp;rsquo;s best known sites. Quantcast connects the planning, buying, and media fulfillment processes, delivering unparalleled advertising performance at exceptional scale. Launched in 2006, Quantcast is headquartered in San Francisco with offices in New York, London and Ireland and additional satellite offices throughout the US.  With our world-class Engineering team, Quantcast is building one of the largest and most advanced distributed computing systems on the planet handling up to 20 billion real-time transactions per day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-marketing-manager-web-and-mobile-measurement-quantcast-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-marketing-manager-web-and-mobile-measurement-quantcast-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Web Developer at Technosoft Corporation in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile Web developer, HTML Programmer.  Requires experience with mobile web development.  A proven record with writing, debugging, and maintaining HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, CSS3, jQuery &amp;amp; jQueryMobile.  This team member will participate in the full development life cycle including design, development, implementation/integration, maintenance and documentation.  Analyzes, designs, implements and supports web related applications support of company’s internet/intranet strategy. Maintains e-commerce or business-related applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML5, CSS/CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery &amp;amp; jQueryMobile, modernizer.js, Server Platforms (IIS, Apache)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-developer-technosoft-corporation-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-developer-technosoft-corporation-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>