<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Zaarly in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Zaarly is changing how the economy works. That&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;hellip; just a little global economic disruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zaarly enables people to ask for anything from people nearby. A simple idea; but when it takes root in a community, the impact is profound. Buyers decide what they want and the price they want to pay and someone from the community makes it happen, creating a job and keeping money local. Zaarly helps anyone invest directly into their local economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, we’re a tech company, but what we&amp;rsquo;re building helps people change their community.  These are big ideas requiring enormous talent, borderline fanaticism and maybe a small dose of insanity. We&amp;rsquo;ve got an amazing team with the right mix.  Let&amp;rsquo;s do this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re a geek at heart, and you dream in mobile. You download apps from the App Store to dissect them and figure out how they were built. You ache to be part of a startup where your work is front and center. You&amp;rsquo;re tired of working on boring projects that you don&amp;rsquo;t believe in. You&amp;rsquo;re ready to work with a team that is doing something big, something worthwhile, something ridiculously cool. Right on! You&amp;rsquo;re hired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect, build and maintain the Zaarly iPhone app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create new, exciting features and push code to hundreds of thousands of iPhone Zaarly users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up-to-date on the latest iPhone SDK developments, respond to customer feedback &amp;amp; testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing native iPhone apps or other mobile apps is strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Objective-C skills (Ruby and C/C++/ are a plus).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eye for great design and user experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate within a close-knit team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hard-working and a fast learner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have one or more iPhone apps published in the App Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice-to-Have’s:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Startup experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-zaarly-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-zaarly-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at UberConference in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ÜberConference took home first prize in the Battlefield competition at TechCrunch Distrupt. A free audio conferencing service with a visual interface, ÜberConference solves the most common problems faced in teleconferencing including making a conference easy to join, knowing who is participating, knowing who is speaking, and making advanced features easy to use. Recent updates include Evernote integration, instant conferences and in-conference chat. ÜberConference is available on the web, with mobile versions coming soon. (This is where you come in)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write gorgeous and optimized code for the iOS platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect, build, iterate and manage our set of mobile applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner closely with our design team to produce an application that flows seamlessly and works intuitively with our users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our mobile team is fairly small and self-directed so each person is responsible for at least one critical part of a project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particulars of experience are not as important to us as generally being a smart person. Smart people learn quickly so use the bullet points below as a guideline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience releasing at least one application into the App Store.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building applications in memory- and network-constrained scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency with Objective-C and Cocoa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cutting-edge iOS technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong framework outside of iOS is always a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ÜberConference is working on the future of communications and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for great people to join us. We&amp;rsquo;re a small team, obsessed with elegant design and efficient solutions to big problems. Our office is fast-paced, loud and crazy. We like making things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% paid Medical, Dental and Vision Plan for you and your dependents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday Weekly Socials and a Company Game Room complete with a game consoles, a ping pong and a beer pong table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cell Phone, Home Internet and Gym reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free healthy as well as unhealthy snacks and drinks are available in the kitchen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose your setup (monitor, laptop, mouse, keyboard etc…)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iPad for all new employees and your very own company jacket!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-uberconference-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-uberconference-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Grockit in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Grockit is an innovative, venture backed start-up based in San Francisco. Our most recent creation is called Learnist. Our mission: To develop online technologies that revolutionize the current state of education, enabling real-time collaborative learning. We are growing and looking for a Ruby on Rails Developer to join our creative and collaborative team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Some of the things we&amp;rsquo;re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years of iOS development experience using Cocoa/Objective-C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience or Great Curiosity in Agile Development &amp;amp; Lean Start Up Practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examples of brilliance in applications that you&amp;rsquo;ve developed and a trail of successful projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incredible coding skills. Proven experience in profiling, debugging, troubleshooting crashes and memory leaks is a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge and experience with data driven applications and web-based APIs: SOAP, REST, or RSS, and structured data like JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive teammate, able to work closely with your peers and cross-functional teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can-do, hard-working, startup friendly attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-grockit-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-grockit-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at ZehnerGroup in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ZehnerGroup is seeking an iOS Developer to help build a very interesting product. We are looking for someone that can come in and take charge on the app from day one. This will be a 2-month contract. For the right candidate we will have full-time options for Mac app and iPhone/iPad development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Objective-C, Cocoa, ImageKit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with version control systems such as Git/Hg/Svn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of experience in application development and UI programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know well how to write applications to consume RESTful Web Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have worked in at least one real (in-production) application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Django or Rails development is a bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Ability to take ownership&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable collaborating with designers, front-end developers and other team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object-oriented design and development strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web services experiences is a bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Los Angeles / San Francisco candidates are preferred.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energetic team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great benefits package&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free parking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No recruiters please.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About ZehnerGroup&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through strategy, design, and technology innovation ZehnerGroup builds startups and transforms established organizations. Headquartered in Los Angeles, we pride ourselves in clean, usable interfaces backed by scalable technology solutions. By harnessing the power of ZGLabs (Strategy) and ZGInteractive, we offer a complete solution driven by the intersection of business and user goals. Our client list includes some of the most dynamic and successful leaders in their industries. The common thread throughout is an entrepreneurial spirit that pushes boundaries and continually strives for innovation and a competitive advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.zehnergroup.com&quot;&gt;http://www.zehnergroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-zehnergroup-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-zehnergroup-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Developer - Android at Catch in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Catch.com is the leading developer of note-taking and geo-tagging apps in the Google Android Market with over 7 million active installs on Android powered smartphones. Our apps also work on iPad, iPhone, and the web. Catch.com makes it easy to capture and tag notes, places, photos, voice and other information and save it securely online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for someone who has been building user-facing applications (desktop, web, and/or mobile) for at least five years and has been writing Android apps for at least a year. As a startup, we value people who can work on their own to get something done and out the door quickly. But we also want developers who know when to slow down, get input from other people on the team, and make sure that what they&amp;rsquo;re building today will accelerate what we need to do tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You’ll get a gold star and a commemorative calendar if you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know how to implement and use Android Intent-based services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are comfortable with hybrid online/offline designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement background tasks that don’t suck battery life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently query and manage large data sets on mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the Android UI guidelines but aren&amp;rsquo;t limited by them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have something to say about security, both on-device and off-device&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can talk knowledgeably about structured and unstructured data and how people interact with such data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have done work with iOS, Windows Mobile, Blackberry, or other mobile platforms in addition to Android.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In your cover letter, please tell us about one mobile app that you really admire and one thing you think that app should have done differently.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-developer-android-catch-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-developer-android-catch-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Apple in Santa Clara Valley, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Apple is looking for an experienced iOS developer with a passion for delivering great new apps iPhone and iPad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong object-oriented programming and design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In depth understanding of Objective-C design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience with UIKit, CoreAnimation, and the iOS SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong UI development skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for quality and attention to interface details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The individual must be self motivated, an excellent problem solver and a fast learner. Very strong technical skills and demonstrated experience in writing commercial grade apps for iOS is a must. The candidate will work with talented engineers in a fast paced, technically demanding environment to deliver new features. &amp;ndash; Experience developing apps driven by XML or JSON web services &amp;ndash; Knowledge of C and C++ &amp;ndash; Experience writing multi-threaded, asynchronous code. GCD experience a plus. &amp;ndash; Strong debugging and performance testing with GDB and Instruments&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in computer science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-apple-santa-clara-valley-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Mobile Web Developer at Aetna in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This is a rare opportunity to help shape the future of Healthcare and drive innovation throughout Healthcare IT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Web Developer will provide development &amp;amp; technical integration support across web environments in support of marketing &amp;amp; sales initiatives in the emerging Healthcare IT industry. This role will also develop &amp;amp; deliver web solutions designed by top firms across the country for Aetnas Emerging Business division.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidate must have strong leadership, communication and technical skills as well as the ability to work well in a team environment. The ability to handle aggressive timelines is a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recognized as an expert and a leader throughout the IT community. Utilizes in-depth knowledge of the organizations tactical and strategic business objectives, the enterprise technological environment, the organization structure, strategic technological opportunities and requirements. As an individual contributor, this position has no direct line management responsibilities but is a major contributor to the success of mission critical, complex, typically large, often enterprise-wide major architecture projects and innovations. Participates with and provides expert technical consultation to senior IT management strategic planning groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The highest level of education desired for candidates in this position is a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;FUNCTIONAL EXPERIENCES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Functional &amp;ndash; Information Technology/Application development/7-10 Years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technology/Developing Competitive Technology and Architecture/MASTERY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;DESIRED SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technology/Promoting Emerging Technology/ADVANCED&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL JOB INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead web development projects delivering configurable/customizable solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate solution design and assembly based on design provided by UX team(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with marketing, product design &amp;amp; development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the maintenance of product and integrated solution documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other web development teams supporting web product roadmaps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Personal Characteristics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership, communication and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in fast paced cross functional team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated and comfortable making day to day decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a do whatever it takes attitude: delivery first, polish later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Skills Required&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of key web technologies (HTML5, CSS3, PhoneGap, Javascript, JQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JSON, ReST and Web APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with commercial web design and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of scrum processes and agile technical practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with customers to elicit technical requirements and objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Edge, etc) a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Apache Jackrabbit or Adobe CQ a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Degree and Positions Held&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-6 years in web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MS/BS in Computer Science or related field (Masters a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held previous role on web product team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior work in Healthcare industry desirable though not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please note that benefit eligibility may vary by position. Click here to review the benefits associated with this position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aetna does not permit the use of tobacco related products or drugs in the workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-web-developer-aetna-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-web-developer-aetna-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Web Consultant at Moovweb in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This position is part of the Professional Services group responsible for working directly with clients and partners to adapt existing desktop websites for the mobile, tablet, and app form factors. The Mobile Web Consultant rapidly builds and launches client websites and apps across a variety of verticals and industries. Working in a small, high-octane group with some of the best and most experienced mobile web consultants out there, this role requires a combination of web &amp;amp; app development, design, and time &amp;amp; client management skills. Occasional-to-often travel may be required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master the features, functionality, and best practices of the Moovweb mobile platform for web and app development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with our clients and partners to create mobile and app versions of their desktop websites in a rapid fashion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively manage multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather requirements and drive the project plan for on-going software releases and updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with clients' product managers and architects to ensure solutions meet customers' needs and business goals, keeping all parties up to date on progress and any issues that are encountered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate activities with internal Engineering and Operations teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively contribute to our group knowledge base&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-facing, confident, and savvy individual who can represent Moovweb effectively and honorably with our clients' business and technical teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated problem-solving skills with anecdotes from previous work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer Science degree or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable of both Android and iOS development platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in HTML, CSS, and web standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript and AJAX scripting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled at debugging web pages and mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good design sensibilities and awareness of UX best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in or with large system integrators such as TCS, CSC, and Accenture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior assignments as a technical trainer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux command line&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby or Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git version control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SCSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XPath&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object-oriented programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Moovweb&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moovweb is a software company transforming post-PC web development in a radically better model. Our technology is innovative, disruptive and just plain cool. Our cloud-based platform is global, high performance and reliable. Our customers include some of the biggest brands on the planet that rely on us to deliver millions of mobile page views every day. We have patents pending on website virtualization and transformation, two concepts we invented. And our development environment is simple, sophisticated and very powerful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll be joining an elite group of marketers, developers, consultants and sales people who are intensely focused on building a great company. We hire the best and brightest; people that are passionate about collaborating with our customers to deliver something special; something unique. Our people are sharp, dedicated and just plain fun. We’re based in downtown San Francisco and you’ll work from our office with the rest of the team.  We offer competitive salary, generous equity, healthcare, 401(K), lots of food, a computer setup of your choice, and other fun benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-consultant-moovweb-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-consultant-moovweb-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Developer (Android &amp; iOS) at NexGen Poker in Santa Monica, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;NexGen was founded by two serial entrepreneurs that have been very successful in their past startups which were in the web advertising area. Anticipating the law changes in CA to allow online poker and using their experience and numerous contacts they initiated the online poker room idea with an Indian casino partner on the order of 2 years ago. During 2012, the back-end technology for the company was developed by a single person who has extensive experience in the online poker industry. Benefitting from this experience, the current system has been shown to be efficient, fast and scalable to a level that can easily handle the anticipated load of players in CA online poker community ($1B) industry) and eventually a very opportunistic ($35B) global industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;NexGen&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Developer &amp;ndash; Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced architect of mobile and web games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands technology trade-offs for development platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has directed game developers on either mobile or web platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop against a variety of web architectures and services (HTTP, SOAP, REST, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing project within a version control system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have excellent problem solving skills and love technical challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be self-motivated and able to multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Android development experience using cross platform tools. i.e. creating one code base that can be compiled for both Android and iOS on same platform a plus, e.g. use of LiveCode, Marmalade, Corona&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to take initiative to be productive and efficient&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work independently and within a team, depending on the situation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requires hands-on architecting, designing, and coding new features on IOS and/or Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate with team members in design reviews and code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ yrs of development experience in IOS and/or Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ yrs of object oriented design, data structures, design patterns and problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;NexGen Poker Gaming Product Details &amp;ndash; Desktop (PC &amp;amp; Mac), Web &amp;amp; Mobile (Android &amp;amp; iOS)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re developing a legal, regulated online poker system. At this time we have a working core system that can play all the games and is well on its way to being fully compliant with the regulatory requirements that will be in place when legislation passes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The online poker system that will be the focus of our development has several components:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The core set of services that will run all the games and provide the game results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The game play client that will be a downloadable PC program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile versions of the game play client for Web, Android and iOS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The database and back-end reporting capability for company support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company website portal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We currently have demonstrated a complete core system with a demo game play client to our interested parties (regulators and investors). In this demonstration we have shown that not only does the system work, but that it has profound and unique scalability and performance characteristics that will put us in the forefront of being able to provide the top system in this market. We will also be pursuing strategic partnerships to provide this system to other regulated environments both domestic and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-developer-nexgen-poker-santa-monica-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-developer-nexgen-poker-santa-monica-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at FunnelHub in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an iOS developer who is a quick learner, who is passionate for creating exciting and intuitive software. We want someone who would like to push the platform to its limits, with implementation approaches transcending even Apple&amp;rsquo;s first-party apps. We have locations in San Mateo and San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are an exciting well-funded startup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would be working with Design and Product teams to create beautiful interfaces that facilitate what users want to do. You are care about details and believe that a task isn&amp;rsquo;t complete until everything is just right. Caring about users and believing the little things matter is more important than experience, but practice implementing user interfaces and iOS applications is a plus. You know Objective-C and Cocoa Touch well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Objective-C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functional knowledge of the iOS SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examples of iOS applications you wrote, released or unreleased&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with client-server applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Services integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Media integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-funnelhub-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-funnelhub-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>