<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Agent at (mt) Media Temple in Culver City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Traits of Success:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a smart, energetic, and team-focused person&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A love of all things “web”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A knack for solving difficult problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ability to clearly communicate complex ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong customer service background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to troubleshoot a wide variety of technical issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s been our typical practice to refrain from requiring our employees to deadlift 300 pounds, but from time to time, you may be required to lift something in the 50 pound range (FYI…)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FTP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;POP, IMAP, and SMTP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apache&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bash shell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DNS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Media Temple:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From its inception in 1998, (mt) Media Temple has been on a mission to help people and businesses succeed online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over 125,000 customers in 100 countries now rely on Media Temple&amp;rsquo;s simple tools for domain registration, web hosting, business applications, virtual servers, and other cloud services to power more than 1.5 million websites. We take pride in offering a premium service at a competitive price, along with exemplary 24/7 customer support. Our customers range from everyday people to top bloggers, creative professionals, and small businesses, as well as large enterprises like Starbucks, Adidas, Samsung, and Toyota.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With 200 dedicated, U.S.-based employees, Media Temple has been repeatedly recognized as one of the fastest growing companies in North America—and one of the best places to work. Find us anytime on the web at http://mediatemple.net or on Twitter @MediaTemple.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-agent-mt-media-temple-culver-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-agent-mt-media-temple-culver-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Support Representative at Scribd in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Scribd is a YCombinator startup based in San Francisco looking for a Technical Support Representative to help Scribd&amp;rsquo;s users over the web and email with any issue whether it is for a simple password reset or complex publishing advice. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an enthusiastic, knowledgeable, tech-minded person to join our Customer Support team and help us deliver top-notch service. We want to make the experience for our customers the most enjoyable and enticing possible, while building on our business model. If you&amp;rsquo;re excited by this challenge, we want you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scribd’s vision is to build the future of reading and publishing by making it easy to share and discover entertaining, informative and engaging written content across the web and mobile devices. Notably, we&amp;rsquo;re already one of the top 100 sites on the web with over 90 million monthly visitors. From a technology perspective we have scaled the world&amp;rsquo;s third largest ruby on rails site, invented the first HTML5 document reader, and done original work on textual analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve won lots of awards, raised $20M along the way and we&amp;rsquo;re at the threshold of some breakthrough launches, but the journey is only 1% finished, and we’re looking for best breed of folks to take Scribd to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who you are and what you&amp;rsquo;ll do:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an enthusiastic, knowledgeable, tech-minded person to join our Technical Support team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem analysis and problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and accuracy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication with engineering teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adaptability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-initiative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stress tolerance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ year experience in an online customer service role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displayed understanding of customer support principles and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with (or knowledge of) cloud computing and cloud tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start-up experience a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High school diploma or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You’ll make us even happier if you bring:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zendesk and Scribd experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Working at Scribd: a pretty sweet gig&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scribd is a technology company based in San Francisco. We&amp;rsquo;re rapidly changing the publishing industry and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for talented technologists to help us. It&amp;rsquo;s not a normal job, but we think it&amp;rsquo;s pretty awesome anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scribd&amp;rsquo;s vision is to build the world&amp;rsquo;s digital library. Scribd&amp;rsquo;s product is used today to publish and discover written works of all kinds: everything from books and short stories to powerpoints about programming languages and Ph.D. theses. Scribd is profitable and is one of the largest sites on the web, but the journey is only 1% finished. We are still a very small team and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for excellent product and engineering minds to take us to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-representative-scribd-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-representative-scribd-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Manager at Fitbit in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Fitbit is a venture-backed growth oriented company building consumer oriented, web-connected health and fitness devices with a focus on design and user experience (http://www.fitbit.com). Our mission is nothing short of making the world a healthier place! Our current product offering includes the Fitbit Tracker, a tiny all-day personal monitor that tracks calories burned, steps taken, distance traveled, time taken to fall asleep, and sleep quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The data from the Fitbit Tracker is wirelessly uploaded to our web site, where users can view and interact with their data and share with others via an interactive dash board. The Aria scale is a recent addition to our product line that wirelessly uploads weight, BMI, and fat percentage to our interactive website, providing users with a comprehensive health and fitness program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage San Francisco based customer service team of 20+ agents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor inbound customer contact volume and ensure we meet/exceed defined response times&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit/select/hire customer service agents as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build staff schedule model based on contact arrival pattern&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain headcount forecast and reconcile with budget targets quarterly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide coaching and development of team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with:  engineering, product management and quality assurance teams around new product launches and enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop process efficiencies where required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, implement and oversee quality assurance process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review customer contacts daily to ensure agents have current and effective content to respond to customer inquiries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive initiatives to increase customer self-service and first contact resolution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure all internal and external knowledgebase content is current and accurate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resolve customer escalations and drive process/policy improvements through root cause analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build strong relationship with partner teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute assignments within specified deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Measure and achieve target metrics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agent quality score &gt;85%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customer Satisfaction &gt; 90%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staff schedule adherence &gt; 90%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Response time SLAs within 90% of targets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for helping people find solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in consumer electronics, health and wellness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and people skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent leadership skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive in a dynamic, fast-paced, team-based environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years of management experience in a customer service role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated high level of proficiency with Microsoft Office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to successfully self-manage multiple projects and tasks simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent attention to detail and quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High personal productivity with demonstrated follow-up ability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of experience handling chat, email, social and phone support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Desk.com and Salesforce.com CRM a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with multi-language support a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with startup companies a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Fitbit Inc.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fitbit is a consumer electronics company inspiring people to live healthier lifestyles. The startup&amp;rsquo;s flagship product is the Fitbit Tracker, which measures the wearer&amp;rsquo;s movement in three dimensions and calculates steps taken, distance traveled, calories burned, and sleep activity. The Tracker syncs wirelessly to Fitbit.com, where users can input additional data and track their fitness using a plethora of charts and graphs, participate in group challenges, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fitbit Tracker has won numerous prestigious industrial design awards and has been reviewed positively in the Wall Street Journal, Wired, Forbes, New York Times, Glamour, and others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Using the Fitbit Tracker is like having a personal trainer, nutritionist and sleep doctor attached to your hip at all times,” wrote Claire Cain Miller in the New York Times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Fitbit by a mile,” said Tim O’Reilly at TechCrunch50 in 2009. “They understand what kind of business they are in. They know how their gonna make money.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fitbit was founded in 2007 by longtime technology entrepreneurs James Park and Eric Friedman. The company is well capitalized and is backed in part by Foundry Group, True Ventures, and SoftTech VC.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-manager-fitbit-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-manager-fitbit-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Technical Support Specialist at DudaMobile in Palo Alto, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Duda Mobile is looking for one or two rockstar tech/web support specialists with great communication skills, a passion for customer service, a good handle on HTML/CSS, and a desire to contribute to a fast-growing mobile tech start up. In this role, you will provide hands-on support to our growing customer base, helping to identify, troubleshoot and resolve issues related to our mobile website platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recent college graduates&lt;/em&gt; who are smart and talented individuals will have the opportunity to join a tech start-up and grow within the company to other roles. Based out of a collaborative tech-loft in Palo Alto, Duda is a fast growing start-up that&amp;rsquo;s driving the explosive growth in the mobile web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ONLY JUNIOR LEVEL APPLICANTS WITH ONE- TO TWO-YEARS OF EXPERIENCE NEED APPLY. (note: this is not a IT position)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide customer support and technical issue resolution via e-Mail, phone and chat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know the ins and outs of the DudaMobile product &amp;mdash; and love it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate directly with customers and partners (all over the world!) on a daily basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for customer service and helping others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent technical skills, ability to deal with the nitty-gritty of troubleshooting and problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A love of all things mobile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building websites using HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of how websites are structured (server vs. client)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work independently and efficiently to meet deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to promptly answer support related email, phone calls and other electronic communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self motivated, detail-oriented and organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication (oral and written) skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to work extremely hard for the pleasure of being part of a great team and building an amazing product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience in support roles &amp;ndash; a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA degree from an excellent university &amp;ndash; a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-technical-support-specialist-dudamobile-palo-alto-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-technical-support-specialist-dudamobile-palo-alto-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Geek at Jimdo in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Jimdo is looking for a customer support geek in our San Francisco office to provide better support for our growing userbase in the US and Canada. You&amp;rsquo;ll join our growing team in San Francisco to help Jimdo users build and and succeed with their websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Jimdo, we give our users an easy-to-use but powerful way to create their own websites. Jimdo&amp;rsquo;s strengths are usability (we have passionate users pushing 70), a high degree of visual flexibility (it&amp;rsquo;s very easy to integrate your own design), and high-quality presentation of photos, videos, and text. Over 8 million users around the world are already building their websites with Jimdo &amp;mdash; and we&amp;rsquo;re continuing to grow exponentially.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jimdo provides awesome email support to users around the globe in 11 languages. We have a powerful product with a lot of features (online store, blog, and more), and superior customer service is one of the special reasons why people love Jimdo. We want them to feel comfortable using a do-it-yourself product with just email and chat support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is full-time and located in our office in San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll be doing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help Jimdo customers efficiently and professionally with all issues related to their websites. This includes domains, email, widgets, SEO, and other best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain great tutorials and help articles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve internal workflows and user experience. Collect and share feedback from customers with our team. Help make Jimdo a little better every day!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are on a mission to make every Jimdo user happy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web geek, experience with creating and/or maintaining websites/blogs/stores&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in email support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in chat support a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very friendly and personable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate complex problems in customer-friendly language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to think outside of the box and find creative ways to solve customer problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working for Jimdo in San Francisco is special since you&amp;rsquo;ll feel like you&amp;rsquo;re at a small startup &amp;mdash; but with a big team behind you. We want everyone who joins Jimdo to visit the office in Hamburg, Germany, about once a year to get to know and work with the European team. You could combine this with a holiday in Europe ;&amp;ndash;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three weeks of vacation each year (we expect you to take it!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Centrally located office in San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s Mission District&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Several health insurance options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision and dental insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still unconvinced? Here are even more reasons to work at Jimdo!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To apply, please fill out the application, including your cover letter and résumé.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-geek-jimdo-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-geek-jimdo-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Specialist at Intacct in San Jose, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Customer Support Specialist will respond to client inquiries regarding the Intacct Saas software solution. The Specialist will need to prioritize and multi-task on a daily basis, while maintaining a high level of confidence and professionalism. The Specialist must be able to work on complex problems, while balancing a large workload in a fast paced environment. The Specialist will work closely with the Quality Assurance, Product Management and Engineering groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist clients with accounting related questions when using the Intacct application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to customer inquiries via live help (Chat), online customer portal, and phone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listen and understand the customer&amp;rsquo;s needs and provide proactive suggestions as well as answers to improve customers' use and satisfaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily Case Management, which includes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining, updating and prioritizing to meet the published customer SLA’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logging cases with accurate information to provide a full record of each issue and resolution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Escalating cases as appropriate and coordinating problem resolution with appropriate departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logging and tracking escalations to Engineering within Ticketmaster&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the development of internal knowledge base and customer solution portal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate new features to customers and stay current on releases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When applicable, providing 24 X 7 support coverage on a rotating basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May require working off standard hours due to manager requests, or system down calls to ensure timely support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Business Administration, Accounting, Management Information System or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic accounting knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with an Accounting or ERP/Financial software application is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ERP/SaaS and CRM software a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills with the ability to multi-task in a fast paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to learn quickly and research issues for which you may not have an immediate answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly enthusiastic, positive-minded, customer focused, service-orientated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English language written and verbal communication skills, including clear speaking voice and good use of grammar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven success in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of internet technologies including knowledge of web browsers, internet security settings, and common problems associated with both&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-intacct-san-jose-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-intacct-san-jose-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Specialist at Intacct in San Jose, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in this job opening? Are you the perfect fit for our organization? Click on Apply Now! and we will walk you through our Online Application process. If you know of someone else who might be interested, please send this opportunity to a friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Customer Support Specialist will respond to client inquiries regarding the Intacct Saas software solution. The Specialist will need to prioritize and multi-task on a daily basis, while maintaining a high level of confidence and professionalism. The Specialist must be able to work on complex problems, while balancing a large workload in a fast paced environment. The Specialist will work closely with the Quality Assurance, Product Management and Engineering groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist clients with accounting related questions when using the Intacct application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to customer inquiries via live help (Chat), online customer portal, and phone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listen and understand the customer&amp;rsquo;s needs and provide proactive suggestions as well as answers to improve customers' use and satisfaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily Case Management, which includes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining, updating and prioritizing to meet the published customer SLA’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logging cases with accurate information to provide a full record of each issue and resolution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Escalating cases as appropriate and coordinating problem resolution with appropriate departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logging and tracking escalations to Engineering within Ticketmaster&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the development of internal knowledge base and customer solution portal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate new features to customers and stay current on releases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When applicable, providing 24 X 7 support coverage on a rotating basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May require working off standard hours due to manager requests, or system down calls to ensure timely support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Business Administration, Accounting, Management Information System or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic accounting knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with an Accounting or ERP/Financial software application is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ERP/SaaS and CRM software a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills with the ability to multi-task in a fast paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to learn quickly and research issues for which you may not have an immediate answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly enthusiastic, positive-minded, customer focused, service-orientated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English language written and verbal communication skills, including clear speaking voice and good use of grammar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven success in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of internet technologies including knowledge of web browsers, internet security settings, and common problems associated with both&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-intacct-san-jose-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-intacct-san-jose-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director/Product Manager at Mahalo in Culver City, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Mahalo is looking for a Art Director + Product Manager who will take our products to the next level through world-class designs that create a stunning, emotional, and functional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want you to be involved in every aspect of product design, including bringing your own ideas to our products. We&amp;rsquo;ve learned quickly that the line between design, function, and interface on mobile is thin &amp;mdash; if it exists at all. This job requires strong leadership abilities to mentor and guide a product team of awesome designers, videographers and content creators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are in the process of developing our Inside.com brand + product, so this is an exceptional opportunity to put your stamp on what will be an awesome, media-shifting product (we&amp;rsquo;re sure!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;General Reqs:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-10+ years of experience in design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid portfolio (including world-class product designs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent UI/UX design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong typography and composition skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to effectively translate designs into final assets using appropriate tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Leadership + Management Reqs:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the creative development process, providing creative feedback to team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a productive, supportive environment for the Product team. Be a mentor by providing both creative and technical expertise and leadership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritize tasks and meet deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make decisions on a daily basis that ensure both efficiency and creative quality. Set expectations and standards (build a culture) for creative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and manage design artifacts, creative mock-ups and maintain consistency of creative elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a fluent understanding of current Web, email and interactive trends, technologies and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize a broad skill set that includes: app and web design, email, social, mobile and other digital media types&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;About Mahalo/Inside.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Mahalo/Inside.com is experimenting in the educational, self-improvement and real-time content space through mobile, web, and video. We believe that the future of data consumption is in mobile and plan to change the way people learn and consumer information in a big way. We&amp;rsquo;ve already released multiple top-ranked apps in the Apple App Store and are looking for talented individuals to help us in achieving our mission. We&amp;rsquo;re a Silicon Valley-style tech company that happens to be in LA. This kind of opportunity is VERY rare and the rewards of working with us are potentially life changing. We&amp;rsquo;re well funded by Sequoia (the same people that backed Google, Yahoo, and YouTube), as well as Newscorp, Mark Cuban, Elon Musk (Paypal, Tesla, Space X), and CBS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you believe that you fit the requirements and are up for the challenge, please send us your PORTFOLIO and RESUME.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-product-manager-mahalo-culver-city-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-product-manager-mahalo-culver-city-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Specialist at Practice Fusion in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Practice Fusion is looking for a bright, energetic, and scrappy customer service expert to join our Customer Support team in San Francisco. Customer Support Specialists provide Phenomenal Support™ to doctors and medical practices with Practice Fusion&amp;rsquo;s free, web-based EHR. The ideal candidate should have a solid customer service background and a passion for learning new technology. We’re looking for someone who is motivated, personable and professional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide live chat, email and phone support to Practice Fusion’s community of EHR users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educate users on the functionality and use of the Practice Fusion EHR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot technical issues and escalate bugs appropriately&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain high levels of customer satisfaction by providing fast and accurate responses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document and manage customer interactions in our NetSuite CRM system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moderate the PF Answers forum and respond to user questions and feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify trends in customer questions and issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and refine support best practices and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 1-2 years customer service experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent troubleshooting and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avid user of technology who keeps up with the latest tech trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills, able to quickly compose clear and concise answers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friendly, patient and professional phone demeanor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organization skills and high attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated, self-starter with an excellent work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership skills for guidance in training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependable with the ability to work in a fast-paced startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local (SF Bay Area)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College graduate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ticketing or issue tracking systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NetSuite CRM experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training, leadership experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Healthcare sector experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Practice Fusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Practice Fusion’s revolutionary web-based Electronic Medical Records (EMR) software helps doctors go digital and save lives by making patient data available anytime, anywhere—for free. We have over 170,000+ medical professional users serving over 40 million patients, making us the fastest growing EHR community in the country. Our booming team of 185+ employees and recent $34 million Series C round led by Artis Ventures also makes us one of the fastest growing startups in the health IT sector. We are centrally located in the Union Square district of San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unsolicited Resumes: Practice Fusion will not pay a fee to any employment agency or third party for the referral of candidates unless the agency or third party has signed a formal agreement by an authorized member of our Human Resources Department. Unsolicited resumes from employment agencies or third parties of any kind will become the property of Practice Fusion and will be considered gratuitous, no-fee referrals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-practice-fusion-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-practice-fusion-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Support Specialist at Edmodo in San Mateo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Edmodo’s mission is to connect all learners with the people and resources they need to reach their full potential. On Edmodo, teachers are at the center of a powerful network that connects them to students, administrators, parents, and publishers. This network surfaces the world’s best resources and tools, providing the building blocks of a high quality education. In Edmodo’s secure environment, teachers and students can collaborate, share content, and use educational apps to augment in-classroom learning. These powerful capabilities enable teachers to personalize learning for every student. Edmodo is free for teachers and students and always will be.  The company is headquartered in San Mateo, CA. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.edmodo.com&quot;&gt;http://www.edmodo.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the Role&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Technical Specialist is responsible for the resolution of technical cases. This includes characterization of the incident, reproduction, diagnosis and analysis of the root cause.  The ideal candidate will have experience with a fast paced, evolving product and have excellent prioritization and troubleshooting skills. The Technical Specialist will contribute to the team by suggesting specific feature requests, sharing engineering release information, and developing both the internal and external knowledge base on product functionality and best practices. The Technical Specialist on the Support Team is an expert of the Edmodo product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have ownership over cases from start to finish including troubleshooting, communicating with the customer, and pulling in other teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reproduce and analyze cases to inform the engineering and QA teams processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Engineering and Product teams to resolve cases or escalate if necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand and become an expert in Edmodo with limited internal documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create processes for communicating important technical announcements with the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide clear and accurate support for customers in written and verbal form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritize, characterize and surface trends in troubleshooting cases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare analytical reports on cases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the knowledge base by writing articles on Edmodo functionality, workarounds and best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-6 years of previous experience working in a technical customer support team, preferably within a highly scaled, consumer facing web application startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience providing direct written customer support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one these areas: Database technology (SQL); Web technology (HTML, JavaScript, CSS, XML, PHP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of current Windows and Mac Operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize, manage, multi-task and initiate projects cross-functionally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to train teammates on complex topics in a simple manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstration of strong troubleshooting, problem solving and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works well in a team environment, is highly motivated to resolve customer concerns and maintains a positive attitude.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to “think like a user”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of bug tracking software such as Pivotal Tracker a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of browsers and Internet security best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Exceptional Candidates&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have demonstrated passion and experience in K12 education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have worked in or with an IT department of a K12 school district&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Working at Edmodo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Edmodo, we are working together to create an environment that fosters learning and growth and encourages creativity, transparency, and diversity. Hear what it’s like to work at Edmodo, directly from the Edmodo team: http://www.jobs.edmodo.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Edmodo offers a comprehensive compensation package, which includes the following benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aetna Medical PPO 10, HMO 15, and HSA options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kaiser Medical PPO 30 Option&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gaurdian Dental PPO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VSP Vision PPO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short-term and long-term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LIFE &amp;amp; AD&amp;amp;D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vanguard 401(K)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domestic partner coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vacation time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wellness time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organic catered daily food, snacks and drinks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid public transportation and parking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The position is located in downtown San Mateo, minutes from the 101, 280, and 92 freeways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edmodo is an equal opportunity employer and does not unlawfully discriminate in employment. Equal access to employment, services, and programs is available to all persons.  Those applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application and/or interview process should notify a representative of the organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note: Though submitting a resume to Edmodo implies that you are interested in a position(s), it does not imply that you are an applicant. You are not considered an applicant until you have been contacted directly by a Human Resources representative requesting that you begin the designated application process, which may involve phone and/or in-person interview(s), job-related testing, and background checking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-specialist-edmodo-san-mateo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-specialist-edmodo-san-mateo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>