<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ca-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Support Specialist at Edmodo in San Mateo, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Edmodo’s mission is to connect all learners with the people and resources they need to reach their full potential. On Edmodo, teachers are at the center of a powerful network that connects them to students, administrators, parents, and publishers. This network surfaces the world’s best resources and tools, providing the building blocks of a high quality education. In Edmodo’s secure environment, teachers and students can collaborate, share content, and use educational apps to augment in-classroom learning. These powerful capabilities enable teachers to personalize learning for every student. Edmodo is free for teachers and students and always will be.  The company is headquartered in San Mateo, CA. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.edmodo.com&quot;&gt;http://www.edmodo.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the Role&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Technical Specialist is responsible for the resolution of technical cases. This includes characterization of the incident, reproduction, diagnosis and analysis of the root cause.  The ideal candidate will have experience with a fast paced, evolving product and have excellent prioritization and troubleshooting skills. The Technical Specialist will contribute to the team by suggesting specific feature requests, sharing engineering release information, and developing both the internal and external knowledge base on product functionality and best practices. The Technical Specialist on the Support Team is an expert of the Edmodo product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have ownership over cases from start to finish including troubleshooting, communicating with the customer, and pulling in other teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reproduce and analyze cases to inform the engineering and QA teams processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Engineering and Product teams to resolve cases or escalate if necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand and become an expert in Edmodo with limited internal documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create processes for communicating important technical announcements with the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide clear and accurate support for customers in written and verbal form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritize, characterize and surface trends in troubleshooting cases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare analytical reports on cases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the knowledge base by writing articles on Edmodo functionality, workarounds and best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-6 years of previous experience working in a technical customer support team, preferably within a highly scaled, consumer facing web application startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience providing direct written customer support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one these areas: Database technology (SQL); Web technology (HTML, JavaScript, CSS, XML, PHP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of current Windows and Mac Operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize, manage, multi-task and initiate projects cross-functionally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to train teammates on complex topics in a simple manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstration of strong troubleshooting, problem solving and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works well in a team environment, is highly motivated to resolve customer concerns and maintains a positive attitude.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to “think like a user”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of bug tracking software such as Pivotal Tracker a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of browsers and Internet security best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Exceptional Candidates&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have demonstrated passion and experience in K12 education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have worked in or with an IT department of a K12 school district&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Working at Edmodo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Edmodo, we are working together to create an environment that fosters learning and growth and encourages creativity, transparency, and diversity. Hear what it’s like to work at Edmodo, directly from the Edmodo team: http://www.jobs.edmodo.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Edmodo offers a comprehensive compensation package, which includes the following benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aetna Medical PPO 10, HMO 15, and HSA options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kaiser Medical PPO 30 Option&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gaurdian Dental PPO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VSP Vision PPO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short-term and long-term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LIFE &amp;amp; AD&amp;amp;D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vanguard 401(K)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domestic partner coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vacation time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wellness time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organic catered daily food, snacks and drinks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid public transportation and parking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The position is located in downtown San Mateo, minutes from the 101, 280, and 92 freeways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edmodo is an equal opportunity employer and does not unlawfully discriminate in employment. Equal access to employment, services, and programs is available to all persons.  Those applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application and/or interview process should notify a representative of the organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note: Though submitting a resume to Edmodo implies that you are interested in a position(s), it does not imply that you are an applicant. You are not considered an applicant until you have been contacted directly by a Human Resources representative requesting that you begin the designated application process, which may involve phone and/or in-person interview(s), job-related testing, and background checking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-specialist-edmodo-san-mateo-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-specialist-edmodo-san-mateo-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Specialist at Practice Fusion in San Francisco, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Practice Fusion is looking for a bright, energetic, and scrappy customer service expert to join our Customer Support team in San Francisco. Customer Support Specialists provide Phenomenal Support™ to doctors and medical practices with Practice Fusion&amp;rsquo;s free, web-based EHR. The ideal candidate should have a solid customer service background and a passion for learning new technology. We’re looking for someone who is motivated, personable and professional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide live chat, email and phone support to Practice Fusion’s community of EHR users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educate users on the functionality and use of the Practice Fusion EHR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot technical issues and escalate bugs appropriately&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain high levels of customer satisfaction by providing fast and accurate responses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document and manage customer interactions in our NetSuite CRM system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moderate the PF Answers forum and respond to user questions and feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify trends in customer questions and issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and refine support best practices and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 1-2 years customer service experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent troubleshooting and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avid user of technology who keeps up with the latest tech trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills, able to quickly compose clear and concise answers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friendly, patient and professional phone demeanor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organization skills and high attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated, self-starter with an excellent work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership skills for guidance in training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependable with the ability to work in a fast-paced startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local (SF Bay Area)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College graduate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ticketing or issue tracking systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NetSuite CRM experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training, leadership experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Healthcare sector experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-practice-fusion-san-francisco-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-practice-fusion-san-francisco-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Retention Specialist at Duda Mobile Inc in Mountain View, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;DudaMobile is currently looking for an amazing Customer Retention Specialist with outstanding communication skills. As a Customer Retention Specialist, you will be engaging with Duda’s customers to make sure they are happy and make sure they remain our customers. You will be asked to tackle tricky problems (for instance, when a customer’s credit card has been declined) and provide elegant and easy solutions to our customers’ issues. The job requires a passion for talking and emailing, an even temperament and a never-give-up attitude.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Recent college graduates who are smart and talented are encouraged to apply.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you love the mobile web, you love people, you love communicating and you love providing help, we want to hear from you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide proactive account and billing help directly to our growing customer base. This includes: speaking to every single customer who has any sort of difficulty paying Duda, and proactively reaching out to customers to prevent any cancelation of service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate directly with customers and partners on a daily basis (by phone and email).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with our Sales and Support teams on a daily basis to resolve queries quickly and efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently reduce the number of customers who do not renew service with DudaMobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Genuine passion for customer service and helping others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication (oral and written) skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work independently and efficiently to meet deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to promptly answer issues that may come in from a wide range of channels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to turn-around negative situations into a positive lasting relationships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self motivated, detail-oriented and organized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to explain the benefits and importance of having a mobile presence online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dedicated to following through on each and every customer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to work extremely hard for the pleasure of being part of a great team and building an amazing product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited about startups and mobile technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with online billing platforms – a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience in customer facing roles &amp;ndash; a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA degree from an excellent university &amp;ndash; a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-retention-specialist-duda-mobile-inc-mountain-view-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-retention-specialist-duda-mobile-inc-mountain-view-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director Customer Support at Hulu in Los Angeles, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Hulu Support team is dedicated to providing customer support so awesome that it will make users’ heads spin. Seriously. Our goal is to be the absolute best in the world at what we do, and this is a challenge we do not take lightly. We send emails in prose, tweet troubleshooting steps in less than 140 characters, and answer calls so fast users haven’t realized the phone was ringing. We call this “the support we wish we got everywhere else”, and as we go about providing it, we’re looking for a Director of Customer Support to help us take our goals to a new level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be joining a creative and exciting technology company that is on a strong growth trajectory &amp;mdash; we&amp;rsquo;ve been ahead of expectations in all measures of success since our founding in 2007. We pride ourselves on adding people to the team who can perform at a high level while exercising impeccable judgment. You know the type – they are intellectually curious, relentless in their pursuit of better ways, and possess an atypically high attention to detail. We trust them to do the right thing, give them the resources necessary to do so, and try to have some fun along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Director of Customer Support, you will be reporting to the VP of Product Development. While you will assume leadership of current day-to-day activities, your mission will be to establish Hulu as the customer support organization others want to replicate. This challenge will involve managing the continued growth of the organization, refining the customer support strategy, scaling to additional locations in the US, and building the tools and processes needed to implement that strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other core responsibilities will include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exemplifying the Hulu culture on a daily basis, and fostering it in your team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining and driving the ongoing development of Hulu&amp;rsquo;s customer support strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focusing on continual improvement of self-help and live-support tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping each team member grow and develop, while merging individual players into a motivated and passionate team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Growing the CSA leadership team, and mentoring in core management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifying and communicating key feedback trends to Product and Development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hiring and training the right people to grow a high performing customer support team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing quality of service metrics that ensure a premium-quality customer experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;lsquo;Leading from the front&amp;rsquo; by pitching in and responding to customer contacts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remaining flexible in your schedule, as we intend to provide 24/7 support in the next year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just anyone gets to be part of Hulu. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a proven leader who has developed and motivated people, and shaped strong performing teams. While experience working in media and/or technology companies is helpful, we think it&amp;rsquo;s also valuable to have had exposure to multiple industries. Of course it will help to have experience building and scaling CS teams, but just as important, you must demonstrate rabid passion for customers and an understanding that customer support is really both a form of direct marketing and a valuable source of product feedback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in managing, mentoring and motivating high-performing teams in a constructive manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independence, high energy, and a proven ability to drive results under pressure and in the face of ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An analytical mindset and a relentless drive to find innovative ways to improve processes and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of web technology and support challenges in the tech industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of call center operations and best practices, but also the ability to develop a team that can resolve issues without relying on scripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with multiple support channels, including an understanding of the scalability and cost effectiveness of web channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing multiple support locations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A background in marketing and turning customers into brand ambassadors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUESTIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think you’ve got what it takes? Well, Pop Quiz Hotshot, please take a minute to answer the next two questions, and send them in along with your resume:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Question 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below are brief descriptions of two scenarios someone might have as a customer out in “the real world”. Please choose one of them, put yourself in the shoes of that person, and write a review about what the experience was like (something like a Yelp review). There’s no right or wrong scenario to choose, so don’t spend too much time psychoanalyzing your choice. All we ask is that you keep your response shorter than 500 words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Scenario A&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visiting a new doctor’s office for the first time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The receptionist at the front desk was snooty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You arrived on time, but had to wait 47 minutes until the doctor saw you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The doctor was super friendly, and had amazing bedside manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The only available parking garage cost $15 per hour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You were promised test results by the next day, but never received them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Scenario B&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Checking out the brand new restaurant on the block&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You walked in at 7PM on a Friday night, and were quoted a 45 minute wait&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The host was super friendly and apologetic for the long delay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After 5 minutes, the manager found you outside to let you know a table had opened up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During your meal, the server delivered the wrong drink order (twice)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When the check came, you noticed the drinks had been taken off the bill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Question 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OK, now picture this. You’re managing a team of CSAs, but decide to jump in the queue to stay current on customer contacts. Please write what you would consider to be the ideal response to the following customer&amp;rsquo;s questions. Basically, rock their world like you’d expect your team to&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi Hulu,
I recently became a Hulu Plus subscriber but I have two quick questions. First, even though I&amp;rsquo;m paying, why am I still seeing commercials that stutter? Secondly, will I be able to watch all the episodes of The Big Bang Theory and The Office on my TV and iPhone at the same time with Hulu Plus?
Thanks for your help!
Bucky&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-customer-support-hulu-los-angeles-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-customer-support-hulu-los-angeles-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Specialist at Responsys in San Bruno, CA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The candidate must be able to work directly with customers in high-pressure situations; have strong analytic, organizational, time management, and communication skills; thrive in a team environment; and possess the willingness to do whatever it takes to achieve the highest level of customer satisfaction. The candidate will interact with cross-functional teams including Production Support and Engineering. This position requires HTML and SQL debugging skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The job responsibilities include, but are not limited to, analyze, track and resolve customer issues in a professional, timely manner; identify alternate solutions when necessary and communicate them to customers; develop and implement web based support initiatives including internal knowledge base, and customer facing solutions; Manage escalated cases and track to resolution; Debug HTML and SQL related issues.  This position also requires participation in the on-call rotation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-7 years customer support experience for software applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years with multi-tiered application support experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding interpersonal and telephone skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to function and thrive in a team environment with an appreciation of aggressive goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energetic, with a strong desire to succeed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some knowledge of TCP/IP networking with good understanding of SMTP, DNS, and HTTP protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some knowledge of Linux/Unix operating systems with the ability to write and debug shell scripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some knowledge of relational database management systems with the ability to write and debug SQL queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge JavaScript a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-responsys-san-bruno-ca</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-responsys-san-bruno-ca</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>