<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/co-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Ruby on Rails Developer at White Cheetah, Inc. in Fort Collins, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Whitecheetah is looking high and low for incredible Ruby on Rails developers. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got awesome Rails skills and are plugged in enough to be reading this post, we know you already probably have a pretty good Rails gig going, so we&amp;rsquo;ll cut to the chase: We think you should jump ship and join Whitecheetah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with 2 other developers and an additional team of students over the summer, build an incredible SAAS application with powerful companion app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be hyper-responsive to customer feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have fun, build great relationships in corporate and academia, and learn in the process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know your stuff, and have architected and built at least one large scale Rails application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You believe in Agile, you are fun, and you are cool to work with.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You take pride in clean, scalable, maintainable, testable code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know how roll with Test Driven Development and Continuous Integration environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You aren&amp;rsquo;t phased when you have to bust down barriers, set up systems, or learn new technologies to get something working.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You might also have some great mobile development skills, some front end web design skills, or some GIS skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Either way, your previous work will speak for itself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are more interested in your skills and experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commensurate with experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-on-rails-developer-white-cheetah-inc-fort-collins-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-on-rails-developer-white-cheetah-inc-fort-collins-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Database Developer/DBA at Mobile Accord in Denver, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for an opportunity to have your work directly impact social change the world over?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile Accord, founded in 2005, is the leading enterprise mobile platform provider dedicated to driving social change through the mobile phone. Mobile Accord empowers individuals and entire countries to facilitate change using our revolutionary scalable services including mobile donation, communication, and polling systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Headquartered in Denver, Colorado, Mobile Accord currently operates services across five continents in countries such as Afghanistan, Pakistan, Tunisia and the Democratic Republic of Congo.  Our goal is to bring open communication platforms to those who are currently censored or oppressed regardless of location or economic restrictions.  We offer a flexible and casual work environment that isn’t perfect for everyone – but it might be perfect for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a Database Developer to create and support our data warehouses.  This position will be responsible for developing and implementing of state of the art big data solutions and platforms.  This position reports to the Data Architect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of automated ETL processes with special focus on data flow, error recovery, and exception handling and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Warehouse development and design (database design, T-SQL development and OLAP cube development)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and implement highly available, scalable and accurate data solutions used for business operations and client deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports developers for all SQL Server needs and enforcement of naming conventions, relational database modeling and other database standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists with logical and physical database design and implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducts structured testing of database designs, applications and technology platforms to confirm functionality and performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists with security administration, backup and recovery planning to ensure the database environment is stable and capable of meeting ongoing business needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years experience SQL Server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience with SQL Server Integration Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience with SQL Server Analysis Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge and experience with MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge with front end and query tools, backup and recovery strategies and performance and tuning techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability and desire to quickly learn and adapt to new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely self-motivated and highly organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take initiative and work with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to exercise good judgment and discretion in confidential matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoys a fun, dynamic and challenging work environment within a start-up culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong commitment to making a social impact&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A. in Computer Science or Information Systems preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Mobile Accord is a private firm with approximately 35 employees.  The company provides employer paid benefits, paid time off and a casual work environment – dogs included!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile Accord, Inc. is an Equal Opportunity Employer and welcomes diversity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/database-developer-dba-mobile-accord-denver-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/database-developer-dba-mobile-accord-denver-co</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>