<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/co-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer WordPress at Encoding.com in Aspen, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Encoding.com is seeking a Web Developer/Designer with specific experience maintaining and performing high level (theme, plugin, CSS customization of the WordPress platform for a complex website. Candidate should have 3-5 years of relevant experience for a full-time position in our new downtown Aspen office. Encoding.com is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest video encoding service serving large media and entertainment companies (AOL, ESPN, Getty), news organizations (Dow Jones, Reuters, Scripps), and brand marketers (RedBull, Hurley, Puma) with high volume conversion of their video content into the various formats and packaging for delivery on web, mobile, tablet, set top box and tablets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and code landing pages and manage changes with company section stake holders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop custom WordPress plugins to automate content management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate landing page and sign up process optimization and A/B testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build wireframes and manage revisions with company stake holders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience with front end HTML, CSS, Javascript development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide portfolio of relevant work accompanied by specific role performed in each project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of the WordPress platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience with Photoshop, Illustrator, Fireworks and other design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Internet marketing terminology and concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of popular video distribution trends (ie, web, mobile, tablet, set top box and tablets.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP/MySQL skills a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organizational and time management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled at identifying and solving problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-wordpress-encoding-com-aspen-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-wordpress-encoding-com-aspen-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Ruby Application Developer at Plink, Inc. in Denver, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;If you are a motivated, hard worker and you’re excited to be an integral part of a new and innovative start up, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plink is a new online to offline rewards program that motivates our members through online media channels to shop and dine offline. We have currently signed on some of the nation’s largest brands (including Burger King, Taco Bell, Arby’s, 7-Eleven, Outback Steakhouse and more) to our program and we’re excited to bring on more.  We are building a cutting edge, disruptive platform that bridges the gap between online media and offline sales. Recently we were selected by Business Insider as one of the top 8 start-ups of 2012. We are an energetic, fast-paced, rapidly growing company and we have an immediate opening for a full-time Application Developer. Think you have what it takes to make an impact? We’d like to see your resume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;POSITION &amp;amp; SUMMARY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a member of Plink’s software engineering team we’re looking for you to bring in proven experience building real world scalable web applications. You should be comfortable working independently and with a team of engineers who are not only passionate about the software, but the business as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is comfortable in a fast-paced, venture-backed startup environment and will bring with them a strong work ethic and creative problem solving skills. Solving tough technical problems using innovative techniques and cutting (sometimes even bleeding) edge technologies are really what get your juices flowing. You thrive on speed, learning and a rapidly changing competitive landscape. You take pride in producing clean, elegant code and enjoy producing web applications that use the latest in front-end development techniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in all phases of the software development lifecycle.  Design, develop, test, document and maintain new and existing applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in relational database design and the maintenance of existing databases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand technical infrastructure and recommend solutions consistent with the environment, technical knowledge, resources, availability requirements, enterprise architecture and other considerations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhibit excellent project management/business skills to go along with software development skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhibit a strong desire to learn and understand all aspects of our operations and be able to interact directly with other departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface with business leadership, business users and technical personnel to gather requirements, design, implement, and maintain various projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review and analyze system specifications to determine whether all required elements have been exercised and included.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop integrations and customizations with third party applications and platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advise and work with users to resolve specific problems or make changes in programs, provide alternative programming approaches, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical guidance to internal business and IT teams on aspects of application security, performance, quality and scalability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and implement tools and technologies outside of base set of skills as needs arise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience with Ruby/Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience in web application development, expert level HTML, CSS, Javascript, T-SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience with relational database design and development including SQL, PL/SQL, T-SQL, stored procedures, triggers, user defined functions, cursors, views and ER design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Apache Web server, MySQL, MS SQL Server and their respective tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience managing and processing large amounts of data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using batch commands to automate routine maintenance operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable in a small, intense and high-growth start-up environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PREFERRED&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of other web programming technologies (PHP, Coldfusion, Python)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Linux, shell scripting, and regular expressions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git version control experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloud infrastructure experience, specifically Amazon Web Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery, Bootstrap CSS, responsive web design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing unit tests using RSpec or Cucumber&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-application-developer-plink-inc-denver-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-application-developer-plink-inc-denver-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Jackson National Life Insurance Company in Denver, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Jackson National Life Insurance Company® (&amp;ldquo;Jackson®&amp;rdquo;) has an opening for a Web Developer. Jackson is one of the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest and fastest growing financial services companies, with over $100 billion in total assets.  We offer a range of retirement products and services including variable, fixed and fixed index annuities.  Please visit our website at www.jackson.com for more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Purpose&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate for this position will construct graphical user interfaces that effectively translate and communicate identity and functionality for optimal display on the web. Responsibilities will be focused on the coding of presentation layer web pages. This individual must have a strong understanding of GUI architecture, site navigation and web design principles, and the ability to create and maintain web pages quickly and efficiently. All work produced by the Web Developer must meet or exceed Corporate standards for web code. An extreme attention to detail is necessary to assure that all code follows appropriate processes, is accurate, and passes validation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to hand-code in X/HTML, JavaScript, and CSS while strictly adhering to current W3C specifications/recommendations for optimized semantic markup (no generation of code)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use of Adobe Dreamweaver as a primary guide and pre-production check&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce quality, pixel-perfect, hand-coded Web pages from Photoshop files and wireframe documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slice and optimize graphics using Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow coding and layout standards co-developed by User Interface Designers and Graphic Artists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create and communicate original conceptual ideas while staying within the parameters of each project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements (Knowledge, Skills &amp;amp; Abilities)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years experience with X/HTML, JavaScript, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One to three years experience working in content management systems preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One to three years experience with a large website and managing templates within a Content Management System across many pages in an organized and logical manner preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Jackson offers an outstanding benefits package including competitive pay, bonuses, comprehensive health insurance benefits, a 401(k) retirement plan with matching, and a college tuition reimbursement program for employees and eligible dependents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Online applications requested.  Contact human.resources@jackson.com for alternate formats for accommodation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Company facilities and campuses are tobacco-free environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above statements are intended to describe the general nature and level of work being performed by people assigned to this classification. They are not to be construed as an exhaustive list of all job duties performed by the personnel so classified.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-jackson-national-life-insurance-company-denver-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-jackson-national-life-insurance-company-denver-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Quick Left in Boulder, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for talented Ruby and JavaScript developers to join our team in Boulder, Colorado. Qualified applicants have been building applications with Ruby on Rails for several years and have a deep understanding of server architectures and current web technologies. Work on open source projects is a definite plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quick Left is a company run by developers, for developers. We value direct and honest communication with our clients and value pragmatic solutions above all else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developers choose their tools and technologies. Developers run stand-ups. Developers set project pacing and schedules. We love making great applications, and we want you to come join us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Competitive salary, excellent benefits, the latest technologies. We know what our values are and give our developers everything they need to get the job done. Benfits include, but aren&amp;rsquo;t limited to: Paid vacation and sick time, 401k match, medical benefits and monthly in-office events and meetups. The fridge is always stocked and beer is on tap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the hands-on, collaborative nature of our practice, we&amp;rsquo;re only entertaining applicants willing to work full time at our Boulder office. Relocation expenses are covered if you&amp;rsquo;re moving from out of state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s how the interview goes down:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s get to know each other a little. What makes you tick? Let&amp;rsquo;s talk in person, on the phone or over video chat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll dig into the technical details of your work. Be prepared to talk about your experiences solving business problems with software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll invite you in for some pair programming. We&amp;rsquo;ll write some code together. This is where it gets fun.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-quick-left-boulder-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-quick-left-boulder-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Ruby on Rails Developer at ZOLL in Broomfield, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between this job and being a super hero? Both involve saving lives, but we actually pay you.
We are the leader for management and training of life saving devices such as defibrillators. We have the resources and stability of a large company, but the nimbleness, ambition, and determination of a startup, because we used to be one.
We have a small, highly motivated team and the most important thing is to be a demonstrated self-starter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What we have to offer you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did I mention super hero? Our office is casual enough you could wear a super hero costume, although shorts and flip flops may be more appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intellectually engaging discussions about software architecture among self-proclaimed experts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appreciation that the work you do makes us a better company (mostly in the form of a competitive salary and benefits, but could also include cookies).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We mean what we say &amp;ndash; We&amp;rsquo;re on Forbes list of 100 Most Trustworthy Companies for three consecutive years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stability &amp;ndash; We&amp;rsquo;re on Fortune&amp;rsquo;s list of 100 Fastest-Growing Companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;What we are looking for from you:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Super hero like ability to adapt to whatever is thrown at you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby on Rails coding skills that would make DHH proud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nearly insatiable appetite to solve difficult problems fast, which may mean the fewest CPU cycles or developer cycles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ok, and maybe some technical prowess with Git/Github, TDD, Postgres, OSX, Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design/front-end skills are a big plus &amp;ndash; particularly standards-based clean, maintainable markup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sense of humor, because really, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t this all be fun?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-broomfield-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-broomfield-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Back-End Web Developer at Occipital in Boulder, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you want to push the boundaries of what’s possible in web technology to help build the future of augmented reality? Are you able to hold a complete understanding of a complex backend system in your head to build fast and reliable web applications and APIs? Do you have a deep understanding of how networking, databases, and servers work down to the bare metal? Then we really want to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re creating a computer vision platform to power the next generation of augmented reality. This is an incredibly complex endeavor that will require everything from sophisticated computer vision algorithms running on mobile devices, to vast storage of visual information, to taking advantage of GPU servers for fast parallel image processing. An important part of this platform will be the web backend system required to tie it all together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our currently launched product, 360 Panorama, has millions of users and huge potential that we have yet to tap. 360 Panorama users are helping us build the 360VERSE &amp;ndash; a way to explore the world through 360 views, searchable by location AND time (currently in beta, launching soon).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for a web wizard who is excited to help us expand on 360 Panorama and 360VERSE and also help us build the computer vision platform that will usher in a new wave of augmented reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;If you have experience with most of the following, we’d love to talk to you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Python or other server side scripting language experience (most of our backend is written in Python)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MVC frameworks (we use Django)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Node.js (used on our GPU servers)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgres or other SQL experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Geospatial / location search using PostGIS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*nix server administration and automation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usage of cloud services, including storage and server provisioning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of front-end technologies (e.g. Javascript, HTML5, WebGL)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and ability to debug the full web stack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of networking protocols and ability to implement and design new ones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/back-end-web-developer-occipital-boulder-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/back-end-web-developer-occipital-boulder-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Developer at Factory Design Labs in Denver, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;POSITION SUMMARY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’re looking for someone that not only loves Rails, but also has a desire to understand the inner workings and underpinnings of the framework. Design driven development is what we aspire to and BDD is our focus. Our projects move at a fast pace, and Cucumber and Rspec help keep us honest. We work hard but we don&amp;rsquo;t take ourselves too seriously, so be prepared to write a lot of code while sipping whatever is in the keg this week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Developer is responsible for development and debugging of new and existing web applications and services. Primary responsibilities include writing specs and code to implement requirements for a given application. Excellent attention to detail and personal responsibility are a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow Factory development methodologies (a healthy blend of the best the agile world has to offer)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take initiative during discussions of process and development improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write stories and specs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce stable, well-architected code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occasionally wrangle some front-end code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pair-program when needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide complexity- and time-based estimates for projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up to date with the latest technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some travel may be required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ year of backend web development experience, including database experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6+ months experience with the Ruby language and the Rails framework, with a solid understanding of the Ruby on Rails stack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a strong appricieation in OO programming and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some knowledge of web standards, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Past exposure to test driven development and agile development processes a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with jQuery or similar JS frameworks a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with version control systems (Git preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in an advertising agency setting a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work outside of normal business hours as job duties or assignment requires, sometime  with little or no advance notification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills with a willingness to speak with both internal stakeholders and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tolerance for bad puns a bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/developer-factory-design-labs-denver-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/developer-factory-design-labs-denver-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Ruby on Rails Developer at White Cheetah, Inc. in Fort Collins, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Whitecheetah is looking high and low for incredible Ruby on Rails developers. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got awesome Rails skills and are plugged in enough to be reading this post, we know you already probably have a pretty good Rails gig going, so we&amp;rsquo;ll cut to the chase: We think you should jump ship and join Whitecheetah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with 2 other developers and an additional team of students over the summer, build an incredible SAAS application with powerful companion app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be hyper-responsive to customer feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have fun, build great relationships in corporate and academia, and learn in the process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know your stuff, and have architected and built at least one large scale Rails application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You believe in Agile, you are fun, and you are cool to work with.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You take pride in clean, scalable, maintainable, testable code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know how roll with Test Driven Development and Continuous Integration environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You aren&amp;rsquo;t phased when you have to bust down barriers, set up systems, or learn new technologies to get something working.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You might also have some great mobile development skills, some front end web design skills, or some GIS skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Either way, your previous work will speak for itself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are more interested in your skills and experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commensurate with experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-on-rails-developer-white-cheetah-inc-fort-collins-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-on-rails-developer-white-cheetah-inc-fort-collins-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Database Developer/DBA at Mobile Accord in Denver, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for an opportunity to have your work directly impact social change the world over?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile Accord, founded in 2005, is the leading enterprise mobile platform provider dedicated to driving social change through the mobile phone. Mobile Accord empowers individuals and entire countries to facilitate change using our revolutionary scalable services including mobile donation, communication, and polling systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Headquartered in Denver, Colorado, Mobile Accord currently operates services across five continents in countries such as Afghanistan, Pakistan, Tunisia and the Democratic Republic of Congo.  Our goal is to bring open communication platforms to those who are currently censored or oppressed regardless of location or economic restrictions.  We offer a flexible and casual work environment that isn’t perfect for everyone – but it might be perfect for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a Database Developer to create and support our data warehouses.  This position will be responsible for developing and implementing of state of the art big data solutions and platforms.  This position reports to the Data Architect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of automated ETL processes with special focus on data flow, error recovery, and exception handling and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Warehouse development and design (database design, T-SQL development and OLAP cube development)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and implement highly available, scalable and accurate data solutions used for business operations and client deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports developers for all SQL Server needs and enforcement of naming conventions, relational database modeling and other database standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists with logical and physical database design and implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducts structured testing of database designs, applications and technology platforms to confirm functionality and performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists with security administration, backup and recovery planning to ensure the database environment is stable and capable of meeting ongoing business needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years experience SQL Server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience with SQL Server Integration Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience with SQL Server Analysis Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge and experience with MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge with front end and query tools, backup and recovery strategies and performance and tuning techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability and desire to quickly learn and adapt to new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely self-motivated and highly organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take initiative and work with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to exercise good judgment and discretion in confidential matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoys a fun, dynamic and challenging work environment within a start-up culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong commitment to making a social impact&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A. in Computer Science or Information Systems preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Mobile Accord is a private firm with approximately 35 employees.  The company provides employer paid benefits, paid time off and a casual work environment – dogs included!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile Accord, Inc. is an Equal Opportunity Employer and welcomes diversity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/database-developer-dba-mobile-accord-denver-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/database-developer-dba-mobile-accord-denver-co</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>