<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/co-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at Xantrex Technology Inc. in Fort Collins, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a global specialist in energy management with operations in more than 100 countries, Schneider Electric offers integrated solutions across multiple market segments, including leadership positions in Utilities &amp;amp; Infrastructures, Industries &amp;amp; Machine Manufacturers, Non-residential Buildings, Data Centres &amp;amp; Networks and in Residential. Focused on making energy safe, reliable, efficient, productive and green, the Group&amp;rsquo;s 130,000 plus employees achieved sales of 22.4 billion euros in 2011, through an active commitment to help individuals and organizations make the most of their energy. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.schneider-electric.com&quot;&gt;http://www.schneider-electric.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schneider Electric has an outstanding opportunity for a passionate and motivated individual to assume the role of User Experience Designer in our Fort Collins, CO location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need someone who can produce high-quality, usable, and pleasurable experiences for a wide range of video software products. Someone who can quickly get inside the user&amp;rsquo;s head and know what motivates them. Someone who understands instinctively how to design a good experience, and knows what it takes to make that design a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a UX Designer, you will be involved in the full range of UX design tasks: UI design, interaction design, information architecture, prototyping, wireframes, storyboards, design specifications, user research, and usability testing. In addition to being part of a team of UX and visual designers, you will interact daily with engineering, product management, and marketing teams to produce the next generation of our video management applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead design efforts from concept through implementation including translating user needs into highly usable applications in partnership with other UX designers, engineering, and product management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design wireframes, storyboards, mock-ups, and prototypes to effectively communicate the user experience of features to internal stakeholders and project team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct user research, expert evaluations, and usability studies of prototypes and existing products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, document, and evangelize user interaction guidelines and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure a consistent interactive experience across applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements (in order of importance):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to work in a fast-paced yet laid back environment where excellence is the norm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong instincts for creating usable, attractive designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written, verbal, and visual communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate with visual designers and developers to achieve desired end result&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively translate project requirements into prototypes/wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working independently as sole designer on large projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Borderline annoying attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years UX design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to ensure designs are accurately carried out through the implementation stage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience with browser-based interaction design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firm grasp on current web technologies (limitations &amp;amp; capabilities)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working knowledge of HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile app design experience (iOS and/or Android)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to push against obstacles in the way of a truly pleasurable user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisdom to know when to stop pushing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to accept design input/critique from UX team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation, moderation, and interview skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience performing usability testing for desktop, web, and mobile interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with creation and use of personas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s or Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in User Experience design, HCI, visual design, or related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML/CSS development experience (please indicate proficiency and how recent)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual design experience (please provide links to examples)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of responsive web design (theory and practice)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Axure RP Pro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Adobe Creative Suite products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in an Agile development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong drive to learn and try new things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Care. Connect. Challenge. Commit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our values define our company. Who we are, our customer approach, how we do business, what it&amp;rsquo;s like to work here, and the kind of people we want to attract and retain. We care for our planet, our customers, our company, our team, and ourselves. We connect to customers and colleagues; we are open and respectful. We challenge others and embrace challenges ourselves. We commit to change by leading the change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Schneider Electric, because we value our employees, we offer a competitive benefits package that includes medical, dental and vision, matching 401(k), training and development opportunities and much more. Join Schneider Electric and together, let&amp;rsquo;s make the most of your energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-xantrex-technology-inc-fort-collins-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-xantrex-technology-inc-fort-collins-co</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>