<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/co-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Marketing Project Manager at Starz Entertainment, LLC in Englewood, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Primary Responsibility:  Manage all activities associated with a Digital Marketing brand and product-related projects including, creative development, managing internal departmental and agency relationships, and publishing in digital environments (newsletters, websites, social platforms, apps, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Involved in a variety of on-going creative and measurable tactics to engage STARZ and ENCORE subscribers and non-subscribers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop digital extensions of affiliate programs and any new emerging digital acquisition platforms, new content development and other online marketing initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the Sr. Digital Marketing Manager to execute the digital strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage brand/show-related campaigns delivered via social sites, email and company website including, writing copy for social properties, gathering assets for the original series or movies on the networks and use of a publishing platform tool to schedule updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze digital metrics and trends to improve and/or add functionality, drive repeat visits, longer time spent on site/page and increase conversions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for initiating, coordinating creative development, tracking timelines, documenting requests/changes and communicating the status of all assigned projects to other departments as appropriate, including: Creative, Public Relations, Consumer Marketing and Programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Content Managers to identify and optimize on content production and workflow processes in CMS, and to troubleshoot and assist in providing solutions for bugs/defects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and/or evaluate new and enhanced feature documentation for the integration of new technologies into Starz.com, keeping pace with developments in digital marketing helping to ensure that Starz’ web and mobile presence is creatively and technologically sound.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains a strong technical understanding of the latest web and online technologies and applications available in the industry, troubleshooting and independently researching and resolving problems and issues regarding website content delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform quality assurance and user acceptance testing on company web products/presence to ensure the quality of content and accessibility/usability of product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures that appropriate enhancements are made to web sites and applications with regard to new products/services, technologies, systems, and processes, etc. in support of Digital Marketing business goals and objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes ideas and recommendations toward product, process and system improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain regular traffic reports for the business with clear analysis to guide editorial, product development and commercial decision making (Omniture Site Catalyst and Google Analytics).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attend client and departmental meetings as requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage internal departmental relationships, including on-air promotions, brand, and creative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with external email service provider to publish email newsletters as well as assist with managing content updates and creative layout changes to refine and optimize campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with internal Legal team to ensure compliance with legal guidelines on all campaign tactics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage all work to brand guidelines and messaging standards as directed by the Sr. Digital Marketing Manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education, Knowledge, and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s of Art or Bachelor’s of Science degree in Marketing, Communication or similar discipline preferred; Minimum two years Digital Marketing experience, preferably in an advertising agency, or entertainment environment; Experience in Digital/Interactive and/or project management; Strong appreciation, experience and understanding best in class web design &amp;amp; usability, social media, mobile and new/emerging digital platforms; And/or training; And/or combination of education and experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills, attention to detail, flexibility and endurance to multi-task and prioritize across many projects with varying deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated and detail-oriented, with excellent time-management skills, strong interpersonal skills and the ability to function well in a collaborative, team oriented environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Search Engine Marketing and Optimization a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mature user of key social spaces, i.e. actively and regularly use both Twitter and Facebook for personal or business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An interest, passion in learning about new methods of promotion in the digital arena and willing to explore new technologies as well as assess what other networks are doing in support of their campaigns for entertainment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with social media monitoring and management tool(s) a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred hands-on experience with social media strategy, analytics and optimization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable in all Microsoft Office applications, including Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint and Project software applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-marketing-project-manager-starz-entertainment-llc-englewood-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-marketing-project-manager-starz-entertainment-llc-englewood-co</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Lead Creative Director Markit On Demand Boulder Co at Markit On Demand in Boulder, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you make things that are as elegant and efficient as they are beautiful? Do you look at your banks ATM screen and think about ways to make it better? Do you get excited about working with a multi-disciplinary design team that draws on 50 foot whiteboards? Want an opportunity to work with clients on every continent (well, except Antarctica)? Then we should talk. Markit on Demand in Boulder Colorado is looking for designers to join our expanding team. Interaction and Information design is the realm we work in every day &amp;ndash; web, app, mobile and print are all our methods of delivery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Creative Lead will join the design management team as a peer and work closely with company-wide executives to leverage their innovative design experience and leadership. The ideal candidate can expertly separate outstanding UX/design from the mediocre and is impassioned with defining design styles based on user experience, client strategy and creative guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates must have six plus years of interactive experience (agency or internal) with a user/digital experience focus with a minimum of three years in the Creative Director (or similar) role. The candidate must be self-motivated, willing to be challenged by the MOD/Markit management team and our clients, as well as work thoughtfully in building bridges with our global co-workers. The focus of the position is to define innovative user interfaces and interaction styles which result in improved user satisfaction and efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative drive to design the best user experience possible, strong software/web development design communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open to feedback and knows how and when to defend design choices. Oversees visual and information architecture design and development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide strong conceptual, creative direction and leadership for internal and external client presentations, prototypes, and potential pitches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain strong relationships with current clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to define the creative vision and drive concepts to craft innovative interactive experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to guide and inspire the creative team from concept through delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects from a creative leadership perspective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceive and shape experience-oriented design solutions that fulfill strategic business objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspire, motivate and manage creative teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor and lead junior, intermediate and senior creative staff through critique of their work in order to maintain consistent creative and stellar quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage deadlines, predict risk and be on top of projects that require extra attention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with other teams (Development, QA, Software Engineering, PM etc.) through project lifecycles to ensure quality and efficiency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate clear solutions to turn challenges around.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivate designers to come up with innovative concepts and ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand remarkable design, execution and interactions vs. what is average and safe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Embrace a fast-paced environment and deliver exceptional quality even under tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand user experience and work closely with UX Leads and Managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate clearly both internally and externally. Work across teams both functionally and proactively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Professional Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6-8 years experience in a creative leadership role in an interactive agency or internal environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ongoing education preferred: Associate, Bachelor’s or Master’s degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communicator – both verbally, written and presentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five plus years of interactive experience defining and driving the design process and direction of both small and large projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of creating and designing any interactive experiences across multiple platforms such as interactive advertising, mobile applications and websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid time estimation and resource planning skills. Ability to travel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced experience managing the creative development process in a client-services environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation skills and persuasive communication abilities at all levels of both internal and client organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to prioritize work and resources across engagements based on short and long-term needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven mentoring, supervisory, and team-building skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What do we do?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our work must be beautiful, usable, and tell a story. We love digging into complex and messy problems because that&amp;rsquo;s our opportunity to tease a little order out of the chaos. We work with other designers, developers, financial analysts, and our clients to set new standards for information design. This work is widely used, billions of views each day (that’s billion, with a ‘b’), so what you do here matters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Exciting, right?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a team of over 30 designers, and as business continues to grow, so do we. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for people who can create compelling experiences, who live and die by the grid, and who can see a story in a thousand data points. The skills we employ include everything from user research, information architecture and wireframes to pixel-perfect interactive comps. We hope Adobe Creative Suite is an extension of your hands, you know enough CSS to be dangerous and maybe even play around in Processing from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Still interested?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;This might be your kind of place if you&amp;hellip;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;think design lies in the intentionally imperfect union of form and function.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;can tell us a story through numbers alone. Or chopsticks for that matter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;discovered Tufte and realized you weren&amp;rsquo;t alone in your obsession.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Oh, and us? How nice of you to ask. We&amp;hellip;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;don&amp;rsquo;t love cubicles. Or barriers of any kind really.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;blush when clients call us data geeks, or tell us we&amp;rsquo;re detail obsessed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are equally fascinated by Radiolab and Planet Money.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;On top of the good stuff like competitive salaries, health insurance, and 401k, there's…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;getting paid to bike, bus or carpool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;unlimited chocolate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;time to work on what you want (like that crazy idea you have been dreaming about for months).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;So if you think you&amp;rsquo;d be a good fit here, send us…&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;your résumé. We need to see how well you color inside the lines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;your portfolio, Dribbble link or any other work examples. Coloring outside the lines is encouraged.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a link to your favorite data visualization and what about it resonates with you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What We Offer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Markit on Demand, Inc. has been in business for almost 20 years. Headquartered at the base of the Rocky Mountains in Boulder, Colorado, Markit On Demand has over 400 employees that are focused on the design, development and hosting of financial web sites, reports, and tools. We deliver innovative, high quality products to help our clients and their customers visualize, manipulate and understand complex financial information. Our compelling, presentation-rich services for financial professionals and individual investors have won acclaim for our clients, many of whom rank at the top of the Gomez and Forbes awards. Our products are custom designed for each client, completely private-labeled, and fully integrated into the client’s other offerings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acquired by Markit in 2010, Markit On Demand has entered a promising and exciting business relationship and continues to grow and create new career opportunities for exceptional people who want to awaken their curiosity and strengthen their creative thinking and critical problem solving skills in a demanding, results oriented and client focused work environment. Markit is a leading, global financial information services company with over 2,300 employees. The company provides independent data, valuations and trade processing across all asset classes in order to enhance transparency, reduce risk and improve operational efficiency. Over 1,500 institutions use Markit’s independent services as clients &amp;ndash; including investment banks, hedge funds, asset managers,central banks, regulators, rating agencies and insurance companies &amp;ndash; providing round-the-clock support from offices in London, New York, Dallas, Toronto, Amsterdam, Frankfurt, Singapore, Tokyo, Sydney, Calgary, Vancouver, Boulder, New Delhi, Chicago and Henley on Thames.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Markit On Demand offers a terrific working environment that creates an abundance of opportunities for motivated individuals. We possess a unique and compelling culture that is intellectually stimulating, encourages creativity and recognizes individual and team contribution. We offer a great benefits package including medical with HSA/FSA, dental, vision, 401K with Company Match, vacation and personal days, alternative transportation benefits and there really is an unlimited supply of chocolate!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary is based on experience. Markit On Demand is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We respectfully request no agency or recruiter inquiries or candidate submissions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-lead-creative-director-markit-on-demand-boulder-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-lead-creative-director-markit-on-demand-boulder-co</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>