<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/co-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Occipital in Boulder, CO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;When you see a terrible UI do you have a hundred ideas on how you could do it better? Does creating next-gen user experiences get you out of bed in the morning? Are you so detailed oriented that an unwanted single pixel offset bugs you? Then we really want to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Occipital, we love creating amazing user-experiences on the web that work for all common browsers, but we also love pushing the envelope with the latest tech. With 360 Panorama, for example, we created an interactive viewer that works across almost every browser, but we also added gyro support for the mobile safari browser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But we’ve just started scratching the surface of what’s possible with the font-end web, and we will do a lot more. The experiences we create around our computer vision powered products are brand new and require next-gen interfaces &amp;ndash; we want someone who can help us bring these experiences to the web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Do most of the following apply to you?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real artists ship &amp;ndash; You have a strong desire to help build something that is the best in the world and ship it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Details matter &amp;ndash; You believe everything should have a reason, down to the placement of a button and the size of a text field, even if that reason is that it looks better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User experience above all else &amp;ndash; You’ll deal with things like browser compatibility issues in an elegant way to make sure users on all popular browsers have a great experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have an active Github account and can show us some code you are proud of.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can tap into a user’s sensorimotor cortex to create Natural User Interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You write bulletproof, well-commented and reusable Javascript and know when to use libraries like jQuery and when to just write something custom for performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve built something with WebGL and have tons of ideas on how to take advantage of it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You want to push the asynchronous envelope with Node.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience with Python/Django.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve built something using maps or geo data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You believe 3D is a big part of the future, and you like to subtly integrate it into normal 2D web experiences, but then go all out when you’ve got HTML5 and WebGL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience building something non-trivial using Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You want to join the team that’s building the future of Augmented Reality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-occipital-boulder-co</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-occipital-boulder-co</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>