<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ct-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP Developer at Priceline.com in Norwalk, CT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At priceline.com, the marketing team is looking for a rock solid PHP Web Developer to develop a vast array of applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe in hiring smart people who love what they do. Do you value craftsmanship? Rock PHP, HTML, CSS, and Javascript? We want to talk to you.  Ever used node.js?  Can write your own jQuery plugin? All the better. Can write your own Canvas based graphing framework. Apply right away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look for well-rounded technologists who thrive in a creative, no-red-tape environment.                                                                                                                                                   You’ll be part of a flat, small, tight-knit team delivering real value to customers, with the ability to respond quickly and see immediate results. We’ve kept the best parts of being an original dot-com start-up&amp;mdash;the passion of creating something new every day&amp;mdash;and blended it with the perks of a thriving international company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be responsible for developing solutions that power our email and social promotion initiatives. Including but not limited to reporting systems, templating systems, caching algorithms, customer behavior systems.. and so forth..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But don’t take our word for it. Apply online and talk to us to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of PHP and developing data driven applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent work experience with HTML, JavaScript, CSS and AJAX.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of SQL and using relational databases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of NoSQL solutions is a HUGE plus. Bonus points for MongoDB experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong multitasking, time management, team work and analytical problem-solving skills is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years work experience in web development role required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years experience programming web applications using PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Linux and Windows environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-developer-priceline-com-norwalk-ct</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-developer-priceline-com-norwalk-ct</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>