<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ct-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. UX / UI Designer - Web &amp; Mobile Apps at Project One in Bristol, CT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking two (2) Sr. UX Designers for a leading Broadcast &amp;amp; Digital Media Company.  One (1) position will be based in NYC; the other will be worked onsite in Connecticut.  Both are long term projects that will run 12+ months, or may convert to an employee position with our client after 4-6 months.  W2 ONLY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both UX Designers will work closely with various development teams on multiple client and customer-facing projects.  As a Sr. UX Designer, you&amp;rsquo;ll assist with the design of websites, web applications, desktop and mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6+ years experience working as a User Experience Designer, Interaction Designer, Information Architect (or closely related field) in the design of websites, web applications, desktop, and/or mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design Expertise, an eye for clean visual designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software Skills &amp;ndash; Proficiency with design and software prototyping tools, including Adobe Creative Suite, Axure, HTML, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of UI/UX principles and best practices, and the latest trends in design and user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equivalent experience in end user research, including conducting usability tests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evidence of continuing coursework/education in Design and User Experience (in order to demonstrate passion and desire to keep knowledge base current&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of user-centered design methods and usability principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation, interpersonal and analytical skills, including the ability to communicate complex, interactive design concepts clearly and persuasively across different audiences and varying levels of the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in comparing, contrasting, and prioritizing among alternative approaches to meeting design objectives, and using judgment to suggest solutions to design problems that optimize among customer needs, business constraints, and technological realities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to take an idea from concept to implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent design skills, including strong understanding of typography, layout, color, and composition and visualization principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of and experience creating UX deliverables such as personas, scenarios, use cases, user stories, task flows, flow charts, storyboards, site maps, information architectures, mockups, wireframes, prototypes, user interface, and style guides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience researching and creating user workflows using Omnigraffle or Visio)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education &amp;ndash; Bachelors Degree in Human Computer Interaction, User Experience Design, Interaction Design, Information Architecture, User Interface Design, Human Factors, Graphic Design, Technical Communication or related field, or equivalent combination of education and experience;  Masters degree a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with diagramming software such as Visio or Omnigraffle is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Axure Rapid Prototyping knowledge a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Denis Ganev&lt;br/&gt;
Direct: (212) 792-6369&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-ux-ui-designer-web-and-mobile-apps-project-one-bristol-ct</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-ux-ui-designer-web-and-mobile-apps-project-one-bristol-ct</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Designer Creative Services at CIGNA in Hartford, CT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;In support of CIGNA&amp;rsquo;s goals to increase the health, well-being, and security of the individuals we serve, CIGNA sells a comprehensive suite of medical insurance, health advocacy solutions and group insurance products, that address the unique health and financial security needs of individuals.  These products/solutions are sold to employers, government institutions and individuals either directly or through partnerships with Brokers and Consultants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CIGNA Marketing organization partners with Business Units, Sales Organizations and other functional support groups to build the CIGNA brand, products and programs to make CIGNA the preferred brand in the marketplace.  This is accomplished by translating business objectives into effective programs and initiatives, through a combination of applying broad marketing expertise, supported by a robust Business Intelligence competency.  Within Marketing, the Marketing Communications organization is responsible for developing and executing Business and Segment specific Marketing Communications Plans which help retain and grow CIGNA&amp;rsquo;s diverse customer base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You combine a solid design background with a passion for technology. Responsible for the conception, design, and execution of visual experiences for interactive initiatives including websites, microsites, email marketing, mobile, applications, epublications, infographics, banner ads, social and other technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;KEY DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively interprets a client’s needs as outlined in creative briefs and translate them into compelling interactive designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applies design theory and takes into consideration content, navigational structure and usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partners well with copywriter to concept creative, on-strategy ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applies a strong understanding of interactive knowledge, including visual design, front-end development, usability and technology standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of working to deadlines on multiple projects concurrently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to the development of digital standards and procedures for creative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learns about and understands Cigna’s businesses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains stewardship of Cigna’s brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PREFERRED POSITION REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 8years of interactive design, prior experience in an agency setting preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite, Flash; web technologies including HTML, CSS, social, mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work in a dynamic, high-volume, matrix-oriented environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player; enthusiastic, demonstrates a can-do attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently delivers good work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-designer-creative-services-cigna-hartford-ct</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-designer-creative-services-cigna-hartford-ct</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Designer - NBC Sports Group at NBC Sports Network in Stamford, CT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;NBCUniversal is one of the world’s leading media and entertainment companies in the development, production, and marketing of entertainment, news, and information to a global audience. NBCUniversal owns and operates a valuable portfolio of news and entertainment television networks, a premier motion picture company, significant television production operations, a leading television stations group, and world-renowned theme parks. Comcast Corporation owns a controlling 51% interest in NBCUniversal, with GE holding a 49% stake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NBC Sports is synonymous with superior production that elevates the event, broad promotion, and mutually-beneficial partnerships. Known as America’s Olympic Network, NBC has broadcast 12 Olympic Games, more than any other network. Its ability to amass large audiences with broad promotion, particularly for the Olympics, has resulted in NBC Sports broadcasting nine of the top 10 most-watched events in U.S. television history, including the 2008 Beijing Olympic Games which stands at No. 1 all time with 215 million viewers. In 2009, NBC Sports won the prestigious Peabody Award for its production of the Beijing Games and was named ‘Best in Sports Television’ at the Sports Business Awards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for Interactive designers with the creative passion, high standard of design, and proven technical ability necessary to successfully extend the NBC Sports brand across a wide variety of interactive promotional materials. The selected candidate will become part of the newly formed NBC Sports Agency, and work with a dynamic, fun, and talented creative team on some of the most exciting projects imaginable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concepts, design, and implementation of flash banners, web interfaces, web applications, online marketing, mobile applications, social media, and new untapped interactive technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and prepare brand relevant key art for use on web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Creative Director, design team, copywriters, producers and marketing to ensure a unified brand look online&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain files and archive for efficient release, sharing, and repurposing with particular emphasis on adhering to rights agreements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead additional interactive designers when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Construct clean, easy readable code, wireframes, flash templates, and timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually source new outlets for photography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications/Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years interactive design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash AS2/AS3, and latest HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with designing and implementing flash banner ads and rich media files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge of HTML5, DHTML, JavaScript, Cascading Style Sheets, XML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of Web architecture, page layout, typography, photo editing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle many projects simultaneously and to react flexibly and immediately to changes that may occur in a fast-paced, deadline-driven team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication, interpersonal, presentation and creative skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Characteristics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College degree in design, interactive graphics, or related field is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile application design &amp;amp; programming experience a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated; work well under pressure; goal-oriented, self-motivated and proactive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great “can do” attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Eligibility Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interested candidates must submit a resume through www.nbcunicareers.com to be considered (job id #8830BR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be willing to submit to a background investigation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be willing to work in Stamford, CT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be 18 years of age or older&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is the policy of NBCUniversal and NBCUniversal&amp;rsquo;s affiliated businesses to consider all qualified applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, national origin, sex (including pregnancy) sexual orientation, age, disability, veteran status or other characteristics protected by law&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-designer-nbc-sports-group-nbc-sports-network-stamford-ct</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-designer-nbc-sports-group-nbc-sports-network-stamford-ct</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Designer Creative Services at Cigna in Hartford, CT</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;THE TEAM&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In support of CIGNA&amp;rsquo;s goals to increase the health, well-being, and security of the individuals we serve, CIGNA sells a comprehensive suite of medical insurance, health advocacy solutions and group insurance products, that address the unique health and financial security needs of individuals.  These products/solutions are sold to employers, government institutions and individuals either directly or through partnerships with Brokers and Consultants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CIGNA Marketing organization partners with Business Units, Sales Organizations and other functional support groups to build the CIGNA brand, products and programs to make CIGNA the preferred brand in the marketplace.  This is accomplished by translating business objectives into effective programs and initiatives, through a combination of applying broad marketing expertise, supported by a robust Business Intelligence competency.  Within Marketing, the Marketing Communications organization is responsible for developing and executing Business and Segment specific Marketing Communications Plans which help retain and grow CIGNA&amp;rsquo;s diverse customer base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You combine a solid design background with a passion for technology. Responsible for the conception, design, and execution of visual experiences for interactive initiatives including websites, microsites, email marketing, mobile, applications, epublications, infographics, banner ads, social and other technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;KEY DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively interprets a client’s needs as outlined in creative briefs and translate them into compelling interactive designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applies design theory and takes into consideration content, navigational structure and usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partners well with copywriter to concept creative, on-strategy ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applies a strong understanding of interactive knowledge, including visual design, front-end development, usability and technology standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of working to deadlines on multiple projects concurrently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to the development of digital standards and procedures for creative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learns about and understands Cigna’s businesses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains stewardship of Cigna’s brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PREFERRED POSITION REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 8years of interactive design, prior experience in an agency setting preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite, Flash; web technologies including HTML, CSS, social, mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work in a dynamic, high-volume, matrix-oriented environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player; enthusiastic, demonstrates a can-do attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently delivers good work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-designer-creative-services-cigna-hartford-ct</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-designer-creative-services-cigna-hartford-ct</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>