<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/dc-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Drupal Developer at Share Our Strength in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Jr. Drupal Developer will lead the functional and technical design, development, testing, integration, and ongoing support of Share Our Strength&amp;rsquo;s platform web sites.​ This role will be responsible for managing, supporting and optimizing existing systems as well as building out new systems. Must have at least three years of experience in front-end development: HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with team members and internal stakeholders to spec out and build front-end web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as the production lead, which includes adding new features and content types, writing and maintaining clean code, and making sure websites function across multiple browsers and mobile devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balance scope, timelines, and meeting deadlines, prioritizing tasks, and communicating in a busy environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively monitor and troubleshoot issues and application performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement web best practices, build products that are strongly rooted in creating seamless user experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in CS or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years web development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of HTML, JavaScript / JQuery, XML, CSS, PHP required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience implementing and developing within Drupal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability in writing standards-based, semantically correct code following SEO best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of cross-browser issues and debugging.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong grasp of the latest web standards and how to code in them (HTML 5, WC3).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of Web 2.0 with an emphasis on social media integration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication/presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to prioritize and manage multiple projects/tasks in a deadline-driven environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in or experience with responsive design a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Convio&amp;rsquo;s API and its integration in third party platforms a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Submit resume, cover letter, salary requirements, and design samples (can be in PDF or URL format) to: jobs@strength.org. Reference job title &amp;ldquo;Jr. Drupal Developer&amp;rdquo; in the subject line. No calls please. Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-drupal-developer-share-our-strength-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-drupal-developer-share-our-strength-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Department Of The Treasury in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of the Comptroller of the Currency is among the top places to work in the federal government. The OCC ensures a safe and sound banking system for all Americans and ensures fair treatment and equal access for all national bank customers. Our culture promotes creative and thoughtful contributions by people in all positions, and an environment that values and encourages diversity. If you are an inquisitive, investigative individual with high standards of your own, consider the OCC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The OCC is a bureau of the U.S. Department of the Treasury, which has a distinguished history dating back to the founding of our nation. As the steward of U.S. economic and financial systems, Treasury is a major and influential leader in today&amp;rsquo;s global economy. We have over 100,000 employees across the country and around the world. Come Join the Department of the Treasury and Invest in Tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is located in the Web and Electronic Publishing Office, Public Affairs Operations. The incumbent serves as an IT Specialist (Web Developer) responsible for developing, coding, and testing of Web pages,reviewing the work of others, implementing user-centered design principles in developing and implementing web sites, publishing and managing content using a Content Management System (CMS), and implementing Web technologies and applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;KEY INFORMATION:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are a &amp;ldquo;status applicant&amp;rdquo; and wish to be considered for this position under both merit promotion and competitive procedures, you must also submit an application under vacancy announcement MP-TW-13-046D. &amp;ldquo;Status applicants&amp;rdquo; are individuals who are current or former permanent Federal civilian employees who hold or held non-temporary appointments in the competitive service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &amp;ldquo;Print Preview&amp;rdquo; to review the entire announcement before applying.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;DUTIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;As a IT Specialist (Web Developer), you will:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs and codes Web pages using best practices related to user interface engineering, accessibility and usability.  Uses programming languages such as XML, HTML, DHTML, JavaScript, and other languages to develop web pages and content. Uses code to automatically include content from other sources via RSS, XML, and similar technologies.  Creates scripts, applications, and APIs using PHP, JSP, and other languages. Troubleshoots code issues, to include reviewing and de-bugging code. Edits source code to place new pages in the appropriate location on the Web site. Publishes pages on the Web server using manual and automated publishing processes. Conducts Web publishing system administration routines and special projects, including daily updating of the organization’s Web sites, maintenance and monitoring of Web services, and general user support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates efforts with network and security specialists to ensure compliance with applicable policies. Develops and oversees the development of templates, content types, and workflows for use in the content management system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plans, executes, and analyzes usability data to design user friendly Web sites and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates information architecture diagrams, navigation maps, wireframes, and prototypes. Tests new pages to ensure correct formatting, display, and properly functioning links. Ensures that new Web pages are consistent with relevant design and formatting standards. Conducts Web quality assurance tasks as assigned. Advises content developers on Web page requirements and coding standards. Reviews and recommends enhancements. Diagnoses and troubleshoots Web site operational problems such as broken links or file directory, server, or application problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engages in technical communities (e.g. seeking peer advice, finding documentation to resolve technical problems). Works within a team of developers to effectively meet deliverables and schedules in a dynamic publishing environment. Accurately tracks and manages project tasks, activities, and documentation. Experience with Web Content Management Systems including Percussion Rhythmyx, XML publishing tools including Arbortext, and e-mail subscription management services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order for your application to be considered, you must meet the following requirements within 60 calendar days after the closing date of this announcement:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position requires General Experience that all applicants must have IT-related experience demonstrating each of the four competencies listed below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to Detail &amp;ndash; Is thorough when performing work and conscientious about attending to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customer Service &amp;ndash; Works with clients and customers (that is, any individuals who use or receive the services or products that your work unit produces, including the general public, individuals who work in the agency, other agencies, or organizations outside the Government) to assess their needs, provide information or assistance, resolve their problems, or satisfy their expectations; knows about available products and services; is committed to providing quality products and services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oral Communication &amp;ndash; Expresses information (for example, ideas or facts) to individuals or groups effectively, taking into account the audience and nature of the information (for example, technical, sensitive, controversial); makes clear and convincing oral presentations; listens to others, attends to nonverbal cues, and responds appropriately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem Solving &amp;ndash; Identifies problems; determines accuracy and relevance of information; uses sound judgment to generate and evaluate alternatives, and to make recommendations.  AND&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have one year of specialized experience at a level of difficulty and responsibility equivalent to the NB-IV level in the Federal service. The experience may have been gained in either the public or private sector. One year of experience refers to full-time work; part-time work is considered on a prorated basis. Specialized experience for this position includes: coordinating daily Web site operations, recommending functional and technical improvements to the Web sites, testing Web pages, publishing and managing content using a Content Management System (CMS), implementing Web technologies and applications, and measuring Web site success.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;AND&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to meeting the specialized experience for this position, applicants must meet the selective placement factor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Selective Placement Factor:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knowledge and experience using Percussion Rhythmyx Content Management System to produce, publish and manage Web sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click &amp;ldquo;Print Preview&amp;rdquo; to review the entire announcement before applying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;HOW YOU WILL BE EVALUATED:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your application includes your:&lt;/strong&gt;
1. Resume, 2. Responses to the online questions, and 3. Required documents. We use a multi-step process to evaluate and refer applicants: 1. Minimum Requirements: Your application must show that you meet all requirements, including the education and/or experience required for this position. You may be found &amp;ldquo;not qualified&amp;rdquo; if you do not possess the minimum competencies required for the position. If your application is incomplete, we may rate you as ineligible. 2. Rating: Qualified applicants will be evaluated in the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe your ability to analyze system requirements for web sites, web-based applications, content management systems or mobile applications; and to design and deploy solutions to meet those requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe your ability to use a Web Content Management System including Percussion Rhythmyx, XML publishing tools including Arbortext, and email subscription management services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe your ability to work on technical projects, and communicate technical issues both orally and in writing to project team members, customers, and stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We may lower your rating if your responses to the online questions are not supported by the education and/or experience described in your application. Category Rating will be used to rank and select eligible candidates. If qualified, you will be assigned to one of three categories (Outstanding, Excellent, or Qualified) depending on your experience and education related to this position. Veterans' preference is applied after applicants are assessed. Preference-eligibles will be listed at the top of their assigned category and considered before non-preference-eligibles in that category. Qualified preference-eligibles with a compensable service-connected disability of 10% or more will be listed at the top of the highest category. 3. Referral: If you are among the top qualified candidates, your application may be referred to a selecting official for consideration and possible interview. If you are a displaced or surplus Federal employee (eligible for the Career Transition Assistance Plan (CTAP)/Interagency Career Transition Assistance Plan (ICTAP), you must be rated as well qualified to receive special selection priority. &amp;ldquo;Well-qualified&amp;rdquo; means that you must be assigned to the Excellent category. We recommend that you preview the online questions for this announcement before you start the application process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;BENEFITS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a workplace that is respectful, fair, and values diversity. Our comprehensive benefits are very generous &amp;ndash; helping you to reach your personal goals by supporting your professional growth, health, well-being, and your family needs. Our benefits package includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ten paid holidays, 13 days of sick leave, and 13 to 26 days of vacation time each year;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to insurance programs that may be continued after you retire;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A wide choice of health insurance plans, coverage for pre-existing conditions, and no waiting periods. We pay a substantial amount of the health insurance premiums;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A performance-based merit pay program designed to reward employees for excellent performance;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free OCC dental and vision insurance, long-term disability, and business travel insurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;OTHER INFORMATION:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Important information regarding Ethics and Conflicts of Interest:   OCC ethics standards generally prohibit employees, their spouses, and minor children from owning securities, such as stock, of banks or savings associations or their affiliates, such as bank holding companies and savings and loan holding companies. While waivers of this restriction may be available in limited circumstances to permit retention of such interests acquired prior to OCC employment, employees may be required to divest these interests. If you or your immediate family own such securities, you should discuss these issues with the OCC recruiter, who can provide you contact information for an OCC ethics official.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation benefits will be paid in accordance with OCC&amp;rsquo;s relocation policy. Free real estate information on job locations is available by calling OCC&amp;rsquo;s relocation management firm at 1-877-237-5068.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We may select from this announcement or any other source to fill one or more vacancies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;CONDITIONS OF EMPLOYMENT:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If selected for this position, you will be required to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete a one-year probationary period (unless already completed).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete a Declaration for Federal Employment to determine your suitability for Federal employment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are a male applicant born after December 31, 1959, certify that you have registered with the Selective Service System or are exempt from having to do so.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have your salary sent to a financial institution of your choice by Direct Deposit/Electronic Funds Transfer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go through a Personal Identity Verification (PIV) process that requires two forms of identification from the Form I-9. Federal law requires verification of the identity and employment eligibility of all new hires in the U.S.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel locally or overnight may be required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obtain and use a Government-issued charge card for business-related travel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successfully complete a background investigation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;HOW TO APPLY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following instructions outline our application process. You must complete this on-line application process and submit any applicable required documents by 11:59 p.m. Eastern Time (ET) on the closing date of this announcement. If applying on-line poses an extreme hardship, you must contact the human resources office no later than noon Eastern Time on the closing date. After this time, requests to apply will not be granted. Treasury provides reasonable accommodation to applicants with disabilities on a case-by-case basis. Please contact us if you require this for any part of the application and hiring process. Hearing impaired applicants may use TDD # (202) 874-5642. Please note that all required documents must be received by the closing date and that we will determine your eligibility and qualifications based solely on the material received by the closing date. Step 1 &amp;ndash; Review the Job Announcement Before you apply, we suggest you review the entire job announcement. Pay close attention to the Major Duties section and the How You Will Be Evaluated section where you will see the areas upon which your application will be evaluated and a link for previewing online questions. Step 2 &amp;ndash; Create or Upload a resume with USAJOBS (www.usajobs.gov)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create or upload a resume in USAJOBS. You may wish to customize your resume to ensure it supports your responses to the online questions and addresses the Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities listed in the How You Will Be Evaluated section of the job announcement. For resume tips, click here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Although you must enter your Social Security Number (SSN) for USAJOBS, we will only see the last four digits for identification purposes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply Online Click the &amp;ldquo;Apply Online&amp;rdquo; button on this announcement and then select the resume you wish to submit with your application. You will be redirected to the Department of the Treasury&amp;rsquo;s CareerConnector website to complete the application process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer the Online Questions and Submit Your Online Application If this is your first time on Treasury&amp;rsquo;s CareerConnector website, you will be prompted to register by answering questions related to your eligibility for Federal employment. The system will save these responses and take you back to the main screen so that you can answer the job-specific questions. Select &amp;ldquo;Take me to the assessment&amp;rdquo; and click on the &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo; button to answer the job-specific questions. You must answer all the questions and click the &amp;ldquo;Finish&amp;rdquo; button.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review and Confirm Your Submission You will now have the option to upload a document or print fax cover-sheets for documents (see Step 6 for details). Once you click &amp;ldquo;Done,&amp;rdquo; you will see a summary of your application for your review. You may also print a copy for your records. When you click &amp;ldquo;Finish&amp;rdquo; at the bottom of the page, you will then be directed back to USAJOBS where you can confirm that your application has been submitted and track your application status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submit Documents You can submit any applicable required or optional documents (see below) by document upload, fax, or e-mail. Whichever method you choose, please include the job announcement number with your documents. To protect your privacy, we encourage you to remove your SSN from any documents that you submit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Document Upload:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may upload documents in one of two ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you finish answering the questions in the job announcement, you will be prompted to upload your document(s) to your application. You will be given the choice to either upload the document as part of the application process or you can select a document that you&amp;rsquo;ve already loaded on USAJOBS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can upload a document to an existing application by logging into your USAJOBS account profile. Click on &amp;ldquo;My Applications&amp;rdquo; and search for the vacancy. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve located the vacancy, click on the vacancy and select &amp;ldquo;Apply Online.&amp;rdquo; Move through your existing application to the Documents page and select Upload in order to add a document to your application. Be certain to review your complete application for confirmation that the document uploaded. In the Application Review section, you may verify acceptance of your documents in CareerConnector if you see them listed on the &amp;ldquo;Vacancy Documents&amp;rdquo; screen. Then, click on &amp;ldquo;Finished&amp;rdquo; to be returned to USAJOBS. Fax: Print a fax cover-sheet in CareerConnector by following the &amp;ldquo;Faxing Supporting Documentation&amp;rdquo; instructions. The fax number will be provided on the cover-sheet. E-Mail: Send your documents by e-mail to OCCHRDEU@occ.treas.gov. We can accept documents in the following formats: PDF or Word.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIRED DOCUMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that all required documents must be received by the closing date and that we will determine your eligibility and qualifications based solely on the material received by the closing date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VETERANS' PREFERENCE DOCUMENTATION If you are claiming veterans' preference, you must submit a copy of your Certificate of Release or Discharge From Active Duty, DD-214 (Member 4 copy), or other official documentation from a branch of the Armed Forces or the Department of Veterans Affairs showing dates of service and type of discharge. Ten-point preference eligibles must also submit an Application for 10-point Veteran Preference, SF-15, along with the required documentation listed on the back of the form. For more information on veterans' preference, click here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CTAP/ICTAP DOCUMENTATION If you are a displaced or surplus Federal employee eligible for consideration under the Career Transition Assistance Plan (CTAP) or Interagency Career Transition Assistance Plan (ICTAP), you must submit proof of eligibility. For a detailed list of documents, click here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SPECIAL APPOINTING AUTHORITIES DOCUMENTATION If you are applying for consideration under a special appointing authority, you must provide the required supporting documentation. DOCUMENTS: In addition to required documents, you may submit the following:
**Cover letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;AGENCY CONTACT INFO:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saundra Keys
Phone: 972-277-9659
Fax: 999-999-9999
TDD: 202-649-6157
Email: OCCHRDEU@occ.treas.gov
Agency Information:
Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC)
225 E. John Carpenter Freeway
Suite 500
Irving, TX
75062
US&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;WHAT TO EXPECT NEXT:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may check the status of your application for this position at any time by logging onto the USAJOBS &amp;ldquo;My Account&amp;rdquo; tab and clicking on &amp;ldquo;Application Status.&amp;rdquo; We also recommend you opt to receive status change emails through USAJOBS by logging into &amp;ldquo;Notification Settings.&amp;rdquo; You will receive final notification via email when this vacancy has been filled. Please notify us if your contact information changes after the closing date of the announcement. Also, note that if you provide an email address that is inaccurate or if your mailbox is full or blocked (e.g., spam-blocker), you may not receive important communication that could affect your consideration for this position.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-department-of-the-treasury-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-department-of-the-treasury-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Acquia in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Web Developer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acquia is looking for a web developer to perform content production, HTML/CSS and CMS tasks in a fast-paced, short-deadline, high pressure work environment. The web developer will support the agency’s digital strategy needs while working with a larger development team to incorporate development efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The web developer will:
* Publish material authored by various stakeholders to multiple web sites under tight deadlines. Published content will take the form of pages, microsites, webforms, RSS feeds, and other web features presenting content and documents.
* Utilize advanced HTML writing and editing skills, advanced knowledge of Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), and intermediate knowledge of JavaScript to support web publishing needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a U.S. Citizen and have the ability to obtain a security clearance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a self-starter that thrives in a fast-paced work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a full-time on-site position located in NW Washington, DC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years of web development experience is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communications required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Drupal and/or PHP is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform basic web development tasks including HTML markup, formatting and presentation using CSS, and implementation of Javascript tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity/experience with Drupal and the Adobe Photoshop Suite is desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working within ticketing systems such as JIRA a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-acquia-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-acquia-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Acquia in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Acquia is looking for a web developer to perform content production, HTML/CSS and CMS tasks in a fast-paced, short-deadline, high pressure work environment. The web developer will support the agency’s digital strategy needs while working with a larger development team to incorporate development efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The web developer will:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish material authored by various stakeholders to multiple web sites under tight deadlines. Published content will take the form of pages, microsites, webforms, RSS feeds, and other web features presenting content and documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize advanced HTML writing and editing skills, advanced knowledge of Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), and intermediate knowledge of JavaScript to support web publishing needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a U.S. Citizen and have the ability to obtain a security clearance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a self-starter that thrives in a fast-paced work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a full-time on-site position located in NW Washington, DC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years of web development experience is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communications required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Drupal and/or PHP is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform basic web development tasks including HTML markup, formatting and presentation using CSS, and implementation of Javascript tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity/experience with Drupal and the Adobe Photoshop Suite is desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working within ticketing systems such as JIRA a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-acquia-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-acquia-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Center for the Study of Services in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Center for the Study of Services (CSS), a Washington DC nonprofit, seeks an experienced, creative, cutting edge web developer to work full-time with our web-development team on implementation of local and national consumer information projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Minimum requirements are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of advanced experience in web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience designing and coding user-friendly and responsive client-side web pages using jQuery, jQuery Mobile, Bootstrap, and HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience developing AJAX and REST enabled web sites in secure environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in XML/JSON, JavaScript, and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ColdFusion/PHP experience (Preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AWS Cloud experience (Preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of SQL and Microsoft SQL Server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to effectively adapt to changing technology and apply it as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local candidates only, no remote workers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Full-time, near metro. Sane hours. Competitive compensation. Only candidates providing a resume and salary history will be considered. Background checks required.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-center-for-the-study-of-services-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-center-for-the-study-of-services-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Applications Programmer/Developer at First Book in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About the position:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First Book is applying technology and business approaches to the challenge of providing all children in the US and Canada with access to books. First Book currently serves more than 20,000 Title I schools, afterschool initiatives, clinics, shelters, and a wide variety of other programs serving children in need. Though powerful, First Book is only reaching a small fraction of the approximately 2 million programs and Title I classrooms eligible for our help. We have exciting opportunities to use technology to serve more and more of these programs and are looking for a Web Applications Programmer to join our technology team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and maintenance of First Book web applications built using open source technologies, custom applications, or new module specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure quality of work through development and implementation of QA procedures and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research, develop logic, code, test, and deploy several Web projects with minimal assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a PHP web application from the ground up, as well as modify and build on existing code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-5 years of Information Technology experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have first-rate knowledge of Object Oriented Programming concepts, HTML, PHP, JavaScript, and MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to work in a structured team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with building highly interactive, highly trafficked, database driven web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong SQL query development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Magento or any ecommerce product is highly desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technical Skill Set&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of object oriented programming and programming principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of the PHP programming language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of HTML, Cascading Style Sheets, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed knowledge of Web protocols and programming requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior familiarity of UNIX operating system (primarily Linux) and Apache&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of MySQL database (developer fundamentals)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Magento ecommerce product suite desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates are invited to submit a resume and a cover letter to jobs@firstbook.org &amp;ndash; please be sure to put WebPrg in the subject line of your email. No phone calls please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-applications-programmer-developer-first-book-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-applications-programmer-developer-first-book-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>