<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/dc-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Acquia in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Acquia is looking for a web developer to perform content production, HTML/CSS and CMS tasks in a fast-paced, short-deadline, high pressure work environment. The web developer will support the agency’s digital strategy needs while working with a larger development team to incorporate development efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The web developer will:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish material authored by various stakeholders to multiple web sites under tight deadlines. Published content will take the form of pages, microsites, webforms, RSS feeds, and other web features presenting content and documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize advanced HTML writing and editing skills, advanced knowledge of Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), and intermediate knowledge of JavaScript to support web publishing needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a U.S. Citizen and have the ability to obtain a security clearance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a self-starter that thrives in a fast-paced work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a full-time on-site position located in NW Washington, DC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years of web development experience is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communications required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Drupal and/or PHP is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform basic web development tasks including HTML markup, formatting and presentation using CSS, and implementation of Javascript tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity/experience with Drupal and the Adobe Photoshop Suite is desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working within ticketing systems such as JIRA a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-acquia-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-acquia-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Center for the Study of Services in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Center for the Study of Services (CSS), a Washington DC nonprofit, seeks an experienced, creative, cutting edge web developer to work full-time with our web-development team on implementation of local and national consumer information projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Minimum requirements are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of advanced experience in web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience designing and coding user-friendly and responsive client-side web pages using jQuery, jQuery Mobile, Bootstrap, and HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience developing AJAX and REST enabled web sites in secure environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in XML/JSON, JavaScript, and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ColdFusion/PHP experience (Preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AWS Cloud experience (Preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of SQL and Microsoft SQL Server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to effectively adapt to changing technology and apply it as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local candidates only, no remote workers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Full-time, near metro. Sane hours. Competitive compensation. Only candidates providing a resume and salary history will be considered. Background checks required.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-center-for-the-study-of-services-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-center-for-the-study-of-services-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Applications Programmer/Developer at First Book in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About the position:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First Book is applying technology and business approaches to the challenge of providing all children in the US and Canada with access to books. First Book currently serves more than 20,000 Title I schools, afterschool initiatives, clinics, shelters, and a wide variety of other programs serving children in need. Though powerful, First Book is only reaching a small fraction of the approximately 2 million programs and Title I classrooms eligible for our help. We have exciting opportunities to use technology to serve more and more of these programs and are looking for a Web Applications Programmer to join our technology team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and maintenance of First Book web applications built using open source technologies, custom applications, or new module specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure quality of work through development and implementation of QA procedures and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research, develop logic, code, test, and deploy several Web projects with minimal assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a PHP web application from the ground up, as well as modify and build on existing code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-5 years of Information Technology experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have first-rate knowledge of Object Oriented Programming concepts, HTML, PHP, JavaScript, and MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to work in a structured team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with building highly interactive, highly trafficked, database driven web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong SQL query development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Magento or any ecommerce product is highly desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technical Skill Set&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of object oriented programming and programming principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of the PHP programming language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of HTML, Cascading Style Sheets, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed knowledge of Web protocols and programming requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior familiarity of UNIX operating system (primarily Linux) and Apache&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of MySQL database (developer fundamentals)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Magento ecommerce product suite desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates are invited to submit a resume and a cover letter to jobs@firstbook.org &amp;ndash; please be sure to put WebPrg in the subject line of your email. No phone calls please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-applications-programmer-developer-first-book-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-applications-programmer-developer-first-book-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>