<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/dc-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at SDL Government in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;SDL Government is seeking a UX Designer in the Washington DC Area to join our platform development team. SDL has a proven track record of success, implementing enterprise software and providing best practices at some of the largest and most well-known companies in the world. SDL Government will do the same in the government sector.   As a UX Designer, you will be a key technical resource for new platform development. Join our company in a fast-paced, dynamic environment with an expanding market, and potential for personal development and growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this position is a hands-on designer, who must be capable of performing UI design, mockups, and wireframes, and seeing those concepts through the development process and into final solutions. The position involves coordinating tightly with other Senior Developers as well as Product Owner and other team members to meet business needs.
You will contribute to UI design and directly implement mockups and wireframes that will guide development efforts on efficient, scalable and performance-ready services and web applications. Previous exposure to agile development methodologies and extensive knowledge of desktop and web-based UI systems highly desired. Must be able to demonstrate prior leadership ability in terms of both technical and project successes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those items are applied here specifically in the areas of machine translation and natural language processing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Product Managers, Product Owners and UI Engineers to develop UX specifications for (wireframes, detailed mockups, prototypes, page flows and personas) and supporting documentation for each release in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation in periodic software development meetings following agile development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis and discussion of internal standards and patterns with development, user experience, and architecture team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with architects to enable instrumentation of products to capture UX-centric metrics, and translate them into future improvements to usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize and conduct active user research and studies to evaluate current implementation and translate findings into design improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong multi-tasking skills and the ability to self-teach are must-have attributes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates must be able to communicate well within a team environment and also work independently on self-directed tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated and creative problem solvers will have opportunities to influence future projects and guide research directions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years designing user experience for web applications (not web sites) with successful market launch of at least one such application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong knowledge of usability, user interactions, personas, information architecture in the context of web applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Solid portfolio of UX work related to SaaS applications for both Enterprise and Consumer market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Good understanding of current web UI technologies/concepts (CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, social media, iPhone apps)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience and desire to learn more about other languages such as C++/Boost, Python, Scala, Javascript, and others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to initially work from a home office in addition to periodic travel to Los Angeles, particularly during initial training period and periodic knowledge exchange&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Must be able to transition soon to permanent job site based in or near Reston, VA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Must be U.S. Citizen with an Active Secret or above security clearance, or eligible for same&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Competitive salary and benefits, and potential for bonuses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About SDL Government&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a technology company that provides language translation solutions for Government Big Data.  We provide a purpose-built United States Government (USG) Language Platformto translate massive amounts of data quickly, accurately and cost effectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Volume, Velocity and Variety of data, multiplied by the number of languages required to protect USG interests, have transformed Government Big Data challenges into Government Big Language™ challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During the Arab Spring alone, social media generated billions of emails, tweets, chats, text messages per hour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In 2006, 80% &gt; of internet content was in English,  by 2014 more than 80% &gt; will be in a language other than English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Cases of our Statistical Machine Translation(SMT) engine include DOMEX; Instant Cross-Lingual Chat; Foreign Media Broadcast Monitoring; Cross-Language Search; Web Monitoring/Scraping in over 80 languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About SDL&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SDL, Plc is the dominant player in the language translation industry.  SDL language technology solutions have been successfully deployed by hundreds of enterprises and government agencies across the globe. Our translation productivity software is used by over 185 thousand professional linguists around the world; and 42 out of the top 50 global brands use SDL, such as Adobe, AOL, Oracle, eBay, Xilinx, Wal-Mart, Cisco, Symantec, Sun, Siemens, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-sdl-government-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-sdl-government-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphics Designer at Fulcrum IT in Bolling AFB, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Serves as a graphic/web/multimedia designer. Provide design to support to high-visibility intelligence products at the client&amp;rsquo;s request. Very strong conceptual design and illustration skills as well as attention to typography and information design required. Working knowledge of web and multimedia technologies and familiarity with publishing and structured authoring software such as SGML, HTML, or XML is helpful but not necessary. Candidate must demonstrate strong presentation, interpersonal, oral, and written communications skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evening/Night shift 3:30pm-12:00 am. Differentials do apply with a 10% differential from 2-10pm and a 15% differential from 10pm-12am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NOTE: A portfolio and/or samples will be required prior to a formal interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of web and multimedia technologies and familiarity with publishing and structured authoring software such as SGML, HTML, or XML is helpful but not necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must demonstrate strong presentation, interpersonal, oral, and written communications skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide design to support to high-visibility intelligence products at the client&amp;rsquo;s request.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency on Mac platform and with Adobe software (Photoshop, Illustrator, inDesign, and Acrobat).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties may be assigned, as necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education/Experience: Bachelor’s Degree with 6 years of experience, AA with 8 years or HS with 10 years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computers: Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe Creative Suite, Experience with SharePoint, proficient on a Mac platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Certificates: None&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clearance: TS/SCI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US Passport: Not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills &amp;amp; Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a self-starter yet comfortable working in a collaborative team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work individually and in a collaborative team environment w/demonstrated customer support skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform at a high level in high ops tempo environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong typographic and design sense with attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to conceptualize illustrations and information design, following through to finished product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of World Wide Web and multimedia technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with electronic publishing and structured authoring software (SGML, HTML, or XML).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired or Preferred Knowledge, Skills &amp;amp; Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Physical Demands &amp;ndash; The physical demands described here are representative of those that must be met by an employee to successfully perform the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While performing the duties of this Job, the employee is regularly required to sit and talk or hear. The employee is frequently required to walk; use hands to finger, handle, or feel and reach with hands and arms. The employee is occasionally required to stand; climb or balance and stoop, kneel, crouch, or crawl. The employee must occasionally lift and/or move up to 20 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If visits to areas of operations overseas are required with this position, you may be exposed to extreme cold or hot weather conditions. Is occasionally exposed to fumes or airborne particles, toxic or caustic chemicals, and loud noise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fulcrum IT Services is an information technology (IT) company based in Centreville, Virginia, that provides IT solutions and services for federal, state, local, and commercial customers. Fulcrum IT specializes in the areas of Enterprise Services, Applications Development, Data Management, Cyber Security, and Intelligence Analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fulcrum IT is an Equal Opportunity / Affirmative Action Employer. M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“CJ”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphics-designer-fulcrum-it-bolling-afb-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphics-designer-fulcrum-it-bolling-afb-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Graphic Designer - Contract at Thelan, Inc. in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Roles and responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The DC.Gov web portal consists of over 100 District agency websites and provides District residents and businesses with online access to government services and information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, OCTO is migrating all DC.Gov websites to its Drupal content management system. This project is scheduled to complete all migrations by September 30, 2013, and includes the DC.Gov home page and resource center landing pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of this redesign of the DC.Gov home page, OCTO is looking for a Web/Graphic Designer to provide their expertise to develop graphic elements and a responsive design for the DC.Gov Portal to be compatible for desktops, tablets, smart phones and other mobile devices. &lt;em&gt;This assignment is expected to last for 2 months&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web/Graphic Designer is expected to have an expert graphical and web design background and good technical knowledge of user Interface development tools. Must have proven experience in visualizing and designing responsive web sites with table-free and CSS controlled layouts. The Web/Graphic Designer will be responsible for the design elements of the DC.Gov Portal with proven ability to design web sites with a focus on user-centric design. A portfolio of high-quality work should be submitted along with the application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web/Graphic Designer should be able to create new designs and redesign and refine our existing site and wireframes and assist with the various phases of the design process, including creating an overall concept for the DC.Gov Portal and landing pages, refining existing website styles and guides, adapt designs for tablet and mobile devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: OCTO will consider applicants who must work remotely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Behavior Characteristics:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent communication skills; able to articulate/present ideas in a clear and concise manner; able to work well with the team and independently. Able to work in an environment with changing priorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 Months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skill set&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite – Particularly Photoshop, Dreamweaver and Fireworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Section 508 accessibility regulations and Plain Language knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usability – Understanding of user testing, standards-based coding and browser compatibility issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 &amp;ndash; Experience using HTML5 in responsive designs and web typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3 – Experience using CSS3 in responsive designs and web typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript – Knowledge in programming using Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XML – Knowledge in programming using XML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP/Drupal Theming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of government operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic design with an emphasis on typography, brand identity and minimalist design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience   5 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-thelan-inc-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-thelan-inc-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer - Responsive Design at Qualcomm in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The DC.Gov web portal consists of over 100 District agency websites and provides District residents and businesses with online access to government services and information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Government of District of Columbia Office of the Chief Technology Officer (OCTO) Web Maintenance Team manages the website content management system; publication workflow; provides editorial and standards oversight for all content; and assists and advises other District projects in integrating new content into the DC.Gov web portal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, OCTO is migrating all DC.Gov websites to its Drupal content management system. This project is scheduled to complete all migrations by September 30, 2013, and includes the DC.Gov home page and resource center pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of this redesign and migration of the DC.Gov home page, OCTO is looking for a Web Designer to provide their expertise to develop a responsive design for the DC.Gov Portal to be compatible for desktops, tablets, smart phones and other mobile devices.  This assignment is expected to last for 2 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Designer is expected to have an expert graphical and web wesign background and good technical knowledge of user Interface development tools. Must have proven experience in visualizing and designing responsive web sites with table-free and CSS controlled layouts. The Web Designer will be responsible for the design and some front-end development of the DC.Gov Portal with proven ability to design web sites with a focus on user-centric design.  A portfolio of high-quality work should be submitted along with the application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Designer should be able to create new designs and redesign and refine our existing site and wireframes and assist with the various phases of the design process, including creating an overall concept for the DC.Gov Portal and landing pages, refining existing website and page template styles and guides, adapt designs for tablet and mobile devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Behavior Characteristics:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent communication skills; able to articulate/present ideas in a clear and concise manner; able to work well with the team and independently. Able to work in an environment with changing priorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;TECHNICAL REQUIREMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite – Particularly Photoshop, Dreamweaver and Fireworks required 6 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Section 508 accessibility regulations and Plain Language knowledge required 6 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usability – Understanding of user testing, standards-based coding and browser compatibility issues required 6 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oral and written communication skills required 4 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 &amp;ndash; Experience using HTML5 in responsive designs and web typography highly desired 3 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3 – Experience using CSS3 in responsive designs and web typography highly desired 3 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript – Knowledge in programming using Javascript highly desired 3 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XML – Knowledge in programming using XML highly desired 3 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP/Drupal Theming required 2 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of government operations highly desired 2 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic design with an emphasis on typography, brand identity and minimalist designr equired 4 Years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;When submitting resumes, please be sure to include and highlight your qualifications related to the position so that your application will not be rejected by the system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-responsive-design-qualcomm-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-responsive-design-qualcomm-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at United States Conference of Catholic Bishops in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About The Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for design, page layout, and print production. Primary work includes project design, page flow, photo research, review of proofs, as well as print production of assigned projects. Work also includes general project coordination as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macintosh capabilities including proven work experience utilizing desktop and illustration software packages (e.g. InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, QuarkXpress, Dreamweaver).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proofreading skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple project management following schedules and budget restraints.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A degree from a four-year accredited college, trade or technical school, or related work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience. Major Field/Specialty: Communication Art, Publication Design, Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About the Employer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The USCCB is an assembly of the Catholic Church hierarchy who work together to unify, coordinate, promote, and carry on Catholic activities in the United States; to organize and conduct religious, charitable, and social welfare work at home and abroad; to aid in education; and to care for immigrants. The bishops themselves constitute the membership of the Conference and are served by a staff of over 350 lay people, priests, deacons, and religious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No telephone calls, please.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-united-states-conference-of-catholic-bishops-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-united-states-conference-of-catholic-bishops-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>