<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/dc-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Assistant Director for Interactive Management at American Constitution Society for Law... in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This is a new position at the American Constitution Society for Law and Policy (ACS). The Assistant Director for Interactive Management will work in the Department of Public Education but will also be responsible for working with the other departments. In particular, the Development Department will play a key role in helping to determine assignments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At ACS, we work in a team environment which requires all team members to be agile in their work efforts and contribute to the group as a whole, stepping outside of traditional silos and working cross-functionally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Web Management&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage all aspects of the website, including new capabilities, feature enhancements, ongoing product management, measurement and refinement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest and implement additions, changes, and upgrades such as streamlined architecture, design and graphic enhancements, navigation improvements, additional tools and new features that will help achieve the organization’s online goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a leading-edge understanding of website management, user experience and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, socialize and maintain a web governance structure and standards based on industry best practices, usability and business needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the tracking and monitoring of web feedback and analyze relevant statistics; make recommendations for enhancement as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help implement outreach and online marketing strategies and online fundraising campaigns to complement the organization’s ambitious program goals and help achieve growth objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and lead online marketing activities including tagging, online advertising, viral marketing, and search engine marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Database Management&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify database requirements by interviewing team; analyzing department applications, programming, and operations; evaluating existing systems and designing proposed systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare users by conducting training, providing information, and resolving problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support all database functions with special emphasis on membership database&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and maintain online constituent databases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist Development Department in executing online fundraising campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Social Media Management&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for understanding the latest social media technologies and “best in class” programs and creating benchmarks, analytics/metrics and policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with the development of innovative and scalable social marketing plans/programs to optimize performance against key performance indicators; think creatively and plan strategically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate best in class practices effectively with teams and organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement social media strategies and report statistics on analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist communications team in expanding social networking efforts, including blogging, Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram, Flickr, YouTube and others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage online communities through unique strategies and campaigns to increase website traffic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop strategies to enhance the e-newsletter and increase open and click-through rates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven expertise in interactive design and the successful application of these principles to web-based product and service creation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal communications and relationship-building skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage and prioritize multiple projects and tasks simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter and creative thinker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;System and tools knowledge: understanding of databases, CMS Systems, Adobe Photoshop, analytics tools, Drupal, Salesforce, Raiser’s Edge, HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong critical thinking and ability to think strategically (and not be driven by tactics)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pro-active and able to manage numerous projects at once&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail; precision and accuracy in tasks; shares our mission&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desirable&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a membership-based organization would be very helpful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent graphic design skills (especially for the web)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Illustrator, Flash and InDesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Success in increasing web traffic, increasing the number of online constituents, and interactive strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creativity and innovation in directing online marketing tasks to complement organization’s mission&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in online advocacy, community-building and fundraising and other web marketing techniques including online advertising, email outreach, social networking, and search engine marketing and optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Javascript, PHP and MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of current legal issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Reports to the Vice President of Public Education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary commensurate with experience. Generous benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter and resume to jobs@ACSLaw.org or fax them to (202) 393-6189.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/assistant-director-for-interactive-management-american-constitution-society-for-law-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/assistant-director-for-interactive-management-american-constitution-society-for-law-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>