<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/dc-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at The Pew Charitable Trusts in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Communications Department&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Communications department plays an instrumental role in positioning Pew to achieve our programmatic and institutional goals. Pew recently completed a detailed assessment of our communications needs and internal structure, and having learned from our past successes and challenges, the department is in the process of reorganizing to improve our efficiency and effectiveness. The department provides a comprehensive range of communications services for all programmatic and administrative units and Trusts-operated projects. Our in-house expertise includes: strategy and message development; editorial support; design and creative services; media event planning; digital and video production and social media. The unit oversees all communications policies, guidelines and processes in order to manage the Pew brand, ensure the production of the highest quality work and effectively steward Pew’s resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Pew Charitable Trusts seeks senior associate, Creative for the Communications department. This new role reports to the director, Creative, and is responsible for front end development of visual solutions for the communications needs of the organization.  He/she applies artistic sensibility, technical skills, communications and problem-solving abilities to advance research and advocacy goals. This position requires the ability to work collaboratively and effectively across a variety of teams and projects with unique topics and objectives. This position is located in the Washington, DC office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The individual must act independently and report regularly to senior staff and team members regarding major project activities. Daily interaction with editorial, creative, and production staff is required. The senior associate, Creative typically provides guidance and direction to lower-level staff. Good judgment and initiative are necessary in coordinating activities and responding to project obligations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data visualization lead from concept to deployment, including all front-end development, QA and data mapping.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work as part of the design team to develop concepts for interactive designs and data visualizations for Pew’s online resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advise design team on technical viability of interactive designs and proposed functionalities on a project by project basis. Includes creative thinking for animations and visual transitions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor development progress to ensure that projects and tasks meet internal deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offer guidance to digital teams efforts to standardize front-end code for site integration and overarching technical requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist digital team in development to help maintain and update email newsletter markup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree and a minimum of four years of relevant, professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to produce forward thinking, efficient, clean, error-free front-end solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of (X)HTML, CSS, JavaScript and JavaScript frameworks (jQuery). Proven ability to translate complex data sets into engaging online data visualizations. Flash knowledge is a plus, but not a requirement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of front-end development techniques used to optimize presentation layer across multiple devices and channels. Strong working knowledge of Adobe Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills, excellent organization, initiative, and flexibility and responsiveness to changing requirements and conditions. Additionally, candidates should work well in a collaborative, team environment, while possessing the ability to work independently as well as set timelines, track progress, lead reviews, and feedback sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Travel&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position will be based in Washington, DC. Occasional travel to Philadelphia may be necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a competitive salary and excellent benefits package, including a generous 401(k) plan, four weeks vacation and flexible benefit options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pew is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-the-pew-charitable-trusts-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-the-pew-charitable-trusts-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Democratic National Committee (DNC) in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a front-end developer to work with our digital team in Washington D.C. In support of President Obama and Democrats across the country, we run one of the most effective, creative, and innovative digital programs in politics. Our digital team will be core to achieving the communications, fundraising and organizing goals of the cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our work is built around Democrats.org and a suite of other digital properties, and we need top-notch developers to help shape it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You should have knowledge of and/or strong interest in:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook and Twitter API integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A/B testing with Optimizely&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web performance optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git/GitHub or other version control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with other digital team members to spec out web applications aligned with our strategic goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeping code clean, and ensuring performance across browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Typography, white space, and other details that occur at the intersection of design and code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing expectations; balancing scope and timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translating requests from non-technical people into very technical products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meeting deadlines, prioritizing tasks and communicating in a busy, fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preference given for experience with:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blue State Digital tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expression Engine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital organizing and fundraising&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jekyll&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SASS/Less&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is at the Democratic National Headquarters in Washington D.C. All applicants must be in D.C. or willing to relocate to Washington D.C.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Democratic National Committee (DNC), is committed to diversity among its staff, and recognizes that its continued success requires the highest commitment to obtaining and retaining a diverse staff that provides the best quality services to supporters and constituents. The DNC is an equal opportunity employer and it our policy to recruit, hire, train, promote and administer any and all personnel actions without regard to sex, race, age, color, creed, national origin, religion, economic status, sexual orientation, veteran status, gender identity or expression, ethnic identity or physical disability, or any other legally protected basis. The DNC will not tolerate any unlawful discrimination and any such conduct is strictly prohibited.
More / LessHow to apply&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To apply, please complete the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.democrats.org/contact/about_jobs&quot;&gt;http://www.democrats.org/contact/about_jobs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NO PHONE CALLS PLEASE&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-democratic-national-committee-dnc-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-democratic-national-committee-dnc-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Resolvit, LLC in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolvit IT &amp;amp; Management Consulting (Resolvit)&lt;/strong&gt; is looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Front End Web Developer&lt;/strong&gt; to work on-site in Washington, DC as a full time Resolvit employee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Front End Web Developer will be responsible for the presentation level of web presence both inside and outside of the CMS. The successful candidate can thrive in an agile development environment utilizing the latest CSS, JS, and responsive design practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The candidate will be responsible for the following areas:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jira to document development progress, code migrations and status on work assignments and communicates these updates during daily stand-ups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews and influences ongoing front-end designs, standards and methods for online presence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops innovative solutions for stable, secure, high-volume web-based applications through our sprint process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Committed to continually learning through actively participating in code reviews and solution demonstrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-call support of front end solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides technical documentation, code comments, and readable code that is properly stored in a version control system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses an intense drive to learn how to improve our core products and services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with UI/UX on critical, large scale web sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing and troubleshooting front end solutions across multiple browsers and devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of the behavior of web application security issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task and grow in a fast paced agile development environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical, written and verbal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years, expert level, javascript and CSS development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of AJAX development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTML5, JSON, XML.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firm grasp of cross-browser JS and CSS complexities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with open JS frameworks such as jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in mobile development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Recommended Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe’s CQ Content Management System.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience  with Adobe’s Test &amp;amp; Target and SiteCatalyst products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with responsive design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Resolvit&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a progressive management and IT consulting firm that helps clients' businesses grow with the power of our people—functional and technical experts who bridge the gap between IT and the business that it supports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our projects focus on software development and infrastructure support in the vertical markets of: telecommunications, healthcare and biotechnology, manufacturing and distribution, finance, media, and government. Our project managers, programmers, designers, analysts, and engineers support Fortune 1000 clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve grown 121% over the last two years. How? We hire the best in their fields—results-focused professionals with skills that are re-deployable from one engagement to the next. Our employees receive excellent benefits to include Health, Dental, Vision, 401K, Tuition Reimbursement and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Resolvit, you&amp;rsquo;ll be one of the people growing our business. We&amp;rsquo;d like to make you part of our success. Contact us to discuss your future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-resolvit-llc-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-resolvit-llc-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Front-End Developer at Onward ITG in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;OnwardITG is partnering with a Global Consulting Firm to provide Technology, Marketing, and Consulting services to the Federal Government. This firm, is seeking a Sr. Associate of Interactive Development to assist with developing the HTML5, CSS and JavaScript code needed to achieve the design and functionality layer of a website they&amp;rsquo;re creating, for the next 3-6 months, with possibility of extension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Main duties and responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front end web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with site developers on given tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examine design compellations to ensure creative can be translated into front-end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with back-end development/developers (code integration)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS2/3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript (jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CMS experience (must be familiar with coding templates for CMS integration)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop or Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-developer-onward-itg-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-developer-onward-itg-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>