<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/dc-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS or Android Mobile Developers at Raretec Consulting in Washington, DC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are hiring experienced iOS and Android Developers. This is a great opportunity for a mid to senior level developer ready to create applications with a great cutting edge organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal potential candidate is innovative, passionate about mobile technology, looks to continue learning and enjoys sharing knowledge and ideas. Strong written and verbal communication are a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;IOS DEVELOPERS:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Links to published apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in xCode, Objective-C, and the iOS Frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing iOS applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of MVC architectures and Web Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in use of modern Web UI frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated and dependable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;ANDROID DEVELOPERS:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of software development experience working with Android devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful track record in developing Android applications (SDK, NDK) with demonstrable portfolio of Android apps you have worked on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with Android APIs and frameworks &amp;ndash; especially the common frameworks and libraries, messaging, networking, web services, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience with various network comms such as SOAP, RESTful APIs,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with server side technology such as Apache, Linux, MySql, MongoDB
&amp;ndash;* Mastery of OO design and design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-or-android-mobile-developers-raretec-consulting-washington-dc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-or-android-mobile-developers-raretec-consulting-washington-dc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>