<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/fl-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP Web Developer at Miles in Sarasota, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Miles markets destinations and hospitality businesses by creating innovative, forward-thinking, integrated online, mobile, email and print content marketing solutions that result in increased visitation, industry participation and measurable results for our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Miles is looking for a full-time LAMP developer skilled in all aspects of web development that enjoys a fun, though hectic and yet very rewarding work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in PHP 5 and object-oriented patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML, CSS, XML, JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge of GNU/Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with relational databases and SQL syntax&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with CodeIgniter, Laravel or another similar MVC framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of JavaScript and AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version-control systems such as SVN or Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with third-party APIs such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube and Google Maps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with jQuery, jQuery UI or similar JavaScript libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with LESS/SASS and responsive web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to maintain and develop existing Drupal projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic Photoshop skills, including the ability to toggle layers, slice images and preserve transparency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Strong communication skills are a huge asset: The developer will be expected to communicate daily with a team lead, as well as non-technical staff, including artists, editors, publishers and project managers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position requires a basic understanding of client-based publishing (i.e. two levels of users – consumers and clients). Candidates must be able to thrive in a fast-paced environment, adapting quickly to changing deadlines and always flexible in shifting tasks to meet deliverables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Miles offers a competitive salary and comprehensive benefits in a fun, dynamic and creative environment. Apply online only at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.milespartnership.com/careers&quot;&gt;http://www.milespartnership.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;, follow the prompts to upload your resume, edit and complete your contact profile, edit and complete our employment application with employment and earnings history, and then answer a brief questionnaire.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-web-developer-miles-sarasota-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-web-developer-miles-sarasota-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Plus Services in Orlando, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain web sites for high profile clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with marketing department to develop visual design of web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with internal developers to create user interfaces for web based applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years of experience in web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent HTML, XHTML and CSS programming skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building of cross-browser and cross-platform compatible solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in debugging CSS, HTML and JS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with javascript and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of web accessibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design sense and ability to create highly usable interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with QA team to ensure products meet desired objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with MVC UI development is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-plus-services-orlando-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-plus-services-orlando-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Plus Services in Orlando, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain web sites for high profile clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with marketing department to develop visual design of web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with internal developers to create user interfaces for web based applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years of experience in web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent HTML, XHTML and CSS programming skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building of cross-browser and cross-platform compatible solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in debugging CSS, HTML and JSProficiency with javascript and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of web accessibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design sense and ability to create highly usable interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with QA team to ensure products meet desired objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with MVC UI development is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-developer-picnicventures-pittsburgh-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-developer-picnicventures-pittsburgh-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>