<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/fl-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Temporary GraphicDesigner-Creative Services at PGA TOUR, Inc. in Ponte Vedra, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We presently are searching for a &lt;strong&gt;Temporary Graphic Designer&lt;/strong&gt; within our &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Creative Services department&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. This position will design print or online literature and collateral materials for all
business units of PGA TOUR. Should be fully capable of using contemporary graphic design software and workstations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create graphic design solutions for projects as requested by supervisor working from sketches, photographs and verbal descriptions to achieve desired results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare all projects for reproduction correctly within established timelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notify supervisor of status of all work projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know current typographical trends and apply to design solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare illustrations ad charts for projects as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommend supplies as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay informed through reading trade publications, other periodicals related to design field and maintain contact with trade membership organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate competent ability with InDesign, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Apple OS, network and other support software needed to complete job requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand functions of all peripheral equipment including scanners, hard drives (internal and external), CD drives and CD read-write devices and PGA TOUR networks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Special Projects or other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualified candidates will have the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or Associate’s degree in graphic design required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 years experience in producing graphics on Macintosh workstations using page layout (InDesign), vector based (Illustrator/freehand) illustration, and raster imaging
(Photoshop) software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work 24-40 hrs/week
Must be proficient with Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, and Adobe Acrobat in an Apple workstation environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to use scanners and networked components like printers and fax machine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General understanding of web software including Dreamweaver and Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know understand typographical resources and font management software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to use email and internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pay rate for this role is $11/hr&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/temporary-graphicdesigner-creative-services-pga-tour-inc.-ponte-vedra-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/temporary-graphicdesigner-creative-services-pga-tour-inc.-ponte-vedra-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Lender Processing Services in Jacksonville, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Information Architect Job Purpose:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provides positive user experience by creating intuitive user interfaces for Web and Mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Information Architect Job Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in user observation, and analyses business requirements to create a user centered design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with the User Interface Information Architect to translate information structures into wireframe models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implements information architecture by preparing prototypes and mockups including page layout and navigational elements. Coordinates with the Information Architect and to produce site concept, visual design, labeling, interface structure, and navigational structure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates graphical elements and icons for use by development  teams to construct software user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updates job knowledge by tracking research regarding web design and usability; participating in educational opportunities; reading professional publications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews completed application screens for adherence to the original design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produces basic HTML and CSS for user interface screens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produces re-usable symbols and UI elements  for leveraging in future mockups and prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to design user interfaces for web, smartphone and tablet devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and experience with interactive usability models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Artistic ability and familiarity with the basic principles of graphic design and color matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Adobe Photoshop and Fireworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand performance needs for users i.e., user workload, user goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with Apple or Microsoft Web usability principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Microsoft Visio and Visio and Adobe Suite graphics programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience with object-oriented design practices and content modeling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience with multiple software interfaces (Web, Mobile, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience using web development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience with Visio and Adobe Suite graphics programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience with HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usability Certification is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-lender-processing-services-jacksonville-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-lender-processing-services-jacksonville-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>