<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/fl-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Bayshore Solutions in Tampa, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bayshore Solutions, a premier Web Marketing and Website Design Company, is happy to announce that it is expanding to the Denver area to better serve its national clients. Bayshore Solutions is headquartered in Tampa, Florida and serves national brands such as Melting Pot Restaurant, JD ByRider, Red Door Spas, and Outback Steakhouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bayshore Solutions was honored by Advertising Age as one of the Top US Interactive Agencies and B to B Magazine Top 20 Interactive Agencies. We also have the honor of being chosen the US Chamber of Commerce Regional Small Business of the Year as well as the Tampa Bay Chamber of Commerce Small Business of the Year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently interviewing potential candidates for the positions of Web Designer and Web Developer. Please visit our website for further details and information for these positions and apply to become part of the growing Bayshore Solutions team! Qualified candidates will be contacted to schedule an initial phone interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe in a fun, team oriented culture. Our associates have a deep understanding of what it means to work as part of a team and inject laughter, humor and passion into their daily routine. Working together, we can create innovative and unique solutions to our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer competitive benefits including low cost employee health care coverage, dental insurance, 401 (k) options, company bonus program, employee of the month parking, free covered parking, monthly lunch &amp;amp; learn and “Towne Hall” meetings, casual Friday’s, recreational game area,  a Health &amp;amp; Wellness committee, Fun Committee and more….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please visit our website at www.bayshoresolutions.com to learn more about these positions and our firm!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Designer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Designer position is responsible for wire framing, creating graphical designs, cutting designs to HTML, and creation of Flash/JavaScript/ActionScript elements based on a define set of business requirements and interaction with the clients/team members. The Designer has an understanding of internet Best Practices, usability concepts, and graphical design. The Designer will collaborate with a cross functional team that includes Programmers, eMarketers, and Project Managers to deliver complete solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties/Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project Delivery – Translate functional requirements into graphical design; establish GUI for the creation of a website and/or a web based application; work with client/team to revise design concepts based on agreed upon direction; cut approved designs to HTML per Bayshore Solutions development standards; Identify potential usability issues within designs; actively style elements from development to ensure design consistency throughout entire project; design various web site elements based on direction from project management; develop CSS/Flash/HTML5/JavaScript/ActionScript elements based on direction from project management; maintain and edit existing websites based on client request; Deliver complete solutions within agreed upon delivery schedules.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business Development/Estimation – Works within the delivery team to contributes tactical solutions based on latest trends, fads, and technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customer Service – Work in a team environment to ensure that graphical designs are in sync with other elements of the project; visualize solutions and communicate ideas within delivery team; identify opportunities to exceed client expectations within applicable project budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership, Innovation &amp;amp; Training – Provide technical and non-technical leadership to assigned projects; Contributes to the intellectual property of the firm while balancing client deliverables; self directs training and research to consistently better ones skillsets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Administration – Record project time into project management software on a daily basis; Meet billable time utilization expectations ensuring individual profitability goals; consistently adheres to Bayshore Solutions’ company policies; demonstrates a positive can do attitude and promotes Bayshore Solutions team culture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and/or Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience designing web sites and GUI using Adobe Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Flash, Illustrator, and InDesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Established technical skills in designing and developing websites using HTML, HTML5, CSS, ActionScript 3.0, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of various Content Management Software (CMS) and integration methods with custom designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-4 years of experience in delivering web based solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-4 years of experience working in a team based environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-bayshore-solutions-tampa-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-bayshore-solutions-tampa-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Media/Web Designer at FIS Global in Jacksonville, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;JOB SUMMARY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for the development of interactive graphics, demos, Web applications, banner ads, e-mails and online marketing needs for Web and mobile/tablet products while ensuring corporate branding is maintained. The position demands a strong creative background and initiative to meet company strategies and goals. Responsibility to use the testing, reporting and statistics tools to optimize &amp;amp; measure creative performance. Candidate must have a strong creative online portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of interactive graphics, demos, Web applications, banner ads, e-mails and online marketing needs for Web and mobile/tablet products while ensuring corporate branding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage day-to-day creative development requests associated with all product lines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance for planning creative campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct regular analysis and provide recommendations regarding creative performance of advertising campaigns, user interaction, response rates, conversion rates, demographics and other key performance indicators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for timely and accurate delivery of all creative needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide variations and options for creative optimization and testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate to ensure designs fit within brand standards and system capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop HTML emails and online digital magazine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other related duties assigned as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS AND ABILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Graphic Design/Multimedia preferred, with a strong interactive portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate should have a strong design background, and be fluent in the interactive portion of the  Adobe Creative Suite applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 or more years relevant work experience in creative marketing services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Html, CSS, JavaScript skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with analyzing site metrics using WebTrends or Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a fast-paced environment and manage multiple, concurrent projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work independently, but also good at collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated and self-disciplined to stay informed on cutting-edge digital technology and design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills that are a Plus:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copywriting experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SEO/PPC strategy techniques and experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Adaptive, Responsive, and other mobile technologies and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video editing and compositing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical website knowledge and server experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Advanced professional role.  Highly-skilled with extensive proficiency.  Works on multiple projects as a project lead or frequently as the subject matter expert.  Works on projects/issues of medium to high complexity that require demonstrated knowledge across multiple communication principles and technologies.  Works under minimal supervision on complex projects.*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ADA Disclaimer:  In developing this job description care was taken to include all competencies needed to successfully perform in this position.  However, for Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) purposes, the essential functions of the job may or may not have been described for purposes of ADA reasonable accommodation.  All reasonable accommodation requests will be reviewed and evaluated on a case-by-case basis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-media-web-designer-fis-global-jacksonville-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-media-web-designer-fis-global-jacksonville-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Community Blood Centers of Florida, Inc. in Orlando, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Responsible for the concept and execution of visual layouts, web pages, and deliverables that support marketing initiatives. Work alongside marketing team to complete various print and electronic design projects and take a proactive role in the concept phase of marketing material development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The list of essential functions, as outlined herein, is intended to be representative of the duties and responsibilities performed within this classification. It is not necessarily descriptive of any one position in the class. The omission of an essential function does not preclude management from assigning duties not listed herein if such functions are a logical assignment to the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Involvement in all phases of design process for print, web and other media, including conception, research, budgeting, design, production, placement and maintenance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and incorporate content and design deliverables into web pages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create designs, concepts, and layouts based on knowledge of layout principles and aesthetic design understanding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm and mock up ideas and present to appropriate customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with creative team and customers to finalize concepts and artwork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Provide general project support to the director of marketing and communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Archive files and manage digital assets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with third party vendors where needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Physical assembly and hands on production when needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures proper operation of hardware and software equipment by completing preventive maintenance requirements and following manufacturers’ troubleshooting instructions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty and responsibility satisfactorily.  The requirements listed below are representative of the knowledge, skill, and/or ability required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;EDUCATION AND/OR EXPERIENCE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum of Bachelor’s Degree in Graphic Design or related field with strong emphasis on web programming and five (5) years Graphic Design /Web experience or an equivalent combination of education, certification, training, and/or experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proficient with Adobe Creative Suite, with emphasis on Adobe InDesign, Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.Working understanding of HTML, experience with Content Management Systems (CMS) and general web publishing ability.Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint and Outlook.Operating system experience on both Macintosh (primary) and Windows (secondary) platforms.Digital photography experience.  Extensive prepress and print production knowledge.Copywriting and proofreading experience.Audio, video and animation knowledge a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;CERTIFICATES, LICENSES, REGISTRATIONS AND DESIGNATIONS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS AND ABILITIES&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of graphic and web design concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of content structure and full command of the English language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write in various styles for diverse audiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to establish and maintain effective and cooperative working relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational and time management skills; ability to adhere to deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skill in operating office equipment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bilingual Spanish preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;PHYSICAL REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work environment characteristics described here are representative of those an employee encounters while performing the essential functions of this job.  Functionsinvolve the ability to exert light physical effort usually involving some lifting, carrying, pushing and/or pulling of objects and materials of light weight (up to 20 pounds).  May involve some climbing, balancing, stooping, kneeling, crouching, crawling, walking or standing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;ENVIRONMENTAL REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work environment characteristics described here are representative of those an employee encounters while performing the essential functions of this job.  Functions are regularly performed inside without potential for exposure to adverse conditions, such as dirt, dust, pollen, odors, fumes and/or poor ventilation, wetness, humidity, rain, temperature and noise extremes, machinery and/or moving vehicles, vibrations, electric currents, animals/wildlife, toxic/poisonous agents, gases or chemicals, oils and other cutting fluids, violence and/or disease, or pathogenic substances.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-community-blood-centers-of-florida-inc-orlando-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-community-blood-centers-of-florida-inc-orlando-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Web Designer at SpectorSoft in West Palm Beach, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;SpectorSoft is looking for a talented website developer/designer to fill an entry-level position within our marketing team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our ideal candidate is a motivated, creative, and detail oriented team player with a great attitude who wants to be a valuable part of our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is perfect for the person looking for a ground floor position with lots of opportunity for growth in a fast-paced creative environment. You will be working immediately on multiple web sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing web sites using HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updating and maintenance of existing websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in HTML5, XHTML, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of web standards and semantic code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery and Javascript experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of browser capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of cross-browser compatibility a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to convert designs into web standards compliant HTML5/XHTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to convert designs into HTML email&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of source control (GIT / Mercurial) a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of web standards (progressive enhancement and graceful degradation a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong desire to stay on top of latest web technologies and development techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong time management and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of graphic optimization and browser limitations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-designer-spectorsoft-west-palm-beach-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-designer-spectorsoft-west-palm-beach-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Temporary GraphicDesigner-Creative Services at PGA TOUR, Inc. in Ponte Vedra, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We presently are searching for a &lt;strong&gt;Temporary Graphic Designer&lt;/strong&gt; within our &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Creative Services department&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. This position will design print or online literature and collateral materials for all
business units of PGA TOUR. Should be fully capable of using contemporary graphic design software and workstations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create graphic design solutions for projects as requested by supervisor working from sketches, photographs and verbal descriptions to achieve desired results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare all projects for reproduction correctly within established timelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notify supervisor of status of all work projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know current typographical trends and apply to design solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare illustrations ad charts for projects as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommend supplies as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay informed through reading trade publications, other periodicals related to design field and maintain contact with trade membership organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate competent ability with InDesign, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Apple OS, network and other support software needed to complete job requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand functions of all peripheral equipment including scanners, hard drives (internal and external), CD drives and CD read-write devices and PGA TOUR networks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Special Projects or other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualified candidates will have the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or Associate’s degree in graphic design required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 years experience in producing graphics on Macintosh workstations using page layout (InDesign), vector based (Illustrator/freehand) illustration, and raster imaging
(Photoshop) software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work 24-40 hrs/week
Must be proficient with Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, and Adobe Acrobat in an Apple workstation environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to use scanners and networked components like printers and fax machine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General understanding of web software including Dreamweaver and Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know understand typographical resources and font management software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to use email and internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pay rate for this role is $11/hr&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/temporary-graphicdesigner-creative-services-pga-tour-inc.-ponte-vedra-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/temporary-graphicdesigner-creative-services-pga-tour-inc.-ponte-vedra-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Lender Processing Services in Jacksonville, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Information Architect Job Purpose:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provides positive user experience by creating intuitive user interfaces for Web and Mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Information Architect Job Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in user observation, and analyses business requirements to create a user centered design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with the User Interface Information Architect to translate information structures into wireframe models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implements information architecture by preparing prototypes and mockups including page layout and navigational elements. Coordinates with the Information Architect and to produce site concept, visual design, labeling, interface structure, and navigational structure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates graphical elements and icons for use by development  teams to construct software user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updates job knowledge by tracking research regarding web design and usability; participating in educational opportunities; reading professional publications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews completed application screens for adherence to the original design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produces basic HTML and CSS for user interface screens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produces re-usable symbols and UI elements  for leveraging in future mockups and prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to design user interfaces for web, smartphone and tablet devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and experience with interactive usability models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Artistic ability and familiarity with the basic principles of graphic design and color matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Adobe Photoshop and Fireworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand performance needs for users i.e., user workload, user goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with Apple or Microsoft Web usability principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Microsoft Visio and Visio and Adobe Suite graphics programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience with object-oriented design practices and content modeling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience with multiple software interfaces (Web, Mobile, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience using web development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience with Visio and Adobe Suite graphics programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years &amp;ndash; Experience with HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usability Certification is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-lender-processing-services-jacksonville-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-lender-processing-services-jacksonville-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>