<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/fl-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Raretec Consulting in Miami, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client a well-funded Miami start-up needs you help to expand across mobile and Smart TV platforms using both an in-house team and third party platform specialists. We are working with cutting edge technology to build an amazing product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need the following skill and qualification to join the team:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Mentality :&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You see mobile as part of a larger experience system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Required Skills :&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Knowledge of Objective C, XCode, Interface Builder and Instruments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building and delivering highly scalable, reliable, and complex software systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of professional software engineering best practices for the software development life cycle, including coding standards, code reviews, source control management, continuous integration, build processes, testing, and operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile/Scrum Methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A commitment to writing quality code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eagerness to learn new things and to help others do the same.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Pluses (Nice to haves):&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience working with Smart TV app platforms like Google TV, Samsung, Roku, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Audio/Video solutions for iOS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-App Purchases and Commerce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribution to open source projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Python, Flash, PHP or SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Your duties will include:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively contributing to a complex, innovative, and exciting new app and browser experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updates job knowledge by studying state-of-the-art development tools, programming techniques, and computing equipment; participating in educational opportunities; reading professional publications; maintaining personal networks; participating in professional organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops software solutions by studying information needs; conferring with users; studying systems flow, data usage, and work processes; investigating problem areas; following the software development lifecycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being constantly vigilant against pranks from your co-workers while simultaneously plotting your own revenge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;What’s in it for you:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performance based workplace with flexible hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly skilled small agile core development team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will be a highly publicized company after launch so you get bragging rights on the innovation front with your friends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flat organization with no politics and a family atmosphere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Killer office space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-raretec-consulting-miami-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-raretec-consulting-miami-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>