<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/fl-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Mobile &amp; Web Developers at Mobiquity in Gainesville, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Remember when every mobile application was &amp;ldquo;out-of-the-box,&amp;rdquo; because no one had ever built anything like it?  Forget that &amp;mdash; remember when saying &amp;ldquo;out-of-the-box&amp;rdquo; was actually an &amp;ldquo;out-of-the-box&amp;rdquo; thing to say?  Then you&amp;rsquo;ll understand Mobiquity&amp;rsquo;s excitement about designing and supporting applications for the old school companies for whom mobile is truly something new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you may have heard, we are planning to open a new Delivery Center in Gainesville, FL. Gainesville is where a lot of the magic is going to happen, and we are looking for bright young minds to help create incredible software experiences that will be touched by thousands, if not millions of people. Bright young minds who have &amp;mdash; or haven&amp;rsquo;t! &amp;mdash; studied the computer sciences, but who most definitely &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; dabbled in mobile / web application development. You&amp;rsquo;re unrelentingly passionate about the mobile experience, whether your course of study focused on the ethical ramifications of the Gaia Hypothesis as it relates to environmental preservation or the leaf depth and familial structure of (a,b) trees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong desire to learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing software using object oriented languages (Java, Objective-C, C++, C#, or similar)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience with Android or iOS software development technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding and exposure to web technologies such as HTML5, CSS and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven understanding of software development techniques, concepts and process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High energy, confident, and ambitious individual&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must consistently perform at the highest levels in a dynamic and fast paced team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a passionate communicator, willing to challenge and enhance ideas while preserving relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science or equivalent work experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Professional Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your career will take off in the Mobiquity Academy program. The selected candidate will receive admission to our Academy program that will provide invaluable professional development opportunities. The Academy offers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An introduction to Mobiquity’s software development process, tools and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development coaching from industry veterans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An opportunity to work collaboratively with other developers in a hands-on environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to focus on and learn technologies that interest you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation and Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer competitive salaries, bonus and a comprehensive benefit program&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Please Respond:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are seeking the benefits of working for an exciting organization and want to be a part of a team of professionals who pride themselves on success and service excellence, please e-mail your résumé and cover letter to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Department of Recruitment, Mobiquity
careers@mobiquityinc.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: The information listed above is intended to describe the general nature and level of this position. Essential functions and responsibilities may change as business needs require.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobiquity is an EEO / AA Employer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-mobile-and-web-developers-mobiquity-gainesville-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-mobile-and-web-developers-mobiquity-gainesville-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP and iOS Developer at Mayors Jewelers in Tamarac, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Mayors is migrating our e-commerce web site to Magento and is currently seeking a PHP and iOS Developer to embrace the new look and feel along with the new architecture and file structure of Magento. The ideal candidate should be an expert PHP programmer and will work alongside our internal IT management and development team to help develop a new PHP based application environment and create necessary PHP programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;In this role,  you will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a cohesive and user friendly PHP application with Magento;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop high-level flowcharts that map work flows and functions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and code new customer facing marketing tools;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be responsible for the look and feel and intuitive flow of the applicaiton;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accept direction for design and aesthetics from IT and Marketing groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;To perform the essential duties of the PHP and iOS Developer, an individual must have:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstratable expertise in developing PHP5-based database-driven applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to hand-code HTML, JavaScript, and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstratable expertise in developing iOS-based applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing Magento based web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to work with heterogeneous systems, including IBM System i (iSeries/i5/AS400) server and DB2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to work at our offices in Tamarac, FL (relocation not budgeted).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;The following attributes are desired:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with MVC frameworks, such as Zend Framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Zend Studio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with AJAX.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency wtih Appcelerator Titanium.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OO Skills (Object-oriented development).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Computer Science or Information Technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to configure AMP (Apache, MySql, and PHP).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please send cover letter, resume and work samples (feel free to include a Web site link to your material in the cover letter).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-and-ios-developer-mayors-jewelers-tamarac-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-and-ios-developer-mayors-jewelers-tamarac-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Raretec Consulting in Miami, FL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client a well-funded Miami start-up needs you help to expand across mobile and Smart TV platforms using both an in-house team and third party platform specialists. We are working with cutting edge technology to build an amazing product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need the following skill and qualification to join the team:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Mentality :&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You see mobile as part of a larger experience system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Required Skills :&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Knowledge of Objective C, XCode, Interface Builder and Instruments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building and delivering highly scalable, reliable, and complex software systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of professional software engineering best practices for the software development life cycle, including coding standards, code reviews, source control management, continuous integration, build processes, testing, and operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile/Scrum Methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A commitment to writing quality code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eagerness to learn new things and to help others do the same.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Pluses (Nice to haves):&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience working with Smart TV app platforms like Google TV, Samsung, Roku, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Audio/Video solutions for iOS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-App Purchases and Commerce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribution to open source projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Python, Flash, PHP or SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Your duties will include:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively contributing to a complex, innovative, and exciting new app and browser experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updates job knowledge by studying state-of-the-art development tools, programming techniques, and computing equipment; participating in educational opportunities; reading professional publications; maintaining personal networks; participating in professional organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops software solutions by studying information needs; conferring with users; studying systems flow, data usage, and work processes; investigating problem areas; following the software development lifecycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being constantly vigilant against pranks from your co-workers while simultaneously plotting your own revenge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;What’s in it for you:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performance based workplace with flexible hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly skilled small agile core development team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will be a highly publicized company after launch so you get bragging rights on the innovation front with your friends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flat organization with no politics and a family atmosphere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Killer office space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-raretec-consulting-miami-fl</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-raretec-consulting-miami-fl</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>