<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ga-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at KickApps in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;KIT digital (NASDAQ: KITD) is a premium provider of end-to-end video technology and services. The KIT Platform, the company’s cloud-based solution, helps media &amp;amp; entertainment, network operator and non-media enterprise clients to produce, manage and deliver multi-screen social video experiences to audiences wherever they are. KIT digital services more than 2,200 clients in over 50 countries, including some of the world’s biggest brands, such as Airbus, The Associated Press, BBC, Best Buy, Bristol-Myers Squibb, Disney-ABC, FedEx, GM, Google, HP, MTV, News Corp, Telecom Argentina, Telefonica, Universal Studios, Verizon, Vodafone and Volkswagen. With its executive offices in New York and operational headquarters in Prague, KIT digital maintains other principal offices in Atlanta, San Diego, Beijing, Boston, Cairo, Chennai, Cologne, Dubai, Ely (U.K.), Hong Kong, London, Madrid, Melbourne (Australia), Paris, San Francisco, Singapore and Stockholm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Webmaster/ Web Developer is responsible for full-time Web development and content and information management. As a dedicated Webmaster and developer, this individual will develop, operate, and maintain the Global OVP Internet Web site and related Web-based software, client websites, portals and associated data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports to: Project Manager&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as technical authority and administrator of the company’s Web site and subordinate Web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as developer of the company’s clients’ Web sites and subordinate Web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance in determining the most appropriate methods for delivering information via the Internet; providing recommendations for improvements, and applying new innovations in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate and notify Web server management for enhancement, bugs, and performance issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide support for third-party apps and integrated functionality from vendors including 123FlashChat, ChatRoll, and Invideous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor Web statistics using programs in hypertext markup language (HTML)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload content onto the sites; enhance and modify the sites periodically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce a consistent visual image by promoting uniform font, format, icons, images, layout design, and modularization consistent with policy, and ensure links are current and active&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain awareness of current innovations and improvements in Web technologies and capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain a strategic plan for the organization’s Internet presence based on client priorities, policy directions, and goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide the capability to be contacted immediately and at all times in the event there is a need for crisis website or content management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Key Challenges You Will Overcome:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acting as a stable force that effectively manages and leads in an environment of ambiguity and rapid change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executing KIT Digital’s vision and goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balancing the importance of business development with execution and operational excellence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College degree preferred. BS in Computer Science or Engineering is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience with developing Web sites in HTML.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of HTML, DOM, CSS, and JavaScript is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of web application development processes, from the layout/user interface to analytics gathering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing Web sites with Expression Engine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with computer graphics and multimedia design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to operate independently and effectively with minimum direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on SaaS platforms highly desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess excellent organization, communication and problem-solving skills and have the ability to prioritize and handle a variety of tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion and enthusiasm for the media / entertainment domains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;WIIFM? (What’s In It For Me?)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive pay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical / Dental / Vision / Life Insurance / 401K benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20 days PTO and 10 paid holidays per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast paced, entrepreneurial environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Massive growth opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respect for your ideas and recognition for a job well-done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International travel opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to the latest cloud computing, video-on-demand, and web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NOT working in a corner cube on legacy solutions that nobody will ever see&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For jobs located in the United States, KIT digital participates in the E-Verify program. Please click the E-Verify link below for more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E-Verify&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kit digital is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. Applicants are considered for all positions without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability, sexual orientation, ancestry, marital or veteran status&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-kickapps-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-kickapps-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Turner Broadcasting in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This position provides high-quality development and support for year round college sports on NCAA.com and associated web products. Projects include streaming video, video on demand, live data streaming, template-driven publishing, design implementation, prototyping, social media integration, automated syndication of content and web analytics. The technology stack includes Drupal as the primary CMS as well as custom-built applications and publishing systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position works closely with a development team using the available infrastructure and provides technical leadership. The Senior Web Developer has specific technical expertise and exceptional personal initiative that they regularly share with the group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;DUTIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop web and mobile dynamic and data driven solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform web development, template development, testing, debugging, integration, documentation and deployment in accordance with industry best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in workflow design and analyze existing production and implementation processes in order to ensure scalable solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor junior web developers on technical issues and modern web development best practices. Demonstrate ability to balance own technical work with mentoring role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently meet or exceed deadlines on projects. Assist in maintaining operational queue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to task identification, work effort estimates, and work schedules for development and maintenance activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in the analysis, definition, and scoping of efficient, cost effective application solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with internal departments to provide associated deliverables required for the successful completion of development and maintenance assignments (e.g. business development, database development, web designers, end-user training).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researches new technologies; provide ideas for technical or workflow / process improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides on-call support as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-7 years experience developing websites for business purposes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with large-scale database-driven web development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong PHP Web application development and support experience, including planning for load, QA and database interaction. Drupal development experience important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of the web and web browsers, their capabilities and limitations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of HTML, CSS, AJAX, JavaScript (and popular frameworks), PHP, MySQL, Perl, XML/XSLT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and critical thinking skills, as well as strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good interpersonal skills, and written and verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize multiple tasks effectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS PREFERRED:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience leading teams of other developers on successful high-profile, high-visibility web projects with advanced caching technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development experience with Drupal, Object Oriented Design, Automation, Unix shell scripting, XSLT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 years of mobile web site development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in all phases of web site development and maintenance life cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EDUCATION:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turner Broadcasting System, Inc. and its subsidiaries are Equal Opportunity Employers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turner Broadcasting System, Inc. and its subsidiaries are E-Verify users.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-turner-broadcasting-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-turner-broadcasting-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at WebMD in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;WebMD (NASDAQ: WMBD) is the most recognized and trusted brand of health information
and the leading provider of health information services, serving consumers, physicians, healthcare professionals, employers and health plans through our public and private online portals and WebMD the Magazine. The WebMD Health Network includes WebMD, Medscape, MedicineNet, eMedicine, RxList, theheart.org and Medscape Education.  Our consumer portals and mobile health applications provide engaging, relevant and credible health and wellness information, personalized health assessment tools and access to online communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WebMD is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About this Job&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Senior Web Developer at WebMD, you will lead efforts in developing lightweight, standards-compliant web programs that will be used by millions of people. You will play a key role in building WebMD products like Symptom Checker, WebMD Communities, and WebMD Mobile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create cross-browser, fully functional web pages using XHTML, CSS, and JavaScript, while strictly adhering to accessibility and W3C web standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with business clients, internal and external, to scope, structure and deliver complex web products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with developers, product managers, designers, web publishers, producers and back-end engineers to support site operations and meet project deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot and resolve code issues, and mentor other developers on best practices and group standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review new code (self and peer) following W3C web standards and strict QA guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support site operations through creating / updating site code and configuring content via in-house CMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Minimum Qualifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in technical discipline or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years relevant work experience (must provide XHTML/CSS/JS code examples)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience hand-coding XHTML using semantic markup, the latest W3C web standards, and CSS layout / positioning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of JavaScript and jQuery coding patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience providing Technical Leadership by setting and enforcing coding standards across an ongoing program of development, and mentoring developers on growth of skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to lead work efforts across an organization and drive communications with a variety of clients, including functioning as a Scrum Master&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated technical growth and specialization of skills within web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years relevant work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of HTML5, CSS3 and XSL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with an Javascript MVC framework such as Backbone.js, Spine.js, Ember.js, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with client side templating like Handlebars.js, Mustache.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep experience developing modular, object-oriented JavaScript applications and concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge and real-world experience working with XSL, XSLT, and XML stylesheets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert working knowledge of WCAG/508 compliance and accessibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with large scale Content Management Systems in support of an enterprise, public-facing website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-webmd-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-webmd-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>