<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ga-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>User-Interface Art Director eCommerce at Carters, Inc in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Carter&amp;rsquo;s, Inc. (NYSE:CRI), is the largest branded marketer in the United States of apparel and related products exclusively for babies and young children. The Company owns the Carter&amp;rsquo;s and OshKosh B'gosh brands, two of the most recognized brands in the marketplace. These brands are sold in leading department stores, national chains, and specialty retailers domestically and internationally. They are also sold through more than 600 Company-operated stores in the United States and Canada and on-line. Carter&amp;rsquo;s is headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia. If you dream of working with innovative colleagues who support and inspire you, Count on Carter&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The eCommerce Art Director (UI) is responsible for gathering, understanding and translating business requirements into digital experiences across multiple channels including web, mobile, tablet, kiosk and social.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the eCommerce Creative Director, this position will work closely with teams inside and outside of Design including Brand, Site Operations, Development, Marketing and others depending on individual project needs. The ideal candidate will be an expert in all topics related to user experience strategy, interface design, user-centered design, information architecture and usability. The candidate will consistently generate new ideas, approaches and strategies that further the online experience for both brands and utilize industry best practices/UI standards to define and implement user interfaces that effectively communicate to our consumer audience. A firm understanding of user-centered design processes and interaction design principles will be crucial in this role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leveraging a strong conceptual and visual design background that includes typography, color theory, illustration, photography, video, animation and interactivity; the Art Director (UI) will lead rapid-design concepting, the maintaining a formal digital design style guide, cross-team collaboration, and articulation of design rationale and presentations of design work. Also, this is a hands-on position, requiring the ability to create &amp;ldquo;prototypical&amp;rdquo; design work that reinforces a conceptual vision for the rest of the creative team to extend those designs and concepts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create compelling interactive experiences for websites/microsites, smartphone, tablet, email, online advertising and social&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and create innovative concepts in keeping with project scope, strategic positioning, and timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop user interface solutions and enhanced navigation systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with User Experience (UX) team to breath life into site maps, wireframe and schematics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage research and analytics to create, refine and enhance brand experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead other creative team members in creative exploration and campaign creation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in Functional Specifications and Business Requirements definition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present user interface recommendations to internal and external teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface extensively with UX and functional users to confirm the applicability of design alternatives, identify and recommend options, and address user concerns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead other designers in exploration and production of site enhancements and campaign creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience and Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven strong conceptual and strategic thinking skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert-level proficiently with Photoshop, Flash, Dreamweaver and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have significant experience in information design, user interface design, human computer interaction and/or usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adept with HTML, CSS, and Javascript. Ideally experienced with HTML 5, video production and motion graphics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have deep knowledge in areas of responsive design, ecommerce and/or large site design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal and problem solving skills necessary to interface with all levels of the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexibility and the ability to multi-task in a fast paced deadline driven environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong team player with enthusiasm, positive attitude and high level of initiative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Graphic Design, Web Design, Human Computer Interaction or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience directly designing interfaces for web and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience working as a Senior Designer/Art Director in the interactive space or other relevant areas experience in a web-based corporation, interactive agency, or internet retailer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of web technologies and how to design for them; Flash, plus traditional desktop and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written, presentation and problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your interest in Carter&amp;rsquo;s. Carter&amp;rsquo;s is an Equal Opportunity Employer committed to a diverse and inclusive work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visit http://carters.submit4jobs.com/ today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-art-director-ecommerce-carters-inc-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-art-director-ecommerce-carters-inc-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director, UX at Moxie in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Moxie Interactive is looking for a strategic-minded user experience professional to partner with us in designing user-focused online, mobile and out-of-home experiences and systems. Creativity, innovation and “moxie” are our key assets as we build the next gen digital experiences for our clients. The architect must be a motivated self-starter who is able to work individually and collaborate with other team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills, Abilities &amp;amp; Competencies:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show enthusiasm, creativity and knowledge of cutting-edge technology and campaigns when brainstorming new projects with our teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Express designs through wireframes, site maps, schematics, flow charts, storyboards, prototypes, interaction specifications and other artifacts to describe the intended user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define site architecture and navigation that serves as a blueprint upon which all other aspects are built.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with our IT and Creative teams to insure best UX practices are followed on all projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in internal and client reviews with teams and clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent wireframing, site map and diagramming skills (Visio, Omnigraffle, iRise, etc. ).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive wireframing/prototyping skills (Flash Catalyst, Balsamiq, Microsoft Expressions, Axure).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of site design; mastery in principles of Web design (HTML, CSS, Flash).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design skills and knowledge of design software (Photoshop, Illustrator, Fireworks, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of user interface design processes and methodology. Experience creating user models, including persona and scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication skills, leadership and interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to closely collaborate with other disciplines, including business analysis, project management, technical architecture and engineering. Ability to work with teams a must!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable in a fast-paced, flexible and creative environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with designing for mobile devices (iPhone or Android apps) or OOH a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with pattern libraries and Visio stencil libraries a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of BS or BA degree in relevant field. Master’s degree a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on large, complex web sites. Ecommerce and agency experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All interview candidates must be prepared to show a portfolio of representative past work such as wireframes, user flows, site maps, and writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of BS or BA degree in relevant field. Master’s degree a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on large, complex web sites. Ecommerce and agency experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent wireframing, site map and diagramming skills (Visio, Omnigraffle, iRise, etc. )&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-ux-moxie-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-ux-moxie-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>