<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ga-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Capgemini in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Capgemini, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost providers of consulting, technology and outsourcing services, enables its clients to transform and perform through technologies. Capgemini provides its clients with insights and capabilities that boost their freedom to achieve superior results through a unique way of working &amp;ndash; the Collaborative Business Experience &amp;ndash; and through a global delivery model called Rightshore®, which aims to offer the right resources in the right location at competitive cost. Present in 40 countries, Capgemini reported 2011 global revenues of EUR 9.7 billion and employs over 120,000 people worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capgemini US LLC and its U.S. affiliates are EEO/AA employers.  Capgemini conducts all employment-related activities without regard to race, religion, color, national origin, age, sex, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity/expression, disability, citizenship status, genetics, or status as a Vietnam-era, special disabled and other covered veteran status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the Capgemini Technology Services Group, this person will be responsible for developing software solutions. This person will work closely with our clients and must demonstrate professional knowledge to ensure that the work products and deliverables are of the highest caliber to ensure client satisfaction. This person will also apply subject matter expertise to identify, develop, and implement techniques to improve engagement productivity, increase efficiencies, mitigate risks, resolve issues, and optimize cost savings and efficiencies for each client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has strong understanding of major iOS Design &amp;amp; Development paradigms spanning User Experience (native, HTML 5/Webkit), web services (REST &amp;amp; JSON), etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executes complete life cycle for complex application components based on functional requirements; considers device capacity and limitations, operating time, and form of desired results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepares detailed specs from which programs will be written; designs, codes, tests, debugs, documents, &amp;amp; maintains those programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzes and revises existing system logic; assists in development and documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzes functional design/overall application technical design and develops detailed module technical specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Codes moderately complex application components based on design specs, while adhering to defined programming standards, structured coding techniques, and development methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience with mobile applications (iPhone, Android, Windows Mobile)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience with Objective-C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Subversion, SQL, XML, JSON and Web Services (ReST)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Ajax, HTML5, CSS, and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technology:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing software solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with business requirements, technical analysis and design, coding, testing, and implementation of customizations within software environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing reports, workflows and metrics within software environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of categorizing and prioritizing analysis and mapping workload for planning and forecasting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of integration points and the order in which these must be executed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with design, implementation, and support of knowledge management solutions and related technologies for collaborative information sharing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with gap analysis and strategic roadmap/blueprint development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with large Full Life Cycle (FLC) project implementations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Delivery:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience within a delivery role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with client facing consulting engagements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience within management consulting or consulting services (Big 4 preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Soft Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong executive presence and ability to interact with CxO level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentors team members in technology, architecture and delivery of applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful teamwork experience and demonstrated leadership abilities are required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates a shared sense of direction and community among the teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to transfer knowledge and stay aware of current trends and technical advancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to articulate and present different points-of-views on various technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time management skills are a must; as well as the ability to be flexible and creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MUST be willing to travel extensively, up to 100%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College degree in a related area of study, with advanced degree highly preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong track record of professional success, preferably in the Consulting Services arena&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-capgemini-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-capgemini-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile / Web UI Developer at Merlin Mobility in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merlin Mobility is looking for a Mobile and Web User Interface Developer to play a significant role developing the front-end and mobile components of our unique web-based platform for augmented reality content development. This mid-level position presents an opportunity to strongly influence the design and functionality of our groundbreaking mobile AR player and associated 3D web-based application both leveraging the latest technologies and standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing and coding our web-based AR CMS and authoring platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing interactive web-based 3D content manipulation system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing mobile UI for delivering and interacting with mobile AR content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing and maintaining company web presence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years web and mobile UI development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated high-visibility web/mobile portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript with client/server side MVC frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in cross-browser compliance and cross-platform applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong demonstrated UI design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to Have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science or BFA in Interactive Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of 3D web tech (i.e. WebGL, Canvas, Three.js)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with GUI development in Unity Game Engine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interest in 3D/AR user interface development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with agile development and version control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preference for local applicants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At merlinmobilityTM, we use Augmented Reality (AR), to deliver technical instructions to iOS and Android devices. Equipment, devices or parts are viewed &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; through the camera of a mobile device. While viewing, a transparent layer appears, providing step-by-step instructions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studies demonstrate that 82% of learners struggle making the mental jump from traditional instructions to the physical object they are working on. merlinmobilityTM eliminates this hurdle by displaying instructions in situ, or &amp;ldquo;directly over&amp;rdquo; the subject matter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-ui-developer-merlin-mobility-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-ui-developer-merlin-mobility-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile / Web UX / UI Designer at Merlin Mobility in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merlin Mobility is looking for a Mobile and Web User Experience and Interface Designer to play a significant role designing the front-end and mobile interfaces for our unique web-based augmented reality content development toolset. This position presents an opportunity to strongly influence the look and feel of our groundbreaking mobile AR platform and create rich 3D and AR user interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing web-based AR CMS and authoring platform user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing web-based 3D content manipulation system interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing mobile UI for delivering and interacting with mobile AR content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing and maintaining company web presence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Image manipulation and general graphic design duties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years practicing mobile and/or web-based UI design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated high-visibility web/mobile portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to maintain design consistency via the use of style guides, style sheets and enforcement of established standards and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to assess, analyze, think and speak critically about visual issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled in developing wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Photoshop, Illustrator and wireframe tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to Have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BFA in Graphic/UX/UI design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript with client/server side MVC frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in cross-browser compliance and cross-platform applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in 3D/AR user interface development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with agile development and version control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preference for local applicants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At merlinmobilityTM, we use Augmented Reality (AR), to deliver technical instructions to iOS and Android devices. Equipment, devices or parts are viewed &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; through the camera of a mobile device. While viewing, a transparent layer appears, providing step-by-step instructions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studies demonstrate that 82% of learners struggle making the mental jump from traditional instructions to the physical object they are working on. merlinmobilityTM eliminates this hurdle by displaying instructions in situ&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-ux-ui-designer-merlin-mobility-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-ux-ui-designer-merlin-mobility-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Mobile / Web UX / UI Designer at Merlin Mobility in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merlin Mobility is looking for a Senior Mobile and Web User Experience and Interface Designer to play a significant role designing the front-end and mobile interfaces for our unique web-based augmented reality content development toolset. This position presents an opportunity to strongly influence the look and feel of our groundbreaking mobile AR platform and create rich 3D and AR user interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing web-based AR CMS and authoring platform user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing web-based 3D content manipulation system interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing mobile UI for delivering and interacting with mobile AR content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing and maintaining company web presence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years practicing mobile and/or web-based UI design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated high-visibility web/mobile portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to maintain design consistency via the use of style guides, style sheets and enforcement of established standards and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to assess, analyze, think and speak critically about visual issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled in developing wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Photoshop, Illustrator and wireframe tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to Have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MS/MFA in UX/UI design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript with client/server side MVC frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in cross-browser compliance and cross-platform applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in 3D/AR user interface development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with agile development and version control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preference for local applicants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At merlinmobilityTM, we use Augmented Reality (AR), to deliver technical instructions to iOS and Android devices. Equipment, devices or parts are viewed &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; through the camera of a mobile device. While viewing, a transparent layer appears, providing step-by-step instructions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studies demonstrate that 82% of learners struggle making the mental jump from traditional instructions to the physical object they are working on. merlinmobilityTM eliminates this hurdle by displaying instructions in situ, or &amp;ldquo;directly over&amp;rdquo; the subject matter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-web-ux-ui-designer-merlin-mobility-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-web-ux-ui-designer-merlin-mobility-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Mobile / Web UI Developer at Merlin Mobility in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merlin Mobility is looking for a Senior Mobile and Web User Interface Developer to play a significant role developing the front-end and mobile components of our unique web-based platform for augmented reality content development. This mid-level position presents an opportunity to strongly influence the design and functionality of our groundbreaking mobile AR player and associated 3D web-based application both leveraging the latest technologies and standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing and coding our web-based AR CMS and authoring platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing interactive web-based 3D content manipulation system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing mobile UI for delivering and interacting with mobile AR content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing and maintaining company web presence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years web and mobile UI development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated high-visibility web/mobile portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript with client/server side MVC frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in cross-browser compliance and cross-platform applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong demonstrated UI design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to Have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MS in Computer Science or MFA in Interactive Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of 3D web tech (i.e. WebGL, Canvas, Three.js)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with GUI development in Unity Game Engine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interest in 3D/AR user interface development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with agile development and version control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preference for local applicants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At merlinmobilityTM, we use Augmented Reality (AR), to deliver technical instructions to iOS and Android devices. Equipment, devices or parts are viewed &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; through the camera of a mobile device. While viewing, a transparent layer appears, providing step-by-step instructions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studies demonstrate that 82% of learners struggle making the mental jump from traditional instructions to the physical object they are working on. merlinmobilityTM eliminates this hurdle by displaying instructions in situ, or &amp;ldquo;directly over&amp;rdquo; the subject matter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-web-ui-developer-merlin-mobility-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mobile-web-ui-developer-merlin-mobility-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Application Developer at Cisco Systems in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;For years, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s vision has been to change the way the world works, lives, plays, and learns. Our vision is more relevant today than ever. We made the Internet what it is today. First, we focused on creating connectivity. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re entering the Internet of Everything transition—an era where we&amp;rsquo;ll help create unprecedented value by connecting the unconnected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Everything is a global industry phenomenon that is driving the biggest market transition for Cisco and our customers. This includes the intelligent connection of people, process, data, and things. It&amp;rsquo;s where everything is converged on the Internet, making networked connections more relevant and valuable than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cisco Service Provider Video Technology Group (SPVTG) is a world leader in software solutions for broadcast television and broadband media. Our cutting edge products include conditional access, interactive television and data broadcast systems. Our technologies are transforming how service providers and media companies deliver next-generation video experiences to millions of consumers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of SPVTG, the Professional Services group provides end-to-end video solutions for the global television industry from in home set-top boxes, mobile and tablet to broadcast software on various digital TV platforms including cable, satellite, and broadband networks. We simplify convergence by delivering broadcast, on-demand, and OTT content using multiple platforms to multiple devices enabling content to be enjoyed anywhere, anytime, on any device. We have an opportunity for a Android Application Developer to work in our Atlanta, GA office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis of new requirements from clients and internal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing components and defining external interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing part of a subsystem or complex components including all supporting tests and documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining existing code as required and advocating for improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining a commitment to a quality approach to software development, leading reviews and ensuring the quality of development and test activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritizing a busy work schedule to meet tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeping ahead of emerging technologies and gives significant input during technical discussions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years experience developing with the Android SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A well versed understanding of the Android UI design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to take standard Android UI components and build custom UI components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/Masters in Computer Science, software engineering, or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Published at least one app to the Google Play store (Must be able to showcase and explain an Android application you have worked on during the Interview)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to take standard Android UI components and build custom UI components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-application-developer-cisco-systems-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-application-developer-cisco-systems-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior iOS Developer at AKQA, Inc. in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;AKQA is a global interactive agency that uses innovative ideas and technology to deliver results for the world&amp;rsquo;s leading brands. For more than a decade, AKQA has been recognized as a pioneer and innovator, providing marketing, digital product design and e-commerce solutions to clients. Our global staff of more than 900 people is located in seven offices including San Francisco, New York, Washington, D.C., London, Amsterdam, Berlin and Shanghai.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AKQA&amp;rsquo;s objective has never been to be &amp;ldquo;bigger&amp;rdquo; than anyone else. Just better. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s the ideas we generate or our world-class implementations, this objective makes us focus on what&amp;rsquo;s important: the quality of our solutions. We want the best talent for the most rewarding and challenging jobs anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AKQA is looking for a Senior Creative Developer with a strong dedication to recent and upcoming technologies. You will have the drive to develop innovative technical solutions that may have not been created before. As a member of the AKQA Technology team you must be inspired by technology and have a passion for creating innovative technical solutions. You will contribute to AKQA’s founding values – Innovation, Service, Quality and Thought and will be excited about being part of our success.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-akqa-inc-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-akqa-inc-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Developer Web and Mobile at Collinson Media in Norcross, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Collinson Media and Events is one of the nation&amp;rsquo;s fastest-growing media companies specializing in destination marketing. Its major interests include digital programs and solutions, meetings business magazines and trade shows, travel guides for newspapers and leisure magazines, and destination information distribution through broadcast and custom programs — all surrounding tourism, travel, meetings and conventions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an experienced developer to design, code and maintain online and mobile websites, mobile web applications and native device applications for the iPhone, iPad, and Android platforms.  Excellent communication and time management skills required in addition to technical expertise.  The ideal candidate will be a strong team player and self-motivated, able to rapidly adapt to changing business and customer demands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Minimum qualifications required:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience with the web/software development cycle: product specification, design, implementation, QA, launch, and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of mobile application development experience for iOS and Android platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Desired Skills / Platforms:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drupal / Joomla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordpress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL Database Architecture &amp;amp; Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile Development (iOS, Android and mobile web)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Bonus Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User Interface Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Programming for SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information Architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Aesthetic Sense&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Additional Information All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/developer-web-and-mobile-collinson-media-norcross-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/developer-web-and-mobile-collinson-media-norcross-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UI/UX Web and Mobile Developer (Mobile) at U.S. Bank in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About Elavon&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elavon provides end-to-end payment processing services to merchants and financial institutions in the United States, Brazil, Canada, Mexico, Puerto Rico, and throughout Europe. Our payment products are supported by the most reliable network in the industry and include credit and debit card processing, electronic check services, gift cards, dynamic currency conversion, multi-currency support, and cross-border acquiring. We handle every aspect of the acquiring relationship—transaction processing, risk and underwriting, settlement, equipment deployment, chargeback management, reporting, and customer service. Our customers can also count on us to keep their payment processing compliant with changing payment security requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elavon employs about 3,600 people located worldwide. Together, we support more than one million clients spread among the retail, restaurant, hospitality, government, healthcare, education, and e-commerce sectors. Elavon utilizes a white-label branding model, and we work with strong partners to market our services through a variety of sales channels, including large financial institutions, community banks, trade associations, government agencies, and ISOs/MSPs. We are the:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 airline processor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 hospitality processor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 U.S. acquirer, based on bank card volume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 European acquirer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Elavon’s Global Acquiring Solutions organization is part of U.S. Bank’s Payment Services division. U.S. Bancorp is the fifth-largest commercial bank in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elavon launched a global cross-functional team focused on launching revenue generating mobile commerce products. The focus of this team will include mobile payments, mobile payment acceptance, integrated value-add services and other adjacent technologies in conjunction with the Mobile Commerce Strategy of the Elavon business.  The specific product focus will be on products and solutions related to the evolution at the point-of-sale (POS) and the interactive payment experience on smartphones and tablet devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;UI/UX Web and Mobile Developer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Scope:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Owner of and accountable for UI/UX design, wire frames and team marketing presence on web and mobile products developed within the Mobile Commerce Solutions cross-functional team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within a cross-functional team in an Agile/SCRUM development cycle to deliver industry-leading innovation around payments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in turning user stories into wireframes to create a holistic visual understanding of the desired solution prior and during Agile sprints around Web and Mobile development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate your own understanding of user problems and opportunities for improvement and share your insights;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate business needs and product requirements into best-in-class, user-focused, and intuitive user experiences;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm and mock up interaction and interface design ideas within the cross-functional team;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present ideas and adjust designs based on feedback;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Envision, design, and iterate by building prototypes, rapidly-producing, multiple possible approaches for internal review and usability testing;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Product Managers to create visuals for incorporating into product specifications;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design current interfaces while planning for the direction of future iterations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively and closely with the visual design team as UX/UI is integrated into finished web pages and mobile applications;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the engineering team during the development process to ensure that designs are properly implemented and to maximize usability and performance;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop Information Architecture documentation including site maps, user flows, schematics, and navigation models;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with the design of product marketing, sales documentation, conference-related material, and other go-to-market articles; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Successful applicants will exemplify US Bank&amp;rsquo;s ethical principles of uncompromising integrity, respect for others, accountability for decisions and actions, and good citizenship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Your Career is Here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic Requirements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A bachelor’s degree in computer science, engineering, finance, accounting, or other business- or technology-related field, including:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of five years of UI/UX experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level with Adobe Photoshop or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web, Mobile, and Tablet (iOS and Android) design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of CSS2/CSS3 and HTML (HTML5 and JavaScript a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly proficient at creating wireframes, mockups, and prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile (e.g. SCRUM), iterative and Waterfall software development certifications and/or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal, verbal, and written communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership, influencing, decision, problem-solving, and strategic management skills to facilitate working in a global, cross-functional team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work well with a variety of personalities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PC proficiency using a variety of software packages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limited to moderate travel – 0-25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualification&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MBA attainment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-ux-web-and-mobile-developer-%28mobile%29-u.s.-bank-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-ux-web-and-mobile-developer-%28mobile%29-u.s.-bank-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Cognizant in Atlanta, GA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a strong iOS developer for one of our retail clients in Atlanta, GA*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Must Have Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong hands-on iOS development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in leading and executing end-to-end Mobile projects including web-service integration, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity to advanced iOS concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding communication skills and ability to articulate best practices in design and development of iOS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good exposure to trends in Mobility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Roles / Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with customers on their mobility initiatives and contribute towards development on mobile website and mobile application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate capabilities in best programming practices in iOS, coding standards and guidelines for iOS projects, optimized ways of design and code development for Mobility engagements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Organization Marketing Statement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cognizant (NASDAQ: CTSH) is a global IT services and business process outsourcing solutions provider headquartered in Teaneck, N.J. Founded in 1994 as an IT development and maintenance services arm of The Dun &amp;amp; Bradstreet Corporation, the company spun-off as an independent organization two years later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since 1996, Cognizant has worked closely with large organizations to help them build stronger, more efficient, and agile businesses. By leveraging highly flexible business processes, a seamless global delivery network as well as deep domain expertise, Cognizant delivers a better ‘return on outsourcing’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cognizant is an Equal Opportunity Employer M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree with 4-7 years of experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-cognizant-atlanta-ga</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-cognizant-atlanta-ga</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>