<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/hi-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Ruby On Rails Web Developer at Wall-to-Wall Studios in Honolulu, HI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Wall-to-Wall Studios (W|W) is looking for a Web Developer to fill an immediate position. Among the wide gamut of web-based projects on our docket, we also maintain a CMS built in-house and tailored to our clients' needs. Our technology stack includes Ruby on Rails, PHP, CakePHP, MySQL, Git, jQuery, OS X, Linux, and more. This is a position in which self-starters and people passionate about the Web will thrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wall-to-Wall Studios (&lt;a href=&quot;http://walltowall.com&quot;&gt;http://walltowall.com&lt;/a&gt;) is a multidisciplinary creative branding and interactive agency. Founded in 1992, we are a boutique strategic firm located in Honolulu, HI and Pittsburgh, PA. Our work spans many industries, and our clients are just as diverse &amp;ndash; big, small and in between; local, regional and national. We have experience representing the full emotional and aesthetic spectrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an award-winning, independent agency, we work closely with our clients to produce smart, branded and interactive solutions with consistent, targeted messaging that reinforces strong customer relationships. Our marketing initiatives create awareness, build brands, drive acquisitions, and identify customer behavior &amp;ndash; delivering real results to our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(THIS POSITION IS FOR OUR HONOLULU OFFICE. APPLICANTS NOT RESIDING IN THE STATE OF HAWAII NEED NOT APPLY. YES, WE KNOW YOU&amp;rsquo;VE ALWAYS WANTED TO MOVE HERE, BUT NO RELOCATION PACKAGE IS PROVIDED. )&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact with clients — Join our team in meeting with clients, filtering feedback, and presenting jaw-dropping work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a team player from beginning to end — Collaborate with our team of talented designers and account managers to work from initial client concepts to a final production ready website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frontend Development — Use your constantly increasing mental database of HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript frameworks to craft beautiful and usable interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Backend Development — Develop high-quality web applications while improving and maintaining an existing MVC code base in Ruby on Rails and PHP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Server administration — Deploy websites and applications into a LAMP environment. Fine-tune and improve server architecture with benchmarking and load testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication — Effectively communicate technical details to non-technical team members and clients. Must be able to give explanations in a compelling, articulate, and occasionally comedic manner via email.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The ideal candidate will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be well-versed in object-oriented programming and have intermediate to expert-level skills in a language like PHP, Ruby, or Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not be afraid to write SQL queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Care about building well-designed, user-centric software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be an advocate of user experience, interface design, and web standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excel in an open, fast-paced work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loves to write tests to maintain a codebase with a team of several people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a grasp on front-end coding trends as we are aggressively growing our emphasis on support for mobile devices (iPhone, iPad, etc.) and deploying Responsive Design solutions for virtually all projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience creating websites and applications in the technologies listed below and possess an insatiable desire to learn more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Experience in the following a plus:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A PHP framework such as CakePHP, CodeIgniter, Symfony&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sass, LESS, and CoffeeScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of a Javascript framework (jQuery, Dojo, Prototype, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apache, Nginx&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git, Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux system administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acceptance testing and behavior-driven development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end development trends, including Responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A top-of-the-line development setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great collaborative, learning and creative environment, in the coolest office space in Honolulu&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diverse range of clients and assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Benefits including medical, dental and vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re always interested in meeting creative, smart, talented, dedicated team players with a sense of humor. (Hey&amp;hellip; maybe that&amp;rsquo;s you.) Show us what you&amp;rsquo;re made of. Good luck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wall-to-Wall, Inc. is an EEO/AA employer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-web-developer-wall-to-wall-studios-honolulu-hi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-web-developer-wall-to-wall-studios-honolulu-hi</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>