<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/id-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Designer at Coldwater Creek in Sandpoint, ID</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Why Coldwater Creek?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re a company that takes great pride in our heritage and our unique brand identity. Yes, we’re also a multi-million-dollar household-name women’s apparel company. Here you’ll be part of a small-scale, high-visibility team.  We offer a competitive salary, benefits and a comprehensive relocation package.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What we’re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you a Web Designer who thrives at taking abstract ideas and minimal visualization and turning them into relevant and engaging customer experiences?  Can you align these experiences with the brand mission?  Do you have experience designing for online retail and solid working knowledge of producing graphics, images and other file types for web development? This creative position requires excellent design, concepting and UI skills that maximize typography, content and imagery to deliver a design solution that is leveraged across media platforms.  If you’re ready to be a member of our in-house design team supporting the design director, team members and other internal clients, then we’d love to talk to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you’ll do:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop creative solutions that push the limits of design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present creative concepts both internally and externally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be an advocate and evangelist for creative process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create seasonal campaigns for online&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct photographers and illustrators when needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver projects that consistently align with the brand and business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate ideas and concepts to other team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with copywriters, marketing, merchandising, and studio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively manage and communicate project status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you bring:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-7 years online retail experience creating interactive web designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Web Design or related field of study from credited University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly proficient in Adobe Photoshop, InDesign and Adobe Illustrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Flash or other animated programs a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong conceptual design and typography skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in solving design problems with the ability to create a consistent, on brand, visual direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attentive to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage time effectively, prioritize work and be deadline focused&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple projects simultaneously and be adaptable to changing priorities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works well independently as well as in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML limitations as they pertain to web design necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-designer-coldwater-creek-sandpoint-id</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-designer-coldwater-creek-sandpoint-id</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>