<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/id-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Mobile Developer at Bodybuilding.com in Meridian, ID</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bodybuilding.com is the world’s largest online sports nutrition retailer, offering its visitors over 12,000 products, over 25,000 articles, 2,000 plus videos and a robust social network with over 900,000 members all designed to help our visitors achieve their health, fitness and appearance goals!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Values:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always be truthful and honest in every aspect of business.
Give back to the people that you owe your success to.
Setting goals creates the roadmap to positive gains.
Great things will happen with a passion for competition.
It’s our goal to make the big idea bigger.
Our mission is not complete until the customer says “WOW!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Our Mission:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To help our visitors reach their health, fitness and appearance goals through information, motivation, and supplementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an Android Developer who is passionate about creating amazing apps with elegant code.  With millions of existing members and thousands joining each day the Community mobile developers are tasked with building mobile apps that leverage our highly scalable technology stacks and bring to market a “best in class” mobile application for the social/health/fitness space. The ideal candidate is passionate about engineering and will work in a highly collaborative, team environment creating next-generation apps for Bodybuilding.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and implement high quality, fast and maintainable mobile applications in alignment with the Community Platform’s roadmap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Designers, Product Owners and Testers through the development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consider testing, documentation and deployment up front and ensure all is thoroughly covered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work as a member of a SCRUM team with the relentless pursuit to ship value to our site visitors ASAP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share in the ownership of Community Platform critical production escalations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years Object Oriented software development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience developing native application on Android devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SOA environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience defining, developing and maintaining web services and applications on Android that consume them (REST,JSON, XML)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate ability to work as a team and deliver at startup speed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with object-oriented principles and development patterns like MVC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good technical, analytical, and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have examples of published apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comparable mobile app development experience with iOS is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wicket experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Bodybuilding.com offers its employees several benefits such as: health, dental and vision insurance; 401(k); Competitive bonuses; Gym Membership Reimbursement; Employee Discount; Employee Fitness program; Book Reading program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bodybuilding.com LLC is an Equal Opportunity Employer. The above information has been designed to indicate the general nature and level of work performed by employees in this classification.  It is not designed to contain or to be interpreted as a comprehensive inventory of all duties, responsibilities, and qualifications required of the employee assigned to this job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Bodybuilding.com:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bodybuilding.com is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest online retailer for sports supplements and nutritional products in the world. Here at Bodybuilding.com, we are passionate about helping our visitors reach their health, fitness and appearance goals through information, motivation, and supplementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bodybuilding.com currently employs over 500 employees between the Boise headquarters and three warehouses in Idaho, Florida and Pennsylvania and are continuing to grow at a rapid pace. We are looking for innovative individuals who thrive in a creative, energetic and passionate work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can view current openings at &lt;a href=&quot;http://careers.bodybuilding.com&quot;&gt;http://careers.bodybuilding.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-mobile-developer-bodybuilding-com-meridian-id</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-mobile-developer-bodybuilding-com-meridian-id</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>