<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/il-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Integrys Energy Group in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Integrys Business Support, a subsidiary of Integrys Energy Group, is currently recruiting for a Graphic Designer for our office in Chicago.  This position reports to the Manager – Creative Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize and design internal and external communications using a variety of media and creative solutions to reach target audience. Optimize graphics and photography for print, web and video. Edit and produce corporate videos. Collaborate on projects from concept to completion, including brainstorming, conception and designing, for print, web and video. Work with print vendors to prepare and preflight documents to meet their respective press specifications. Maintain consistent brand representation across all forms of communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage daily, multiple deadlines on creative projects. Complete special projects as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree in Marketing, Communications, Graphics Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years demonstrated experience using Illustrator, In-Design, Photoshop, and Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years working knowledge of preparing files for print and web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience with visual design including graphic design, layout, color theory and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience in  Graphic Design with experience in advertising/design industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ year working knowledge of Microsoft Office Products, including Word, Excel, PowerPoint and SharePoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ year experience assisting with video editing and production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe Premiere Pro and After Affects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Integrys Energy Group, Inc. (NYSE: TEG) is a Fortune 1,000 company focused on delivering energy and related services to more than 2 million customers in the U.S.  Our subsidiaries, with nearly 5,000 employees, are creating a premier and growing energy company.  We have exciting career opportunities that will reward energetic people who help us meet the challenge!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a competitive salary and a comprehensive benefits package.  Interested candidates must apply online at www.integrysgroup.com no later than March 31, 2013.  Integrys reserves the right to modify the application deadline or discontinue accepting applications for any position if deemed necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Equal Opportunity /Affirmative Action Employer
All qualified candidates, including minorities, women, veterans and people with disabilities are encouraged to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-integrys-energy-group-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-integrys-energy-group-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Brella Productions in Illinois</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brella Productions, a Chicagoland new-media production company, is seeking a Senior Print Graphic Designer to start immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you all about the details? Is multi-tasking a breeze for you? Would you like to work in a busy, creative, problem solving environment with other artists and designers? If you are a friendly, self-motivated person who loves to make awesome graphics for interactive and print, then we are looking for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is currently an opening for an experienced Senior Print Graphic Designer to join our team on-site at a client’s suburban North Chicago, IL location (near Gurnee, IL).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate should enjoy designing for a variety of applications, but have strong print experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The hours for this job are Monday – Friday 9:00 AM – 5:00 PM – On Location Near Gurnee, IL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with in-house account managers, project managers and clients to translate script content and design concepts into graphics for a variety of print applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to work on tedious repetitive elements one week and very complex fun elements the next.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multitask and deal well with a busy production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create a variety of designs to suit the style and needs of the client within a specific Brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within existing project management and QA structures to ensure clean workflow (and to be kind to your fellow designers, testers and project managers).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability (and desire) to continue acquiring new design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient in all Adobe design software, a high level  knowledge of InDesign required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be highly proficient in Microsoft office products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be both Macintosh and PC knowledgeable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely detail oriented with great organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pharmaceutical or medical project experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of graphic design terms and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a busy design department, working with several programmers and designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to set and maintain both short and long term deadlines*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to takes notes, self manage and follow through on complex projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to take on new projects and generally seek out ways to help others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be highly organized, reliable and proactive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to troubleshoot difficult or sensitive problems and find positive solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working directly with our other staff programmers and our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to troubleshoot difficult or sensitive problems and find positive solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to drive to or commute via Metra to the client site in North Chicago, IL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with All Adobe Products, InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of related professional experience and a college degree or 5+ years of related professional graphics experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-brella-productions-illinois</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-brella-productions-illinois</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Interface Designer at Salesforce in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1999, Salesforce.com is the enterprise cloud computing leader. Our social and mobile cloud technologies, including our flagship sales and CRM applications, help companies connect with customers, partners, and employees in entirely new ways. With more than 100,000 customers worldwide, we are proud to contribute to the success of companies of all sizes and industries, around the globe. If you&amp;rsquo;re passionate about innovation, come help revolutionize how companies collaborate and communicate with customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salesforce.com Services is seeking a Senior User Interface Designer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking innovative and passionate Senior User Interface Designers who share our vision of bringing the power of cloud computing to enterprises.  The Senior Web Designer will work closely with the creative director and mobile application developers on conceptualizing and designing applications for iPhone, iPad, Android, and other mobile devices. Your PRIMARY responsibility will be to translate wireframe interaction designs and storyboards into final visual designs for desktop applications, mobile applications and web applications. You should have experience translating user-centered design research and usability testing to guide designs. You will also be responsible for documenting these designs in a design specification document.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills/Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design portfolio with 4+ years education, 7+ years design and interactive work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online portfolio that showcases strong typography skills and B2C examples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive advertising background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience at either an ad agencies or corporate in-house department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed and diverse communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to articulate creative ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven aptitude for quick creative thinking with acute attention to detail within demanding deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid working knowledge of the latest versions of Mac OS, Photoshop, Fireworks, and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-interface-designer-salesforce-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-interface-designer-salesforce-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface Designer at Solstice Consulting in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Solstice Mobile is seeking a UI Designer to join our rapidly expanding UX Department. This person should be creative, with an eye for design. If you are passionate about mobility and understand the concepts of human computer interaction, and graphic design – read on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What we are looking for in you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Graphic Art/Design or related field (required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite (primarily Photoshop, Illustrator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to collaborate when needed or work independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working closely with development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to create user-centered design based on your understanding of HCI fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to Manage multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone who can articulate user experience issues and concerns and overall design principles to team members and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for design and interest in mobile technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you can look forward to in the job:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taking a client’s vision from conception to completion and delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translating requirements into a beautiful experience for the end user&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Producing wireframes and prototypes for mobile apps and websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User interface and graphic design for mobile apps and websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some internal branding or design work for Solstice websites, blogs or newsletter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internal design for our mobile application product development suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Any front end coding experience (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript for desktop or mobile) is a plus however we are looking for a creative designer. An eye for design is a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like a position you would like to hear more about or be considered for, please apply with your resume and your portfolio (required).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-designer-solstice-consulting-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-designer-solstice-consulting-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Studio Digital Artist Designer at Trisect in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The primary responsibility of the Studio Digital Artist is to use their expertise in
design and computer applications to review final designs and layouts. In finalizing
the products, artists may suggest improvements and modify formats to increase
the quality of production and ensure that standards are met. Technical duties
include scaling, cropping, production retouching, repositioning, pre-flighting,
eliminating defective images and archiving files. Design duties will require taking
current assets and creating creative layouts for keylines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Specific Responsibilities &amp;amp; Expectations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Technical/Craft&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient experience with the Adobe Creative Suite (latest version)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learns and adheres to all studio processes and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepares keylined artwork for production, per print specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quality check hi-resolution images per client and/or internal markups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transfers finished files to vendors via approved delivery methods, on time and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;within budget&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executes creative design as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists in maintaining digital asset management system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews all projects with Studio Director and/or Studio Manager before final
release of artwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Checks proofs, prepares mockups and supports the Studio Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Design&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works closely with the Art Director to create layouts that are Studio ready&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restructures layouts and artwork to fit into various sizes and formats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manipulates, corrects and finalizes artwork in both pixel and vector formats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recreates designers’ original layouts from previous assets (sketches) to be
used for various layouts or keylines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Communication&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updates Studio and Production personnel as to status of each project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listens and applies constructive criticism to work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Career Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stays current with software technologies used in Studio/Production work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seeks out improvement, training and growth opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrates ability to work as part of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Problem Solving&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays perseverance in pursuing work with energy and drive, especially in
the face of resistance or setbacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible with timelines and last-minute changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College degree in Graphic Design/Liberal Arts or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe CS5 software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with and understanding of creating assets for printing/web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to execute “light design” while keylining&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of pre-press experience with an ad agency, publisher or printer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About the Agency&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are one of the fastest-growing marketing agencies in the country. We are a
close-knit group of marketing professionals who believe in the power of an idea.
We think being an independent agency is a fundamental advantage that allows
us to create unexpected value—both in our focus on people and our investment
in our clients’ business. We work with clients such as Kimberly-Clark, DeVry
University, ConAgra, U.S. Cellular and Kawasaki. Please visit our website for
more information about our agency (Tris3ct.com).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/studio-digital-artist-designer-trisect-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/studio-digital-artist-designer-trisect-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Designer - Contract at Critical Mass in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Senior Designer is an original thinker and project group leader who conceives creative concepts and translates them into a visual format. Working in the Creative Department and under the supervision of an art director, the Senior Designer is a team player who is skilled in matching strategic direction with appropriate design results for the Internet and Web-based marketing initiatives. The Senior Designer is a leader capable of directing up to 4 designers, with the ability to follow up and mentor those designers. Attention to detail, combined with a strong working knowledge of design-related applications is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing solutions that meet or exceed strategic objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating highly usable interface solutions focused on user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading a project or group of projects with limited input from an Art Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guiding and directing up to 4 designers with thorough delegation, follow-up and mentoring&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rationalizing solutions with the project team and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balancing creative requirements with client business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing: mood boards; storyboards; interactive page layouts; site grids and interface demos; photo retouching and enhancements; animated GIFs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing quality assurance on creative deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building and maintaining a team rapport with creative team personnel, account managers, &amp;amp; project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visualize and verbalize your ideas to team and client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design portfolio with 2+ years education, 2+ years design and interactive work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed and diverse communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to articulate creative ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven aptitude for quick creative thinking with acute attention to detail within demanding deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid working knowledge of the latest versions of Mac OS, Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the strengths and limitations of Flash, After Effects, QuickTime, Director, and ImageReady.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-contract-critical-mass-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-contract-critical-mass-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer - Contract at Critical Mass in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Designer is an original thinker who contributes to the development of creative concepts, translating them into visual and interactive form. Working in the Creative Services Department, the Designer is a team player who is skilled in matching strategic direction with appropriate design results for the Internet and Web-based marketing initiatives. Attention to detail, combined with a strong working knowledge of design-related applications is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing solutions that meet or exceed strategic objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating interactive design concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing: mood boards; storyboards; interactive page layouts; site grids and interface demos; photo retouching and enhancements; animated GIFs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing quality assurance on creative deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building and maintaining a team rapport with creative team personnel, account managers, &amp;amp; project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design portfolio with 2+ years education, 1+ years design and interactive work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong visual, interactive, illustration, and graphic design skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid working knowledge of the latest design toolsets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timely, responsible, prepared and do what it takes to get the job done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable brainstorming and contributing to the bigger idea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed and diverse communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to articulate creative ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven aptitude for quick creative thinking with acute attention to detail within demanding deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid working knowledge of the latest versions of Mac OS, Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the strengths and limitations of Flash, After Effects, QuickTime, Director, and ImageReady.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of information architecture and hierarchy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of interactivity and the Web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for design and eagerness to collaborate with other creative people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for and commitment to the profession of visual communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid footing on the line between creative expression and commercial reality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self motivated, organized and accountable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustration in both electronic and traditional media is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motion graphics experience for the Web and video is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-contract-critical-mass-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-contract-critical-mass-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Tyndale House Publishers in Carol Stream, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Tyndale House Publishers, founded in 1962, is the world’s largest privately held Christian publisher of books, Bibles, and digital media. Tyndale has published many New York Times bestsellers. The largest portion of its profit goes to the nonprofit Tyndale House Foundation, which makes grants to help meet the physical and spiritual needs of people around the world. Tyndale was founded to publish Living Letters, which later comprised part of The Living Bible, a contemporary paraphrase of the Bible that became a global publishing phenomenon. Tyndale now publishes the Holy Bible, New Living Translation (NLT), the translation of choice for millions of people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are just getting your career started and/or have some graphic design experience, we would like for you to consider this open position on our book cover team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an exciting opportunity to be part of our wonderful in-house Design team! Tyndale is seeking qualified candidates for a graphic designer position on its Design team. This position will design and produce art and copy layouts for Tyndale&amp;rsquo;s book covers, interiors, and packaging. Primary responsibilities include initiating and following through on projects from conception to completion by working closely with Art Directors to evaluate an individual project&amp;rsquo;s needs, preparing comps or prototypes according to instructions of group publishers and Art Directors, working with Art Buyer and Art Directors to select and supervise outside photographers and illustrators, checking final production files and proofs for accuracy in coordination with Art Directors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified candidates will be a college graduate with a BFA or BA degree in graphic design, or have equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of two years of related work experience is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of pre-press and packaging design is required, and an overall knowledge of printing processes is desired.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive working knowledge of InDesign, Photoshop, and Illustrator on the Mac OS are a must for this position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills and the ability to work well with a team are essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to read, analyze, and interpret general design periodicals, professional journals, and technical procedures is important for this position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-tyndale-house-publishers-carol-stream-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-tyndale-house-publishers-carol-stream-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Production Designer at Manifest Digital in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We’re Manifest (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.manifestdigital.com&quot;&gt;http://www.manifestdigital.com&lt;/a&gt;), an award winning independent interactive agency based out of Chicago, IL. We work with some of the most compelling brands in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For us, it’s not truly great work if it doesn’t blow our own minds, first. However, this isn’t creative for creative’s sake, it’s creative with purpose. Our work sparks conversations, gets people talking, and engages our audience in compelling, meaningful ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2001, we currently have 100+ full-time employees. Some of our clients include LEGO, Universal Pictures, Warner Bros, Bally Total Fitness, McDonalds, Sony Pictures, 20th Century Fox, Avon, Coca-Cola, Nike, Burton Snowboards, Namco Bandai Games… and many, many more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;OVERVIEW&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a creative Interactive Production Artist for high-end production work. Candidate should be able to use Photoshop and Illustrator in their sleep and be comfortable creating or applying style guides to high-fidelity wireframes. They should possess the ability to handle multiple projects at once, be flexible and collaborative and be able to straddle solid graphic design and great user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in Photoshop production, particularly cutting up graphics, setting up files for web or application production and adhering to graphic design standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent design and typography skills applicable to web. Mobile and tablet a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly detail oriented, with a drive for perfection down to the last pixel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrives in a challenging, fast-paced, workplace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishes rapport and collaborates easily with designers, UX, and project management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to adhere to a consistent graphic production and check-in process, while also identifying opportunities for improvement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resourceful, adaptable, creative, and results-oriented with high energy and a positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop and Illustrator a must. CS Suite a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years experience in a hands-on digital agency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/production-designer-manifest-digital-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/production-designer-manifest-digital-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Frey in Illinois</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a talented designer to join our small but fast growing team in Roselle. At Frey Design, we design thoughtful and innovative print, web, and multimedia designs for small to large national corporations. We’re a company looking to make some noise in the Chicagoland agency scene in the coming years, and would love for you to be a part of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The in-office hours and times are flexible, the contract period is flexible, and the pay is competitive. If you are looking to pick up extra hours, looking for a possible full time, or would just like a set part time job… please reach out to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects from design concept to completion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to demonstrate creativity and high quality standards under tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for final art preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Specific Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert eye for details — nothing is insignificant!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio that demonstrates a strong understanding of design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess an untrained quality; outstanding aesthetic taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of all Adobe CS6 products (InDesign, Illustrator &amp;amp; Photoshop)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent collaboration &amp;amp; communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice-to-haves&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML, CSS, Flash, Wordpress and/or Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We also encourage you to submit your Twitter feed and LinkedIn profile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apply using the application form located on this page. Please, no phone calls and no outside recruiters. At this time we are considering applicants in the Chicagoland area only.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-frey-illinois</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-frey-illinois</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>