<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/il-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. Experience Designer at Sapient in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to SapientNitro, where ideas reign supreme. Here, customer experiences are what drive us, game-changing marketing is conceived, awards are won, and technology is at the very heart of bringing our creative ideas to life. There’s no shame in being ambitious here; career growth is a priority for us – we help one another climb, we don’t climb over one-another. Clients aren’t just customers, they’re partners. Integrity and a team-driven environment serve as incubators for entrepreneurial minds. Getting goose bumps? Good. If you’re ready to be an idea engineer with some of the best collaborators in the industry, let’s see where you can put your talents to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Title&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Information Architect, Level 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Information Architects at SapientNitro are responsible for the navigation, organization, interaction design, and business/user process engineering for leading-edge Web solutions, software, mobile and other interactive devices. This involves application of user-centered design methods to translate user needs, business objectives, and technology capabilities into world-class user experience for leading companies. Additionally, this role involves leading tracks of work, being the client point of contact, and guiding developers and other designers/ Information Architects in projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate existing sites in terms of their persuasiveness, emotional design, and conversion; assess properties for usefulness, usability, visual design, content, and branding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead participatory design/user testing sessions; lead Information Architects in the sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and document meaningful patterns from the user research, audit the findings; provide recommendations to the client/internal team based on findings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead development of personas/segmentations based on research findings; integrate personas/segmentations with related deliverables such as opportunity maps and wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare, conduct, and analyze behavioral in-context research events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify opportunities to create business value and improve the user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute participatory requirements gathering sessions, participate in debrief sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct and analyze stakeholder interviews to understand key success factors for a project or pursuit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present concepts to clients and internal stakeholders with research and best practice annotations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide consultancy to other IAs in layout, placement and content of design elements towards persuasive design strategy; mentor junior Information Architects towards client delivery and excellence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance to Visual Designers for creating optimal emotional engagement and “connectedness”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop Navigation Model, Primary and Secondary Navigation structure; develop Sitemap as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze task flows, task decompositions and create optimal Task Flow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop frameworks describing key aspects of proposed experience, how it reconciles business/user needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create prototypes using tools such as InDesign, Visio, Axure as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present concepts to clients and internal stakeholders with annotations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with Project Manager and Project Director to assemble a quality IA team for small to medium projects; assist with management of the IA schedule and resource plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and motivate the IA team to realize overall goals and deliver a successful project on time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide direction to, and help set up evaluation criteria for, other Information Architects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct periodic Knowledge Sharing sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree required; preferred in design-related discipline: Interaction, Information or Interface design; Human-Computer Interaction; Design Planning; Graphic Design; Communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-5 years of industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates must be versed in user-centered design methods and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient to expert in: InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Visio, Microsoft Office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellence in analytical thinking, process-oriented skills, verbal and written skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on multiple projects simultaneously, ability to work collaboratively on multi-disciplinary teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in a consulting firm or agency preferred, prior experience in UI design for mobile devices a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About SapientNitro&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SapientNitroSM, part of Sapient®, is an integrated marketing and technology services firm. We create and engineer highly relevant experiences that accelerate business growth and fuel brand advocacy for our clients. By combining multi-channel marketing, multi-channel commerce, and the technology that binds them, we influence customer behavior across the spectrum of content, communication and commerce channels, resulting in deeper, more meaningful relationships between customers and brands. SapientNitro services global leaders such as Citi, The Coca-Cola Company, Foot Locker, Singapore Airlines, Target, and Vodafone through our operations in North America, Europe, and Asia-Pacific. For more information, visit www.sapientnitro.com or follow us on Twitter @sapientnitro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sapient is a registered service mark of Sapient Corporation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-experience-designer-sapient-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-experience-designer-sapient-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Visual Designer at CSC in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CSC, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most innovative and successful IT services firms, is looking for candidates to help grow our talented consulting team. We are looking for individuals who:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strive for excellence in everything they do&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring a partnering approach to their job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on the innovative use of technology to overcome business challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seek to work in a environment that respects individual ideas and diversity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Specifically, we are seeking to hire a Visual Designer with three or more years of interactive experience to join our User Experience (UX) team to help collaborate on web/mobile user interface designs.  Work with team members to convert wireframes into elegant visual design comps.  Play a critical role in designing user interfaces and enhancing the visual treatment of existing web applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with a information architects, business analysts and web developers to help determine the best solution for the end users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create design deliverables such as storyboards, mock-ups, mood boards, prototypes, and design specs, using methods varying from sketching to Adobe Creative Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find ways to visualize data heavy content in a way that makes the material more easily understood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define and document design guidelines for consistency of look, tone and feel of applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide direction for visual design projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the full design life-cycle by partnering with the testing teams, developers, and other project members to develop quality and effective solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;You will leverage and grow your knowledge and skills in a fast-paced, rewarding environment &amp;mdash; working side-by-side with our team of world class consultants. In addition to a rewarding work environment, CSC offers an outstanding set of benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Successful candidate will have a stellar portfolio of design excellence and will have managed user interface solutions for mobile and web-based applications. Technical expertise with Adobe Creative Suite CS5, and at least 3 years of expert level consulting/agency experience with Photoshop is desired. Usability and user experience methodology and practices experience is preferred. Educational background should include a BFA or MFA degree with 3 years of commercial experience in visual design for web and mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential job functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative workshops to define visual design requirements and brand/style directions for mobile and web user interface designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideation sessions with clients to establish rough design concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing concept directions for new visual designs for complex web and mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Fortune 500 clients to employ user interface design best practices for the solution implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating workflows, wireframes and documentation for development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create production ready graphics in Photoshop for prototypes and final development solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find innovative design solutions for complex user interface design problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pixel Perfect execution for all comps and production graphics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs technical analyses to the sub-system level (Technical).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops software program specifications for various levels of complexity and codes programs from high level specifications or derived logical processes (DLPs) on two or more technical platforms (Technical).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototypes business applications and raises prototypes to production levels (Technical).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrates understanding of the Catalyst approach and applies components of the architecture, development, integration and deployment phases to day-to-day activities (Methodology).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coaches 3-5 project team resources in area of expertise (Management).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands and applies business process design techniques (Business).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gains the confidence of clients and company staff in specialty area and builds strong relationships with the working group (Relationship Management).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extends role on current assignment due to level of application and process knowledge, when possible (Leverage).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates in a variety of presentation settings including small to medium sized groups, project teams, internal task forces and training classes; contributes to formal written deliverables (Communication).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;General Education, Skills, and Experience Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in visual design within an interactive context.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of user experience / graphic design principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with an iterative design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to work with and design functionality that supports complex calculations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors of Fine Arts (BFA) or Masters of Fine Arts (MFA)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of design  for web sites and a solid knowledge of HTML /CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No travel restrictions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent combination of education and experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in a related field preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two or more years of experience in technical analysis, programming, and testing, preferably in a consulting environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with CSC Catalyst and/or equivalent client-mandated methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with software programming and testing standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with data modeling and database techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work as part of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;CSC is an Equal Opportunity Employer M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-visual-designer-csc-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-visual-designer-csc-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI/UX Designer at Thermo Fisher Scientific in Vernon Hills, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an outstanding User Interface / Experience Designer to join our eMarketing team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for creating and implementing attractive and effective website designs that align with their respective brands, achieve conversion goals, and provide the end user with an excellent experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this role, the User Interface / Experience Designer will work to create an intuitive and cohesive look, feel and overall user experience for our sites and applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with a cross-functional team that includes engineers, product managers to create simple, easy to use websites and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for defining and improving all web-based interfaces and content areas for all online ecommerce properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop innovative solutions for front-end web, mobile, and interactive projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm, research, wireframe, design and refine user experiences &amp;ndash; all within specified product requirements and deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and implement user flows and interactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine dimensions, styles and design for various mobile/tablet devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect and perform usability sessions with key stakeholders and customers to get feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for reviewing various platforms to ensure consistency across all outlets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the stakeholders and development to achieve the desired look and feel of the user interface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep apprised of new developments/technology and best practices within web design/development sector and implement these ideas and functions into company websites, where applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements/Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 plus years experience in web design, user interface design, or related field.  eCommerce and/or software design is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree required or equivalent combination of experience and education (preferred area of study: Engineering, Human Computer Interaction (HCI), Design, Writing, or other similar fields).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in HTML, JavaScript and CSS layout skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing front-end user experience solutions for consumer software development using modern web technologies such as AJAX, Ruby on Rails, or related skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional user interface and experience design skills and an understanding of user-centered design disciplines and principals, especially e-commerce based UI/UX.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for Web / mobile product, UX and visual design, including experience designing iOS and Android phone and/or tablet applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and experience with various internet marketing disciplines, including search engine optimization, search and display advertising, email marketing, user experience best practices, A/B testing, conversion optimization, and website analytics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Non-Negotiable Hiring Criteria:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience producing user-interface changes that increase conversion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must flourish in a fast paced, iterative, deadline driven environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and organizational skills are critical to success among this company of talented individuals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to provide online portfolio or other relevant UI and UX work samples.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The above statements are intended to describe the general nature and level of the work being performed by people assigned to this job.  They are not an exhaustive list of all of the duties and responsibilities associated with it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-designer-thermo-fisher-scientific-vernon-hills-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-designer-thermo-fisher-scientific-vernon-hills-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Product Designer at Trunk Club in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Senior Product Designer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Location: Chicago, IL
Type: Full-time
Experience: Senior-Level&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trunk Club (trunkclub.com) was started to solve a simple problem – shopping for clothes in stores or online just doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for most guys. It’s overwhelming, inconvenient, and takes way too much time. With Trunk Club, guys discover awesome clothes that are perfect for them without ever having to go shopping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We combine top brands, expert service, and unparalleled convenience to deliver a highly personalized experience that helps guys look their best and saves them time. We start by scouring the planet for the very best in men’s apparel, curating an ever-evolving assortment of pieces from our favorite designers. With the best inventory anywhere as our point of departure, an Expert on our team hand-selects a trunk of items based on each customer’s needs and tastes. They keep what they love and send the rest right back to us, at no cost to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team is based in Chicago, IL and has grown from four to over one hundred since starting out in December 2009. We are backed by awesome investors, including US Venture Partners, Greycroft Partners, Anthos Capital, and Apex Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We solve difficult technology problems every day with the goal of scaling our service platform to a large, diverse customer base while also increasing operational efficiency. We are a small, agile development team with fast iterations and high degrees of personal ownership, so we see the results of our code immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about changing the way retail works, so we&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you if you’re interested in this role!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Working at Trunk Club, you would:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with other designers, product managers, and developers to produce designs for our internal and customer-facing products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own the user interface of key end-to-end customer experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Institutionalize user empathy for our customers and team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help research user needs, create rapid prototypes, and collect feedback from users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help establish style guidelines and reusable design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate sketches, wireframes, and interactions into rich visual designs that follow product style guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commit to aggressive deadlines and contribute to setting and meeting team goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seek to proactively solve problems and generate remarkable, beautiful, game-changing tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help build the product/UX/technology teams and culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help define our customer strategy, contribute to the vision for our company and make it happen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to build a world-class consumer service company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You probably have&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8-15 years experience in interactive web application/user interface design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in Computer Science, HCI, Design or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A professional portfolio online that demonstrates your passion for craft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced visual design skills in layout and composition, color theory, and use of photography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in industry tools e.g. Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of web technologies such as Javascript and HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with mobile and responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Agile developments and a desire to work in one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing other designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An exceptional work ethic, a drive to create, a preference for action and collaboration, an intrinsic ability to teach and learn, an awesome attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Contact: John Tucker, VP of Member Experience (john@trunkclub.com) with additional questions about this role.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-product-designer-trunk-club-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-product-designer-trunk-club-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at The Carle Foundation in Urbana, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position works closely with other department staff to design and produce the printed and visual materials portions of the company&amp;rsquo;s communications products. This is achieved through means of graphic, electronic and web design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Associates degree in Graphic Design or related field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One year combined experience in Graphic Design, desktop publishing and/or related field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Knowledge/Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess advanced graphic design skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess ability and/or aptitude for web design, photography, audio/video production and editing, three-dimensional design, animation and illustration skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient in the use of personal computers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient in the use of office machines, and specialized graphics industry equipment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess knowledge and aptitude of traditional and digital printing processes, pre-press processes and basic typesetting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient working with hands, and possess superior craftsmanship skills in producing and assembling graphic design-related mock-ups and presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess effective communication, problem solving and decision making skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be self-motivated, take direction effectively and be capable of working independently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must perform basic mathematic, and linear measurement calculations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be knowledgeable of commercial printing and graphic design industry terms, processes and tools. including Microsoft, Adobe and Corel design suite applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And must exhibit and exercise good critical, organizational and interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-the-carle-foundation-urbana-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-the-carle-foundation-urbana-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer - Print/Web/Video at Reynolds and Reynolds in Northbrook, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Heal n Cure specializes in core wellness through physician supervision and management. We are committed to assisting our patients in achieving opti­mal health and wellness. Our award-winning team of board certified physicians has deliv­ered dramatic results in manag­ing and reversing all modifiable health risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Heal n Cure&amp;rsquo;s Quality of Care &amp;ndash; Recognized by Institutions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a Premier Medical Wellness Center. We have delivered excellent clinical results. We have received the Top Tier recognition for quality of care and cost efficiency from both Blue Cross Blue Shield and United Healthcare. For further details click below &amp;ndash;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.healncure.com/our_team/recognition&quot;&gt;http://www.healncure.com/our_team/recognition&lt;/a&gt;
Heal n Cure&amp;rsquo;s Quality of Care &amp;ndash; Appreciated by Patients
Our success is clinically proven on thousands of patients we have worked with. We have achieved incredible clinical outcomes within a short period of time. Please refer to the following (about 2 minutes each) videos from our patients.
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.healncure.com/testimonials/inspire&quot;&gt;http://www.healncure.com/testimonials/inspire&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you have experience advertising with Google Ads or Facebook Ads?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are you able to create and edit HTML pages and email campaigns/blasts?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you shot and edited video before?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are you proficient with Adobe software such as Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you created marketing collateral such as brochures and posters?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like you, then Heal n Cure has an opportunity for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a multi-faceted creative designer who is social media savvy and can come up with new marketing ideas. Being a jack of all trades will put you in a great position. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who can take their own and other&amp;rsquo;s ideas, and turn them into reality. Your design will tell people about how Heal n Cure is changing lives and saving healthcare expenses. Your innovative creatives will help make us a renown Medical Wellness Center. You will see your designs put to test immediately. Similar or past work experience with Medical Spas or wellness centers would be a plus. We are growing quickly so the candidate must be able to work in a quick and growing environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are changing lives every day, and want someone with similar passion for their work. To see some of the impact we have made, please refer to testimonials for our care. http://www.healncure.com/testimonials/inspire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be required to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem Solve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit pictures (resizing, color correction, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create marketing collateral (brochures, posters, business cards)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shoot and edit videos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post blog/website content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and send email campaigns/blasts (HTML)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create marketing presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a liaison between Heal n Cure and printers/vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BFA Degree in Graphic Design, Marketing, or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years design/marketing experience in a professional environment is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple projects at the same time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Task manage efficiently while staying focused and organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have basic HTML and CSS skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be able to shoot and edit video to create video testimonials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Drupal based websites is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being Tech savvy is also a plus as you may need to troubleshoot printers and some equipment if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Candidates must be proficient in the following softwares:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Premiere Pro or Final Cut Pro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The position is part time and approximately 30 hrs a week, with the possibility to grow into a full time position. There is a possibility of doing some of the work off site, however you will be required on site two to three days a week. You will need to bring your own laptop with the above software.We can provide a PC for basic office use, but it will not contain any of the required design software. It is very important that you are reliable, proactive, and keep the delivery commitments. You must have a reliable method of transportation and communication. Candidates must be able to be onsite first thing in the morning if required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On your application, please mention&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Availability.  We need 20 hours on-site per week. Total hours may be upto 30/week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant Paid experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desired hourly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Links to your past work or samples if possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-print-web-video-reynolds-and-reynolds-northbrook-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-print-web-video-reynolds-and-reynolds-northbrook-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at Manifest Digital in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Interaction Designer will be expected to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and facilitate design workshops and decision-making in partnership with creative, content and technology disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop sketches and prototypes to convey interaction and functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop detailed navigation flows, site maps, wireframes and interface design/ functional specifications that capture site processes and all user interaction points within the system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create information hierarchies and site navigation for experiences across browser, mobile/tablet and kiosk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write or contribute to the development of use cases and business process flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To perform this job successfully, an individual must meet the following criteria:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to articulate a point of view on process, approach and client-facing interaction design recommendations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid background with the web and web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of leading interaction design trends and patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent visual/verbal communicator with a demonstrated strong creative vision for organizing interactive information systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with prototyping software, preferably Axure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely detail-oriented, flexible and able to work in a fast-paced, demanding environment with aggressive development schedules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with conducting or overseeing usability sessions, task analysis, heuristic evaluation, rapid prototyping and persona development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to travel up to 25-40% within the Chicagoland and Milwaukee area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science, Information Systems or HCI (or equivalent work experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consulting background preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;NITTY-GRITTY Portfolio presentation is expected, to include URLs of websites or samples of user interface design that reflect candidate’s work as well as documentation that led to the site, including wireframes, site maps, navigation flows, interaction design specs, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-manifest-digital-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-manifest-digital-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Designer at ArtVersion in Lake Bluff, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;No phonecalls, no agencies and headhunters, Chicago based candidates only, no telecommuting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ArtVersion Interactive Agency is seeking a interactive designer with 2-5 years of experience. Must be proficient in Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Microsoft Office and be able to work on both Mac OSX and PC platforms. Knowledge in HTML5 and CSS3 big plus. Candidate must have good understanding of branding, web production, mobile and desktop user interface design and user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Successful candidate will be organized, efficient, detail oriented and team-player. It will have a positive, &amp;ldquo;can-do&amp;rdquo; attitude and work well under deadlines and pressure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidate’s portfolio will need to showcase understanding of aesthetics, a strong eye in producing design across multiple project types and medias, show strong typography skills and great layout sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a part-time to full-time, on-site position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and produce creative briefs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with creative team from start of design to production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and produce web and print projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with outside vendors on producing creative projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meet with clients and provide project parameters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sell and communicate company capabilities to clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualified candidates MUST provide the following in PDF format:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover Letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary History&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;References&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design Portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-designer-artversion-lake-bluff-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-designer-artversion-lake-bluff-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Trinity International University in Deerfield, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Located forty miles north of Chicago, Trinity International University’s Marketing and Creative Services (MCS) enjoys a faith-based, fast-paced and exciting university culture with a real sense of community. We’re passionate, creative people with an insatiable desire to learn new things and who love to dream on our clients’ behalf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can relate to the statements below, let&amp;rsquo;s talk:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re a Christ follower and are personally committed to Him, supporting the mission of Trinity and the goals/values of the MCS team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re an experienced print designer who watches tutorials on Adobe CS6 tips for fun or you may not have a great deal of experience but your potential and portfolio SCREAM AMAZING!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love to problem solve creative challenges and can easily blaze through oodles of edits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You value collaboration, but can get projects done on your own&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re organized, continually back up your files, and frequent HOW, Print, and Communications Arts magazines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy sharing what you know with graphic design students who occasionally invade your personal space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re funny. No really, laughing at daunting deadlines is a sign of a super hero&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;This is the skills set we&amp;rsquo;re looking for:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mac OS X&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;nDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, and Acrobat CS6 (but CS5 is fine)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fonts, kerning and leading invade your dreams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Additional Desired Qualifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would earn Brownie Points for:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;llustration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motion graphics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Photography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Working Conditions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Good Stuff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PTO, great benefits, good salary, free university courses, and a choice, open studio environment with an innovative team on a beautiful campus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Trinity International University is an Equal Opportunity Employer. Women and minorities are encouraged to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-trinity-international-university-deerfield-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-trinity-international-university-deerfield-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Total Web Management in Schaumburg, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A professional website helps companies to represent their business online to a wider market and enables them to reach potential customers. A professional business website helps companies to generate leads and to establish a positive image and reputation. This is a powerful marketing tool and building an online identity contributes to business’s credibility. A website improves local and national exposure and gives companies a marketing edge. Nowadays, all leading organizations, corporations and companies have a strong online presence and have managed to expand their reach just by building a strong online presence. Having a business website will reduce the costs of sharing information and will allow your clients the ability to find you with ease. Online marketing and well designed website have proven to be the best tools in building a positive corporate identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total Web Management offers effective professional web design solutions for your business. We provide technical and marketing consultation services as well as a web market analysis. We offer services specializing in Web Design, Web Design Consulting, Search Engine Optimization, Graphic Design, Social Media Strategies &amp;amp; Marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Develop and design marketing materials including product packaging, sales collateral, logos, advertising,  and other related communication materials for us and our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independently design and create marketing materials required to support brand strategies, product placement and sell through for us and our clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with internal customers regarding project objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in building and setting of brand standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with vendors to ensure cost effective and timely completion of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct market trend and competitive analysis to support marketing solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copy writing that clearly and succinctly communicates messaging to consumers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proofing to ensure quality and accuracy of work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce and edit, in-house, product videos for use in mobile marketing and social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local Travel up to 50%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-total-web-management-schaumburg-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-total-web-management-schaumburg-il</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>