<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/il-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at iCrossing in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;iCrossing is looking for a Art Director for their Chicago office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a designer. You live and breathe design and have the portfolio to support it. You are an entrepreneur. You have the innate ability to manage projects, people and client expectations. A designer with a knack for marketing – it all comes together in the Art Director role at iCrossing’s San Francisco office. You’ll provide forward-thinking creative leadership and inspire creative collaboration within our agency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a trained eye on challenging the industry status quo, you’ll be continually engaged in delivering outstanding work on projects large and small, from web engagements to display advertising and internal promotions to external presentations. Equally comfortable leading a team of designers, presenting to clients, and defining strategy, you’ll also get to keep your own creative muscles flexed as you personally create and design for our ever-expanding list of Fortune 500 clients. Adjectives used to describe your creative work…killer, award-winning, re-defining, how did they do that? Adjectives to describe your management skills…cool, calm, organized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide forward-thinking creative leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspire creative collaboration across the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively translate branding and marketing strategies for a wide range of clients/verticals into exceptional creative concepts and executions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and create innovative concepts in keeping with project scope: strategic positioning, business requirements, timelines, and budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead design team in delivery of outstanding design for all-things digital: large scale web engagements, online advertising, digital marketing, business development initiatives, brand boards, and video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as mentor to design team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare creative deliverables (brand boards, creative comps, and style guides)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present creative concepts internally and externally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage entire creative process and large-scale projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-year degree in a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-4 years in a leadership role in an interactive, design, or advertising agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven success in online and offline media delivered in an impressive portfolio of work (electronic submission or URL preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistent display of interest and involvement in the industry. Applicants are encouraged to include links/references to relevant activities that help round out their experience and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-icrossing-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-icrossing-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Art Director at Magnani Caruso Dutton in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We seek a Senior Art Director with exceptional interactive / web design experience to work as a creative lead for our different projects.  The Senior Art Director will be a big picture thinker who can carry a consistent brand message across different information types.  This is a freelance position with potential for full-time permanent hire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Primary responsibility is to lead design and oversee multiple projects.  The Senior Art Director is responsible for developing innovative design directions on projects, oversee and mentor designers, and present work to clients. Under the guidance of the Design Director, the Senior Art Director oversees a wide range of web-related projects including website designs, interactive marketing campaigns, graphic user interfaces, style guides, and presentation materials. This is a great opportunity for experienced creatives to lead interactive projects for major brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of interactive web design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading and managing a team of designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overseeing a project’s design from initial concept to completion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong typographic and layout skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough working knowledge of HTML and current development practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Flash animation and experience with motion design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drawing/illustration skills are highly desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Magnani Caruso Dutton is a leading independent advertising agency located in New York City that has created groundbreaking work for top brands including AT&amp;amp;T, Daily Candy, Discover Financial Services, Genworth Financial, HBO, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, Nautica, Samsung, Sesame Workshop, and Tiffany &amp;amp; Co.  Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mcdpartners.com&quot;&gt;http://www.mcdpartners.com&lt;/a&gt;.  Follow us on Twitter @mcdpartners.com, and on Facebook, www.facebook.com/MagnaniCarusoDutton.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-magnani-caruso-dutton-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-magnani-caruso-dutton-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at Sears in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Functional Graphic Design expertise is mandatory along with team management and client facing skills. Requires the capabilities to direct and enhance the efforts of the creative teams consisting of design managers, designers and copywriters. The successful candidate will have a well-rounded understanding of graphic design, information architecture, usability, technology, and experience design. Applied conceptual strategy, brainstorm facilitation, day-to-day shepherding of a project to completion and team collaboration with engagement managers, production, and technology leads are all part of daily life for a creative director (CD) at Sears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CD fulfills the leadership tasks and deliverables of their businesses. Specifically, the CD leads and directs cross-disciplinary development and execution of short-term (project specific) and long-term (engagement specific) creative strategies. Also responsible for representing and communicating Sears&amp;rsquo;s creative and business philosophy, methodology and capabilities to larger organization, as well as across all departments, business units and service lines. The CD will seek opportunities to collaborate across the Sears network with the OBU and specifically with partners in Engineering, Product Development, and the BU CMO groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are searching for a highly conceptual and collaborative team leader who is constructive, fearless, charismatic, smart, self-possessed and committed to a vision. Passion, perspective, innovation and impact are the Sears core values a potential candidate will be expected to embody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills / Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ten to twelve years of professional experience encompassing a minimum of eight years as a senior level professional in at least two of the following areas: interactive design, advertising, interactive advertising, game interface design, marketing, publishing, broadcast, film or television.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors or higher degree in a creative discipline. Relevant experience and training may be substituted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online portfolio review required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has successfully directed/ managed multidisciplinary creative teams in the production of Interactive, web based, mobile, and print products, and has worked in multi-disciplinary teams that included product managers, project managers, artists, designers, writers, and engineers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong creative and conceptual vision for interactive, and the ability to execute high quality integrated interactive communications against strategic business objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is an expert in graphic and experience design disciplines; demonstrated ability to mentor and guide other designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong comprehension of user experience architecture, front end development and editorial disciplines and methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of project concept creation, site architecture, user-interface specification, functionality specification and interactive design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of front-end interactive design solutions for back-end data systems. Working knowledge of capabilities of different platforms and browsers, and their design constraints on the Web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to direct creative teams including flash designers, designers, and writers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong time management and creative resource management capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has demonstrated ability to direct and multi-task effectively under pressure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fulfills leadership tasks and deliverables of a CD in support of the office of the DVP. Specifically, leads and directs across disciplines, the development and execution of short term (project specific) and long term (account specific) creative strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures creative scope, schedule and budget are accurate. Develops and signs-off on creative estimates and ensures high quality, profitable execution of creative deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops and executes account growth strategies with account core team members to meet account goals set by the engagement lead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates with DVP and UX OPS resource manager in projections for, and assignment of, creative discipline group members to projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an awareness of status and project deliverables of all discipline group members' project work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates constructively in inter-department and cross-service line communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to the evolution and maintenance of each creative discipline workflow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takes an active role in developing, maintaining and refining a vision for the direction of the interactive communications industry. Develops oneself toward thorough leadership. speaks publicly, representing Sears creative discipline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to the communication, demonstration and evolution of the quality standards of Sears creative and experience products to clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-sears-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-sears-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at Resource in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Executive Creative Director, the Creative Director is responsible for creative leadership and management of the Creative Domain.  The Creative Director is highly conceptual – both visually and verbally, fearless leaders who possess a spirit for methodology and innovation, while at the same time remarkably business savvy. The Creative Director is responsible for representing Resource’s thought leadership, methodologies and capabilities to existing and potential clients. The Creative Director also works closely with internal leadership across disciplines to ensure their team’s infrastructure is compatible with the workload it supports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Practice Delivery&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core leadership and development of Creative Talent (Design, Interaction Design and Content) under respective Practice Group&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core creative direction in shaping strategic vision and experience for all client work and responsible for documenting and sharing the Creative POV through formal channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate an environment of inspiration, innovation and turn opportunities into actionable results. Expertise in Interactive Marketing and eRetail is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Client Delivery&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with peers across disciplines to ensure talent and staffing levels are compatible with existing and projected workload. This may include leadership of an Offering team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective and persuasive communicator with clients. Owns relationship with client on behalf of creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultimately responsible for the integrity of the solutions created by the team. Strong leadership qualities are critical to leading and mentoring the team to take calculated risks in the pursuit of innovation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Business Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works closely with Studio leadership to identify and cultivate new opportunities through participation in annual client planning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsibly for assembly and leadership of new business pursuit teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s Degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10+ years experience in leading a team of Design and Content talent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years experience in Interactive Marketing and Interface Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documented examples of shaping and leading creative vision of eRetail, Portal, Promotional and Online Advertising Campaign executions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience in building relationships with Information Architecture, Technology, Strategy and Project Management partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of user interface design and examples of prototype creation to illustrate a high-level concept&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and ability to contribute to analysis of web performance metrics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Travel Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position may require up to 40% travel to and from current or potential client sites, conferences, seminars and/or training sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please Note: This job description is not intended to be a complete list of all responsibilities, duties or skills and due
to the changing nature of the job is subject to review and change at any time, with or without notice.  This position
is exempt based on the FLSA laws.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-resource-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-resource-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Resource in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Reporting to an Associate Creative Director, the Art Director is responsible for creative leadership and ownership of multiple projects. Art Directors mentor, inspire and direct a team of Senior Designers, Designers, Interaction Designers and Production Designers from concept to implementation. Art Directors work closely with Strategy, Client Service and Technology partners to ensure creative concepts and execution meet the established business objectives. Art Directors are also required to effectively communicate with clients in both creative presentations and feedback meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Practice Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept creation and development, design direction, management and execution of overall visual language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct Designers, Interaction Designers and Production Designers regarding interface design and visual hierarchy systems, establishing the design language, execution of design direction, visual asset creation, HTML production and presentation preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photo and video art direction and participation in both pre- and post-production process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining and extending current knowledge base as well as learning about new design tools and software relating to interactive media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ownership of design and functional continuity throughout the development phase of project work, consistently consulting Associate Creative Director for guidance and validation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-facing presentations of creative concepts and design progress throughout the course of project work and creative assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soliciting and assimilating design feedback, establishing priorities and directing/implementing design related revisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Client Delivery&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of the Resource creative process against established timelines and budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staffing of project teams with a close eye on utilization targets for team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active collaboration with Strategy and Creative Domains to ensure effective visual communications and overall functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Business Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to assist in Scoping &amp;amp; estimating projects accurately as well as review and comment on SOW’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in new business opportunity brainstorming and spec work creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s Degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 to 10 years experience in Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years experience in Interactive Marketing and Interface Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive training in graphic design, typography, interaction design and/or visual communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstration of successful leadership experience with a team of at least 5 direct reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding conceptual abilities and collaborative skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong team building and management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills with the ability to present information in verbal, written or visual form to a variety of audiences, from the internal team to client executives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent time management skills and the ability to effectively allocate resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth understanding of interactive usability principles, HTML, dHTML and capabilities of web browsers across platforms is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in the latest versions of design software including: Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash and InDesign. After Effects and sound editing is a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-resource-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-resource-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>