<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feeds/il-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at Resource in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Executive Creative Director, the Creative Director is responsible for creative leadership and management of the Creative Domain.  The Creative Director is highly conceptual – both visually and verbally, fearless leaders who possess a spirit for methodology and innovation, while at the same time remarkably business savvy. The Creative Director is responsible for representing Resource’s thought leadership, methodologies and capabilities to existing and potential clients. The Creative Director also works closely with internal leadership across disciplines to ensure their team’s infrastructure is compatible with the workload it supports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Practice Delivery&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core leadership and development of Creative Talent (Design, Interaction Design and Content) under respective Practice Group&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core creative direction in shaping strategic vision and experience for all client work and responsible for documenting and sharing the Creative POV through formal channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate an environment of inspiration, innovation and turn opportunities into actionable results. Expertise in Interactive Marketing and eRetail is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Client Delivery&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with peers across disciplines to ensure talent and staffing levels are compatible with existing and projected workload. This may include leadership of an Offering team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective and persuasive communicator with clients. Owns relationship with client on behalf of creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultimately responsible for the integrity of the solutions created by the team. Strong leadership qualities are critical to leading and mentoring the team to take calculated risks in the pursuit of innovation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Business Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works closely with Studio leadership to identify and cultivate new opportunities through participation in annual client planning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsibly for assembly and leadership of new business pursuit teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s Degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10+ years experience in leading a team of Design and Content talent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years experience in Interactive Marketing and Interface Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documented examples of shaping and leading creative vision of eRetail, Portal, Promotional and Online Advertising Campaign executions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience in building relationships with Information Architecture, Technology, Strategy and Project Management partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of user interface design and examples of prototype creation to illustrate a high-level concept&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and ability to contribute to analysis of web performance metrics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Travel Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position may require up to 40% travel to and from current or potential client sites, conferences, seminars and/or training sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please Note: This job description is not intended to be a complete list of all responsibilities, duties or skills and due
to the changing nature of the job is subject to review and change at any time, with or without notice.  This position
is exempt based on the FLSA laws.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:47:57 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-resource-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-resource-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Resource in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Reporting to an Associate Creative Director, the Art Director is responsible for creative leadership and ownership of multiple projects. Art Directors mentor, inspire and direct a team of Senior Designers, Designers, Interaction Designers and Production Designers from concept to implementation. Art Directors work closely with Strategy, Client Service and Technology partners to ensure creative concepts and execution meet the established business objectives. Art Directors are also required to effectively communicate with clients in both creative presentations and feedback meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Practice Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept creation and development, design direction, management and execution of overall visual language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct Designers, Interaction Designers and Production Designers regarding interface design and visual hierarchy systems, establishing the design language, execution of design direction, visual asset creation, HTML production and presentation preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photo and video art direction and participation in both pre- and post-production process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining and extending current knowledge base as well as learning about new design tools and software relating to interactive media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ownership of design and functional continuity throughout the development phase of project work, consistently consulting Associate Creative Director for guidance and validation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-facing presentations of creative concepts and design progress throughout the course of project work and creative assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soliciting and assimilating design feedback, establishing priorities and directing/implementing design related revisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Client Delivery&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of the Resource creative process against established timelines and budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staffing of project teams with a close eye on utilization targets for team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active collaboration with Strategy and Creative Domains to ensure effective visual communications and overall functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Business Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to assist in Scoping &amp;amp; estimating projects accurately as well as review and comment on SOW’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in new business opportunity brainstorming and spec work creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s Degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 to 10 years experience in Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years experience in Interactive Marketing and Interface Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive training in graphic design, typography, interaction design and/or visual communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstration of successful leadership experience with a team of at least 5 direct reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding conceptual abilities and collaborative skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong team building and management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills with the ability to present information in verbal, written or visual form to a variety of audiences, from the internal team to client executives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent time management skills and the ability to effectively allocate resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth understanding of interactive usability principles, HTML, dHTML and capabilities of web browsers across platforms is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in the latest versions of design software including: Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash and InDesign. After Effects and sound editing is a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:47:57 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-resource-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-resource-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>