<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/il-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Front-End Developer at Medtelligent in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2005 and based in Chicago, IL, Medtelligent is dedicated to providing cutting-edge technology coupled with superior customer service to the assisted living industry. Our flagship product, ALIS (Assisted Living Intelligent Solutions), provides any and all the tools required to successfully operate an assisted living facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medtelligent Inc. is seeking talented individuals with experience in programming web technologies including CSS, HTML and JavaScript. We are currently building a web based operations management system called ALIS for the long term care industry. ALIS is currently in production use by many long term care facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Front End Developer role involves collaborating with our produce manage and user experience/information architect to define new mockups that satisfy application requirements. The mockups then need to be translated to HTML and CSS, ready for integration with the server side logic. You will also be responsible for integrating JavaScript functionality, building new user controls to enhance and support the desired user experience and managing all CSS/styling templates for the entire application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualified candidates should be comfortable/experienced with the core web technologies including and internet programming. You should also be familiar with server side programming and comfortable with light programming tasks to attach functional user interfaces with existing code/logic/libraries. ALIS is written entirely in C# and makes strategic use of HTML5, JavaScript and CSS for enhanced user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates must be independent, demonstrate strong problem solving skills and initiative. We look for individuals that are highly motivated and solve problems with creativity. You will be working alongside senior developers locally and at remote development centers to write code and deliver working features based on design requirements following an agile software development process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following minimum skills are required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least three years of professional experience, demonstrated by referrals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with CSS, HTML 5, JavaScript and related web technologies (eg. jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in building user interfaces for web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics design skills a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with the Adobe web design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree from an accredited university a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that all your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at MarkIT X in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;MarkITX is looking for a front-end developer to join our team. We want colleagues who are smart and get things done, who are inveterate builders, tinkerers and detectives. We hire people not experience levels, so we have a place for you whether you have built your own MVC framework or are fresh out of school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MarkITx is a B2B exchange for buying and selling IT hardware (anything that goes into a datacenter). We are disrupting the $350B secondary IT market by bringing simplicity and transparency to a process that is currently painful, ugly and untrustworthy. We are a funded startup, working out of 1871. We are a very talented, deeply experienced and tight-knit team. We have some of the best backers and advisors in Chicago. We’ve proven the model, with over $20MM in orders and over $150k per week in transactions, roughly doubling every month. We’re just getting started, and we need your help to scale that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best consumer web apps have far surpassed the best enterprise apps in terms of user experience. Our enterprise users are accustomed to absolutely horrible user experiences with existing options. This gives us a massive opportunity to wow our users with the kind of consumer-grade experience they’re getting used to out of the office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;We Expect&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re more excited about what you can learn, than by what you already know&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can take a project from problem, through ideas and user testing to implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You want to work with a startup, and all that entails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a set of tools that you know intimately&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re happy to give and receive thoughtful criticism&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will quickly get comfortable with our Node.js, Backbone, Handlebars, LESS, Brunch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve used a VCS, and can quickly get comfortable with Git &amp;amp; GitHub&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll commit to production on your first day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll be amazed at how quickly you can move with the right team around you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;We Provide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A team of world-class sales, marketing, engineering, design, data and operations experts who are excited to teach you, and to learn from you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A top-level commitment to open source. We publish and contribute, and you will too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An amazing work environment at 1871, the heart of Chicago’s digital startup ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A competitive compensation package, including equity participation and health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please email us at js@markitx.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-markit-x-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-markit-x-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer / Developer at Grainger Industrial Supplier in Lake Forest, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Grainger is a global leading broad line supplier of facilities maintenance products serving businesses and institutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our 18,000 employees are driven to serve customers and the community in exceptional ways focusing on delivering the highest level of service. The Grainger team works closely with customers to better understand their challenges and provide cost-saving solutions. Grainger&amp;rsquo;s employees serve customers more than 115,000 times every day through multiple channels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of a high-performing team, you’ll be able to develop your talents, and make a difference. Grainger is a Fortune 500 company and a perennial member of Fortune magazine&amp;rsquo;s Most Admired Companies list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position supports web content production for web design, email, and graphics for the Grainger and Specialty brand websites and promotional initiatives. Purpose is to create/develop engaging content and site functionality that encourages conversion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for design, development, quality assurance of company Web sites, e-mail campaigns and other online promotional initiatives while insuring consistent brand voice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Duties include creating, editing and maintaining Web graphics, managing Web site static pages and change requests. Work proficiently with applications and content management systems such as Dreamweaver, Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop), Hybris, Broadvision, Endeca, and others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain web publishing system/schedule, including checking currency, accuracy, quality and availability of content. Enhance/automate the processes for updating and archiving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate ideas, strategies and concepts to meet creative and overall E-Marketing objectives for assigned projects. Create and/or implement graphical content to support projects as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and develop e-commerce opportunities that drive internal and external customer satisfaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with campaign strategy through collaboration, making recommendations and solidifying approach to assure online customer needs are met.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work cross-functionally to improve the customer experience on the Web site and identify opportunities to increase Web site conversion and revenue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively and cross-functionally with project teams to define/improve site user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with IT to design, develop/code and test new site functionality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with E-Com, especially email Marketing and Online Merchandising teams to implement regular updates; implement Search Engine Optimization (SEO) and Search Engine Marketing (SEM) programs, monitor rankings and calculate ROI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remain current and have a thorough understanding of marketing principles, technologies and best practices to assure favorable online user experiences. Stay abreast of Web design, Web development, Web standards, emerging technologies, multimedia tools and techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acts as positive force within the department to attain group and company objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Web Design, Web Development, Computer Science, Graphic Design, Visual Arts related field or comparable work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3-5 years web design and development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create results oriented designs to meet strategic business requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in XHTML and CSS tableless page layout/design and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience with cross-browser and cross-platform issues (IE, Firefox, Safari, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand standards compliant site design and Web 2.0 concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Photoshop, Illustrator and Dreamweaver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert computer skills (Mac and PC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational and time management skills and the ability to prioritize multiple tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Grainger is an equal opportunity employer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-developer-grainger-industrial-supplier-lake-forest-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-developer-grainger-industrial-supplier-lake-forest-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Web Content Developer at OpticsPlanet in Northbrook, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position will primarily be responsible for creating and managing product content on the Company&amp;rsquo;s websites and online databases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure accurate and coherent product content on the websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post content on the website in a timely manner, in accordance with the overall design and content strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add, remove and edit product information on a daily basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and implement changes and updates to product descriptions, prices, images, and specifications reflecting latest promotions and offers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on implementation of websites using Photoshop and HTML editors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide regular updates to other departments within the organization on the changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications, Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associates Degree in Computer Science preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of one year experience working with HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with digital image manipulation and web graphics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML &amp;amp; CSS knowledge and ability to use various HTML Editors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good working knowledge of Microsoft Office products including MS Excel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of PHP and MySQL is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional knowledge of e-commerce, web and database technologies such as SQL, Yahoo Store, Xcart and graphic design skills is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize tasks and deliver results on time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-content-developer-opticsplanet-northbrook-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-content-developer-opticsplanet-northbrook-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Front-End Developer at ARS Interactive &amp; Advertising in Palatine, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ARS Interactive seeks a creative, self-motivated front-end developer to join our web site and application team. You must be well versed in creating and testing cross-browser solutions, CSS and unobtrusive JavaScript to separate structure, presentation and behavior.
You will work closely with our web developers to produce the front-end templates used in our larger web platform and application projects. Exhibit a high level of professionalism at all times, demonstrating courtesy and attention to detail in all your verbal and written communications. As a member of ARS Interactive, your goal will be to produce high quality, elegant solutions that meet or exceed our clients’ requirements and expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the design team with semantic markup and CSS that accurately renders pages in all required web browsers?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cooperate with developers to provide front-end templates for use in web applications?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide effort and time-commitment estimates for projects?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate daily with Account &amp;amp; Project Managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Requirements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce clean, error-free front end solutions that are well documented, browser compatible and compliant with web standards?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of HTML, CSS and semantic layout techniques, plus JavaScript and prevailing JavaScript frameworks (jQuery)?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make efficient use of Adobe Photoshop as a web production tool, including asset management, guides and optimization strategies?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must thrive in a deadline-driven environment that is design focused and technology agnostic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to Have&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indivdual and/or collaborative experience with Version Control Systems (Subersion, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of AJAX, CSS3, HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;APPLY NOW! We are interested in filling this position quickly as the candidate will play a key role in current client projects, making an impact from day one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARS is a growing agency with a robust portfolio of household brands. We provide innovative, strategic and creative solutions for some of the most iconic consumer names. Come and excel in a dynamic, fast-paced agency environment situated in downtown Palatine, IL — just steps away from the local commuter rail station. ARS is a fully integrated marketing, print &amp;amp; interactive design and content management company with a strong focus on client service, innovation and results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our services include: Advertising &amp;amp; Brand Building, Retail Marketing Point-of-Sale, Interactive Marketing Strategy, Interactive Design and Development, Social Marketing, Email and Database Marketing, E-commerce Solutions, Content Management Systems, Product Content Management, Integrated Multichannel Campaigns, and Web Analytics Consulting. Visit thinkars.com to learn more about ARS!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits and Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fun, casual work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharp, “best of the best” team to collaborate with&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical and dental insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Located right across from the Palatine, IL Metra Station (Free Parking and Train Commuter Benefit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-front-end-developer-ars-interactive-%26-advertising-palatine-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-front-end-developer-ars-interactive-%26-advertising-palatine-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Gorilla Inc. in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in HTML/CSS and able to develop valid client-side markup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Photoshop master with the ability to rapidly assess and slice provided PSDs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of CSS support for both modern and legacy browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with native JavaScript and JavaScript libraries (jQuery, Prototype, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An impeccable eye for detail with the ability to match your UI to any design in a cross-browser environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal and communication skills with an affinity for problem-solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to self-manage during projects and proactively raise issues/concerns to the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to own a project from beginning to end, with a strong sense of pride in a job exceptionally done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML 5 and CSS 3 experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating reusable code and JavaScript Plugins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile platform development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge of PHP Experience with eCommerce platforms such as Magento, Demandware, or ATG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CMS platforms such as WordPress, Sitecore, or Expression Engine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Gorilla is a 15 year-old web design and development agency specializing in eCommerce for multi-channel companies. We have a unique group in a client-driven culture looking to expand our reach to exceed the expectations of our clients. This is a full-time position with great benefits:  Medical, dental and life insurance plans; Health Savings Account; Work-from-home options; 401(k) with 3% company contribution; Corporate bonus and sophisticated caffeine delivery systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking talented Front-End Developers to help bring our industry leading designs to life.  The winning Front-End Developer will be comfortable working alongside both creative designers and server-side developers to ensure a successful project.  The position requires a true &amp;lsquo;Front-End Developer&amp;rsquo; with a mastery of semantic mark-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in collaboration with Gorilla’s creative designers to turn their vision into functional HTML templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in collaboration with Gorilla’s server-side developers to ensure proper implementation of website data and functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help manage projects through the design, development and QA processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create W3C Standards Compliant HTML templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue to expand knowledge of new technologies, as well as strengthen current knowledgebase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-gorilla-inc-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-gorilla-inc-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Siteworx, Inc in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Siteworx is looking for a motivated Front End / User Interface Developer to work on large development projects in our downtown Chicago office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be working directly with our User Experience and Design staff to transition interfaces from concept to reality, then working with our product development staff to integrate the interfaces you create into our technical solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication skills are highly important, as you will need to interface with multiple teams of individuals, as well as clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interested candidates should be well-versed in XHTML/HTML5, CSS 2 &amp;amp; 3, and jQuery.  Experience with the Sencha/ExtJS framework and web content management systems, such as Adobe CQ, Sitecore, EPiServer, or Drupal is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must haves: 4-year degree ( pref. in Computer Science) or related fields is preferred, your past experience, examples of your work, your ability to learn, and your demonstrated passion for technology are more important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteworx is an award-winning interactive agency with deep roots in agile design, Web content management (WCM) and systems integration. For more than a decade, we’ve tapped an uncommon blend of technology and design know-how to discover, create and deploy best in class Web and mobile experiences that deliver business results. Siteworx was recently named to the IMA&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Agencies of 2011 and has been recognized among KMWorld&amp;rsquo;s 100 Companies that Matter in Knowledge Management for the last three consecutive years. Headquartered in Reston, Virginia, Siteworx maintains full-service offices in San Francisco, CA, Atlanta, GA, Chicago, IL, Raleigh, NC, Rochester, NY and New York, NY. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.siteworx.com&quot;&gt;http://www.siteworx.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteworx employees are a unique mix of creative and technical individuals whose skill and dedication have won acclaim and loyalty from our many high profile clients. We are passionate about our work and about our lives, and our culture emphasizes the need to balance them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteworx offers competitive salary and benefits including health, dental and life insurance; 401k plan with employer contribution; vacation, holiday and sick leave; and education reimbursement plan. EOE/M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-siteworx-inc-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-siteworx-inc-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>