<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/il-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface Developer at Trunk Club in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are a close-knit customer acquisition technology team focused on building applications for a business that The New York Times has called &amp;ldquo;revolutionary&amp;rdquo; in the world of retail/e-commerce. Our technology stack is modern and designed for engineer happiness.  We build primarily in Rails 3.2, Coffeescript, HAML/SASS, Backbone.js, and other awesome technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the Company&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trunk Club was founded in 2009 and now has over 175 employees.  Trunk Club has raised over $12M in venture capital from investors including USVP (lead investors in LivingSocial), Greycroft, Apex, and Anthos. Our board also includes Thomas Ryan, CEO of Threadless, and Stuart Larkins, former SVP at Performics/Doubleclick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you’d work on:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototyping interfaces for features on TrunkClub.com and our iPhone app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing landing pages, custom promotions and email marketing campaigns seen by hundreds of thousands of people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Converting design into front-end code (HAML, SASS and CoffeeScript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll work closely with our marketing team, software engineers and stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggesting projects, processes, and practices to help us deliver to our full potential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively participating in the joys and challenges of working as part of a tight-knit, resource-constrained team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What your background might look like:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve started companies, worked at an early-stage start-up or have side projects to show off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have 2+ years of professional user interface design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong design portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience writing front-end code (bonus points for HAML, SASS and CoffeeScript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have worked in a MVC framework (Rails, Django, CodeIgniter, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience with responsive, mobile and tablet design (bonus points for iOS development experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be really happy here if:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re passionate about creating beautiful experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You launch quickly, make data-driven decisions, and iterate quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have deep empathy for customers and internal users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You seek feedback sooner rather than later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You A/B test everything&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re looking to contribute not just to our customer experience, but to our culture and company roadmap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love working collaboratively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re comfortable giving feedback and receiving constructive criticism&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-developer-trunk-club-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-developer-trunk-club-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Sigmaways, Inc in Hoffman Estates, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good experience in HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, Json ,JAVA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sigmaways is a leading global consulting and IT services company with over a decade of on-site and offshore engagements, which continue to deliver state-of-the-art IT solutions through quality and ROI. We offer a wide array of solutions for a range of key verticals and horizontals, from the strategy consulting right through to implementing IT solutions for clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sigmaways is a diverse end-to-end IT solutions provider, helping our customers leverage the market knowledge, technical skills and rich industry experience we have gathered through the years. Our methodologies follow best practices and adhere to ever-changing industry standards so that our customers can achieve their goals through faster time-to-market at the most affordable rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sigmaways is made up of a team of highly skilled IT professionals who follow our unique Right Sourcing delivery model. This allows us to leverage local competencies to offer global competitiveness to our customers, helping us deliver best-of-breed solutions to cater to your unique requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sigmaways' consulting and IT solutions have resulted in technology-intensive transformations that have met the most stringent of international quality standards. Our relationships are based on expertise, knowledge and long term commitment to quality for every single customer engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please call me at  :  510 764 2372&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-sigmaways-inc-hoffman-estates-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-sigmaways-inc-hoffman-estates-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at ARS Interactive in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for amazingly talented front-end developers, ready to create engaging experiences for web, tablets, mobile and maybe even places we haven&amp;rsquo;t thought of yet. You should be a savvy, conceptual thinker with an eye for detail, committed to creating solutions that are technically superb and user focused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have dreams about CSS and can tell the difference between strict and transitional doctypes, then this is the job for you. JQuery abilities are a big plus and light PHP experience would be helpful. Aesthetic design skills and experience with mobile development (iPhone/Android), wouldn&amp;rsquo;t hurt. All this while being fun, energetic and just an overall awesome person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write clean, semantic HTML and CSS code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing clean, unobtrusive Javascript/AJAX code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with cross-browser compatibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eager to learn and grow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work at a fast pace and with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependability, reliability, and attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of agency experience as a front end developer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in web site design, development or equivalent required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CMSs such as Magento, Joomla, Drupal, WordPress, etc. is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail or e-commerce experience are a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be professional, highly motivated and able to thrive in a multi-task environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate a high level of accuracy and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online portfolio required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love of ping-pong is a huge plus!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARS is a growing agency with a robust portfolio of household brands. We provide innovative, strategic and creative solutions for some of the most iconic consumer names. Come and excel in a dynamic, fast-paced agency environment situated in downtown Palatine, IL — just steps away from the local commuter rail station. ARS is a fully integrated marketing, print &amp;amp; interactive design and content management company with a strong focus on client service, innovation and results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our services include: Advertising &amp;amp; Brand Building, Retail Marketing Point-of-Sale, Interactive Marketing Strategy, Interactive Design and Development, Social Marketing, Email and Database Marketing, E-commerce Solutions, Content Management Systems, Product Content Management, Integrated Multichannel Campaigns, and Web Analytics Consulting. Visit thinkars.com to learn more about ARS!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits and Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fun, casual work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharp, “best of the best” team to collaborate with&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical and dental insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Located right across from the Palatine, IL Metra Station (Free Parking and Train Commuter Benefit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ars-interactive-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ars-interactive-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Front-End Developer at Medtelligent in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Medtelligent Inc. is seeking talented individuals with experience in programming web technologies including CSS, HTML and JavaScript. We are currently building a web based operations management system called ALIS for the long term care industry. ALIS is currently in production use by many long term care facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Front End Developer role involves collaborating with our product manager and user experience/information architect to define new mockups that satisfy application requirements. The mockups then need to be translated to HTML and CSS, ready for integration with the server side logic. You will also be responsible for integrating JavaScript functionality, building new user controls to enhance and support the desired user experience and managing all CSS/styling templates for the entire application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualified candidates should be comfortable/experienced with the core web technologies including and internet programming. You should also be familiar with server side programming and comfortable with light programming tasks to attach functional user interfaces with existing code/logic/libraries. ALIS is written entirely in C# and makes strategic use of HTML5, JavaScript and CSS for enhanced user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates must be independent, demonstrate strong problem solving skills and initiative. We look for individuals that are highly motivated and solve problems with creativity. You will be working alongside senior developers locally and at remote development centers to write code and deliver working features based on design requirements following an agile software development process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities for candidates qualified to work in the United States. Direct applicants-only; recruiters need not express interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following minimum skills are required:
At least three years of professional experience, demonstrated by referrals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with CSS, HTML 5, JavaScript and related web technologies (eg. jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in building user interfaces for web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics design skills a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with the Adobe web design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree from an accredited university a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that all your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at cre8 in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;cre8 is a small interactive agency in Chicago&amp;rsquo;s West Loop. We&amp;rsquo;ve been around for over ten years and specialize in small to medium-sized business, B2B and Financial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a mid-level Front-End Developer to help design, re-design and maintain our client&amp;rsquo;s websites as well as our own web app, Lead Zeppelin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate has an eye for detail and can communicate well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate designs from Photoshop to HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hand code HTML 4/5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive Design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize code for SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in an ecommerce setting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self motivated and honest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to code for mobile/responsive websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to code emails that perform in different email clients well&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ExpressionEngine CMS, WordPress or DotNetNuke CMS templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Remote work is fine, we&amp;rsquo;re avid Basecamper&amp;rsquo;s and use Skype/Hangouts occasionally. To be considered, please include reference URLs (at least 3), your availability and rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No agencies, no recruiters, please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-cre8-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-cre8-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Belly in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have a favorite taco joint where you are a local celebrity? Or a bar where everyone knows your name? Here at Belly we eat, breathe and live for those situations.  We&amp;rsquo;ve been told we are the MJ of loyalty, the Oprah of rewards and the Ron Burgundy of fun. But we are humble and our goal is simple: to put smiles on our customers’ faces and help our businesses build a deeper relationship with their customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an excellent front-end developer with a passion for beautiful application design and product development.
You must be a wizard at JavaScript and have a strong appreciation of current and emerging standards.  We’re expanding our product offering to mobile and tablet via PhoneGap and we have extensive back end and customer facing platforms which require sexy UI / UX goodness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this position isn’t for a “designer”, you will still have very strong product instincts and be competent with illustration and design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for the best Developers in Chicago and pay will be extremely competitive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills / Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good startup mentality (we have passion for what we do)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to work hard and be part of something&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appreciation of current and emerging standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some Server-side application development in Ruby on Rails and either PHP or Python is beneficial&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely strong JavaScript skills (we use jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident problem solver and troubleshooter, and you proactively challenge traditional solutions (break the mold).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustration, design, product development, user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fun to hang out with&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unit testing (something like QUnit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appreciation of the entire web stack (a life-cycle developer)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internationalization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQLite / Gears / et.al.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Salary is dependent upon experience, but we want only the best&amp;hellip;.. so again, it will be extremely competitive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting immediately!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-belly-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-belly-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Front-End Developer at Medtelligent in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2005 and based in Chicago, IL, Medtelligent is dedicated to providing cutting-edge technology coupled with superior customer service to the assisted living industry. Our flagship product, ALIS (Assisted Living Intelligent Solutions), provides any and all the tools required to successfully operate an assisted living facility.
Job Description&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medtelligent Inc. is seeking talented individuals with experience in programming web technologies including CSS, HTML and JavaScript. We are currently building a web based operations management system called ALIS for the long term care industry. ALIS is currently in production use by many long term care facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Front End Developer role involves collaborating with our product manager and user experience/information architect to define new mockups that satisfy application requirements. The mockups then need to be translated to HTML and CSS, ready for integration with the server side logic. You will also be responsible for integrating JavaScript functionality, building new user controls to enhance and support the desired user experience and managing all CSS/styling templates for the entire application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualified candidates should be comfortable/experienced with the core web technologies including and internet programming. You should also be familiar with server side programming and comfortable with light programming tasks to attach functional user interfaces with existing code/logic/libraries. ALIS is written entirely in C# and makes strategic use of HTML5, JavaScript and CSS for enhanced user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates must be independent, demonstrate strong problem solving skills and initiative. We look for individuals that are highly motivated and solve problems with creativity. You will be working alongside senior developers locally and at remote development centers to write code and deliver working features based on design requirements following an agile software development process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities for candidates qualified to work in the United States. Direct applicants-only; recruiters need not express interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following minimum skills are required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least three years of professional experience, demonstrated by referrals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with CSS, HTML 5, JavaScript and related web technologies (eg. jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in building user interfaces for web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics design skills a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with the Adobe web design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree from an accredited university a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that all your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Front-End Developer at Roundarch Isobar in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;In addition to utilizing all available front-end technologies, the ideal candidate will have experience developing and supporting enterprise-class web applications and have experience working in structured environments following defined development methodologies including client/server and multi-tiered design and development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leveraging a thorough knowledge of HTML/CSS, MVC frameworks, OOP techniques, and proficiency with JavaScript/DOM and JavaScript frameworks,candidate will work in a collaborative environment to develop front-end technologies that produce interactive digital experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidate will take direction from managers and tech leads while communicating issues, providing estimates and helping to provide creative solutions to technical issues.  Candidates must have IT consulting experience, be team-oriented, and possess effective written and verbal communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideal candidate will have experience interfacing with various back-end technologies, frameworks and services. Candidate must prove the ability to master new/emerging technologies, and take initiative to offer technical direction and creative solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills / Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong command of essential web technologies: XHTML, CSS, Javascript (jQuery/Prototype), AJAX, JSON, DOM Scripting, unobtrusive JavaScript, XML/XSLT, W3C DOM methods and properties, Adobe Photoshop and other graphic editing tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of table-less page layout and positioning, browser behavior and compatibility, cross-browser issues and solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with template engines and web application frameworks a plus: JSP, Velocity, JSF, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to Have&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to scrum (or another agile methodology)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to source code management tools like CVS, SVN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Service Oriented Architecture and Web Service development standards (SOAP, XML, WSDL) and in developing on the Spring and Hibernate frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Ruby and Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Adobe Flex and ActionScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to standard development frameworks such as Hibernate, Spring, Axis2, Struts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-developer-roundarch-isobar-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-developer-roundarch-isobar-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Medtelligent in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2005 and based in Chicago, IL, Medtelligent is dedicated to providing cutting-edge technology coupled with superior customer service to the assisted living industry. Our flagship product, ALIS (Assisted Living Intelligent Solutions), provides any and all the tools required to successfully operate an assisted living facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medtelligent Inc. is seeking talented individuals with experience in programming web technologies including CSS, HTML and JavaScript. We are currently building a web based operations management system called ALIS for the long term care industry. ALIS is currently in production use by many long term care facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Front End Developer role involves collaborating with our produce manage and user experience/information architect to define new mockups that satisfy application requirements. The mockups then need to be translated to HTML and CSS, ready for integration with the server side logic. You will also be responsible for integrating JavaScript functionality, building new user controls to enhance and support the desired user experience and managing all CSS/styling templates for the entire application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualified candidates should be comfortable/experienced with the core web technologies including and internet programming. You should also be familiar with server side programming and comfortable with light programming tasks to attach functional user interfaces with existing code/logic/libraries. ALIS is written entirely in C# and makes strategic use of HTML5, JavaScript and CSS for enhanced user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates must be independent, demonstrate strong problem solving skills and initiative. We look for individuals that are highly motivated and solve problems with creativity. You will be working alongside senior developers locally and at remote development centers to write code and deliver working features based on design requirements following an agile software development process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities for candidates qualified to work in the United States. Direct applicants-only; recruiters need not express interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following minimum skills are required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least three years of professional experience, demonstrated by referrals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with CSS, HTML 5, JavaScript and related web technologies (eg. jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in building user interfaces for web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics design skills a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with the Adobe web design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree from an accredited university a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that all your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Front-End Developer at Medtelligent in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2005 and based in Chicago, IL, Medtelligent is dedicated to providing cutting-edge technology coupled with superior customer service to the assisted living industry. Our flagship product, ALIS (Assisted Living Intelligent Solutions), provides any and all the tools required to successfully operate an assisted living facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medtelligent Inc. is seeking talented individuals with experience in programming web technologies including CSS, HTML and JavaScript. We are currently building a web based operations management system called ALIS for the long term care industry. ALIS is currently in production use by many long term care facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Front End Developer role involves collaborating with our produce manage and user experience/information architect to define new mockups that satisfy application requirements. The mockups then need to be translated to HTML and CSS, ready for integration with the server side logic. You will also be responsible for integrating JavaScript functionality, building new user controls to enhance and support the desired user experience and managing all CSS/styling templates for the entire application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualified candidates should be comfortable/experienced with the core web technologies including and internet programming. You should also be familiar with server side programming and comfortable with light programming tasks to attach functional user interfaces with existing code/logic/libraries. ALIS is written entirely in C# and makes strategic use of HTML5, JavaScript and CSS for enhanced user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates must be independent, demonstrate strong problem solving skills and initiative. We look for individuals that are highly motivated and solve problems with creativity. You will be working alongside senior developers locally and at remote development centers to write code and deliver working features based on design requirements following an agile software development process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following minimum skills are required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least three years of professional experience, demonstrated by referrals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with CSS, HTML 5, JavaScript and related web technologies (eg. jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in building user interfaces for web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics design skills a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with the Adobe web design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree from an accredited university a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company we focus on applying technologies to deliver innovative solutions that address difficult and challenging problems. We currently offer contract based and full-time employment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that all your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-medtelligent-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>