<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/il-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Representative at Centro in Chicago, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT THE TEAM&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Centro’s technology team is building web applications to streamline digital media planning, buying and execution. As a Customer Support Representative, your mission is to drive customer satisfaction by addressing customer needs, communicating product updates, establishing a sustainable user feedback loop, and ensuring the delivery of high quality software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Gig:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Centro Customer Support Representative, you will be responsible for&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responding to customer inquiries through a variety of channels including phone, email and chat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing help content, developing training materials and communicating product updates to ensure timely, relevant and accurate information is provided to our users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing sustainable relationships with lead users and clients to obtain valuable feedback and identify product opportunities for future development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engaging in a product development team and ensuring a fulfilling customer experience through the design, development and delivery of essential features and high quality software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You Are Right For This Job if You:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience working in an environment that requires a high sense of urgency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Embody Centro’s “Raving Fan” ethic and are willing to go the extra mile to satisfy our customers’ needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy collaborating with software developers, product managers, and customers to solve real business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have exceptional written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are positive, professional, tactful and organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;An Ideal Candidate Also Possesses:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with software development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A background in online advertising&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A four-year university degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-representative-centro-chicago-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-representative-centro-chicago-il</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Consultant at BigMachines, Inc. in Deerfield, IL</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;BigMachines is the global leader in delivering cloud-based mission critical applications to the Fortune 2000.  Our industry-leading solutions help companies Sell More and Sell Faster, configuring, pricing, and quoting their complex products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the fifth consecutive year we had two great distinctions: landing on the &amp;ldquo;Inc 5000 list of Fastest Growing Companies&amp;rdquo; and being voted #1 on Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s AppExchange.  BigMachines also just delivered another record-setting year in bookings, revenue, profitability, and customer acquisitions.  We do all of this while managing to maintain an industry-leading 95% customer retention rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking to add exceptional talent across our entire company of great people who play hard as a reward for working even harder.  At BigMachines, we thrive on using unique and unconventional methods to drive remarkable employee success.  (We might have an amazing reputation, but we’re not above taking breaks for cheesecake bake-offs and Nerf gun battles.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are committed to hiring really smart, hip and altogether fantastic people who are intellectually invigorated and inspired by advancing their careers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support our rapid growth, we are seeking talented, motivated team members that bring a passion for assisting customers in solving their problems and developing innovative solutions tailored to their needs. As a Customer Support Specialist, you will have the opportunity to work with a powerful web application using some of the latest technologies. You will work closely with our established customers to maintain and enhance their BigMachines solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BigMachines offers opportunities for long-term career growth to successful team members who aspire to deeper technical, project management, or other leadership roles in the company as we believe in building our team from within. Being a Customer Support Specialist is an ideal place to start your career as you will learn both about innovative technology and a wide breadth of customer business solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note: Aptitude testing is required for all positions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzing potential customer solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training customers to maintain and update their own BigMachines solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively utilizing the BigMachines platform, middleware solutions (WebMethods and/or Cast Iron) and web technologies including XML, HTML, XSLT, Python, and AJAX (Javascript) to meet customer requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improving the customer service process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adhering to all BigMachines security policies, standards and procedures in the performance of job duties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participating in security training provided by BigMachines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reporting any potential security weakness, exposure or suspicious indications to manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand the customer&amp;rsquo;s business and work as a business partner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;0-3 years' experience preferred working on technical projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS or MS degree in Computer Science, Engineering, or a technical field from a reputable 4-year college/university&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and comfort with web programming technologies such as HTML, Javascript, Python, Perl, and XSLT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent problem solving, critical thinking, and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quick learner and able to learn new technologies and web programming languages on own as necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of user interface design and web design constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with eCommerce and CRM solutions is helpful, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to work off hours (nights and weekends) as urgent customer needs dictate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-consultant-bigmachines-inc-deerfield-il</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-consultant-bigmachines-inc-deerfield-il</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>