<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/in-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Stonegate Mortgage Corporation in Indianapolis, IN</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graphic Designer will be responsible for taking ideas and visions and giving them a visual concept that relates back to the branding of the company, product, campaign, etc. He or she will work closely with the executive marketing team to conceptualize and deliver a consistent product that promotes Stonegate Mortgage Corporation
Duties: To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty satisfactorily. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the graphic design of branding, advertising, and corporate communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage multiple projects and effectively communicate the status to the management team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform all other duties as requested or assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To perform this job successfully, an individual must have the following education and/or experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative design experience – will want to see portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with customers and understanding the business goals and creating a finished product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in multi-media design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associates or Bachelor’s in Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in InDesign, HTML, and Final Cut Pro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mortgage industry and/or Financial Services experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-stonegate-mortgage-corporation-indianapolis-in</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-stonegate-mortgage-corporation-indianapolis-in</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at Flow International Corporation in Jeffersonville, IN</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create detailed, manufacturable designs to meet or exceed corporate product requirements. Work independently on task assignments with minor supervision from manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work jointly with the Project Manager and/or other associates to create shop-ready, detailed drawings that are functional and meet product and design specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support project leaders and other engineering associates in the preparation and maintenance of project schedule and budget; assures all necessary drawings are completed to project specifications..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify the tasks required to comply with project specification and provide an estimate of the hours to perform each task. Update project leaders with progress reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on cross-functional teams to develop designs for products. Contribute with sketches, drawings and ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain accurate design layouts and parts lists. Assist in the identification and ordering of long lead items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occasionally performs engineering calculations to ensure performance requirements are met.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface with vendors for procurement of components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on prototype designs, both in drawings, procuring parts and setting up tests as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support planning and assembly and assist in debug of products in manufacturing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May supervise and provide leadership to lower level associates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated skill using the local design tools (Solid Works, Pro E, etc.), Agile or other PDM systems, and other system/software tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of analytical ability where problems are complex.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding and application of geometric dimensioning and tolerancing (GD&amp;amp;T) practices per ASME Y14.5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good oral and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills to work effectively with cross functional and diverse work groups, and a self-starter who can work independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability for innovative/creative thinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work overtime and travel as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate degree in Engineering, plus five (5) years of relevant experience; or,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High school graduate, or equivalent, or trade school, plus seven (7) years of experience in the field of machine design utilizing fluid power and mechanical systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-flow-international-corporation-jeffersonville-in</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-flow-international-corporation-jeffersonville-in</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Kenra Professional in Indianapolis, IN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Kenra Professional has an exciting career opportunity for a  Graphic Designer. Kenra is an Indianapolis-based, privately held professional beauty company that is dedicated to providing performance-driven hair care products that stylists trust and that allow our customers to achieve their desired style. Our products are developed and manufactured to exceptionally high standards and can be found in quality salons throughout North America. Everything we do is aimed at ensuring our customers are happy and they achieve inner and outer beauty. Professional beauty is a passion for our employees; and consequently, we have high employee morale and satisfaction. Kenra is a fast-paced Company that embraces change and is guided by a culture that values integrity, passion, and relationships.
Job Description&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  &lt;strong&gt;Graphic Designer&lt;/strong&gt;  will be responsible for establishing the visual tone and esthetics for all Kenra brands, product launches, advertising campaigns, primary and secondary packaging, promotional displays, retail merchandising, as well as print and digital collateral which supports overall brand positioning, all of which convey consistent interpretations of the brand fundamentals and business objectives. This position will produce visual solutions, using a mix of creative skills and commercial awareness.  The candidate must have imaginative flair, awareness of current fashion trends, and a working knowledge of the latest computer packages and an understanding of material costs and time limits, all which impacts design execution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Essential Job Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptual development of campaigns that support brand positioning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Packaging Design (primary and secondary)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merchandising design for specialty retail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate color and fashion trends to build frame work for photo shoots&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design promotional displays and marketing collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with new design ideas for the company brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrate concepts by designing rough layout of art and copy regarding arrangement, size, type size and style, and related aesthetic concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obtain approval of concept through routing process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create visual images that engage, attract, and sell Kenra&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive to customer needs (internal and/or external) and able to create new and original ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to multi-task, juggle multiple priorities and work within tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail-oriented with an emphasis on accuracy, quality and completeness of task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional, upbeat, energetic, and dependable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take pride in work, is detail oriented, thrives in a collaborative team environment, and is passionate about design, aesthetics, and branding&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online portfolios links or PDF work samples must be supplied with resume&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kenra offers an attractive compensation package, product discounts, and generous health and retirement benefit programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No telephone calls, faxes or agencies please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kenra Professional, LLC, is an Equal Opportunity Employer and does not discriminate with respect to recruitment, hiring, or any other status of employment on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability or any other category protected by law.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-kenra-professional-indianapolis-in</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-kenra-professional-indianapolis-in</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>