<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/la-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Bizzuka, Inc. in Lafayette, LA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bizzuka seeks an amazing and experienced Front End Web Developer/Designer that can expertly turn website designs into real working sites. The ideal candidate must have an expert working knowledge of HTML, JavaScript and CSS, Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator. The candidate must also have a working knowledge of commonly-used web concepts, practices, and procedures. Excellent verbal and written communication skills are required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Specific Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slices Photoshop design files for website implementations applied as a &amp;ldquo;skin&amp;rdquo; to the Bizzuka system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revises and extends existing website and intranet designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scopes design revisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writes custom HTML/JavaScript/CSS for site implementations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works directly with project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relies on experience and judgment to plan and accomplish goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional responsibilities, depending on experience level:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May create new Website and intranet designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May consult with customers to create marketing objectives for their website projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May develop creative briefs and design concepts to meet our customer&amp;rsquo;s business objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May plan and review the navigational user interface design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May troubleshoot, test and oversee the launch of websites and intranets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May act as a liaison for the creative content team and the programming team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May coordinate with other departments to identify challenges, recommend, and implement solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs a variety of complicated tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates schedules with internal and external participants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, JavaScript and CSS, Adobe Photoshop, and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of commonly-used web concepts, practices, and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a different javascript frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to date with latest and upcoming trends (CSS3, HTML5, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-bizzuka-inc-lafayette-la</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-bizzuka-inc-lafayette-la</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>