<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ma-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Drupal Web Developer at Merchant Warehouse in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a web developer who can work with the business and marketing departments to constantly improve our website. This candidate is responsible for the implementation and coding of our website. They will be involved with both the technical and graphical aspect of the website –how the site works and how it looks.  The ideal candidate will have a wide range of web skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support  and continually develop existing web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain few static websites and several CMS websites (Drupal/Wordpress)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement Drupal based websites including installation, configuration, custom module development and theming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debug web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code landing pages associated with marketing campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with designers to create wireframes and assist in the prototyping of the design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new web applications as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Drupal, specifically experience with Drupal 6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in writing cross-browser/platform compatible HTML/XHTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the CMS interface for Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience with PHP, MySQL , JavaScript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the Webform, Chaos Tools Suite, and Views modules for Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience installing, testing, and debugging updates to Drupal core, modules, and themes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drupal theming experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of two years of relevant work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong time-management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior communication skills and experience working directly with designers and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred skills/experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 and CSS3 coding experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Drupal, specifically experience with Drupal 6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and confidence using Version Control with Subversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency working with PHP, MySQL, JavaScript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the Domain Access module for Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drupal module development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with and implementing Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Merchant Warehouse&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merchant Warehouse is a recognized leader in payment acceptance solutions and merchant services. The company enables merchants, agents, POS developers and VARs to achieve strategic business advantage through the delivery of current and emerging payment, offer and program solutions and merchant services that dramatically enhance the merchant-customer experience. Merchant Warehouse is one of the fastest growing and innovative payment solutions companies in North America. For more information about Merchant Warehouse, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://merchantwarehouse.com&quot;&gt;http://merchantwarehouse.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/drupal-web-developer-merchant-warehouse-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/drupal-web-developer-merchant-warehouse-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Staples in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Web Development Team within the Agency at Staples, the Web Developer works directly with interactive designers, copywriters and account team members to create strategically effective and user-centric Marketing and eCommerce pieces, including promotional landing pages, microsites and emails. Core to the position will be supporting our omnichannel marketing &amp;amp; eCommerce teams.
The Web Developer must have the ability to demonstrate high-level hand code, along with a creative eye for detail and design. Development centered on web-standards compliant code and content management systems is a must.
The Developer must be passionate about working with many different types of web programming approaches, and possess the ability to move quickly and comfortably between multiple projects. A desire to stay abreast of emerging technologies and new media applications is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expectations are that the developer will work collaboratively with UX and visual designers on key initiatives to ensure code and creative designs work hand-in-hand and are consistent to the concept. Responsibilities will include creating finished HTML pages from concepts, maintaining existing web content &amp;amp; structure, and ensuring the sites and/or landing pages maintain a strong, consistent look and feel. Solutions should demonstrate a thoughtful approach to strategy and the Easy Brand Promise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Partner with onsite and remote team members, while serving as liaison between design teams and web programming world. Assist other developers with projects as needed. Demonstrate the ability work with little supervision. Ability to brainstorm and present is a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+Years Related Experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor degree in Interactive Development, Computer Science or similar preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in online and rich-media development. In-depth experience in web production; including graphic optimization, slicing and editing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in HTML, JavaScript, XML, CSS, and Flash (Action Scripting), with in working knowledge of other emerging technologies and new media trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work comfortably on Macintosh and PC platforms – must have experience with cross-platform and cross-browser compatibility issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Macintosh OS and Windows operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;URLs of at least 5 existing web-based/interactive communications with explanation of development or production role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all, must have great sense of humor as well as a sense of urgency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Employment Statement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staples is an Equal Opportunity Employer who values the diversity of our people, products, and services.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-staples-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-staples-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>