<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ma-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Web Developer at Euro-Pro in Newton, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Euro-Pro, (creator of the familiar brands Shark® and Ninja®), is a pioneer in innovative cleaning solutions and small household appliances. We have been recognized as one of the &amp;ldquo;Fastest growing, most innovative developers of Home Appliances in the World!&amp;rdquo; Our products provide the latest in easy-to-use technology with a growing line of products that consist of corded and cordless vacuums, steam mops and cleaners, irons and garment steamers, blenders, and a variety of small kitchen appliances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have achieved significant market share in the housewares industry with our functional, innovative products and have become one of the leading companies in the sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Euro-Pro is growing and currently looking for talented, passionate individuals throughout our global offices. We are a Boston-based (Newton, MA) company, with offices in Canada and various locations throughout China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Euro-Pro Highlights&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company revenues have tripled in size over the last three years!!!  Euro Pro has grown from less than $300m to over $900m in Revenue since 2007!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Named to Inc. magazine’s Inc. 5000 list of the fastest-growing private companies in America for the past 3 consecutive years!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awarded Wal-Mart vendor of the Year for the past 4 consecutive years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Euro-Pro is looking for an experienced Associate Web Developer to further the evolution of the organization’s online strategy &amp;amp; execution. This person will maintain our existing websites, both graphically &amp;amp; backend implementation, including but not limited to HTML &amp;amp; video editing/encoding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain &amp;amp; update our existing websites. This includes but is not limited to editing, adding &amp;amp; deleting * pages/photos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure consistency throughout all parts of the website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that all design elements &amp;amp; templates work within a variety of browser types &amp;amp; screen settings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, track &amp;amp; report on site metrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the design, customization &amp;amp; maintenance of our social media accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remain current with emerging web technologies, tools &amp;amp; updates through relevant blogs, events, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Attributes and Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to implement JavaScript-based analytics, conversion &amp;amp; social media APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of LAMP-based web server platforms (Linux/Apache/MySQL/PHP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability work with layered creative files &amp;amp; export web optimized assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work with raw video &amp;amp; produce web optimized assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of XML &amp;amp; JSON data formats used configuration &amp;amp; persistence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong working knowledge of FTP &amp;amp; file synchronization techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in a related field &amp;amp; 1-3 years' experience in developing &amp;amp; maintaining a website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High degree of proficiency in Adobe Photoshop, HTML5, CSS &amp;amp; the DOM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with DIV-based layouts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An intimate knowledge of modern web browsers &amp;amp; their behavior including Mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of content management systems &amp;amp; video editing/encoding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written &amp;amp; oral skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;At Euro-Pro, we are driven to be the best in the industry. We are looking for individuals who want to make a difference. We celebrate and reward initiative, creativity, growth, and commitment to our mission. We will provide the challenge and opportunity to apply all aspects of your experience and skills; you provide the energy, passion, and results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Euro-Pro supports the national policy of Equal Employment Opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is our goal at Euro-Pro to recruit applicants for jobs without regard to race, color, religion, national origin, ancestry, age, sex, sexual orientation, handicap, marital status or veteran status.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-web-developer-euro-pro-newton-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-web-developer-euro-pro-newton-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at HitBliss in Lexington, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;HitBliss is an exciting startup that lets consumers earn money to pay for premium content by engaging with top brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the web development team, you’ll be implementing consumer-facing interfaces for our website that will showcase some of the best premium content from Hollywood and TV networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, maintain, and enhance front-end consumer web applications that will be seen by millions of people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with product management, visual design,  and QA in a highly interactive environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of modern web technologies (HTML, JavaScript, and CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building dynamic websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile web development is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent, energetic, highly technical, and works well under pressure and ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US citizen or permanent resident&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About the Team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were founded by a team of serial entrepreneurs who have built consumer internet ventures from the ground up and exited each of them at multimillion dollar valuations. Our culture is one of ambition, collaboration, and high-energy. If you have an entrepreneurial spirit, love tackling challenging problems, and want to work with a great team, we’d love to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is for a full-time position based in Lexington, MA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer a competitive salary and full benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-hitbliss-lexington-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-hitbliss-lexington-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead Developer at LaunchWare, Inc in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Come build a team and grow with LaunchWare. It’s a great opportunity to be a pivotal player and create awesome applications. This is a full time position. Help lead a growing team and establish yourself as an authority in the Boston development community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have many exciting projects to get involved in, and we continue to seek clients that have significant social impact or provide tangible business value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that software delivered is delivered qualitatively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and mentor a small group of eager learners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a results only environment. Work where and when you want, as long as the work gets done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a very small and innovative consulting company that endeavors to delight its clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with clients to discover and confirm requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve interesting problems in the simplest way possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write well tested and expressive ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate design patterns and architectural techniques that help web applications scale and change with requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build rich internet applications with JQuery and Backbone.js along with other exciting client side technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write tests first and implementation second&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and maintain Rails 3 applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write semantic, W3C compliant markup and unobtrusive, object oriented javascript with JQuery and Backbone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with the company’s principal and founder, Dan Pickett and a growing team of enthusiastic developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What We’re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven track record of building and deploying quality web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean, well thought out code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid communication skills as indicated from references. To be an effective leader, you must communicate extremely effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong, insatiable desire to learn and hone your craft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical, demonstrated knowledge of web standards and best practices in front end development (HTML5/CSS3, Semantic Markup, Progressive Enhancement, W3C compliance, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A demonstrated understanding of the Rails framework and MVC fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three years experience in the web development field, preferably with interpreted, back-end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proficiency in object oriented design and architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;It would rock if you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have team leadership experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have demonstrated leadership abilities outside of development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate gets excited about learning new things and working with various parts of the Rails stack. Your goals should include establishing yourself as a helpful and integral member of the Web Development community at large. If you don’t want to build and share your knowledge, this is not the gig for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resumes are great, but practical application and endorsements from your peers, employers or clients will secure the position. We are extremely selective, so be prepared to justify why you think you’re the best at what you do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most work can and will be done remotely, but we find pairing and collaboration to be most effective when we’re physically working alongside each another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LaunchWare is a web development consultancy that loves to ship. We work towards establishing quantifiable value for all of our clients. We refine, build, and deploy quality software that solves real problems. We speak business first and geek a close second, ensuring that clients get software that solves their problems as simply as possible. We are firm believers in the promises of Agile Development methodologies and efficient web frameworks. We are lifelong learners, teachers, thinkers, and innovators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next year, we plan to continue building great applications for our clients. We’re also building training programs, publications, and our own products as well. Come help shape the vision and be part of the founding team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s truly an opportunity to get involved in some great projects and learn a lot. We hope to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No third parties or agencies, please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-developer-launchware-inc-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-developer-launchware-inc-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Developer at LaunchWare, Inc in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Come learn and grow with LaunchWare. It’s a great opportunity to improve your coding skills and create awesome applications. This is a full time position. Learn all the coolest, client-side technologies like HTML5, SCSS, BackboneJS, and Jasmine while honing your Rails skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wanted to contribute to an application that will really help people find what they need? We’ve launched a network for cancer patients and their loved ones so that they can find better care, more support, and connections with others that have similar experience. We’re anticipating heavy traffic volumes and usage as the client has partnered with American Cancer Society. This is truly a fun, rewarding project and an excellent client. There’s some really interesting problems here around matching users with relevant peers, resources, events, and services among many others. We have many other exciting projects to get involved in, and we continue to seek clients that have significant, social, impact in areas like Healthcare and beyond. Come solve their problems with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a results only environment. Work where and when you want, as long as the work gets done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn design patterns and architectural techniques that help web applications scale and change with requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn JQuery and Backbone.js along with other exciting client side technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to write tests first and implementation second&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and maintain Rails 3 applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to write good user stories, acceptance criteria, and acceptance tests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that software delivered is delivered qualitatively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write semantic, W3C compliant markup and unobtrusive, object oriented javascript with JQuery and Backbone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write well tested and expressive ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve interesting problems in the simplest way possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with clients to discover and confirm requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a very small and innovative consulting company that endeavors to delight its clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with the company’s principal and founder, Dan Pickett and a growing team of enthusiastic developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What We’re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical, demonstrated knowledge of web standards and best practices in front end development (HTML5/CSS3, Semantic Markup, Progressive Enhancement, W3C compliance, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid communication skills as indicated from references. You will interface directly with clients on a regular basis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong, insatiable desire to learn and hone your craft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A demonstrated understanding of the Rails framework and MVC fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two years experience in the web development field, preferably with interpreted, back-end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A familiarity with object oriented design and architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean, well thought out code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;It would rock if you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have built a few rails applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have written javascript and understand JQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ideal candidate gets excited about learning new things and working with various parts of the Rails stack. Your goals should include establishing yourself as a helpful and integral member of the Web Development community at large. If you don’t want to build and share your knowledge, this is not the gig for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Resumes are great, but practical application and endorsements from your peers, employers or clients will secure the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most work can be done remotely, but we find pairing and collaboration to be most effective when we’re physically working alongside each another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LaunchWare is a web development consultancy that loves to ship. We work towards establishing quantifiable value for all of our clients. We refine, build, and deploy quality software that solves real problems. We speak business first and geek a close second, ensuring that clients get software that solves their problems as simply as possible. We are firm believers in the promises of Agile Development methodologies and efficient web frameworks. We are lifelong learners, teachers, thinkers, and innovators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next year, we plan to continue building great applications for our clients. We’re also building training programs, publications, and our own products as well. Come help shape the vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s truly an opportunity to get involved in some great projects and learn a lot. We hope to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No third parties or agencies, please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/developer-launchware-inc-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/developer-launchware-inc-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead Developer at LaunchWare, Inc in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Come build a team and grow with LaunchWare. It’s a great opportunity to be a pivotal player and create awesome applications. This is a full time position. Help lead a growing team and establish yourself as an authority in the Boston development community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have many exciting projects to get involved in, and we continue to seek clients that have significant social impact or provide tangible business value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that software delivered is delivered qualitatively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and mentor a small group of eager learners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a results only environment. Work where and when you want, as long as the work gets done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a very small and innovative consulting company that endeavors to delight its clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with clients to discover and confirm requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve interesting problems in the simplest way possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write well tested and expressive ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate design patterns and architectural techniques that help web applications scale and change with requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build rich internet applications with JQuery and Backbone.js along with other exciting client side technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write tests first and implementation second&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and maintain Rails 3 applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write semantic, W3C compliant markup and unobtrusive, object oriented javascript with JQuery and Backbone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with the company’s principal and founder, Dan Pickett and a growing team of enthusiastic developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What We’re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven track record of building and deploying quality web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean, well thought out code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid communication skills as indicated from references. To be an effective leader, you must communicate extremely effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong, insatiable desire to learn and hone your craft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical, demonstrated knowledge of web standards and best practices in front end development (HTML5/CSS3, Semantic Markup, Progressive Enhancement, W3C compliance, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A demonstrated understanding of the Rails framework and MVC fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three years experience in the web development field, preferably with interpreted, back-end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proficiency in object oriented design and architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;It would rock if you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have team leadership experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have demonstrated leadership abilities outside of development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate gets excited about learning new things and working with various parts of the Rails stack. Your goals should include establishing yourself as a helpful and integral member of the Web Development community at large. If you don’t want to build and share your knowledge, this is not the gig for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resumes are great, but practical application and endorsements from your peers, employers or clients will secure the position. We are extremely selective, so be prepared to justify why you think you’re the best at what you do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most work can and will be done remotely, but we find pairing and collaboration to be most effective when we’re physically working alongside each another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LaunchWare is a web development consultancy that loves to ship. We work towards establishing quantifiable value for all of our clients. We refine, build, and deploy quality software that solves real problems. We speak business first and geek a close second, ensuring that clients get software that solves their problems as simply as possible. We are firm believers in the promises of Agile Development methodologies and efficient web frameworks. We are lifelong learners, teachers, thinkers, and innovators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next year, we plan to continue building great applications for our clients. We’re also building training programs, publications, and our own products as well. Come help shape the vision and be part of the founding team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s truly an opportunity to get involved in some great projects and learn a lot. We hope to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No third parties or agencies, please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-developer-launchware-inc-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-developer-launchware-inc-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Drupal Web Developer at Merchant Warehouse in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a web developer who can work with the business and marketing departments to constantly improve our website. This candidate is responsible for the implementation and coding of our website. They will be involved with both the technical and graphical aspect of the website –how the site works and how it looks.  The ideal candidate will have a wide range of web skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support  and continually develop existing web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain few static websites and several CMS websites (Drupal/Wordpress)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement Drupal based websites including installation, configuration, custom module development and theming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debug web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code landing pages associated with marketing campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with designers to create wireframes and assist in the prototyping of the design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new web applications as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Drupal, specifically experience with Drupal 6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in writing cross-browser/platform compatible HTML/XHTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the CMS interface for Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience with PHP, MySQL , JavaScript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the Webform, Chaos Tools Suite, and Views modules for Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience installing, testing, and debugging updates to Drupal core, modules, and themes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drupal theming experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of two years of relevant work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong time-management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior communication skills and experience working directly with designers and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred skills/experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 and CSS3 coding experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Drupal, specifically experience with Drupal 6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and confidence using Version Control with Subversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency working with PHP, MySQL, JavaScript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the Domain Access module for Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drupal module development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with and implementing Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Merchant Warehouse&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merchant Warehouse is a recognized leader in payment acceptance solutions and merchant services. The company enables merchants, agents, POS developers and VARs to achieve strategic business advantage through the delivery of current and emerging payment, offer and program solutions and merchant services that dramatically enhance the merchant-customer experience. Merchant Warehouse is one of the fastest growing and innovative payment solutions companies in North America. For more information about Merchant Warehouse, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://merchantwarehouse.com&quot;&gt;http://merchantwarehouse.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/drupal-web-developer-merchant-warehouse-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/drupal-web-developer-merchant-warehouse-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Staples in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Web Development Team within the Agency at Staples, the Web Developer works directly with interactive designers, copywriters and account team members to create strategically effective and user-centric Marketing and eCommerce pieces, including promotional landing pages, microsites and emails. Core to the position will be supporting our omnichannel marketing &amp;amp; eCommerce teams.
The Web Developer must have the ability to demonstrate high-level hand code, along with a creative eye for detail and design. Development centered on web-standards compliant code and content management systems is a must.
The Developer must be passionate about working with many different types of web programming approaches, and possess the ability to move quickly and comfortably between multiple projects. A desire to stay abreast of emerging technologies and new media applications is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expectations are that the developer will work collaboratively with UX and visual designers on key initiatives to ensure code and creative designs work hand-in-hand and are consistent to the concept. Responsibilities will include creating finished HTML pages from concepts, maintaining existing web content &amp;amp; structure, and ensuring the sites and/or landing pages maintain a strong, consistent look and feel. Solutions should demonstrate a thoughtful approach to strategy and the Easy Brand Promise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Partner with onsite and remote team members, while serving as liaison between design teams and web programming world. Assist other developers with projects as needed. Demonstrate the ability work with little supervision. Ability to brainstorm and present is a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+Years Related Experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor degree in Interactive Development, Computer Science or similar preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in online and rich-media development. In-depth experience in web production; including graphic optimization, slicing and editing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in HTML, JavaScript, XML, CSS, and Flash (Action Scripting), with in working knowledge of other emerging technologies and new media trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work comfortably on Macintosh and PC platforms – must have experience with cross-platform and cross-browser compatibility issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Macintosh OS and Windows operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;URLs of at least 5 existing web-based/interactive communications with explanation of development or production role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all, must have great sense of humor as well as a sense of urgency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Employment Statement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staples is an Equal Opportunity Employer who values the diversity of our people, products, and services.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-staples-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-staples-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>