<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feeds/ma-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Experience Designer/Interactive Designer at Unitrends in Burlington, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Senior User Experience Designer/Interactive Designer is a critical member of the Marketing team and is the steward for the brand across multiple vehicles and customer experience across all online properties.  The Senior User Experience Designer is responsible for Unitrends primary and associated web sites and platforms, including partner and customer portals, eCommerce platform, CRM/SFA applications and marketing operations platform.  We’re looking for a candidate with outstanding conceptual design skills and a strong understanding of information architecture and user-centered design principles to serve as the in-house resource for all graphic design and brand standards across multiple touch points and vehicles. This candidate is expected to be strongly versed in web best practices, along with a balance of both creative talent and technical depth, arrying both best in class user experience with practical go to market strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Manage Entire Web Environment &amp;amp; Ecosystem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and expand best in class user experience focused web site for North American and international markets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration of the company systems to the web site delivering lead conversions, net new users and eCommerce activity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the continual development of features on the web site(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor web site server and site technical performance – manage site hosting (live and sandbox environments), marketing operations application (Eloqua), and trouble shoot site (content, links, flows, and transaction logs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review statistics and monitor analytics – provide analysis of the web site’s business health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, develop and manage content that’s consistent with the overall brand and drives higher web site ‘stickiness’ and engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate familiarity with content management systems (Kentico)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a consistent look and feel throughout all web properties; create and improve a visual language across the company’s web properties and marketing materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep current with emerging web technologies through relevant blogs, listservs, and events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assure web-based information is archived for future needs and reference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and manage website system and infrastructure, including CMS allowing broader staff to help drive and maintain dynamic content updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create secure data transfer between web and internal systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Be the In-House Design Expert&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves as the expert in graphic design standards, desktop publishing, print production methods, user-centered design, web interface standards, web browser technologies, web accessibility issues, and open and evolving web document and web development standards such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create library ad brand standards for Unitrends across all go to market vehicles – from web properties, to demand gen activities (PPC ads, landing pages, collateral assets, hardware appliances, letterhead, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with staff on projects identifying time constraints, key requirements and assets needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience (5+ years) in interactive visual design with expertise related to B2B high-tech.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in all phases of user experience design: discovery (competitive research, analytics, &amp;amp; interviews, etc), wireframe design, prototyping, user testing, interactive design &amp;amp; creative direction, QA &amp;amp; deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop and present effective site strategies, site maps, wireframes, and user flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work with our internal team to continually refine and evolve our User Experience process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong web graphics production capability and practitioner experience with Photoshop, Fireworks or similar tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design best practices, email marketing, social media, SEM/SEO skills required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with current web development technologies and standards, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX and XML knowledge required.  WordPress or other blog app experience required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing for mobile and responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail, and a commitment to delivering highly-polished designs under tight time constraints.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills – both written and oral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Google Analytics, Adwords, Salesforce.com and Marketing automation system (Eloqua, Marketo, similar application)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 11:54:53 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-unitrends-burlington-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-unitrends-burlington-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>