<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ma-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at SeaChange International in Acton, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Love building cool concepts that go to market? Like collaborating with teams that “get it”? Want to work on the future of television? Here at SeaChange International we are doing just that and more. Come join the experience design team as we chart the future and design some breakthrough products. We are looking for some great talent and here are the details on what the role entails:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce design concepts, create wire frames and mockups based on business requirements, translating product strategy into design concepts that meet brand standards, user goals and business objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within an interdisciplinary team that includes user experience designers, developers, product managers as well as other stakeholders throughout all phases of the development cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with all flavors of user-centered design methodologies and processes including:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create diagrams of business processes and interaction flows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create mock-ups for internal reviews and usability testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong writing and presentation skills as well as demonstrable visual communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interact effectively with other design professionals as well as developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Champion the user experience strategy and vision set by the UX team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a good communicator, self-managing own time and deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience as an interaction designer or user interface designer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree or equivalent in design related field including interaction design, industrial design or human computer interaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on enterprise-scale, web-based commercial software applications. Extensive experience with rich-client interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have an understanding and passionate about user centered research and design and applying it to create effective interaction designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-organized with strong communication skills and the ability to handle multiple tasks/projects simultaneously across multiple teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a global team across time zones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated self-starter with excellent problem-solving skills who enjoys working in a fast-paced, success-driven environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with various design tools – Adobe Creative Suite, Balsamiq, Axure, Visio and OmniGraffle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in an agile development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototyping skills with ProtoShare, HTML/CSS a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;APPLICATION INSTRUCTIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please email your resume in .doc, .docx, .pdf, .txt, .rtf, .html, or .ascii format to the address below. If you wish to enclose a cover letter, please include it in the body of your email message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;103097-CJB-0@schange.hrmdirect.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-seachange-international-acton-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-seachange-international-acton-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Graphic Designer at Staples in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Staples is the world’s largest office products company and a trusted source for office solutions. The company provides products, services and expertise in office supplies, copy &amp;amp; print, technology, facilities and breakroom, and furniture. Staples invented the office superstore concept in 1986 and now has annual sales of $25 billion, ranking second in the world in eCommerce sales. With 90,000 associates worldwide, Staples operates in 26 countries throughout North and South America, Europe, Asia and Australia, making it easy for businesses of all sizes, and consumers. The company is headquartered outside Boston. More information about Staples (Nasdaq: SPLS) is available at www.staples.com/media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Junior Designer is responsible for providing production support to his/her Team. This includes, but is not limited to, performing production edits, participating in generating solutions to design challenges, assisting in the preparation of materials for presentations and reviews, both print and electronic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Junior Designer will receive guidance in many aspects of creative conception and implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she will develop an understanding of brand standards and apply them appropriately to create visual solutions that meet business and user needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Junior Designer will develop an understanding of the Team’s goals in support of the business and learn to recognize when creative is not on strategy to reach out to the extended Team for resolution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be versatile in multiple types of marketing communications and possess ability to move quickly and comfortably between projects while maintaining timely, accurate and high-quality work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Arts/Graphic Design or relevant professional certifications in graphic design from a reputed institute along with 1-2 years of experience in a related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Adobe Creative Suite (CSS) for Macintosh, In-Design, Photoshop, Illustrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor Degree in Graphic Design/Art focus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 years previous design experience and some basic understanding of HTML. Dreamweaver and Flash experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently as well as in a team environment with patience, tact, and diplomacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working understanding of marketing principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be motivated, highly organized, flexible during peak workload, detail oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess excellent time-management and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all, must have great sense of humor as well as a sense of urgency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-graphic-designer-staples-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-graphic-designer-staples-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer/Developer (Mobile) at Buildium in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We need a Mobile UX Developer, ideally with business app experience. Your product will be sleek and super functional on our customers' iPhones, Android devices, and tablets. We want an awesome user experience that feels natural. You can help make that a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot to offer, so do we. A team of smart, awesome people in a highly collaborative environment. Cutting-edge technologies. Great downtown location. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt that we&amp;rsquo;re a BBJ Best Place to Work, or that we&amp;rsquo;re on the Inc. 5000 list of fastest growing companies. We&amp;rsquo;re getting bigger and we need the right people for the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the design team to create and implement an awesome mobile app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Figure out how to build reusable code across our mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide a UI that feels like it belongs on the platform it&amp;rsquo;s running on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and develop the Buildium app for iOS and/or Android with code from visual comps and requirements documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rapidly fix bugs and solve problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay on top of industry issues and trends, particularly with regards to accessibility, usability, and emerging technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years in writing awesome code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on design and development experience in mobile (iOS and/or Android)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail in a rich user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Objective-C and Java&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to build a business application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not afraid to dig into native code to understand it and make it better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication and problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a distributed, unstructured, small company environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-sufficient and comfortable with ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take-What-You-Need time off policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and dental insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) retirement plan with company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Group life, short-term, and long-term disability insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible spending and dependent care accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to work in a small, innovative start-up environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ping-pong and foosball tables for superior hand-eye coordination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Buildium&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buildium LLC is a growing, entrepreneurial cloud-based software company located in Boston&amp;rsquo;s historic Fort Point Channel area. Founded in 2004, Buildium&amp;rsquo;s property management software is used by thousands of landlords, property managers, and associations to manage nearly half a million units in 31 countries around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-developer-mobile-buildium-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-developer-mobile-buildium-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at Buildium in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;There may be other UX Designer job descriptions out there, but at Buildium, we have our own idea of what makes a great UX Designer: a detailed thinker who shows a clear understanding of design problems from business, user, and technical perspectives. Someone who cares deeply about delivering high-quality user experiences that are easy to understand, efficient, and representative of the Buildium brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are also fundamentally curious about the way things work, both in the digital and physical world. They realize the value of process and best practices, but are open to exploring new ways of communicating concepts and information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a UX Designer at Buildium, you&amp;rsquo;ll collaborate with development, marketing, customer care, and other members of the design team to create amazing user experiences with our web and mobile products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buildium is casual, open, collaborative, and noisy at times with a singular focus: building a great company. We eat lunch together, talk about pop culture and current events; and genuinely enjoy each other&amp;rsquo;s company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t hire based on a list of buzzwords or acronyms on your resume. We are not only looking for someone who can create solutions that meet the business and technical requirements; we&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who dreams big about changing the way people interact with technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that&amp;rsquo;s you, apply and link us to your portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create design deliverables such as process flows, wireframes, graphic design assets, specifications, and prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with stakeholders to understand goals, requirements, personas, and context&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate effectively with UX colleagues, technical team members, and other project stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform qualitative and quantitative user research to understand user needs and evaluate design solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish and document interaction design standards for common usage across Buildium&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in interaction design or a related field is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years' experience designing websites and web apps; mobile design and Agile experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience designing complex, data driven web and/or mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio of work showing information architecture, interaction, and visual design artifacts such as sitemaps, process flows, high-fidelity wireframes, screen comps, and functional prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of qualitative user research methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency working with design software tools including Adobe CS5 on your preferred OS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in an unstructured, start-up environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-sufficient, detail oriented, and comfortable with ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take-What-You-Need Paid Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and dental insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) retirement plan with company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Group life, short-term, and long-term disability insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible spending and dependent care accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to work in a small, innovative start-up environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ping-pong and foosball tables for superior hand-eye coordination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Buildium LLC&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buildium LLC is a growing, entrepreneurial cloud-based software company located in Boston&amp;rsquo;s historic Fort Point Channel area. Founded in 2004, Buildium&amp;rsquo;s property management software is used by thousands of landlords, property managers, and associations to manage nearly half a million units in 31 countries around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-buildium-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-buildium-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at ConvergEx Group in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Eze Castle Software is looking for a talented User Experience (UX) Designer to join our Boston-based team. As a member of our UX team, you will work collaboratively with the product management and development teams to transform functional/business specifications into highly polished, intuitive UIs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position affords opportunities to work across a broad range of UX-related disciplines, from UI prototyping and interaction design, to usability testing and information architecture. The ideal candidate will be a well-rounded UX generalist who combines outstanding design skills with strong analytical, technical, and problem-solving abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product managers to understand complex functional requirements and transform them into detailed design specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate design recommendations using wireframes, flowcharts, high-fidelity design comps, interactive prototypes, and the occasional cocktail napkin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create production-ready assets (icons, application themes, etc.) using design tools such as Photoshop, Illustrator, and Expression Blend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocate for the needs of end-users throughout the product design process; evangelize &amp;amp; promote good design principles and best practices throughout the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independently manage multiple, concurrent projects in a fast-paced development environment, proactively ensuring that appropriate UX considerations are made throughout the SDLC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with project stakeholders to build consensus behind the best practical (not always the best possible) design solutions; produce final design specs that balance development deadlines and implementation costs against key design considerations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform UX reviews for projects in active development to ensure that they adhere to design specifications and established style guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize and facilitate small-scale usability tests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help define, document, and communicate formal style guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 4-year degree (B.S. or B.A.), ideally in a related field (design, HCI, human factors, computer science, technical writing, psychology, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of experience designing, developing, or documenting complex software solutions for the web or desktop environments; mobile design experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Adobe Creative Suite; working knowledge of Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of fundamental design principles and usability heuristics; ability to articulate the reasoning behind design decisions and communicate effectively with non-designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototyping experience strongly preferred — e.g. familiarity with WPF, XAML, C#, Expression Blend, Flash, Cocoa, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, or similar. We currently use WPF/XAML for the bulk of our prototyping work. At a minimum, the successful candidate will be tech-savvy, curious, and motivated to learn new skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to create polished, professional designs that anticipate and accommodate the needs of users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants should submit a cover letter, resume, and a portfolio of recent design work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compensation includes a competitive base salary, performance bonus, 401K matching &amp;amp; excellent benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Eze:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eze is a leading investment technology company with locations throughout the U.S., and in London, Rio de Janeiro, Hong Kong, Sydney, and Singapore.  The Eze OMS™, our award-winning order management system (OMS), has been a market leader of investment technology since its launch in 1995.  It is used by over 450 investment managers to streamline their investment process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eze is a member of ConvergEx Group, a leading client-focused technology company providing products and services to asset managers and financial intermediaries globally.  ConvergEx has offices in 22 cities throughout the U.S., Europe, Asia, Australia, and Africa.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-convergex-group-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-convergex-group-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Developer at Buildium, LLC in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve got a lot to offer. Smart, awesome people in a highly collaborative environment. Cutting-edge technologies. Great downtown location. It doesn’t hurt that we’re a BBJ Best Place to Work, or that we’re on the Inc. 5000 list of fastest growing companies. We’re growing and we need the right people for the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Buildium UX Developer, you’ll have a voice on a team tasked with improving performance in a critical area of development. Utilizing the latest web development standards, technologies, and solid hands-on technical skills, you’ll create web applications that function properly across a variety of browsers and platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with designers to translate visual concepts into robust online user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create web-optimized assets and standards-compliant code from visual comps and requirements documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refine our CSS framework while maintaining the integrity of the web application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide accurate timing estimates for work based on verbal and written specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and document code that is reusable and well-thought-out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a high awareness of industry issues and trends, particularly with regard to accessibility, usability, and emerging front-end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aid in the growth of Buildium&amp;rsquo;s skills in User Experience development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in writing standards and cross-browser compliant code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to test and debug code in the development and browser environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in writing valid HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with jQuery, Modernizr, Knockout, LESS and other cutting edge JavaScript and CSS frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Web Accessibility standards like 508 Compliance or WAI Aria is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a distributed, unstructured, small company environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-sufficient and comfortable with ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and dental insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) retirement plan with company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Group life, short-term, and long-term disability insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible spending and dependent care accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take What You Need time off policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to work in a small, innovative start-up environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ping pong and foosball tables for superior hand-eye coordination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Buildium LLC&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buildium LLC is a small, entrepreneurial cloud-based software company located in Boston&amp;rsquo;s historic Fort Point Channel area. Founded in 2004, Buildium’s property management software is used by thousands of landlords, property managers, and associations to manage nearly half a million units in 31 countries around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, visit us online at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.buildium.com&quot;&gt;http://www.buildium.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-developer-buildium-llc-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-developer-buildium-llc-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Experience Designer at Medullan in Cambridge, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Medullan delivers Health Innovation Consulting for both Fortune 500 Clients and Employee Founded Start-Ups.  Medullan’s focus is on Innovation Strategy, Rapid Prototyping &amp;amp; Beta Testing of Digital Solutions including Mobile Apps, and Spin-Offs (start-ups founded by our employees).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medullan is seeking UX Designers who can think like a business person, understand the needs of a market and a target audiences, and then translate those needs into beautiful software designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Role and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participation in discovery workshops, design research, early-stage ideation, iterative interaction design and information architecture design, visual design, leading design presentations, and everything in between
Hand-off of designs, guidelines, and insight to implementation teams&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience of User Experience Design (Information Architecture, Interaction Design, Wireframes, Graphics, and Icons)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness of the latest and the most exciting design trends:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing for smart phones &amp;amp; other touch enabled devices,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing responsive web pages, and Data visualization techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;“I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about building great software, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to get a chance to use my skills to build products that can really help people and change the face of modern Healthcare.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andre B. Black&lt;br/&gt;
Chief Creative Officer&lt;br/&gt;
Medullan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A successful track record with clients, with at least 1 referenceable example
Exceptional communication, relationship, and presentation skills. Mastery of concise writing and active listening&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative thinking and problem solving skills. You dream big, but you have a &amp;ldquo;get it done&amp;rdquo; mentality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to meet deadlines, manage project scope, and handle conflicting priorities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the health care industry and marketing concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience Consulting and facilitating client workshops/meetings and possess illustration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experimented with coding (iOS apps, rich websites) and designing for multiple types of devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Agile Development methodologies or geographically distributed teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-medullan-cambridge-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-medullan-cambridge-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Graphic Designer at OneBeacon Insurance in Canton, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We currently have an opportunity for an Web/Graphic Designer to join our Marketing &amp;amp; Communications team located in Canton, MA. The Designer helps drive our creative visual communication efforts across multiple channels (primarily digital, but some print, merchandise, etc.). Digital design initiatives include the front-end design of our websites, microsites, e-marketing campaigns and mobile sites. The ideal candidate must have excellent visual design skills and a solid understanding of user interface design, concept development, branding and typography. Experience in print design is a plus. This position is a key member of OneBeacon’s Marketing &amp;amp; Communications team, which supports a broad variety of specialty insurance businesses and service groups across the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to marketing initiatives in support of key business objectives with the balance of the Marketing &amp;amp; Communications team through consulting and design related to visual communications matters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with the team to develop and execute online creative strategies in support of integrated communications plans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to OneBeacon’s brand and its individual business units’ visual identities and design language through the execution of high caliber design that balances established brand work and new innovative concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports the creation of original designs from kick-off to post-launch updates&amp;mdash;through creation and presentation of site maps, wireframes and design mockups&amp;mdash;for online campaigns to promote OneBeacon’s businesses and services and to support specific events such as product launches, conferences, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handles production efforts associated with printed collateral including providing job specifications, monitoring job traffic and attending on-site press checks when necessary to ensure quality control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs communication tools to empower the various businesses to handle communications matters directly including e-newsletter templates, report and document styles, PowerPoint presentation templates and logo files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handles requests for web-ready images, including optimizing and repurposing existing images and creating new images based on client needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with OneBeacon’s IT staff to ensure the seamless transition of design concepts to in-house web developers for implementation, including the delivery of approved style sheets and themes, and supporting user acceptance testing and quality assurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Through the application of design and usability principles, contributes to online experiences that are compelling, visually engaging and user-focused to successfully drive targeted actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remains aware of emerging digital design trends, technologies and resources to ensure current practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven self-starter with demonstrated creative instincts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solid conceptual thinker; creative problem solver, innovative. * Solid understanding of design considerations for screen, typography, color, composition and hierarchy and how these elements interact to create compelling design solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand process for creating wireframes and mock-ups to visually present design concepts and information architecture to clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, PhotoShop, Illustrator), and Microsoft Office (Outlook, Word, PowerPoint, Excel). Basic HTML, XHTML and CSS coding skills. Understanding of user experience (UX), information architecture (IA), design patterns, accessibility, web standards and browser compatibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with content management publishing platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent customer service skills; ability to communicate in both the business and technical environments and collaborate with other designers and third party vendors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate with developers about web technologies like JavaScript, JQuery, XML-based Web applications and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in both the Windows and Mac environments. Experience with wireframing tools (i.e. Visio etc), video, or animation a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B.A. or B.F.A. with a design focus. The ideal candidate will have 2-4 years of Web design experience in a corporate or agency setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OneBeacon Insurance Group, Ltd. is a Bermuda-domiciled holding company that is publicly traded on the New York Stock Exchange under the symbol &amp;lsquo;OB.&amp;rsquo; OneBeacon’s underwriting companies offer a range of specialty insurance products sold through independent agencies, regional and national brokers, wholesalers and managing general agencies. Each business is managed by an experienced team of specialty insurance professionals focused on a specific customer group or industry segment. OneBeacon’s solutions target professional liability; ocean and inland marine; entertainment, sports and leisure; excess property; environmental; group accident; programs; public entities; commercial surety; technology; and tuition refund. For further information about our products and services visit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.onebeacon.com&quot;&gt;http://www.onebeacon.com&lt;/a&gt; and to remain up to date on OneBeacon’s news, follow us on Twitter @OneBeaconIns or visit our online newsroom: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.onebeacon.com/newsroom&quot;&gt;http://www.onebeacon.com/newsroom&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-onebeacon-insurance-canton-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-onebeacon-insurance-canton-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Brafton in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Roles and responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What is Brafton Graphics Like?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are passionate about information design and struggle to understand when numbers and stats are misrepresented. We research to discover narratives that become visually communicative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a team our days revolve around deadlines, clients, team brainstorm sessions, critiques, a demanding schedule that values quality as much as turnaround and a workload that&amp;rsquo;s only for the strong. Oh and we also love puns and discovering narratives in random statistics. Still reading? Then we want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Located in the heart of Boston&amp;rsquo;s Financial District, Brafton&amp;rsquo;s Graphics team has grown immensely since late 2011 when it was an army of two. Since then the team has grown to nine in total and with the influx of more work looks to add to that number. This is why the team has been one of the fastest growing and most innovating within the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;THE JOB&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Brafton Graphic Designer you will be responsible for working with our clients to create custom infographics. Graphics range from data-driven or brand-focused. Our designers are required to be proficient in research, aware of trends in social media and open to various topics that can range from fashion to finance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;YOUR ROLE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graphic Designer collaborates with the Design Manager, clients and various internal departments. Ideal candidates will be able to spearhead high design standards, provide excellent customer service and work on a tight deadline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;CORE RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graphic Designer is tasked with project production and delivery, including (but not limited to) the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doing internet-based primary research for infographics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-time delivery of graphics to clients. Missed deadlines will NOT be tolerated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corresponding with clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occasionally formatting whitepapers, case studies, brochures and one-pagers for clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Competencies/Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earned a Degree in Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Indesign, Illustrator and Photoshop (We run on CS6)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with interactive design methods: HTML5, Java, After Effects, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Salesforce is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with project management system Basecamp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter with strong attention to detail, including proofreading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with Gmail/Google Docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working with PCs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1-2years&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-brafton-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-brafton-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead Visual Designer at Staples in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a member of the Agency at Staples, the Lead Visual Designer will work within the Experience Design team serving as lead designer on various web-based &amp;amp; interactive initiatives. As a member of this highly creative and highly innovative team responsibilities include, spearheading over-arching visual and user-interface creation, along with collaborative problem solving. The Lead Designer will partner closely with Design Managers, other Designers, Copywriters, Usability experts, Developers and internal Business Partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lead Visual Designer will work collaboratively with the extended Experience Design and Creative Development teams to ensure alignment of brand and user-experience standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Designer must be familiar with the aspects and steps of the creative/UI design process in building interactive design solutions for online properties. This includes experience in executing concept sketches, visual &amp;amp; information design and wireframes, while supporting the strategic vision, Easy Brand Promise, and over-arching business objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demonstrating the ability to execute design solutions that keep our customers top of mind will be a priority, the Lead Visual Designer will need to work closely with fellow Designers assisting others with projects as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Establish credibility with business partners and team members throughout the organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maintain an understanding of business partners’ e-commerce, m-commerce and mobile marketing objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay abreast of competitive &amp;amp; emerging landscape. Ability to take a project from requirements into concept through final execution is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree required; Interaction Design or related disciplines strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of visual/UI design experience for the web. Experience in mobile and interaction design a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of current UI visual standards for the Web, with knowledge of mobile standards for Windows, iOS, and Android a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in wireframe creation, user-experience architecture, visual &amp;amp; interaction design best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concepting and illustration skills strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create solutions from initial concept through final execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite a must. Experience with Balsamiq, and Versions, or similar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of front-end development tools – HTML, CSS, Javascript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong time-management &amp;amp; communication skills, with a proven ability to take on multiple projects simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all, must have great sense of humor as well as a sense of urgency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Employment Statement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staples is an Equal Opportunity Employer who values the diversity of our people, products, and services.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-visual-designer-staples-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-visual-designer-staples-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>