<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ma-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Graphic Designer at OneBeacon Insurance in Canton, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We currently have an opportunity for an Web/Graphic Designer to join our Marketing &amp;amp; Communications team located in Canton, MA. The Designer helps drive our creative visual communication efforts across multiple channels (primarily digital, but some print, merchandise, etc.). Digital design initiatives include the front-end design of our websites, microsites, e-marketing campaigns and mobile sites. The ideal candidate must have excellent visual design skills and a solid understanding of user interface design, concept development, branding and typography. Experience in print design is a plus. This position is a key member of OneBeacon’s Marketing &amp;amp; Communications team, which supports a broad variety of specialty insurance businesses and service groups across the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to marketing initiatives in support of key business objectives with the balance of the Marketing &amp;amp; Communications team through consulting and design related to visual communications matters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with the team to develop and execute online creative strategies in support of integrated communications plans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to OneBeacon’s brand and its individual business units’ visual identities and design language through the execution of high caliber design that balances established brand work and new innovative concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports the creation of original designs from kick-off to post-launch updates&amp;mdash;through creation and presentation of site maps, wireframes and design mockups&amp;mdash;for online campaigns to promote OneBeacon’s businesses and services and to support specific events such as product launches, conferences, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handles production efforts associated with printed collateral including providing job specifications, monitoring job traffic and attending on-site press checks when necessary to ensure quality control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs communication tools to empower the various businesses to handle communications matters directly including e-newsletter templates, report and document styles, PowerPoint presentation templates and logo files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handles requests for web-ready images, including optimizing and repurposing existing images and creating new images based on client needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with OneBeacon’s IT staff to ensure the seamless transition of design concepts to in-house web developers for implementation, including the delivery of approved style sheets and themes, and supporting user acceptance testing and quality assurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Through the application of design and usability principles, contributes to online experiences that are compelling, visually engaging and user-focused to successfully drive targeted actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remains aware of emerging digital design trends, technologies and resources to ensure current practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven self-starter with demonstrated creative instincts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solid conceptual thinker; creative problem solver, innovative. * Solid understanding of design considerations for screen, typography, color, composition and hierarchy and how these elements interact to create compelling design solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand process for creating wireframes and mock-ups to visually present design concepts and information architecture to clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, PhotoShop, Illustrator), and Microsoft Office (Outlook, Word, PowerPoint, Excel). Basic HTML, XHTML and CSS coding skills. Understanding of user experience (UX), information architecture (IA), design patterns, accessibility, web standards and browser compatibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with content management publishing platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent customer service skills; ability to communicate in both the business and technical environments and collaborate with other designers and third party vendors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate with developers about web technologies like JavaScript, JQuery, XML-based Web applications and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in both the Windows and Mac environments. Experience with wireframing tools (i.e. Visio etc), video, or animation a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B.A. or B.F.A. with a design focus. The ideal candidate will have 2-4 years of Web design experience in a corporate or agency setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OneBeacon Insurance Group, Ltd. is a Bermuda-domiciled holding company that is publicly traded on the New York Stock Exchange under the symbol &amp;lsquo;OB.&amp;rsquo; OneBeacon’s underwriting companies offer a range of specialty insurance products sold through independent agencies, regional and national brokers, wholesalers and managing general agencies. Each business is managed by an experienced team of specialty insurance professionals focused on a specific customer group or industry segment. OneBeacon’s solutions target professional liability; ocean and inland marine; entertainment, sports and leisure; excess property; environmental; group accident; programs; public entities; commercial surety; technology; and tuition refund. For further information about our products and services visit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.onebeacon.com&quot;&gt;http://www.onebeacon.com&lt;/a&gt; and to remain up to date on OneBeacon’s news, follow us on Twitter @OneBeaconIns or visit our online newsroom: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.onebeacon.com/newsroom&quot;&gt;http://www.onebeacon.com/newsroom&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-onebeacon-insurance-canton-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-onebeacon-insurance-canton-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Brafton in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Roles and responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What is Brafton Graphics Like?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are passionate about information design and struggle to understand when numbers and stats are misrepresented. We research to discover narratives that become visually communicative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a team our days revolve around deadlines, clients, team brainstorm sessions, critiques, a demanding schedule that values quality as much as turnaround and a workload that&amp;rsquo;s only for the strong. Oh and we also love puns and discovering narratives in random statistics. Still reading? Then we want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Located in the heart of Boston&amp;rsquo;s Financial District, Brafton&amp;rsquo;s Graphics team has grown immensely since late 2011 when it was an army of two. Since then the team has grown to nine in total and with the influx of more work looks to add to that number. This is why the team has been one of the fastest growing and most innovating within the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;THE JOB&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Brafton Graphic Designer you will be responsible for working with our clients to create custom infographics. Graphics range from data-driven or brand-focused. Our designers are required to be proficient in research, aware of trends in social media and open to various topics that can range from fashion to finance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;YOUR ROLE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graphic Designer collaborates with the Design Manager, clients and various internal departments. Ideal candidates will be able to spearhead high design standards, provide excellent customer service and work on a tight deadline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;CORE RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graphic Designer is tasked with project production and delivery, including (but not limited to) the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doing internet-based primary research for infographics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-time delivery of graphics to clients. Missed deadlines will NOT be tolerated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corresponding with clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occasionally formatting whitepapers, case studies, brochures and one-pagers for clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Competencies/Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earned a Degree in Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Indesign, Illustrator and Photoshop (We run on CS6)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with interactive design methods: HTML5, Java, After Effects, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Salesforce is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with project management system Basecamp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter with strong attention to detail, including proofreading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with Gmail/Google Docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working with PCs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1-2years&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-brafton-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-brafton-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead Visual Designer at Staples in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a member of the Agency at Staples, the Lead Visual Designer will work within the Experience Design team serving as lead designer on various web-based &amp;amp; interactive initiatives. As a member of this highly creative and highly innovative team responsibilities include, spearheading over-arching visual and user-interface creation, along with collaborative problem solving. The Lead Designer will partner closely with Design Managers, other Designers, Copywriters, Usability experts, Developers and internal Business Partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lead Visual Designer will work collaboratively with the extended Experience Design and Creative Development teams to ensure alignment of brand and user-experience standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Designer must be familiar with the aspects and steps of the creative/UI design process in building interactive design solutions for online properties. This includes experience in executing concept sketches, visual &amp;amp; information design and wireframes, while supporting the strategic vision, Easy Brand Promise, and over-arching business objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demonstrating the ability to execute design solutions that keep our customers top of mind will be a priority, the Lead Visual Designer will need to work closely with fellow Designers assisting others with projects as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Establish credibility with business partners and team members throughout the organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maintain an understanding of business partners’ e-commerce, m-commerce and mobile marketing objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay abreast of competitive &amp;amp; emerging landscape. Ability to take a project from requirements into concept through final execution is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree required; Interaction Design or related disciplines strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of visual/UI design experience for the web. Experience in mobile and interaction design a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of current UI visual standards for the Web, with knowledge of mobile standards for Windows, iOS, and Android a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in wireframe creation, user-experience architecture, visual &amp;amp; interaction design best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concepting and illustration skills strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create solutions from initial concept through final execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite a must. Experience with Balsamiq, and Versions, or similar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of front-end development tools – HTML, CSS, Javascript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong time-management &amp;amp; communication skills, with a proven ability to take on multiple projects simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all, must have great sense of humor as well as a sense of urgency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Employment Statement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staples is an Equal Opportunity Employer who values the diversity of our people, products, and services.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-visual-designer-staples-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-visual-designer-staples-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UIDesigner at Litmus in Cambridge, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re bootstrapped, profitable and proud. You&amp;rsquo;ll be working with our team of
developers building cool stuff, with amazing people. Here&amp;rsquo;s what some of our 11
person crew have to say about Litmus:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Everyone. Gives. A. Shit. (about the tech, the products, the customers, each other). Trust and ownership are important here. We build products that scratch our own itch. We experiment, we celebrate (big things (like throwing a launch party), and small (beers at the end of the week)). Oh, and there&amp;rsquo;s no red tape, bullshit posturing, timecards or org charts!&amp;rdquo;
&lt;strong&gt;Eddie, Ruby Developer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Aside from software architecture and syntax, there hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a task that I have begun that I have known how to do. It is a constant learning experience and we often times find ourselves building things that have never been built before.&amp;rdquo;
&lt;strong&gt;Justin, C# Developer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re in charge of our own future and aren&amp;rsquo;t beholden by a board, investors or anyone else. I feel like the people I work for care more for our customers and their employees than most other companies do.&amp;rdquo;
&lt;strong&gt;Justine, Marketing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Super cool office! &amp;ndash; Our office is amazing and we do a lot of cool things here. Kinect + beer fridays + fun :) It&amp;rsquo;s also easy to get to and a great location.&amp;rdquo;
&lt;strong&gt;Danielle, Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The &quot;founders&amp;rdquo; are in the thick of it. Also, the collective responsibility, I feel like I could rely on any team member for help.&amp;ldquo;
&lt;strong&gt;James, Account Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About The Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer everything you&amp;rsquo;d expect from a cutting edge, financially successful start
up. Great salary, full health care benefits, 28 days paid vacation (yes, on top of
public holidays!), beautiful office space complete with a Kinect, beer fridge and
Sonos sound system. We also buy you lunch, every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be working with the very best money can buy: SSD drives, dual Apple
Displays, Aeron chairs, huge desks, 10&quot; tablets and whatever else you need to be
awesome at what you do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I mention our office? Seconds from the Central Square T in Cambridge, we have the 11th floor to ourselves. Stunning views, beautiful furniture and top of the line equipment. You have to see it; it&amp;rsquo;s stunning. Design is a key selling point of our products. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone to take over responsibility for all aspects of design and user experience at Litmus. We&amp;rsquo;ll give you all the resources and support you need to craft beautiful, elegant experiences that delight our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be responsible for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing the user interfaces for all our web-based products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with our development team to oversee the implementation of your designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Co-ordinating user testing of our product and your own prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jumping in to help with user experience decisions whenever they arise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The ideal candidate has:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio showcasing excellent skills in design and UX principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of layout, typography, color and other design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in front-end technologies (HTML, CSS, Javascript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Watch our &lt;a href=&quot;http://litmus.com/meet-the-team&quot;&gt;&amp;lsquo;Meet the team&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt; video.&lt;br/&gt;
Read more about &lt;a href=&quot;http://litmus.com&quot;&gt;Litmus and our products&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/uidesigner-litmus-cambridge-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/uidesigner-litmus-cambridge-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at Staples in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a member of the Agency at Staples, the User Experience Designer will work directly with other designers, copywriters and developers to create effective creative designs for e-commerce and related Staples’ web properties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The User Experience Designer will work collaboratively with the extended user-experience and visual design teams maintaining alignment of brand and UX standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities will include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initial brainstorming and concepting through optimized graphic production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This member of the design team will apply their visual/UX design knowledge while integrating usability research &amp;amp; web analytics data into final solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrating experience in executing concept sketches, information design hierarchy and wireframes that support the strategic vision will be essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The User Experience Designer will work interdependently with other team members on key initiatives to ensure creative execution maintains a strong, consistent user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solutions should demonstrate a thoughtful approach to strategy and our Easy Brand Promise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish credibility with team members throughout the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a strong understanding of our core business objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate a passion for staying abreast of competitive &amp;amp; emerging landscape&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills and the ability to present are a must&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor’s degree required; Interaction Design or related disciplines strongly preferred 3+ years of web-based visual and/or user interface design&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Preferred&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of current UI standards for the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive experience in wireframe creation, site navigation &amp;amp; interaction design best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create solutions from initial concept through final execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth experience in Adobe Creative Suite. Experience with Balsamiq, and Versions, or similar would be a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of front-end development process, with familiarity of HTML, CSS, Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess excellent time-management &amp;amp; communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all, must have great sense of humor as well as a sense of urgency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-staples-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-staples-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Designer at Yankee Candle in Deerfield, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Working with the Creative Development team, the Associate Designer is the last person to touch our electronic design files before they’re released for production. The successful candidate is responsible for utilizing the most efficient mechanical and technical solutions for YCC marketing materials, and for making critical technical decisions which impact design content including color, layout, and text. You will ensure that all artwork and files are accurate, adhere to brand standards, meet/exceed time line and deliverable requirements, while following all specifications. In specific:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare electronic design files for prepress and production activities, including layout of text and images.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interpret designer’s vision into print-ready deliverables including variable sizes and shapes, spot/process colors, etc. Ensure the quality and accuracy of files that are created or sent to print publications or vendors to satisfy project requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare PDF versions of creative files; manage internal proofing, and final art release within deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a high level of detail while working with deadline time pressures, and changing priorities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within company branding guidelines. Make technical art file production decisions based on print processes and/or technologies. Consider factors such as cost parameters, substrates, manufacturer/printer limitations, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to attend all walk-throughs and assist with the set-up of all components at store. This includes: hanging signs, adhering window clings and other material as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist designers as needed with mockups, samples, and file preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create production-ready mechanical files; retouch, re-size, crop, imagery as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review/approve vendor proofs for content and color. Assist in developing methods to create and maintain consistent file preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in continuous improvement practices to keep each work process efficient and effective. Assist in organizing, monitoring, archiving, and maintaining files on the server.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A two/four year degree/certificate in Graphic Design or equivalent work experience preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and understanding of graphic preparation, file management and production processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail, and excellent organizational/prioritization skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe InDesign and CS5, as well as Adobe Acrobat in a Mac OS environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven interpersonal skills, and written/verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work independently or as a member of a team in a fast paced, time-sensitive environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Salary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an hourly position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flexibility in work schedule is also required; this may include possible extended hours with minimal notice to meet project expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Notice:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is subject to a criminal background check and potentially and an education verification as part of the application process. At the time of interview, internal and external applicants will be required to sign a release authorizing the company to conduct criminal background check and/or education verification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Yankee CandleCompany, Inc. is an equal opportunity employer and does not unlawfully discriminate against any applicant on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability, sexual orientation, or any other class protected by federal or state law. EOE/M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Company Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Yankee Candle Company, Inc. is the leading designer, manufacturer, wholesaler and retailer of premium scented candles, based on sales, in the giftware industry. Employing approximately 6,000 people world-wide (as of December 31, 2011), Yankee Candle (Headquartered in South Deerfield, Massachusetts) has a 42-year history of offering distinctive products and marketing them as affordable luxuries and consumable gifts, with sales from continuing operations of $785.8 million dollars in fiscal year 2011.Having earned a reputation for superior, long-lasting fragrance quality, Yankee Candle is America’s trusted choice for fragrance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company sells its products through a North American wholesale customer network of approximately 28,800 store locations, a growing base of Company owned and operated retail stores (552 Yankee Candle Stores located in 46 states and 1 province in Canada as of December 31, 2011), direct mail catalogs, and its Internet website (www.yankeecandle.com).  Outside of North America, the Company sells its products primarily through its subsidiary, Yankee Candle Company (Europe), Ltd., which has an international wholesale customer network of approximately 5,700 store locations and distributors covering a combined 49 countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A key contributor to our success has been our vertically integrated business model, which enables us to control most every aspect of our business, from product development to manufacturing to distribution to marketing and sales. This structure allows us to consistently provide high quality and innovative products, deliver them in a timely and efficient manner to customers all over the world and provide excellent customer service. The power of the Yankee Candle® brand and our dedicated and talented employee base truly set us apart from our competitors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our one-of-a-kind Flagship Store in South Deerfield, MA is the world’s largest candle and Christmas store, containing approximately 90,000 square feet of retail and entertainment space, and has been ranked as one of the most popular tourist attractions in Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-designer-yankee-candle-deerfield-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-designer-yankee-candle-deerfield-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UI Designer at CA Technologies in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies (Nasdaq: CA) is an IT management software and solutions company with expertise across all IT environments&amp;mdash;from mainframe and physical, to virtual and cloud. CA manages and secures IT environments and enables customers to deliver more flexible IT services. CA Technologies innovative products and services provide the insight and control essential for IT organizations to power business agility. The majority of the Global Fortune 500 relies on CA Technologies to manage their evolving IT ecosystems. Founded in 1976, CA Technologies serves customers in virtually every country in the world and reported revenue of $4.8 billion in fiscal year 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a qualified Senior UI/Usability Engineer to join our development team at our Framingham, MA office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate would have a strong background in UI design in addition to the below requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3, Javascript, HTML, JSP/Servlets, Portal Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the design and development of web-based and mobile user interfaces for enterprise applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development processes including: SCRUM and Agile methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years of experience in the industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work with local and remote development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent worker who takes initiative with minimal direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First rate communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of automation, unit, and integration testing best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the UI development effort for the CloudMinder, IdentityMinder and GovernanceMinder(IMAG) security product lines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, code, implement, unit and integration test features and code fixes applying best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with QA organization to develop functional test plans, automation tests, and coordinate verification and quality assurance for product releases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the CloudMinder engineering team’s software development process and practices for ensuring high quality deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize source code change management tools, defect tracking, and Agile project management planning and tracking tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review technical documentation updates for product releases. Provide details to support documentation changes to the core publications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with peers in a virtual high-performance team distributed across multiple CA locations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Openly accepting tasks which require research into new areas of knowledge and skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To be here for the long term we focus on things that last, and we are moved in many different ways. What moves you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you build the career you want? You CAn. We&amp;rsquo;re a dynamic company with a strong vision in a growing global market. At a time when customers are demanding more and more from their technology, we&amp;rsquo;re changing the way the world manages IT, to help customers better perform, compete and grow. That&amp;rsquo;s why the majority of leading companies across industries worldwide use our software. It&amp;rsquo;s also why you&amp;rsquo;ll find a wealth of opportunities for important and rewarding work. Come to CA Technologies and build the career you CAn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer competitive salary, company-sponsored premium Medical/Prescription &amp;amp; Dental Plans, company-paid Holidays, Vacation, Personal, Anniversary Service and Sick Days, 401(k) Plan, Education/Training Reimbursement, Charitable Gift Program, Adoption Assistance Program, and Veterinary Care Insurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about CA Technologies and this opportunity, we welcome you to visit our web site at www.ca.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies and all of its subsidiaries are equal opportunity employers. As such, it is our corporate policy to fill positions with qualified candidates regardless of the candidate’s race, color, sex, age, religion, ancestry, national origin, citizenship status, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, genetic information, disability, pregnancy, military status, veteran status or any other protected group status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note to Recruiters and Placement Agencies: CA Technologies does not accept unsolicited agency resumes. Please do not forward unsolicited agency resumes to our website or to any CA Technologies employee. CA Technologies will not pay fees to any third party agency or firm and will not be responsible for any agency fees associated with unsolicited resumes. Unsolicited resumes received will be considered property of CA Technologies and will be processed accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-designer-ca-technologies-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ui-designer-ca-technologies-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Multimedia Designer at Visible Measures Corporation in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Position Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The multimedia designer is responsible for producing designs, multimedia, web pages, and video that help generate visibility and communicate company messaging in a more effective manner. The multimedia designer ensures visual consistency of the brand across all channels, including collateral, decks, videos, advertisements, SWAG, and more. The multimedia designer is responsible for creating visual content that will drive visitors to our site and generate brand visibility, including infographics, interactive features, web pages, widgets, sizzle reels, and other visual content. The multimedia designer needs to be a creator in that they must always be thinking about how they can use design to increase interest for Visible Measures. In addition to creating &amp;ldquo;visual content,&amp;rdquo; the multimedia designer needs to be able to convey complex ideas visually across a number of formats. The multimedia designer must tell our story visually in order to help our audiences better understand the value we deliver. The multimedia designer will also help sales with designs for ad campaigns, parties, and other events. The multimedia designer is responsible for designing and maintaining the company newsletter works closely with the editor of content to publish content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic designer with 3-5 years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA degree in graphic design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly proficient with current versions of Adobe CreativeSuite and familiar with a wide range of other design, web, and multimedia software and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to create infographics and producing designs out of data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of front-end web development &amp;ndash; HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly skilled in both Mac and PC programs such as iWork, PPT and Word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of browser compatibility, UI performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of HTML5, Javascript, and PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must excel at video editing and production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High attention to detail, deadline and results-oriented, and works well in a fast-paced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to visualize complex concepts environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiastic, results-driven self-starter and team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing and producing SWAG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Apply for this Position!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please reference job # MD when applying for this job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send resumes to: careers@visiblemeasures.com, to the attention of Gregg Armitage&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/multimedia-designer-visible-measures-corporation-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/multimedia-designer-visible-measures-corporation-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Experience Designer/Interactive Designer at Unitrends in Burlington, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Senior User Experience Designer/Interactive Designer is a critical member of the Marketing team and is the steward for the brand across multiple vehicles and customer experience across all online properties.  The Senior User Experience Designer is responsible for Unitrends primary and associated web sites and platforms, including partner and customer portals, eCommerce platform, CRM/SFA applications and marketing operations platform.  We’re looking for a candidate with outstanding conceptual design skills and a strong understanding of information architecture and user-centered design principles to serve as the in-house resource for all graphic design and brand standards across multiple touch points and vehicles. This candidate is expected to be strongly versed in web best practices, along with a balance of both creative talent and technical depth, arrying both best in class user experience with practical go to market strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Manage Entire Web Environment &amp;amp; Ecosystem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and expand best in class user experience focused web site for North American and international markets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration of the company systems to the web site delivering lead conversions, net new users and eCommerce activity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the continual development of features on the web site(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor web site server and site technical performance – manage site hosting (live and sandbox environments), marketing operations application (Eloqua), and trouble shoot site (content, links, flows, and transaction logs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review statistics and monitor analytics – provide analysis of the web site’s business health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, develop and manage content that’s consistent with the overall brand and drives higher web site ‘stickiness’ and engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate familiarity with content management systems (Kentico)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a consistent look and feel throughout all web properties; create and improve a visual language across the company’s web properties and marketing materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep current with emerging web technologies through relevant blogs, listservs, and events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assure web-based information is archived for future needs and reference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and manage website system and infrastructure, including CMS allowing broader staff to help drive and maintain dynamic content updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create secure data transfer between web and internal systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Be the In-House Design Expert&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves as the expert in graphic design standards, desktop publishing, print production methods, user-centered design, web interface standards, web browser technologies, web accessibility issues, and open and evolving web document and web development standards such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create library ad brand standards for Unitrends across all go to market vehicles – from web properties, to demand gen activities (PPC ads, landing pages, collateral assets, hardware appliances, letterhead, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with staff on projects identifying time constraints, key requirements and assets needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience (5+ years) in interactive visual design with expertise related to B2B high-tech.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in all phases of user experience design: discovery (competitive research, analytics, &amp;amp; interviews, etc), wireframe design, prototyping, user testing, interactive design &amp;amp; creative direction, QA &amp;amp; deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop and present effective site strategies, site maps, wireframes, and user flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work with our internal team to continually refine and evolve our User Experience process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong web graphics production capability and practitioner experience with Photoshop, Fireworks or similar tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design best practices, email marketing, social media, SEM/SEO skills required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with current web development technologies and standards, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX and XML knowledge required.  WordPress or other blog app experience required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing for mobile and responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail, and a commitment to delivering highly-polished designs under tight time constraints.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills – both written and oral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Google Analytics, Adwords, Salesforce.com and Marketing automation system (Eloqua, Marketo, similar application)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-unitrends-burlington-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-unitrends-burlington-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>