<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ma-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Art Director at VistaPrint in Lexington, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are the perfect blend of left and right brained talents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Environment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be a key member of the creative team and web site design discipline focusing on taking Vistaprint.com, the heart and soul of the brand, to the next generation of user experience, information design, and marketing. As part of the large award-winning in-house North American Marketing and Creative Services agency, you will lead customer conversion and marketing efforts that are redefining our storefront and brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Opportunity:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Art Director you will have an opportunity to showcase your design skills to inspire, drive and advance the Vistaprint web teams capabilities and to deliver high impact experience design across the website and external marketing channels.​&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead multi-disciplinary projects that include ecommerce centric web design and display advertising for campaigns and our storefront&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a thought leader; conceptualize and design with forward thinking, sophisticated style, with a focus on craftsmanship, and customer centricity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide art direction, guidance and manage ongoing projects as well as the day-to-day deliverables of the design team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be an advocate for, and lead in introducing, new design trends, technology and solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead formal and informal critiques to provide effective, relevant feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with Global UX and Creative Leads on large web design strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become a trusted partner with internal clients and business owners by developing strong interpersonal relationships to aid in project development strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A diverse portfolio demonstrating design excellence showcasing a variety of interactive projects, including but not limited to ecommerce/websites, rich media, mobile websites, and native phone/tablet apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong working knowledge of UX/UI design, brand expression, interactive and creative process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years’ creative leadership in an agency or equivalent internal experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years’ experience in ecommerce environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses the ability to execute strategically as well as tactically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organization and time-management skills with exceptional attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing for mobile, both native and in browser a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of After Effects a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation, relationship building and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite both on Mac &amp;amp; PC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient knowledge of web/email and video technologies; CSS, (X)HTML(5), JavaScript/JQuery, Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’ Degree in Graphic Design, Fine Arts, or a related subject&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-art-director-vistaprint-lexington-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-art-director-vistaprint-lexington-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director of Creative Services at Akamai Technologies in Cambridge, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About the Job&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Director of Creative Services seizes the opportunity to amplify and express the Akamai brand through visual communications. The ideal candidate thrives on solving complex communication challenges and translates them into elegantly designed deliverables that align to business objectives. They will lead and inspire a team of designers and manage outside resources to serve as the in-house creative agency for internal clients across the business. This person will be responsible for developing campaign, tradeshow and interactive experiences from concept to completion and will successfully attain the delicate balance between form and function in B2B marketing. They will bring with them best practices for in-house agency models that drive efficiencies and maximize resource deliveries. This position reports to the Vice President of Global Communications and will be managing a staff of five in-house resources and outside freelancers/agencies. A creative portfolio must be submitted along with resume for consideration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;About the Team&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Corporate Communications team brings the Akamai brand to life. The team is responsible for creating and evolving the brand story and ensure consistency across the globe. We do this through integrated communication campaigns that include media and analysts relations, internal and external corporate communications and events, social media and online programs, and thought leadership campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspire and motivate the team from concept to completion of forward-thinking creative initiatives including copywriting, content and collateral development, digital properties, media and advertising, and trade shows and events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide leadership and expertise to continuously drive innovation within creative services initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and apply brand identity systems including typography, photography, color, video and other ingredients to deliver innovative visual solutions that meet the needs of the business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as an enthusiastic brand champion that drives global adoption of the Akamai brand and creative assets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee partners, budgets and workflows to breed a sustainable and fun environment that promotes thinking outside-the-box and allows for diversity in experience among team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current with industry best practices and creative breakthroughs and help to inform and educate the broader team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with cross-functional teams to drive consistency and efficiency in creative expression of the brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor and analyze content adoption and usage, present findings to senior management, and recommend shifts required to optimize.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct regular review and brainstorming sessions to develop team skill set and ensure highest quality of creative deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education: Minimum Bachelor’s Degree in Advertising, Marketing, Journalism, Graphic Arts, Design, Communications or related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10 years of experience in creative management within an enterprise or creative agency, with at least 2 years of B2B experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of demonstrated proficiency in leading design tools such as Illustrator, Photoshop, and InDesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years of leadership experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Desired Qualifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative thinker who has a successful track record of developing market-moving creative ideas and accountability to the overall brand experience and representation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent design skills and an outstanding portfolio that demonstrates the ability to effectively marry strategy and objectives with the creative expression of the brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Succinct creative presentation skills with the ability to articulate and sell concepts to senior management by discussing how those concepts meet the brand’s strategic marketing objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superb written and verbal communications skills with the ability to lead, inspire and articulate your design while advocating best practice solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet deadlines, manage multiple tasks, and track details in a fast-paced environment effectively and efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in working on business projects effectively and patiently with users and colleagues at all levels in dispersed locations around the globe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is relocation available for this position: No&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is US Citizenship required: No&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is a Security Clearance Required: No&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If yes, applicants selected will be subject to a government security investigation &amp;amp; must meet eligibility requirements for access to classified information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Akamai:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one carries more of the world&amp;rsquo;s Web traffic than Akamai, so working with Akamai means you’re helping some of the world’s best known brands succeed in bringing any experience to any device, anywhere. Cloud computing, SaaS, eCommerce, online entertainment and dynamic personalized experiences are all fueled by Akamai technology. Join Akamai and you join a culture that’s extremely intelligent, strongly supportive and passionately committed to delivering world-class solutions. Some of the best minds in business, mathematics, and engineering work at Akamai – leading, learning and shaping the future of the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Contact us!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re excited by Akamai and would like to help change the online landscape please apply. No time to apply? Join our Talent Community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Akamai Technologies is an Affirmative Action, Equal Opportunity employer (M/F/D/V) that values the strength that diversity brings to the workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-creative-services-akamai-technologies-cambridge-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-creative-services-akamai-technologies-cambridge-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>