<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ma-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Web Designer / Developer at ADP in Cambridge, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At ADP we are driven by your success. We engage your unique talents and perspectives. We welcome your ideas on how to do things differently and better. In your efforts to achieve, learn and grow, we support you all the way. If success motivates you, you belong at ADP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspiring Innovation is a core value at ADP and in Dealer Services we offer integrated computing solutions to about 26,000 auto, truck, motorcycle, marine, recreational vehicle and heavy equipment dealers in nearly 90 countries worldwide. To succeed, we invest in technologies, programs and our people to continually improve the way we service and help our clients run their businesses. ADP is recognized as an innovation leader, and is on the Forbes list of the top 100 Most Innovative Companies in the World and is ranked in the Top 50 on IDG&amp;rsquo;s Computerworld list of the 100 Best Places to Work in Information Technology (IT).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technology at ADP. It&amp;rsquo;s the foundation of the products and services that have made us a world-wide leader in workforce solutions. With us, you can combine technical skills and business acumen, to effectively consult as well as solve technical challenges. You have the opportunity to train on leading-edge technologies that continually redefine what&amp;rsquo;s possible in our industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Candidate Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of webpages, email and display creatives using HTML5 / CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create engaging email creatives and code them to render beautifully on various platforms and browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ambition to have true ownership the design aspects of the department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Creative Web Designer is the &amp;ldquo;in-house&amp;rdquo; designer for this business unit within ADP, and focuses on consumer engagement through creative web page and email development and design of new web pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ADP business unit, &amp;ldquo;Autotegrity,&amp;rdquo; is a data analytics and quantitative marketing company that runs an automotive shopping service connecting consumers with auto dealers. We help consumers find the vehicle that is right for them, while also helping dealerships find highly qualified, locally targeted customers. Our rigorous approach to data, along with our proprietary analytics system and search marketing platform are helping us redefine the lead buying process in the automotive space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design of webpages, email and display creatives based on seasonality, demographics, consumer interest and promotions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 / CSS coding for new and existing email creatives that drive high user engagement for desktop and mobile devices, the various user clients and browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A/B/C testing, for all new designs including desktop, mobile, email, and website layout/user interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay up to date on latest email code, design and website optimization techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of rapid web and email creative development using HTML5 and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic experience in SQL and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create engaging email creatives and code them to render beautifully on various devices and browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in creating tables by hand in HTML5 / CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of web application development processes, for desktop, tablet, and mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of rapid web and email creative development using HTML5 and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic experience in SQL and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create engaging email creatives and code them to render beautifully on various devices and browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in creating tables by hand in HTML5 / CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of web application development processes, for desktop, tablet, and mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About ADP:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We power organizations with insightful solutions that drive business success. Consistently named one of the &amp;ldquo;Most Admired Companies&amp;rdquo; by FORTUNE® Magazine, and recognized by Forbes® as one of &amp;ldquo;The World&amp;rsquo;s Most Innovative Companies,&amp;rdquo; ADP has over a half-million clients around the globe and 60+ years of experience as a world-wide leader of business outsourcing solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ADP is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer; M/F/D/V. ADP believes that diversity leads to strength.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Benefits of a Career at ADP:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At ADP, our associates are the key to our success! At ADP you will enjoy a vibrant and diverse organization with exceptional leadership committed to providing every associate with career building opportunities. Our environment is fast paced and dynamic with work/life initiatives that allow for individual goals to be realized. ADP offers benefits that are second to none.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Some Benefits Include:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Matched 401K&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock Purchase Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal Days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition Reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corporate Discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Referral Bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Plus, you will have access to our extensive offering of on-line and instructor led training which is made available to all associates through our Global Learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The TOP reasons to ADVANCE your career ADP !!!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TOP NOTCH benefits package, 401K and Pension plan, along with numerous company perks for all associates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ComputerWorld Top 100 Best Places to Work in I/T&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;InformationWeek: Ranked 7th of top business technology innovators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fortune&amp;rsquo;s list of America&amp;rsquo;s Most Admired Companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DiversityInc Top 50 Companies for Diversity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forbes list of The World&amp;rsquo;s Most Innovative Companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diversity MBA Magazine: &amp;ldquo;50 Out Front for Diversity Leadership: Best Places for Diverse Managers to Work&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of only 4 AAA rated organizations by Standard &amp;amp; Poor&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corporate Equality Index: 100% rating and &amp;ldquo;Best Places to Work&amp;rdquo; by the Human Rights Campaign Foundation for LGBT employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ranked # 1 by Fortune Magazine in the payroll services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working Mother Magazine Best Places to Work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invested more than $12 million in tools and programs over the last three years to enhance our employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equality Company of the Year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training Magazine Rank #17 of the Top 125&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-web-designer-developer-adp-cambridge-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-web-designer-developer-adp-cambridge-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Houghton Mifflin Harcourt in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain site by maintaining content and features of the site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage web-site focused projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help define strategic direction of site by performing competitive analyses and doing research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help determine, acquire, and develop new content for site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wireframe new site pages/sections&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit/load content in CMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform monthly site analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General ad hoc reporting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set up ad campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage user feedback mailboxes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer customer queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write content for newsletters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in strategic discussions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social media interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational skills and the ability to juggle multiple deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of digital media formats used for text, images, video, audio and interactive media required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with HTML, CSS, and Javascript. Comfort working with PHP a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Sitecore, Flash, Flex and/or Web authoring tools a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of spreadsheets and basic data manipulation, including data-scraping and conversion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of user interface design principles, web design best practices and a graphic creation a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly learn and troubleshoot new and existing technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates should be flexible, self-motivated and enthusiastic team players.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-houghton-mifflin-harcourt-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-houghton-mifflin-harcourt-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer (UX) at Educate Online in Danvers, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;For more than a decade, Educate Online has built gateway skills for Career and College Readiness through personalized, live online instruction in reading, math and writing for K-20 students. Students connect and interact with an Educate Online faculty member through our online learning environment comprised of a vast network of U.S.-based, multilingual, state-certified teachers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Educate Online’s mastery-based approach produces significant academic gains: on average, students experience more than a 1.0 grade-level improvement in just 26 hours of one-on-one, live online instruction. Educate Online’s main offices are located in Danvers, MA and Baltimore, MD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Educate Online maintains an A Rating with the Better Business Bureau.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an experienced Front-End Developer with working knowledge of creating data rich, interactive, web experiences. The successful candidate will work within a team of like minded UX, Dev and QA folks to deliver our next generation education platform.  That person should be able to work within an Agile team, be able to collaborate to find optimal solutions to various design problems, and most of all be able to deliver on all things front-end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be working for a strong IT/Development team under our CTO who was named Boston&amp;rsquo;s CIO of the Year in 2012. Access to the best resources and talented team members to accomplish the task at hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take part in Agile process, scrums, planning, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to project discussions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver on Front-end sprint tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with UX to execute an excellent user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the Dev team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with QA on front-end bugs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTML5, CSS, CoffeeScript, and JS frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with UI/UX on data rich, interactive web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing and troubleshooting front end solutions across multiple browsers and devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A love for good interactive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eye for typography and all things visual&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy creative problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the education space a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Educate Online is proud to be an EEO/AA employer: M/F/D/V.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ux-educate-online-danvers-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ux-educate-online-danvers-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior/Mid Front-End Developer at Cloudant in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Cloudant is looking to add a Front-End Developer to our fast growing team. This individual would be responsible for collaborating with back-end developers on planning and implementing code that can drive our product and service offerings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a company, we need help showing off what our product and service can do as well as inspire where we’re going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Must have skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with open-source standards in HTML and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep experience with Javascript, including libraries (jQuery, Underscore), as well as MVC frameworks (Backbone.js)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of RESTful APIs and JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate and clear communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git, or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice-to-haves:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building event driven, server-side apps with Node.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NoSQL DB experience (CouchDB, MongoDB)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS and Android development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UX chops&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build interfaces for the front-end&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build browser-based software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data visualization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile dev&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible and adaptable to project and company changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with front-end and back-end developers by sharing new tools and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and share industry innovations and trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promote Cloudant via social networks, blogs, and speaking engagements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ yrs building production web apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Cloudant&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cloudant provides developers of large or fast-growing Web and mobile applications with the world’s first globally distributed “data layer as a service” for loading, storing, analyzing, and distributing application data. The Cloudant Data Layer is a managed service that helps developers to eliminate the delays, costs, and distractions inherent in working with databases and their administrators, while providing unmatched scalability, availability, and performance. This capability accelerates time-to-market and time-to-innovation, because it frees developers from the mechanics of data management so they can focus exclusively on creating great applications. Cloudant is privately held and backed by top-tier investors including Avalon Ventures and Y Combinator. For more information, visit https://cloudant.com/.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mid-front-end-developer-cloudant-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-mid-front-end-developer-cloudant-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Designer/Developer Responsive at Propel Marketing in Quincy, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Propel Marketing helps small and medium sized businesses better serve their customers by improving their internet presence and marketing efforts. This is accomplished through a constant effort to identify new challenges these businesses face and creating elegant and affordable solutions to conquer those challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our primary areas of expertise revolve around web and mobile applications, targeted interactive media advertising, SEM/SEO and Social Media management. We have an unwavering enthusiasm about the internet and the fundamental shift it is causing in how businesses relate to their patrons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a new company and our tremendous success has created ample opportunities for professional growth and career advancement. We believe culture is a key part of a businesses, and to achieve excellence, every person on the team should love what they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a talented Senior Web Designer/Developer to take ownership of the UI design and HTML/CSS development for Propel’s SaaS web applications. Reporting to the Director of Software Development, the Senior Web Designer will be responsible for taking requirements, user stories, and use cases, and designing a visual concept &amp;amp; workflow which will both satisfy the defined requirements and deliver a superb user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Web Designer will also leverage their extensive design experience to take prototype applications (ie. a working application with a Twitter Bootstrap interface) to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intricate knowledge and experience with responsive design and its implementation nuances will be essential in this role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create wireframes to illustrate high-level solutions to an application and feature requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design user interfaces with a modern and clean aesthetic which focus on delivering intuitive &amp;amp; enjoyable user experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate UI designs into well organized and structured HTML/CSS compatible with modern browsers, and use open source tools &amp;amp; frameworks to improve the structure and maintainability of the front-end code where possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with JavaScript &amp;amp; backend developers to execute implementation of your elegantly designed solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s in it for you?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a great, fun working environment and believe it is critical to create an atmosphere dedicated to personal growth and career mastery. We want people to love what they do and feel excited about their role and unique contributions within their teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to play an important role with a unique company in the internet marketing industry, be given ample opportunities to attend training seminars, networking events, and industry conferences &amp;ndash; all while earning a competitive salary and comprehensive benefits &amp;ndash; please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to apply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of our full-time development positions include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Convenient North Quincy location, close to T stops and major highways&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free parking (Of course the T shuttle drops off right out front too!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Vacation, Sick and Personal Days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health, Dental and Vision Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Casual dress all-day, everyday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-site Gym and Cafeteria&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Caffeine and snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Telecommute days (With Boston&amp;rsquo;s traffic, everyone should offer this!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Randomly cool events: Ping pong tournaments, dinner’s at Legal Seafood and Sam Adam’s Beer Tours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Technical Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ Years designing for the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent sense of design, layout and aesthetics for the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated proficiency with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, or equivilant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of HTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of responsive design implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented, with the ability to execute projects accurately and quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;The Ideal Candidate:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will possess a solid portfolio demonstrating success in taking designs from initial concept to well-executed front-end code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a strong understanding of the user experience, and why it is a critical aspect in successfully designing web application interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A motivated self-starter who enjoys working in a fast-paced team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhibits a passion for understanding new web technologies and innovations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a great attitude with an emphasis on excellence, integrity, creativity, and team spirit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Education:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelors degree in Graphic Design, Interactive Design, or related, and/or equivalent experience is required, and a masters degree is a plus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-designer-developer-responsive-propel-marketing-quincy-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-designer-developer-responsive-propel-marketing-quincy-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Developer at Buildium in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve got a lot to offer. Smart, awesome people in a highly collaborative environment. Cutting-edge technologies. Great downtown location. It doesn’t hurt that we’re a BBJ Best Place to Work, or that we’re on the Inc. 5000 list of fastest growing companies. We’re growing and we need the right people for the job &amp;ndash; local or remote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Buildium UX Developer, you’ll have a voice on a team tasked with improving performance in a critical area of development. Utilizing the latest web development standards, technologies, and solid hands-on technical skills, you’ll create web applications that function properly across a variety of browsers and platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with designers to translate visual concepts into robust online user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create web-optimized assets and standards-compliant code from visual comps and requirements documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refine our CSS framework while maintaining the integrity of the web application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide accurate timing estimates for work based on verbal and written specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and document code that is reusable and well-thought-out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a high awareness of industry issues and trends, particularly with regard to accessibility, usability, and emerging front-end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aid in the growth of Buildium&amp;rsquo;s skills in User Experience development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in writing standards and cross-browser compliant code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to test and debug code in the development and browser environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in writing valid HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with jQuery, Modernizr, Knockout, LESS and other cutting edge JavaScript and CSS frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Web Accessibility standards like 508 Compliance or WAI Aria is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a distributed, unstructured, small company environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-sufficient and comfortable with ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and dental insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) retirement plan with company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Group life, short-term, and long-term disability insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible spending and dependent care accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take What You Need time off policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to work in a small, innovative start-up environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ping pong and foosball tables for superior hand-eye coordination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Salary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$60,000. Some flexibility depending on experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-developer-buildium-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-developer-buildium-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr Front-End Developer-UI Engineer at CA Technologies in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies (Nasdaq: CA) is an IT management software and solutions company with expertise across all IT environments&amp;mdash;from mainframe and physical, to virtual and cloud. CA manages and secures IT environments and enables customers to deliver more flexible IT services. CA Technologies innovative products and services provide the insight and control essential for IT organizations to power business agility. The majority of the Global Fortune 500 relies on CA Technologies to manage their evolving IT ecosystems. Founded in 1976, CA Technologies serves customers in virtually every country in the world and reported revenue of $4.8 billion in fiscal year 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a qualified Senior Front End Developer/UI Engineer to join our development team at our Framingham, MA office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate would have a strong background in UI design in addition to the below requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3, Javascript, HTML, JSP/Servlets, Portal Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the design and development of web-based and mobile user interfaces for enterprise applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development processes including: SCRUM and Agile methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years of experience in the industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work with local and remote development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent worker who takes initiative with minimal direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First rate communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of automation, unit, and integration testing best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the UI development effort for the CloudMinder, IdentityMinder and GovernanceMinder(IMAG) security product lines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, code, implement, unit and integration test features and code fixes applying best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with QA organization to develop functional test plans, automation tests, and coordinate verification and quality assurance for product releases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the CloudMinder engineering team’s software development process and practices for ensuring high quality deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize source code change management tools, defect tracking, and Agile project management planning and tracking tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review technical documentation updates for product releases. Provide details to support documentation changes to the core publications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with peers in a virtual high-performance team distributed across multiple CA locations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Openly accepting tasks which require research into new areas of knowledge and skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Can you build the career you want?  You CAn.  We&amp;rsquo;re a dynamic company with a strong vision in a growing global market. At a time when customers are demanding more and more from their technology, we&amp;rsquo;re changing the way the world manages IT, to help customers better perform, compete and grow. That&amp;rsquo;s why the majority of leading companies across industries worldwide use our software. It&amp;rsquo;s also why you&amp;rsquo;ll find a wealth of opportunities for important and rewarding work.  Come to CA Technologies and build the career you CAn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer competitive salary, company-sponsored premium Medical/Prescription &amp;amp; Dental Plans, company-paid Holidays, Vacation, Personal, Anniversary Service and Sick Days, 401(k) Plan, Education/Training Reimbursement, Charitable Gift Program, Adoption Assistance Program, and Veterinary Care Insurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about CA Technologies and this opportunity, we welcome you to visit our web site at www.ca.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies and all of its subsidiaries are equal opportunity employers. As such, it is our corporate policy to fill positions with qualified candidates regardless of the candidate’s race, color, sex, age, religion, ancestry, national origin, citizenship status, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, genetic information, disability, pregnancy, military status, veteran status or any other protected group status.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-ui-engineer-ca-technologies-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-ui-engineer-ca-technologies-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Principal Front-End Developer/UI Engineer at CA Technologies in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies (Nasdaq: CA) is an IT management software and solutions company with expertise across all IT environments&amp;mdash;from mainframe and physical, to virtual and cloud. CA manages and secures IT environments and enables customers to deliver more flexible IT services. CA Technologies innovative products and services provide the insight and control essential for IT organizations to power business agility. The majority of the Global Fortune 500 relies on CA Technologies to manage their evolving IT ecosystems. Founded in 1976, CA Technologies serves customers in virtually every country in the world and reported revenue of $4.8 billion in fiscal year 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a qualified Senior Front End Developer/ UI Engineer to join our development team at our Framingham, MA office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate would have a strong background in UI design in addition to the below requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3, Javascript, HTML, JSP/Servlets, Portal Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the design and development of web-based and mobile user interfaces for enterprise applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development processes including: SCRUM and Agile methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years of experience in the industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work with local and remote development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent worker who takes initiative with minimal direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First rate communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of automation, unit, and integration testing best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the UI development effort for the CloudMinder, IdentityMinder and GovernanceMinder(IMAG) security product lines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, code, implement, unit and integration test features and code fixes applying best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with QA organization to develop functional test plans, automation tests, and coordinate verification and quality assurance for product releases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the CloudMinder engineering team’s software development process and practices for ensuring high quality deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize source code change management tools, defect tracking, and Agile project management planning and tracking tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review technical documentation updates for product releases. Provide details to support documentation changes to the core publications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with peers in a virtual high-performance team distributed across multiple CA locations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Openly accepting tasks which require research into new areas of knowledge and skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Can you build the career you want?  You CAn.  We&amp;rsquo;re a dynamic company with a strong vision in a growing global market. At a time when customers are demanding more and more from their technology, we&amp;rsquo;re changing the way the world manages IT, to help customers better perform, compete and grow. That&amp;rsquo;s why the majority of leading companies across industries worldwide use our software. It&amp;rsquo;s also why you&amp;rsquo;ll find a wealth of opportunities for important and rewarding work.  Come to CA Technologies and build the career you CAn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer competitive salary, company-sponsored premium Medical/Prescription &amp;amp; Dental Plans, company-paid Holidays, Vacation, Personal, Anniversary Service and Sick Days, 401(k) Plan, Education/Training Reimbursement, Charitable Gift Program, Adoption Assistance Program, and Veterinary Care Insurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about CA Technologies and this opportunity, we welcome you to visit our web site at www.ca.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies and all of its subsidiaries are equal opportunity employers. As such, it is our corporate policy to fill positions with qualified candidates regardless of the candidate’s race, color, sex, age, religion, ancestry, national origin, citizenship status, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, genetic information, disability, pregnancy, military status, veteran status or any other protected group status.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-front-end-developer-ui-engineer-ca-technologies-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-front-end-developer-ui-engineer-ca-technologies-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Programmer/Developer at Smarterer in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You love to build products. You love to hack on web code. You love large scaling challenges, neat and complex algorithms, and working with a talented passionate team making a dent in the universe. You should work at Smarterer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to measure the world’s skills. We’re tapping into the fundamental need for people to be able to measure what they know, engaging the increasing number of digital tools that are part of everyone’s lives, and building a reliable way to prove skills to others (peers, employers, and the world). We’re small but growing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In joining our team, you’ll have a strong voice in our technology and product. We also believe that hacking is akin to painting so we’re not shy about making sure you’ll have the exact right tools for you to get your job done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who we’re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An ideal fit for us would be someone with a strong passion for programming, interest in the whole web technology stack, interest in the philosophy and details of actually making web products work (deployment, testing, as well as dev management and principles). The ideal candidate wants to “own” big pieces of the vision and functionality. We’re very interested in (but not limited to) people who identify themselves as “full stack” developers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t just a coding position, you’ll be a core member of the technology team, deeply involved in both the design and implementation of our technology. Our stack is mostly Javascript and Python using a lightweight, open source, semi-custom framework but our search is not limited to “python people.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Culturally, we’re low-ego and friendly, but super passionate about what we do. We’re looking for someone who is as passionate as we are and who strongly fits with the existing team. As a member of the core team, you’ll not only help us shape our technology and product, but will also help form the culture of our company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus points if you’re good with (or very interested in) these technologies
JavaScript, Python, Ruby, MySQL, AWS (or other cloud providers), Django, SQLAlchemy, Pylons, WSGI, NoSQL, memcached, REST design principles, API design and integration, async/concurrent IO programming&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Boston:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re based right in the middle of the Boston/Cambridge tech scene with hundreds of startups, over 500 regular tech and programming meet-ups and events, and tens of thousands of smart, motivated people building cool, innovative products. Boston is a great place to live and work, with a rich startup and technology ecosystem. If you’re not already in Boston, reach out and we’ll tell you more about why this is the perfect place for a developer to build their career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Smarterer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smarterer scores digital, social, and technical skills using crowdsourced test design and an adaptive scoring algorithm. In the past year, Smarterer users have taken more than 1.9 million tests and answered almost 20 million questions.  Our vision: Become the global standard in skills measurement. The opportunity? Huge!  Smarterer is backed by Google Ventures and True Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-programmer-developer-smarterer-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-programmer-developer-smarterer-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End/ Javascript Developer at Monotype Imaging Inc. in Woburn, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We want a front end developer who realizes that knowing javascript is far more than just being able to hide divs, who understands that the front end of a modern web app needs to be performance oriented and feature driven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MyFonts has a clear mission; to make it simple for everyone to find and buy fonts. We work with thousands of font designers to bring fresh and fashionable font designs to customers in a feature-rich website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the kind of things we do at http://www.myfonts.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll be doing:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with a small team to develop great new features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transforming designs &amp;amp; workflows into brand new, highly functional web apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Making responsive improvements to our existing site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/BA in Computer Science or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Javascript skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid HTML &amp;amp; CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to prioritize work on multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can collaborate with team members, but can complete projects individually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Good to have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience or knowledge of HTML templating systems. We use Smarty.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with source code version control. We use SVN.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing responsive websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eye for keeping visual consistency throughout a product, or better yet, you&amp;rsquo;ve developed working methods that help you to do so.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The position is located in Woburn, MA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a competitive salary and a first-rate benefits package, including medical, dental, vision, life insurance, 401(k) with company match, profit sharing, short and long term disability, paid holidays, vacation, and sick time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-javascript-developer-monotype-imaging-inc-woburn-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-javascript-developer-monotype-imaging-inc-woburn-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>