<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ma-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Agile Front-End Developer at Lexington Solutions in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Lexington Solutions®, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Boston Capital, is looking for an Agile Front End developer with a strong understanding of Agile development practices and a true, demonstrable passion for coding, both in and out of the office. We work in a collaborative, open space environment with a group of talented individuals who are all passionate about agile and building quality software. Fusion™, our flagship asset management product is setting the standard for the Low Income Housing Tax Credit industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;As an Agile Front End Developer you will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;produce standards-compliant front end code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;help user interface code keep pace with new technological developments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;code in a Paired Programming and Test Driven Development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;constantly learn and implement the latest Agile practices such as Kanban and Kaizen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;create high quality, innovative software that truly delivers business value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;work with highly analytical and experienced agile programmers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;use open source tools including Webwork, PicoContainer, Hibernate, JBehave, Groovy, GWT, Jasmin, Apache Tomcat, FIT, JUnit, Velocity, Subversion and more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;collaborate directly with product stakeholders and company executives to gather business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;We are looking for you if you have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years' experience with front end web technologies (HTML, Javascript, CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;knowledge of user interface design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the desire and ability to learn new technologies quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the desire to work in a team environment where you will mentor and learn from fellow developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent knowledge of design patterns and refactoring&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the ability to effectively communicate concepts and ideas to co-workers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Why Lexington Solutions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;work for a growing startup with the financial backing of a stable 38-year old company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;great pay and benefits (health, dental, 401k with match, tuition reimbursement)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;no/minimal travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;located in the heart of downtown Boston, convenient to all public transportation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;40-hour work weeks for great work/life balance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;office closes early on summer Fridays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/agile-front-end-developer-lexington-solutions-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/agile-front-end-developer-lexington-solutions-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Principal UI Engineer/FrontEndDeveloper at CA Technologies in Framingham, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies (NASDAQ: CA) provides IT management solutions that help customers manage and secure complex IT environments to support agile business services. Organizations leverage CA Technologies software and SaaS solutions to accelerate innovation, transform infrastructure and secure data and identities, from the data center to the cloud. Founded in 1976, CA Technologies serves customers in virtually every country in the world and reported revenue of $4.8 billion in fiscal year 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a qualified Senior UI/Usability Engineer to join our development team at our Framingham, MA office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate would have a strong background in UI design in addition to the below requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3, Javascript, HTML, JSP/Servlets, Portal Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the design and development of web-based and mobile user interfaces for enterprise applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development processes including: SCRUM and Agile methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years of experience in the industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work with local and remote development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent worker who takes initiative with minimal direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First rate communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of automation, unit, and integration testing best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the UI development effort for the CloudMinder, IdentityMinder and GovernanceMinder(IMAG) security product lines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, code, implement, unit and integration test features and code fixes applying best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with QA organization to develop functional test plans, automation tests, and coordinate verification and quality assurance for product releases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the CloudMinder engineering team’s software development process and practices for ensuring high quality deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize source code change management tools, defect tracking, and Agile project management planning and tracking tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review technical documentation updates for product releases. Provide details to support documentation changes to the core publications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with peers in a virtual high-performance team distributed across multiple CA locations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Openly accepting tasks which require research into new areas of knowledge and skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To be here for the long term we focus on things that last, and we are moved in many different ways. What moves you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you build the career you want? You CAn. We&amp;rsquo;re a dynamic company with a strong vision in a growing global market. At a time when customers are demanding more and more from their technology, we&amp;rsquo;re changing the way the world manages IT, to help customers better perform, compete and grow. That&amp;rsquo;s why the majority of leading companies across industries worldwide use our software. It&amp;rsquo;s also why you&amp;rsquo;ll find a wealth of opportunities for important and rewarding work. Come to CA Technologies and build the career you CAn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer competitive salary, company-sponsored premium Medical/Prescription &amp;amp; Dental Plans, company-paid Holidays, Vacation, Personal, Anniversary Service and Sick Days, 401(k) Plan, Education/Training Reimbursement, Charitable Gift Program, Adoption Assistance Program, and Veterinary Care Insurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about CA Technologies and this opportunity, we welcome you to visit our web site at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ca.com&quot;&gt;http://www.ca.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies and all of its subsidiaries are equal opportunity employers. As such, it is our corporate policy to fill positions with qualified candidates regardless of the candidate’s race, color, sex, age, religion, ancestry, national origin, citizenship status, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, genetic information, disability, pregnancy, military status, veteran status or any other protected group status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note to Recruiters and Placement Agencies: CA Technologies does not accept unsolicited agency resumes. Please do not forward unsolicited agency resumes to our website or to any CA Technologies employee. CA Technologies will not pay fees to any third party agency or firm and will not be responsible for any agency fees associated with unsolicited resumes. Unsolicited resumes received will be considered property of CA Technologies and will be processed accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-ui-engineer-frontenddeveloper-ca-technologies-framingham-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-ui-engineer-frontenddeveloper-ca-technologies-framingham-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Frontend Developer at Model N in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;With more than 45,000 users in 50+ countries, Model N is the leading provider of Revenue Management solutions optimized for Life Sciences and High Tech manufacturers.  Our SaaS and on-premise solutions enable customers to capture lost revenue, improve gross margin, and reduce financial and regulatory risk.  Through a suite of integrated applications specifically designed to meet the unique business requirements of our client companies, we enable multi-departmental visibility and control over the entire Revenue Management life cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Model N is looking for a talented software engineer for the RMI (Revenue Management Intelligence) business unit. Ideal candidate would have a good sense of UI and strong interests on data visualization, infographics, mobile web &amp;amp; analytics, and learning new UI technologies. You will have the opportunity to work on exciting BI (Business Intelligence) and cloud products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;3Responsibilities:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in an agile team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help and support product managers on UI prototyping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the usability of existing applications and help define UI paradigms and user interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement the defined UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. Degree or higher in Computer Science, Software Engineering or MIS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience with HTML/JavaScript/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with at least one of the following:  jQuery, DoJo, ExtJS or JavaScript framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand Object Oriented Design and Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to learn and quickly pick up new technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usability, UX knowledge or experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;force.com development experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL and Relational database experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;only local area candidates will be considered&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.modeln.com&quot;&gt;http://www.modeln.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/frontend-developer-model-n-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/frontend-developer-model-n-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Tufts University in Medford, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Web Communications, a department under University Relations, uses the web and emerging technologies to engage a diverse audience, including students, prospective students, parents, alumni, faculty, staff, donors and external media, with the Tufts story. To that end, the department is responsible for creating and implementing the university&amp;rsquo;s web communications strategy; managing internal and external online communications channels; and developing content, tools and services for Tufts.edu and related sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web Communications assumes full editorial and design responsibility for the main web presence, presidential initiatives and key administrative units. This includes the continued development and maintenance of the Tufts.edu home page, upper level and all major links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support a consistent brand and visual identity across the university, the department produces guidelines and templates that can be used for school, division and department websites. Web Communications implements custom and commercial web applications to support university-wide web initiatives and provides best practices and standards to university staff involved in web and social media projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary role of the Web Developer is to maintain existing website code, create HTML code from design mockups and develop new interactive features and applications that create an engaging and rich user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position works closely with members of the Web Communications team, and occasionally with clients outside the department, to translate business requirements into functionality that is easy to use and enhances our audience&amp;rsquo;s online experience. This role works in tandem with our internal and freelance web design resources to create elegant graphic user interfaces for websites and applications that support their objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Developer is also responsible for day-to-day maintenance of a set of existing websites and applications that use front-end programming. S/he troubleshoots and tests to ensure sites are accessible in multiple browsers and that all web applications work correctly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person in this role must be able to juggle multiple priorities, understand the needs of our different audiences, communicate clearly to a non-technical audience, and work within tight timelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science, Visual Communications or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four (4) years of direct experience in the field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5/XHTML, CSS3, Object Oriented Programming, XML/JSON, JavaScript/AJAX, and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the WordPress and Drupal frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive Web Design and Mobile Web Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debugging and solving cross-browser issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standard design tools (Photoshop, Illustrator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying code in a LAMP environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in user-experience (UX), usability and web accessibility standards and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of current popular APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to brainstorm creative solutions to problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience collaborating with a diverse, multidisciplinary team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to learn and apply new skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to edit in Flash/Flex/ActionScript to support existing web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong focus on front-end design and modern web practices to create an efficient user-experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in building applications interfacing with Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Vimeo and other social networking sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coding with PHP and MySQL as well as interest in expanding these skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-site SEO best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in higher education a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Special Work Schedule Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On very rare occasions, this person might be called upon to assist with online communications to the Tufts community in the case of a campus emergency or crisis. Otherwise, there are no special work schedule requirements.     &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Tufts University is an AA/EO employer and actively seeks candidates from diverse backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-tufts-university-medford-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-tufts-university-medford-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>