<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ma-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Frontend Developer at Model N in Boston, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;With more than 45,000 users in 50+ countries, Model N is the leading provider of Revenue Management solutions optimized for Life Sciences and High Tech manufacturers.  Our SaaS and on-premise solutions enable customers to capture lost revenue, improve gross margin, and reduce financial and regulatory risk.  Through a suite of integrated applications specifically designed to meet the unique business requirements of our client companies, we enable multi-departmental visibility and control over the entire Revenue Management life cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Model N is looking for a talented software engineer for the RMI (Revenue Management Intelligence) business unit. Ideal candidate would have a good sense of UI and strong interests on data visualization, infographics, mobile web &amp;amp; analytics, and learning new UI technologies. You will have the opportunity to work on exciting BI (Business Intelligence) and cloud products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;3Responsibilities:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in an agile team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help and support product managers on UI prototyping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the usability of existing applications and help define UI paradigms and user interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement the defined UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. Degree or higher in Computer Science, Software Engineering or MIS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience with HTML/JavaScript/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with at least one of the following:  jQuery, DoJo, ExtJS or JavaScript framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand Object Oriented Design and Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to learn and quickly pick up new technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usability, UX knowledge or experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;force.com development experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL and Relational database experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;only local area candidates will be considered&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.modeln.com&quot;&gt;http://www.modeln.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/frontend-developer-model-n-boston-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/frontend-developer-model-n-boston-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Tufts University in Medford, MA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Web Communications, a department under University Relations, uses the web and emerging technologies to engage a diverse audience, including students, prospective students, parents, alumni, faculty, staff, donors and external media, with the Tufts story. To that end, the department is responsible for creating and implementing the university&amp;rsquo;s web communications strategy; managing internal and external online communications channels; and developing content, tools and services for Tufts.edu and related sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web Communications assumes full editorial and design responsibility for the main web presence, presidential initiatives and key administrative units. This includes the continued development and maintenance of the Tufts.edu home page, upper level and all major links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support a consistent brand and visual identity across the university, the department produces guidelines and templates that can be used for school, division and department websites. Web Communications implements custom and commercial web applications to support university-wide web initiatives and provides best practices and standards to university staff involved in web and social media projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary role of the Web Developer is to maintain existing website code, create HTML code from design mockups and develop new interactive features and applications that create an engaging and rich user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position works closely with members of the Web Communications team, and occasionally with clients outside the department, to translate business requirements into functionality that is easy to use and enhances our audience&amp;rsquo;s online experience. This role works in tandem with our internal and freelance web design resources to create elegant graphic user interfaces for websites and applications that support their objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Developer is also responsible for day-to-day maintenance of a set of existing websites and applications that use front-end programming. S/he troubleshoots and tests to ensure sites are accessible in multiple browsers and that all web applications work correctly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person in this role must be able to juggle multiple priorities, understand the needs of our different audiences, communicate clearly to a non-technical audience, and work within tight timelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science, Visual Communications or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four (4) years of direct experience in the field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5/XHTML, CSS3, Object Oriented Programming, XML/JSON, JavaScript/AJAX, and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the WordPress and Drupal frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive Web Design and Mobile Web Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debugging and solving cross-browser issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standard design tools (Photoshop, Illustrator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying code in a LAMP environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in user-experience (UX), usability and web accessibility standards and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of current popular APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to brainstorm creative solutions to problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience collaborating with a diverse, multidisciplinary team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to learn and apply new skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to edit in Flash/Flex/ActionScript to support existing web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong focus on front-end design and modern web practices to create an efficient user-experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in building applications interfacing with Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Vimeo and other social networking sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coding with PHP and MySQL as well as interest in expanding these skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-site SEO best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in higher education a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Special Work Schedule Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On very rare occasions, this person might be called upon to assist with online communications to the Tufts community in the case of a campus emergency or crisis. Otherwise, there are no special work schedule requirements.     &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Tufts University is an AA/EO employer and actively seeks candidates from diverse backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-tufts-university-medford-ma</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-tufts-university-medford-ma</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>