<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/md-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Ruby Software Developer at CyberCore Technologies in Annapolis Junction, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The candidate will work under the direction of the team lead to help develop Ruby/ Ruby on Rails applications for the Strands development effort. This position is for a motivated developer experienced in an agile development environment. Candidates should possess inter- and intra-team skills that allow them to work effectively with external teams to capture requirements and implement said requirements within the development environment. A working knowledge of network designs, principles and practices is helpful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a Full Scope Polygraph&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Ruby, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS and Ajax&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with either Ruby on Rails, or Django frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux and web development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with agile development practices (test driven development, automated unit testing, continuous builds, spins, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the Model–view–controller (MVC) software architecture pattern&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of network designs, principles and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using a multitude of common Internet libraries for JavaScript development (e.g. Bootstrap, Backbone, Express, ExtJS/Sencha Touch)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with XSLTs and XSDs, as well as front end user interface implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with MongoDB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Serialization such as JSON and/or BSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-software-developer-cybercore-technologies-annapolis-junction-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-software-developer-cybercore-technologies-annapolis-junction-md</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Fearless Solutions, LLC in Annapolis Junction, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in HTML5 tags, meta tags, and usage of W3C current spec.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to create RESTful services in NodeJS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to create SSL/TLS wrapped WebSocket data streams in NodeJS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands JavaScript prototypal design patterns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must understand and be familiar with JavaEE design paradigms and be able to reflectthat knowledge into SSJ (server-side JavaScript).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using a multitude of common Internet libraries for JavaScriptdevelopment (Bootstrap, Backbone, Express, ExtJS/Sencha Touch).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge ofJavaScript-focused continuous integration, continuous deployment andbuild processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand and be proficient in the use of client-side storage and caching withAppCache, Local/SessionStorage, and IndexedDB.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be proficient in test-driven design (TDD) or behavior-driven design (BDD), specificallywith QUnit or Jasmine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with CSS3 and reactive design paradigms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand thefundamental differences in the W3C specification adoption betweendifferent families of browsers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to lead and work in Agile/Kanban environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version control with Subversion or Git.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using the Firefox, Chrome, or Safari APIs to build, package, and deploy custom browser extensions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Engineering, Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, Information Systems,Mathematics or related discipline or equivalent documented combination of training and experience.Advanced degree in related technical field desired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Clearance Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a US citizen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have, or be willing to obtain, an active TOP SECRET security clearance, based on a current single scope background investigation (SSBI), as well as a favorable completion of Full Screening Polygraph completed by the U.S. Government.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fearless Solutions is company driven by delivering innovative produces and services to our customers that make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our core values include the &amp;ldquo;Fearless 5&amp;rdquo;: Passion, Integrity, Excellence, Improvement, and Innovation. We keep our competitive advantage by living our values out each day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fearless Solutions is an Equal Opportunity Employer EOE, M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-fearless-solutions-llc-annapolis-junction-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-fearless-solutions-llc-annapolis-junction-md</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Drupal Developer at MMG in Rockville, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;MMG has a full-time opening in our Rockville, MD office for a skilled Drupal Developer. This position will design, develop, test, implement, and maintain client websites using Drupal; work closely with other developers and project teams to identify and modify websites and related applications to function as required; and document current and future configuration processes and policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About MMG&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advancing Health. Accelerating Recruitment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MMG is a full-service global health communications company specializing in patient recruitment and retention for clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We operate in an atmosphere that promotes innovation, excellence, integrity, collaboration, and stewardship. Our team comprises a diverse group of people all working to deliver results: tangible results for our clients, timely results for each other, and fulfilling results for ourselves. This practice has led to enjoyable and long-standing relationships with our clients and our staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree, or equivalent experience, in Computer Science, Engineering, or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years’ experience developing within Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong front-end Drupal experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of source control tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cross-browser compatibility and functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript; XML, XSLT or AJAX; CSS2/CSS3; HTML4/HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Section 508 standards and custom module development a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The desired candidate will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have an energy and passion for cutting-edge technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have an attention to detail and strong problem solving ability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be well organized and able to manage multiple tasks and prioritize as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be adaptable to a fast-paced, demanding, tight-deadline environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy working with a team and sharing knowledge to improve processes and efficiencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have excellent written and verbal communication skills in order to convey thoughts and ideas to staff at all levels of the organization and clients as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be actively involved in the Drupal community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/drupal-developer-mmg-rockville-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/drupal-developer-mmg-rockville-md</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer - Application at Message Systems in Columbia, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Message Systems team is looking for a highly motivated Web Developer to help us design and build our product user interfaces. We currently have several positions available for varying levels of experience.  The successful candidate will be a technically proficient, self-starter with excellent communications skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Developer will be responsible for UI and front-end development, applying their expertise to build a suite of leading messaging products. The Web Developer must possess strong interpersonal skills and deep technical knowledge across a range of technologies including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building and deploying high quality, highly reliable, scalable enterprise software products in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading small teams of developers building sophisticated web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership skills with the ability to mentor other developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be as much at home coding as teaching others about best practices, testing, and building in quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep knowledge and experience with PHP and PHP frameworks such as Zend/CakePHP, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with (X)HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5+ years experience building interactive web applications and user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cross-browser/cross-platform compatibility including knowledge of and ability to solve common associated issues as well as investigate and troubleshoot complex inconsistencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using JavaScript and AJAX libraries such as jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version control systems including Subversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical, problem solving, and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desirable Skills/Knowledge:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with fast UI prototyping, rapid iterations, Agile web development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a LAMP (Linux/Apache/MySql/PHP) environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PostgreSQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is based in Columbia, MD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Message Systems:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1997, Message Systems is a worldwide provider of message management solutions and services for marketing and email service providers (MSPs, ESPs), carriers and Internet service providers (ISPs), social networks and large enterprises that need to manage large volumes of business-critical email and other forms of digital messaging (SMS, MMS, XMPP). Through a combination of technology, partnerships and intellectual capital, Message Systems offers a family of next generation software solutions and services that address the infrastructure and deliverability needs for organizations ranging from e-commerce companies to the Global 2000. With the most powerful message management platform on the market, Message Systems gets billions of unique messages to the right place at the right time every day. Headquartered in Columbia, Maryland, Message Systems has offices and a network of partners in North America, Europe and Asia Pacific.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Message Systems believes in a fun but focused development environment. We have flexible hours, outstanding benefits, and a world-class team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send resumes to jobs@messagesystems.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-application-message-systems-columbia-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-application-message-systems-columbia-md</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Business Intelligence Architect / Senior Developer at Cristal in Hunt Valley, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Cristal and its nearly 4,000 employees across five continents are proud market leaders in manufacturing titanium dioxide products. We are passionate about pursuing perfection in our work, providing for our family of employees, and creating a cleaner, brighter future with the products we make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cristal &amp;ndash; the complete titanium specialists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We live and breathe titanium: we do nothing else, and nobody does it better. Cristal is the second largest titanium dioxide producer in the world, the largest producer of merchant titanium chemicals, the leading manufacturer of specialty titanium products and a fast growing producer of mineral sands&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the brilliance of titanium, Cristal’s pioneering spirit and passion for science and technology our drives innovation. We strive to unleash the brilliance of titanium to provide great opportunities and safe environments for our communities. Cristal&amp;rsquo;s caring and supportive environment with the warmth of family and a strong value system develops and empowers people to reach their fullest potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join our family and experience a career with genuine impact in a company with a pioneering spirit, the warmth of a family and the strength of a multinational&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage, guide, and support the work of the members of the business intelligence team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead &amp;amp; Manage Global project priorities to ensure business objectives are met. Work with business managers to identify where business intelligence can be applied in supporting global business objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the BI report portfolio, limiting duplication and ensuring global and regional requirements are fulfilled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for maintaining the integrity of system configuration (e.g. SAP Business Warehouse).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Function as the company’s top technical expert in the multiple business intelligence software applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage data and business process integrity and support end-user decision-making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and foster collaborative efforts with all integrated business functions and the IT team to identify, establish, and share best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, evaluate and maintain appropriate process and procedure documentation, and KPI’s to support business and system improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical expertise and support of the system to identify, develop and implement business reporting and analysis improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the global Business Solutions team to identify, design and implement changes or reporting enhancements to the SAP system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pursue defined ‘major focus projects’ supporting global business objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that SAP roles comply with internal &amp;amp; external auditing requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage multiple project priorities to ensure business objectives are met.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define standards and best practices for installing, configuring and using business intelligence applications for the purpose of directing and managing the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design specifications and standards for semantic layers and multidimensional models for complex BI projects , across all environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform other duties as required.​&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills Required:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Formal Education/Qualification:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS Degree and 8 years IT experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-7 years of combined SAP and Business Intelligence experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project management: lead small teams of 1 – 3 resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervisory experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prefer experience in a manufacturing environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Function Specific:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architecting background on at least two full life cycle BW Implementations for medium to large projects of high complexity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business Intelligence and Data Warehouse Requirements gathering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data warehouse modelling and implementation using best practise approaches (Kimball, Inmon)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding and experience with at least one front-end reporting and analytical tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication skills: strong presentation / communication / facilitation skills (oral and written)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General consulting skills, including: team facilitation, business case development and business process assessment / strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively interact with the client business community to gather / develop functional and technical requirements and translate the requirements into robust analytics and reporting solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong understanding of dimensional modelling and data warehousing concepts and methodologies and leading full-lifecycle Business Intelligence and Data Warehousing projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery level of knowledge with BW configuration of BW data objects including Infoobjects, Infosources, transfer/Update Rules, ODS, InfoProviders, Multiproviders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery level of BW Extractors from the SAP ERP system and working knowledge of SAP structures, object.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependencies and tables in ECC6.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced working knowledge of interfacing SAP BW to other SAP products, such as FICO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The following skill sets are highly desirable:
&lt;strong&gt; BW system upgrade experience.BW integration with SAP Portal / Netweaver.
&lt;/strong&gt; Master Data Management (MDM).
&lt;strong&gt; Custom ABAP Experience.
&lt;/strong&gt; Web Services development experience with BW.
&lt;strong&gt; Experience with other Business Intelligence and Data warehousing ETL and OLAP technologies.
&lt;/strong&gt; SAP functional experience in FI-CO, SD , HR, MM, PP and QM.
** Background or experience in finance and/or Business Analytics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Business/Industry Specific:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in global manufacturing/commercial environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detailed knowledge and experience of global business processes, ideally in a Chemical Industry sector.​&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/business-intelligence-architect-senior-developer-cristal-hunt-valley-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/business-intelligence-architect-senior-developer-cristal-hunt-valley-md</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>