<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/md-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at FEi in Columbia, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The User Experience (UX) Designer will work in a production environment alongside a team of software developers, system architects, business analysts, QA testers and project managers to create best-of-breed software applications.   The UX Designer is responsible for gathering and documenting UI requirements, conceptualizing and creating UI wireframes, creating style guides, and implementing the UI using standard web based technologies such as HTML/CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Principal Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with business analysts and subject matter experts to gather UI requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare UI requirements documentation such as workflows, diagrams, sketches etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create UI wireframes and/or prototypes, to establish product design patterns, interaction, behavior navigation and content structure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create UI style guides and mockups to establish themes and look and feel of a product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coding and development using latest web based technologies and standards such as: HTML5, CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert proficiency in applying usability design principles and best practices to user interface design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert proficiency using design software including Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate and collaborate effectively with others within a team environment and work independently on individual assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in web application and UI design and development technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with web based technologies: HTML5, CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with web development frameworks: Responsive Design, Grid System etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with W3C validation, accessibility and usability audits, tests/debugging across major web browsers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with accessibility design and development including section 508, WAI-ARIA and WCAG standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency using UI wireframes and prototyping software: iRise, JustInMind etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency using web development software: Dream Weaver, Coda, VisualStudio, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Primary Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;United States-Maryland-Columbia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FEi is a leading IT company specializing in Federal and Local Government data system solutions. For the past decade we have maintained a leading position in providing programming and consulting services in our primary areas of expertise- Behavioral Health Data Systems, and Clinical Trials Software Solutions for institutional systems of care.  At FEi Systems, we recognize that our employees are an important part of our success. We promote a team environment where all employees have the opportunity to achieve professional and personal success. Currently FEi is looking for highly skilled, self-motivated and creative individuals to join our talented team of experts. FEi is an equal opportunity employer that believes in growing and promoting a diverse work force. Our employee compensation and benefits package is competitive within the industry and is designed to help employees meet varying needs throughout their careers and lives. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a rewarding work environment that will challenge your mind and expand your horizons, then joining the FEi team may be right for you. Please send your résumé to TalentAcquisition@FEiSystems.com or view all of our openings at www.Feisystems.com/careers&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-fei-columbia-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-fei-columbia-md</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Transwestern in Columbia, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Transwestern, a national full service commercial real estate company is seeking an experienced Graphic Designer to work in its Columbia, MD office. The Graphic Designer is responsible for assisting the office with all areas of graphics and resource support.  This position requires the person to be efficient and organized while completing various types of graphic design duties related to the Baltimore-Washington commercial real estate market. This position will be responsible for creating flyers, marketing materials, and presentations. The person in the job must be detail-oriented, have a high level of patience, be able to multi-task, have good interpersonal skills, and be able to work under high levels of pressure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate would be proficient in the Adobe Creative Suite, including InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop and Dreamweaver, as well as Microsoft PowerPoint and FrontPage. Experience with Adobe Flash a plus. Experience designing graphics for web a MUST. Basic understanding of the principles of HTML, XHTML and CSS needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL JOB FUNCTIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage design and production requests for proposals and presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and produce property-specific marketing flyers and related materials utilizing brand elements to keep a consistent look and feel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize, plan, design, and produce a wide range of graphic and/or illustrative material, from simple to complex (i.e. brochures, fact sheets, direct mail, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit previously created materials to current specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schedule and execute email campaigns (e-blasts) for brokers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a creative idea generator to market both the team and real estate listings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate the production process; develop and write printing and/or other production specifications, and select appropriate production media and materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compile and package market surveys using CoStar, mapping, aerial imagery and other software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain corporate marketing photography and stock art databases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prints/maintains supply of marketing materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeping current on commercial real estate transactions and events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working directly with the office manager in assisting with administrative duties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional assignments as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;POSITION REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Education:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two-year college degree; four-year preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years related real estate experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real estate license is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic Designer experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Technical Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MUST BE PROFICIENT with Adobe CS 5 (Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, and Acrobat)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient with Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CoStar or Regis is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Personal Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write content and revise copy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess outstanding creativity as well as analytical, communication and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely detail-oriented and organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline sensitive, must strive under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team-player capable of taking on multiple and complex assignments simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Physical:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Transwestern offers an exciting work environment, competitive salary, and excellent benefits which includes medical, dental, vision coverage and 401(k). Transwestern is an equal opportunity employer. Please include resume, salary requirements and references. Please, No phone calls.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-transwestern-columbia-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-transwestern-columbia-md</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Sinclair Broadcast Group in Hunt Valley, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Make your mark in Broadcasting. Sinclair Broadcast Group, Inc is one of the largest and most diversified television broadcasting companies in the nation, programming 112 stations located in 61 geographically diverse markets. Our success is the result of extraordinary employees and an exemplary management team who believes in a vision and is dedicated to making Sinclair Broadcast Group, Inc a communications powerhouse. We are advancing the world of Broadcasting and we want YOU to join our winning team!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Web Designer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sinclair Broadcast Group is looking for a Website Designer for the corporate web department in Hunt Valley, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The candidate will work through our current proprietary Content Management System and Adobe Dreamweaver with other team members to design and maintain the company’s multiple television websites, as well as provide technical, editorial and promotional support to the sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This person will work closely with other members of the Corporate Web Team and the Programming and Development team, as well as with the sales, promotions and news departments at the television stations around the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will be an excellent written and verbal communicator, well-organized, able to multi-task, detail-oriented and comfortable working with people at remote locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates should have experience with PhotoShop, Dreamweaver, Excel, PowerPoint, and Word. Candidates must also have a general familiarity with Content Management Systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of Social Networking platforms, SEO and mobile initiatives, other scripting languages and development of web-based applications a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum 2 years experience required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INTERNAL APPLICANTS AT A SINCLAIR STATION SHOULD SEE THEIR LOCAL HR CONTACT TO APPLY FOR THIS POSITION.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sinclair Broadcast Group, Inc. is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer and Drug Free Workplace!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-sinclair-broadcast-group-hunt-valley-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-sinclair-broadcast-group-hunt-valley-md</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphics/User Interface Designer at GlobalNet Services Inc. in Rockville, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;An innovative and dynamic IT company is seeking a Graphic Designer to support branding and marketing initiatives for company and clients and presentation design. The User Interface Analyst will assess documentation and collateral needs, web design and development, usability research and analysis, print and digital content creation, and assist in application interface design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Support includes evaluating business requirements gathered from multiple sources, reconciling conflicts, and decomposing high-level requirements into details, abstract up from low-level information to a general understanding, and distinguish user requests from the underlying true needs. Also includes development of drafts, mock-ups, or wireframes as appropriate and presentation of overall look and feel, and estimation and budgeting of work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage multiple projects in a quick turnaround environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop budgets and timelines for design projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turn requirements and abstract ideas into a cohesive design for print and/or digital formats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide user interface consulting deliverables including strategy documents, prototypes and usability analysis documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create assets such as: wireframes, mock-ups, prototypes, sitemaps, and  workflows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in defining information architecture and navigation strategy for websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance and expertise for web team in creating new sites and web applications, as well as updating existing web application interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop branding for proposals, marketing materials, websites, and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years in graphics design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert proficiency with desktop design tools (e.g. Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Dreamweaver, MS PowerPoint).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with digital multimedia tools, CSS, HTML, and HTML5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience with Javascript/Jquery/Drupal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years’ experience in user interface design, usability, or information architecture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about design, aesthetics, and best practices for web and mobile devices, including responsive design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work constructively with a team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of initiative and independently motivated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable in a fast-pace environment and handling multiple priorities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on large, complex sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Government sites preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of usability best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of accessibility issues, including section 508 compliance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Working at GNSI:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer our employees comprehensive benefits that respond to their growing needs. From the basics in health care to programs that help manage life’s little turns, some of our benefits include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical Benefits, Prescription Drug Plan, Dental, and Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Accounts for Medical/Dental/Vision and Dependent Care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid Life/AD&amp;amp;D, Short-Term Disability and Long-Term Disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) Retirement Savings Plan with Employer Match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roth 401(k)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SmartBenefits, a transit benefit program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;And Much More.  Please click on the following link for a full list of benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe it is equally important to maintain a work environment that encourages fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some recent Company Sponsored Events:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wii Competitions (bowling, tennis, and golf)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foosball Competition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laser Tag Celebration Event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Murder Mystery Theatre Event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bowling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Picnics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Holiday Celebrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;At GNSI, our people are our most important competitive advantage. We know that our highly skilled work force is vital to our present and future success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GNSI’s commitment to diversity permeates our entire organization, which encourage us to show respect for, and appreciate the value of, all individuals and their unique backgrounds, experiences, styles, approaches and ideas. The diversity of our people has been and will continue to be one of the keys to GNSI’s success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional Details:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local applicants please (relocation expenses are not included). No faxes or calls. Please upload resume as a Word file or PDF. Other formats will not be reviewed or considered. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GlobalNet Services, Inc. (GNSI), a dynamic Information Technology company located in Rockville, MD.  The City of Rockville has been named among the Top 100 Best Places to Live, ranking No. 31 in the August 2010 edition of Money Magazine. Rockville was chosen as one of America&amp;rsquo;s best small cities for families because of its recently rebuilt downtown, economic stability and great schools.  In addition to the Money Magazine designation, Rockville also was selected as an Editors Pick in U.S. News and World Report, which recently released its America&amp;rsquo;s Best Places 2010 list. The City of Rockville is a 13-square-mile city with a population of about 61,000 and is located 12 miles northwest of Washington, D.C.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphics-user-interface-designer-globalnet-services-inc-rockville-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphics-user-interface-designer-globalnet-services-inc-rockville-md</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Entry-Level Graphic Designer at Agora, Inc. in Baltimore, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Agora Financial is looking to hire a creative and highly motivated entry-level graphic designer for its downtown Baltimore office. The right candidate must display excellent design skills as well as communication and organizational abilities and be able to work in a fast-paced, deadline-oriented environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production of multiple monthly printed &amp;amp; online newsletters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing innovative book cover designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing digital ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with design team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic Design degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1–2 years experience working in the industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe CS5 (InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator and Microsoft Office)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mac OSX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML experience and familiarity with content management systems (WordPress is a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Typography skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Personal skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative problem solving skills with a “can do” attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet tight deadlines while maintaining high standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aptitude in working in a fast-paced, ever changing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For consideration applicants MUST submit an online portfolio link, a resume and salary requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be looking for the following in your portfolio: Samples showing large amount of text layouts like newsletters, book layouts, direct mail and creative projects like posters, book covers, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have what it takes, we would love for you to join our dynamic creative team and take advantage of our compensation package including: competitive salary, comprehensive medical benefits, 401k, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/entry-level-graphic-designer-agora-inc-baltimore-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/entry-level-graphic-designer-agora-inc-baltimore-md</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>