<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/md-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Entry-Level Graphic Designer at Agora, Inc. in Baltimore, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Agora Financial is looking to hire a creative and highly motivated entry-level graphic designer for its downtown Baltimore office. The right candidate must display excellent design skills as well as communication and organizational abilities and be able to work in a fast-paced, deadline-oriented environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production of multiple monthly printed &amp;amp; online newsletters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing innovative book cover designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing digital ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with design team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic Design degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1–2 years experience working in the industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe CS5 (InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator and Microsoft Office)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mac OSX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML experience and familiarity with content management systems (WordPress is a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Typography skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Personal skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative problem solving skills with a “can do” attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet tight deadlines while maintaining high standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aptitude in working in a fast-paced, ever changing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For consideration applicants MUST submit an online portfolio link, a resume and salary requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be looking for the following in your portfolio: Samples showing large amount of text layouts like newsletters, book layouts, direct mail and creative projects like posters, book covers, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have what it takes, we would love for you to join our dynamic creative team and take advantage of our compensation package including: competitive salary, comprehensive medical benefits, 401k, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/entry-level-graphic-designer-agora-inc-baltimore-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/entry-level-graphic-designer-agora-inc-baltimore-md</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>