<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/md-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Wireless Support Technician, Blackberry, iOS at Cigna in Baltimore, MD</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a talented Wireless Support Tech Senior Associate to join our team in Baltimore!   This position will provide guidance, assistance, coordination and follow up on client questions, problems or malfunctions of all Wireless Device Equipment maintained by IT Service Desk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Procurement of all wireless devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blackberry Enterprise Server Tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vendor Relations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auditing of Wireless Assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with additional groups to come to a resolution for Outages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually demonstrates professionalism and respect for the customer and team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takes ownership of problem resolution and becomes an advocate of the customer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act as an escalation point from other Service Desk Techs for advanced help requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interprets, evaluates and resolves if possible, telephone inquiries pertaining to the functional operation of all installed application hardware and software products supported by IT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzes simple to moderately complex inquiries and determines appropriate technical area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains thorough and accurate documentation of ticket status and resolution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applies diagnostic utilities to aid in troubleshooting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alerts the client community and team members when a major problem is suspected. Follows up on specific inquires or requests to ensure client satisfaction. Reports problems with procedures and makes suggestions for improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adheres to compliance guidelines along with policies and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As Needed:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs hands-on fixes at the desktop level, including installing and upgrading software, installing anti-virus software, installing hardware, implementing file backups, and configuring systems and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Administer telecom add, move, change requests from end users, software, voice mail, and video conferencing systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate degree in Computer Science or related discipline with an IT focus preferred or equivalent years of progressive experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two years of experience in IT or an equivalent combination of education and work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of IT operations, responsibilities, work flow processes and procedures to resolve most inquiries independently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good analytical and communication skills, sound judgment, and the ability to work effectively with client and other IT staff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of Microsoft Windows XP, 7, Blackberry Enterprise Server and Active Directory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to lift equipment of up to 40 pounds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience with deployment and / or support of client/server systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/wireless-support-technician-blackberry-ios-cigna-baltimore-md</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/wireless-support-technician-blackberry-ios-cigna-baltimore-md</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>