<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mi-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Python Web Developer at Doodle Home in Detroit, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Doodle Home is a web-based interior design destination serving consumers, interior designers and mid- to high-end manufacturers of luxury home furnishings. Founded in 2010, Doodle Home revolutionizes the way interior design is  practiced in the 21st century.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Do/Need&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Python Web Developer works on a project-by-project basis with every level of the team. Focus will be working in Python 2.7, Pylons Pyramid 1.3 and MongoDB on a daily basis to help reach our aggressive development goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand requirements and build initial code and tests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create production-ready code in Python for Pylons Pyramid 1.3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate on new projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in design and code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow and enhance existing development processes by measuring and verifying improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver accurate estimates, provide regular feedback and consistently meet deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General database work in MongoDB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain complex ideas and concepts to non-technical team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of supporting technologies like GIT, Terminal, Bash, SSH, and other web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superb attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two years of experience in Python or several years of experience in PHP, Ruby, or JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience in a test-driven development (TDD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Established portfolio of work or code samples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What&amp;rsquo;ll Make You Special&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User interface implementation experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop and other supporting web development tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Get&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent benefits package that includes a 401(k) match, medical/dental/vision, and much more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to participate in professional and personal development programs, including personal empowerment coaching, leadership training and ongoing personal growth training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other incentives, contests and rewards including trips, event tickets, cash prizes and more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Why We’re Different&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meet the anti-corporate culture of Doodle Home, where there&amp;rsquo;s no daunting hierarchy, &amp;ldquo;boss&amp;rdquo; is a four-letter word, and if you work hard, you&amp;rsquo;re the one who will reap the rewards, both personally and professionally. More than any other place you&amp;rsquo;ll work, we’re dedicated to honing your skills, helping you grow and making sure you have plenty of fun while you’re at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doodle Home is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/python-web-developer-doodle-home-detroit-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/python-web-developer-doodle-home-detroit-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Applications Developer at CU*Answers, Inc. in Grand Rapids, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CU*Answers Web Services is looking for a web developer to join our team.  A well-qualified candidate is a full stack web developer, comfortable with talking to the client (&amp;ldquo;I have people skills!&amp;rdquo;),understanding their design specification, jumping into PhotoShop to knock it out, then rolling to your HTML editor of choice to craft your HTML5 and CSS3 masterpiece.  We are a WordPress shop, so theming, plugin development and administration skills are a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CU*Answers Web Services is a tight-knit marketing and web development team adhering to modern web practices and standards.  Each team members is self-sufficient but available for mentoring and to be mentored &amp;ndash; no egos need apply. On any given day you could beupdating any number of over 200 websites, developing themes or functionality for new clients or continuing to work on larger WP and non-WP web projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full time position including benefits, 401k and bonus potential in a fast paced, ever changing work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researches, designs and executes web-enabled applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with Webmaster to design and launch web sites for CU&lt;em&gt;Answers and CU&lt;/em&gt;Answers clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Day-to-day client site maintenance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep CU*Answers up to date with Internet, browser and related technological changes and industry advancements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a positive contribution as a member of the Technical Resource Team and complete all tasks assigned by management to meet team objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, CSS and JavaScript (jQuery) skills (client side coding)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP and MySQL skills (server side coding)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite experience (design)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WordPress experience in theming and plugin development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WordPress knowledge of management, security, scaling and deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in new and emerging web technologies and knowing when to adopt them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical creativity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to learn and to teach&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform complete project development including project analysis, design, development, delegation of duties as needed, installation, ongoing maintenance, and any necessary documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent attention to detail and accuracy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to use discretion when dealing with sensitive or confidential data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-applications-developer-cu-answers-inc-grand-rapids-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-applications-developer-cu-answers-inc-grand-rapids-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Software Developer at ProQuest in Ann Arbor, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a member of the Global Product Development team at ProQuest, you will be playing a key role in developing the next generation of products that serve the K12 market.  We&amp;rsquo;re looking for seasoned, hands-on front-end developers with rock-solid coding skills, an appreciation for good design, and a passion for building high-quality products for multiple devices using modern web technologies.  This is an opportunity to have a significant impact in the context of a small, highly effective, nimble engineering team building an exciting new product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still interested?  Read on&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you need to be successful:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience spanning several major/minor releases building websites using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery that are fast, support multiple browsers, and are maintainable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with UI designers, product management, and other engineers to design and build web apps and other deliverables from mockups and requirement descriptions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Responsive Design.  Having built websites that support mobile devices is a definite plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile development methodologies such as SCRUM or XP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with test automation with tools such as Selenium is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five or more years of relevant experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Library industry experience big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with ProQuest products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what you want to know about ProQuest:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fantastic people:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where smart is the norm and unique is welcome&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fun location:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Restaurants all around, within walking distance to Briarwood Mall, and approximately 3 miles from Downtown Ann Arbor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Great benefits:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On-site events, flexible scheduling and wellness programs, plus Bike to work benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Awesome office environment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nice office, jeans are the norm and unlimited complimentary coffee and tea for the caffeine craved&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Amazing company:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Annual compensation reviews, generous bonuses, along with being voted as one of the Top Places to Work by Detroit Free Press, four years in a row!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About ProQuest&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ProQuest connects people with vetted, reliable information. We provide seamless access to and navigation of more than 125 billion digital pages of the world&amp;rsquo;s scholarship, delivering it to the desktop and into the workflow of serious researchers in multiple fields, from arts, literature, and social science to general reference, business, science, technology, and medicine. The company is currently rolling out the all-new ProQuest® platform, which moves beyond navigation to empower researchers to use, create, and share content—accelerating research productivity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-software-developer-proquest-ann-arbor-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-software-developer-proquest-ann-arbor-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Entry Level Web Developer at IBM in East Lansing, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The world is getting smarter, triggering unprecedented change. IBM&amp;rsquo;s unparalleled ability to bring together deep business insight, advanced research, analytics, and technology enables IBM Global Business Services to help position its clients for the future. We leverage the proven roadmaps and frameworks that have been developed across 17 industries and the unique combination of skills and experiences of our teams in over 170 countries &amp;ndash; unmatched capabilities. When you join IBM, you&amp;rsquo;ll partner with our clients, and leverage these capabilities to deliver real business value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a member of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading and largest consulting organization, you&amp;rsquo;ll tap into resources that only a global leader like IBM can provide: access to a vast and diverse network of talented professionals; enjoy unparalleled career opportunities; be provided with ongoing training and education that you&amp;rsquo;ll need to succeed; and work on some of the most interesting projects on the planet, helping everyone from organizations to local governments, work smarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us. The first of its kind IBM Global Delivery Center right here in East Lansing, Michigan!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IBM Michigan Delivery Center occupies a unique position in the IT market &amp;mdash; at the intersection of business and technology. This global delivery center provides services to leading-edge clients who are looking for a unique, U.S.-based capability to design, develop, and support their mission-critical applications. IBM&amp;rsquo;s Michigan Delivery Center is a strategic delivery center location that is poised for significant growth over the next few years. As a member of our team, you&amp;rsquo;ll help clients solve some of their most challenging business and technology problems, capitalize on market opportunities, and achieve real value in today&amp;rsquo;s challenging economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Web Developer is responsible for the skilled and proficient development of the complete front end user environment of a web site. The candidate must have the technical competency to be able to develop a web
site without constant supervision using a design document, functional templates and graphical representations. In addition, a thorough understanding and experience developing core JavaScript web site functionality and an understanding of Object Oriented Programming is imperative
As a Web Developer, you will work as a member of an engagement team that:
Maintains, modifies and updates client application programs
Prepares and runs test cases
Debugs programs
Completes all documentation
Follows defined processes, methodologies and procedures&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assumes additional responsibilities as assigned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High School Diploma/GED&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge in in HTML, CSS and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English: Intermediate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year experience in in HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year experience in in Mobile CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year experience in in Mobile jQuery and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note Regarding Travel: The IBM Michigan Delivery Center is an in-bound delivery model where we support our clients from our East Lansing, MI center. Some travel is expected and all candidates must be willing and able to travel to meet our client needs. Travel is typically related to knowledge transfer and training at the client site and could be several months up front (Monday thru Friday).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IBM is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, disability, age, or veteran status.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/entry-level-web-developer-ibm-east-lansing-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/entry-level-web-developer-ibm-east-lansing-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer Intern at Platinum Innovation Group in Detroit, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an enthusiastic Web Developer Intern to work with an internationally recognized company that is small, profitable, and fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where? You&amp;rsquo;d be working in our Detroit office in the heart of Greektown with fast-paced, small but wily teams, and you will see and feel the impact of your work on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a great place to start your career as a developer, this is it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Web Developer Intern you&amp;rsquo;ll be&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting with the development of user interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with backend developers to collaboratively design usable APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with developers and operational staff to identify and prioritize end-user requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with designers to ensure an exceptional user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with Lead Architect to ensure proper code development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be a student of a bachelor, master or PHD degree in a relevant educational qualification.  Additional qualifications include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience in HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about pushing the boundaries of interactive technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the latest web authoring tools and latest Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with cross-platform, multi-browser issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be comfortable working in a collaborative environment with Producers, Designers, and other Developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Detroit, Michigan &amp;ndash; in the heart of Greektown!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Platinum Innovation Group&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the Revolution. Work with a company that’s changing the world.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Platinum Innovation Group is a high performance, business incubator powered by innovation and change. We are disruptive by design. We love solving the world’s toughest business challenges. It’s in our DNA to change the world and improve lives through our portfolio of companies. Our global companies and breakthrough innovations are in the areas of telemedicine, health and beauty, the funeral profession, movie studios, real estate, and genealogy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top talent across the world join PlatinumIG for our &amp;ldquo;change the world&amp;rdquo; mentality; the opportunity to excel in a performance-driven, fast-paced, and competitive atmosphere; the chance to be surrounded by peers and leaders that inspire, motivate, and innovate; and a philosophy that weaves community involvement into its fabric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining a profitable, growing, and dynamic company, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Platinum Innovation Group is an Equal Opportunity Employer and does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, disability, veteran status, sexual orientation or any other classification protected by Federal, State or local law.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-intern-platinum-innovation-group-detroit-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-intern-platinum-innovation-group-detroit-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Formcode Design Group in Royal Oak, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We want to add an experienced Developer to our Detroit-based web design team. We build websites and web applications that are not only good-looking, but sophisticated and supremely functional. That and, we’re always looking for new solutions and technologies to help our clients achieve their goals faster. The person we want to hire should have an intimate knowledge of the full web development stack, from how HTTP works to building front-ends in HTML5 and CSS3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;We want someone who is:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smart and creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works efficiently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a willingness to learn and be challenged&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoyable to be around (and work with!!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Specific Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands object-oriented programming principles and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP experience, especially with: Wordpress and CakePHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loves Javascript and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile website development and good knowlege in how to build responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Believes strongly in good design, usability and efficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a painstaking attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doesn’t just want a place to work, but a environment to learn and be challenged&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is enjoyable to be around (and work with!!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired (but not required):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile application development, especially iOS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of non-relational data stores, e.g. MongoDB, Redis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open source contributions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you can create engaging websites/web applications, communicate well with others and meet the criteria of what was just said above &amp;ndash; then we&amp;rsquo;re definitely interested in meeting you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants must be local and willing to work at our Royal Oak MI office location.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-formcode-design-group-royal-oak-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-formcode-design-group-royal-oak-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>