<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mi-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer Intern at Platinum Innovation Group in Detroit, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an enthusiastic Web Developer Intern to work with an internationally recognized company that is small, profitable, and fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where? You&amp;rsquo;d be working in our Detroit office in the heart of Greektown with fast-paced, small but wily teams, and you will see and feel the impact of your work on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a great place to start your career as a developer, this is it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Web Developer Intern you&amp;rsquo;ll be&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting with the development of user interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with backend developers to collaboratively design usable APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with developers and operational staff to identify and prioritize end-user requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with designers to ensure an exceptional user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with Lead Architect to ensure proper code development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be a student of a bachelor, master or PHD degree in a relevant educational qualification.  Additional qualifications include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience in HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience with Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about pushing the boundaries of interactive technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the latest web authoring tools and latest Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with cross-platform, multi-browser issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be comfortable working in a collaborative environment with Producers, Designers, and other Developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Detroit, Michigan &amp;ndash; in the heart of Greektown!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Platinum Innovation Group&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the Revolution. Work with a company that’s changing the world.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Platinum Innovation Group is a high performance, business incubator powered by innovation and change. We are disruptive by design. We love solving the world’s toughest business challenges. It’s in our DNA to change the world and improve lives through our portfolio of companies. Our global companies and breakthrough innovations are in the areas of telemedicine, health and beauty, the funeral profession, movie studios, real estate, and genealogy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top talent across the world join PlatinumIG for our &amp;ldquo;change the world&amp;rdquo; mentality; the opportunity to excel in a performance-driven, fast-paced, and competitive atmosphere; the chance to be surrounded by peers and leaders that inspire, motivate, and innovate; and a philosophy that weaves community involvement into its fabric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining a profitable, growing, and dynamic company, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Platinum Innovation Group is an Equal Opportunity Employer and does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, disability, veteran status, sexual orientation or any other classification protected by Federal, State or local law.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-intern-platinum-innovation-group-detroit-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-intern-platinum-innovation-group-detroit-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Formcode Design Group in Royal Oak, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We want to add an experienced Developer to our Detroit-based web design team. We build websites and web applications that are not only good-looking, but sophisticated and supremely functional. That and, we’re always looking for new solutions and technologies to help our clients achieve their goals faster. The person we want to hire should have an intimate knowledge of the full web development stack, from how HTTP works to building front-ends in HTML5 and CSS3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;We want someone who is:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smart and creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works efficiently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a willingness to learn and be challenged&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoyable to be around (and work with!!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Specific Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands object-oriented programming principles and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP experience, especially with: Wordpress and CakePHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loves Javascript and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile website development and good knowlege in how to build responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Believes strongly in good design, usability and efficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a painstaking attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doesn’t just want a place to work, but a environment to learn and be challenged&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is enjoyable to be around (and work with!!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired (but not required):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile application development, especially iOS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of non-relational data stores, e.g. MongoDB, Redis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open source contributions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you can create engaging websites/web applications, communicate well with others and meet the criteria of what was just said above &amp;ndash; then we&amp;rsquo;re definitely interested in meeting you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants must be local and willing to work at our Royal Oak MI office location.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-formcode-design-group-royal-oak-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-formcode-design-group-royal-oak-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>