<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mi-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS App Developer (Objective C) at Metro Property Group in Dearborn, MI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Invest in Detroit. Metro Property Group is a global real investment firm with an exceptional track record of creating value for their investors. Uniquely positioned as the largest single-family home landlord in Detroit, we are growing and investing in key neighborhoods and key talent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This newly created position will work closely with our Chief Technology Officer creating world-class solutions for our business and the real estate industry at-large. Specific duties will include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;providing utility and functionality for iOS applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;developing new solutions and fixing issues and errors with existing applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;reviewing the Architecture/Design/Code and suggest solutions and improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;finding effective and efficient solutions for application design and architecture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;testing application performance and reporting issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;migrating applications into the production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ensuring applications are properly documented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The successful candidate must have solid expertise with iOS development using iOS SDK and Objective C.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The successful candidate will also have an understanding of performance and platform limitations of mobile devices and mitigation techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 to 5 years prior related experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Apple iOS application guidelines and compliance requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a results orientated self-starter who consistently produces high-quality work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to meet user defined standards and deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to multitask is critical for this full time position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ability to thrive in a fast-paced, professional office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-app-developer-objective-c-metro-property-group-dearborn-mi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-app-developer-objective-c-metro-property-group-dearborn-mi</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>