<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mn-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at LinkUp in Minneapolis, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our job (and yours if you want to join us) is to fix that.  There are lots of jobs out there.  Great jobs.  An amazing variety of jobs.  Jobs from every industry and location in every corner of the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re the fastest-growing job search engine on the web.  We&amp;rsquo;re not in Silicon Valley, not on the East Coast, but right here in Minneapolis! Completely unique to the industry, LinkUp (www.linkup.com) only has jobs found on company websites – no crap listings, scams, or other jobs that pollute the job hunting experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re on a mission to become the best job search engine on the internet and we would like you to help us get there.  We&amp;rsquo;ve got lots of exciting work to do.  You will be a part of a dynamic and fun team.  You will have the opportunity to both work on new projects and perfect existing technology to help us shape the future of job-seeking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;To be successful, you&amp;rsquo;ll need the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree (or equivalent experience) in computer science or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More than 5 years experience programming in multiple modern programming languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge and experience developing sophisticated web applications in PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work competently on all parts of a modern, full-stack LAMP application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An expert understanding of web technologies and protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work collaboratively or independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Someone that would be a great fit:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can juggle a wide variety of tasks, projects, and priorities when needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can go heads-down for extended periods on a large project when needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands the tradeoffs between different software development lifecycle models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has the discipline to use software project tools correctly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a track record of making accurate development estimates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands an array of software design patterns and when each is applicable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully grasps the principles behind object-oriented design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produces high-quality, elegant work from the architecture, to the component, class, and function, down to the line of code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knows the importance of a clean, consistent, documented codebase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can read and understand code written by other people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is equally competent improving an existing system or building from scratch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is comfortable integrating many disparate technological solutions into a coherent whole&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can optimize an applicaiton on multiple levels to increase performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knows what it takes to bring an application to scale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can produce high-quality markup, styles, and scripts on the front-end&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands the value of good SEO and how to achieve it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uses version control religiously and effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is comfortable on the Linux command line&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can effectively gather requirements from all stakeholders and integrate them into a specification, design, prototype, and finished product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands the tradeoffs between time, cost, resources, scope, quality, and risk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is conversant in a majority of the following technologies:  PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, Apache, Gearman, Memcache, Redis, Solr, Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loves being a critical part of a team doing meaningful work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;We offer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive pay and benefits package&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible, comfortable, ergonomic, laid-back, collaborative work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity for scheduled work from home when appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ownership opportunities in a growing company built on a solid foundation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities for advancement and professional development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to a wide array of modern and cutting-edge languages, tools, technologies, and techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;LinkUp is located in Saint Louis Park, MN between Calhoun and West End.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local candidates or candidates willing to relocate only, please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No recruiters, please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-linkup-minneapolis-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-linkup-minneapolis-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Backend Developer at GoKart Labs in Minnesota</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT GOKART LABS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GoKart Labs is in the digital experience business. We invent, design, develop, launch, promote and optimize digital strategies. We create websites, mobile experiences, applications &amp;amp; businesses for our clients&amp;hellip; and for ourselves. We are growing a team of smart, curious, creative and passionate people who “like things that matter.”
Located in the heart of the Minneapolis Warehouse District, GoKart Labs is an agile organization and believes in open innovation and experimentation while applying data &amp;amp; analytics to constantly improve results and make us all better at what we do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT THE JOB:  BACK-END DEVELOPER&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Back-end Developer will work in a creative and highly collaborative environment to develop custom web based applications and APIs.  Using an agile development methodology, you will engage in a ‘Build, Measure &amp;amp; Expand’ strategy allowing GoKart Labs to deliver digital solutions that evolve and grow with our clients, or the businesses we invent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;MINIMUM TECHNICAL REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience as a professional back-end software engineer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience developing custom web applications and APIs in Ruby, with experience using Rails and/or Sinatra.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience extending a variety of existing applications, frameworks and software libraries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leveraging best practices in software development through the use of proper design patterns, integration/unit testing, security, version control, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;TECHNICAL NICE-TO-HAVE&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience or motivation to learn other open-source technologies, platforms, languages and frameworks (eg. RubyMotion, mongoDB, node.js, PHP, WordPress, Laravel, Heroku, New Relic, capistrano, git)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience / understanding of data modeling best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;CORE BUSINESS EXPECTATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage project deliverables and due dates assuring on-time, high-quality software for our clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with project participants to define and refine requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently meet established deadlines through proper organization and follow up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balance discipline and structure with the necessary flexibility of an emerging company environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT YOUR BACKGROUND&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree in Computer Science, Mathematics or a related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional software development experience working in a team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT THE STRUCTURE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll report to the Director of Technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll work closely with other developers (back-end, front-end, and mobile), group leaders and other employees across the company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;WHAT YOU CAN EXPECT FROM US&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our commitment to your success is enhanced by our competitive compensation and benefits package including paid time off, medical, dental, 401K, profit sharing, metro bus pass, and future growth opportunities within the company.
We work hard to maintain the best possible environment for our employees, where people can learn and grow with the company. We strive to provide a fun, creative environment where everyone feels encouraged to contribute to our processes, decisions, planning and culture. To learn more about us, please visit: www.gokartlabs.com
GoKart Labs is an equal opportunity employer. © 2013 GoKart Labs&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/backend-developer-gokart-labs-minnesota</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/backend-developer-gokart-labs-minnesota</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>