<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mn-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Service Designer at Mayo Clinic in Rochester, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a member of the Center for Innovation, the Service Designer consults internally with the departments, divisions and committees across the clinic looking to innovate the delivery of Mayo&amp;rsquo;s health care services. The Service Designer uses the human-centered and participatory methods of Design to identify unmet patient, provider and institutional needs and creates new service concepts or business strategies to better meet those needs. These methods include: conducting observational research, interviews and workshops; undertaking internal and external research activities; generating conceptual frameworks and formulating insights related to the synthesis of the research data; communicating findings and concepts to project sponsors in a clear and compelling visual manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most projects will be cross-functional in nature, involving split or shared responsibility and problem solving with disciplines and personnel from other areas. The designer is an integral team member who works both independently and collaboratively through each phase of the project with other designers and project participants. Projects assigned to a Service Designer are typically significant and broad in scope, covering major business enhancements. The typical project duration is 12 to 24 months and entails project teams of approximately 10 to 50 members that may be across campus locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Service Designer has joint responsibility for the planning and execution of major complex business critical projects. Ensures project goals are well-defined and aligned with business objectives Ensures project goals are achieved and identifies tasks required to meet project goals. May direct other project team members, including project managers, lab coordinators and other design researchers (including interns &amp;amp; co-ops) assigned to the project. Regularly provides accurate and up-to-date project status information to project stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to direct project responsibilities, the Service Designer is required to support the development, establishment and maturation of the design research methodology &amp;amp; infrastructure within their assigned work area; developing templates, promoting best practices, developing and/or procuring tools, and educating and mentoring team members and other project managers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in interaction, communication or industrial design, environmental design, service design or a related field and 8 years of experience managing design projects &amp;amp; teams OR Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in interaction, communication or industrial design, environmental design, service design or a related and 10 years experience. Demonstrated knowledge of design research tools and methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Must develop and maintain an understanding of major operating systems and overall policies, procedures and objectives of the institution. Excellent interpersonal skills to include presentation, negotiation, persuasion, team facilitation and written communications skills are required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates must have a personal plan for professional development to maintain and update his/her skills, methods and tools. This plan should be aligned with the needs of the individual, the division and the strategic plan for Mayo Clinic. Designer must have ability to independently manage a varied workload of projects with multiple priorities. Must be able to prioritize work that is assigned by the Section Head or requested by a customer through brief outline of the nature of the problem and the overall urgency. Must be capable of consulting, designing/conducting studies, and developing/implementing solutions (problems involve analytical and creative elements) for issues with significant financial and operational impact to the organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incumbent&amp;rsquo;s recommendations may strongly impact clinical and administrative operations and may result in the institution incurring significant expense for the purchase of new equipment/software, hiring of additional personnel, or remodeling/designing facilities. As the work is complicated by an environment of multiple projects having high priority and resistance to change; strong time management skills and sound judgment are required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience Detail:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing research briefs, and writing research protocolsExperience scoping, planning &amp;amp; conducting research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience collecting research data. Experience determining research metrics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience recruiting research subjects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative problem solving skills A curious mind and an enthusiastic work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in design planning and design research methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for enriching the design process with meaningful research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort with ambiguity and complex problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively with a wide variety of professionals/disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated project management ability with an ability to lead complex projects effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to make rough interactive prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash and/or Dreamweaver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to articulate the meaning of your work to colleagues and clients through formal and informal presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves as a mentor for new employees, interns, and trainees In-depth understanding of core institutional processes, clinical practices, and support areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works similar to an independent consultant with own set of clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation Detail:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exempt = Salaried &amp;ndash; Education, experience, and tenure may be considered along with internal equity when job offers are extended. The minimum salary every two weeks is approximately $3280, based on a full-time position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Staffing Specialist:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pauline Ptacek Raiche&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Company Statement:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mayo Clinic offers a wealth of job opportunities, but most essentially, it offers the chance to make a difference by helping others. Employees are mentored in Mayo&amp;rsquo;s culture and our model of care, which values mutual respect, integrity, personal responsibility, innovation and communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mayo Clinic is an affirmative action / equal opportunity educator and employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/service-designer-mayo-clinic-rochester-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/service-designer-mayo-clinic-rochester-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic / Web Designer at TVI Designs in Chanhassen, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;From uniforms and apparel to enterprise recognition systems, Business Impact Group is a proven organization of brand product development using expert tools and techniques to recognize employees and celebrate customers. We strive every day to design, create and provide the very best products and recognition systems for our clients brand and business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are marketing and ad agencies that buy TV time and billboard space, but we know the real media impressions for our clients brand are everywhere else: on the street, the shop floors and on desks across the country and the world.   So think of BIG as an agency; just without the ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;BIG Careers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking growing exponentially and are looking for exceptional talent to join our teams.  BIG offers a collaborative, fast-paced entrepreneurial environment.  The ideal candidates will be flexible and adaptable to change.  Because we are a growing organization, we are looking for those who possess the entrepreneurial spirit; willing to work hard, embrace innovation and change, big picture thinkers, who can also focus on the details.  BIG offers a casual/business casual dress code, competitive compensation including nine paid holidays, flexible PTO, medical, dental, vision, 401k and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Browse our open positions and if you feel there is a potential match to your experience and skills, please apply.  Our recruiters will review your resume and reach out to you regarding your candidate status.   If you are not a fit for a current opening, please be sure to check back often as we are adding new positions frequently.  Thank you for your interest in BIG!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a creative forward-thinking individual to join our creative design team. This person will need to be flexible and adaptable to constant change.  The Graphic/Web Designer will be able to handle multiple projects simultaneously and within tight time constraints. The ideal candidate will be well-rounded with an ability to learn quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preferred candidates will be highly motivated self-starters with a passion for web design and incredible creativity. Strong technical skills with experience in multiple design applications is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The position will require a professional and polished person who is confident and able to be client facing. This role will interact with project managers, vaious organizational departments and client developers, and company stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exceptional design skills and attention to detail are a must. You will be responsible for the design, styling, implementation, content maintenance, configuration, and quality testing of externally facing projects. This position will entail supplying graphic services and technical demo website configurations to support pre and post sale client needs.  The Graphic/Web Designer will also use his/her creative skills and technical know-how to design marketing collateral including extensive PowerPoint presentations.  Candidate must enjoy a fast-paced, multi-tasking, customer service oriented environment. This role requires a strong communicator, who is organized, and understands the importance of quality and team work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Graphic/Web Designer for the eCommerce and Recognition Departments, you will take on a full-time regular position on-site and will be responsible for implementation of improvements and enhancements to graphic design and web design projects. You will be balancing multiple development projects and working with cross functional teams who are technically diverse, high performing, and collaborative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications: Required&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree or technical degree in Graphic / Web Design, Marketing or related field and/or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of Graphic Design and Web Wesign experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML4 (HTML5 highly desired), JavaScript (Advanced JavaScript highly desired), Flash, and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe CS 5.5 Suite, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, and related graphic programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate to Advanced proficiency with Microsoft Office; Word, PowerPoint, Outlook&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications: Desired&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with e-commerce platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B2B marketing experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating with enterprise systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL and database concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dreamweaver experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can-Do attitude with a strong work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong determination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work without a lot of supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong desire to learn and gain new skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with purchased software packages (ERP a plus) and custom developed software applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates will be required to take a skills assessment pre-hire.  You will also be requested to provide a design portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business Impact Group is an EEO employer.  All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines. NOTE: This job description is not all-inclusive.  Additional duties will be assigned according to business needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;NOTICE TO 3rd PARTY RECRUITERS AND AGENCIES:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business Impact Group does not accept solicitations from 3rd party recruiters or agencies.  All unsolicited resumes submitted either through the ATS or directly will become the property of BIG and no fee will be paid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-tvi-designs-chanhassen-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-tvi-designs-chanhassen-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Lead User Experience Designer at Honeywell in Minneapolis, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Honeywell Automation and Control Solutions (ACS), we bring comfort, safety and security to millions of people all over the world.  Come join us and make a difference in their lives.  We’re building a new Global Experience Design (GExD) studio to create our next generation of products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking talented senior/lead user experience designers to create simply amazing experiences for our customers.  We take a human-centered design approach to create a holistic, end-to-end user experience.  We work on a wide variety of products, domains and applications to keep you engaged, challenged and learning. For example,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We conduct ethnographic studies to understand consumers’ unmet needs for home comfort and security, and apply these insights as we develop products and associated Apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We conduct ergonomic studies to inform the design of our safety harnesses and fire fighting gear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We collaborate with operators at major shipping terminals to design control systems for greater security and safety.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We partner with our ePresence team to create a branded, seamless experience on our customer portals and channel websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We ride along with delivery drivers to observe them using packaging scanners, before totally redesigning their mobile scanner. We then go back with appearance models and user interface prototypes to gain feedback as part of our iterative design process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This is the newly created Global Experience Design Studio in Minneapolis, Minnesota. It is a unique opportunity to come build a world-class experience design group at a Fortune 100 company. Come to Honeywell and do that thing you do so well in a fast-paced, supportive environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a top candidate, you will lead user experience design (UXD) initiatives on ACS products globally. You will contribute directly to creating the next generation of user experiences on a wide variety of consumer, commercial, medical and industrial products. GExD delivers an end-to-end user experience across every user touch point.  We use well established human-centered design principles to ensure that Honeywell products and applications are the most useful, usable and desirable products in the marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honeywell International is a leading $34 billion diversified technology corporation with a wide range of businesses including automation and control solutions, aerospace systems, transportation systems, and performance materials. ACS is a $14 billion Strategic Business Group within Honeywell International. ACS is a business fueled by technology innovation, and a leader in a variety of high growth markets, including energy efficiency, smart grid, security, safety products, scanning and mobility, process solutions, and sensing and controls technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position reports directly to the North American User Experience Design Manager, Global Experience Design.  You will be responsible for leading UXD on major ACS projects (home thermostats, security and fire systems, building management systems, mobile scanners) and systems. You will have the opportunity to work with our portfolio of brands to create differentiated brand design languages, work across seven strategic business units on a variety of applications, and collaborate globally with GExD peers and strategic design partners.  You will work with other functional designers in an interdisciplinary studio to create the framework and best practices for a world-class design studios in four international cities.  Together, we will create design strategies, develop advanced design concepts and deliver outstanding products to market that delight our end users. The variety of our businesses and applications will challenge your creative talents and our global footprint will expose you to diverse cultures and developing markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What You Will Be Responsible for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading UXD on major ACS projects, working with other GExD designers across the ACS businesses and collaborating with external design partners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing a clear, consistent voice on end-to-end user experience design to project teams and stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating and executing user-centered designs for products and services that differentiate our brands in the marketplace around the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executing UXD best practices throughout the product development process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with other GExD disciplines, including graphic design, interaction design, and usability specialists in nurturing a world-class organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Model Honeywell core values and behaviors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;As a Senior/Lead User Experience Designer, you will need to have the following talents, skills and experiences:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in UXD best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio of applying user-centered design practices in product development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience; successfully scoping, planning and executing projects in accordance with a phases and gates development process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience leading, developing and managing significant user experience design projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in understanding and synthesizing user needs using a variety of practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in design strategy, trends and how they apply to brand and product planning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating products using: design trends, heuristic reviews, competitive benchmarking, formative and summative usability studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable talent in developing industry-leading user interface designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating low-fidelity to high-fidelity user interface models and prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International experience working with regional businesses and design teams is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In this position, you will collaborate with project teams, both on site and distributed globally. People who are successful in our environment have highly collaborative skills with an ability to communicate effectively at multiple levels in multidisciplinary teams.  As a top candidate, you will have the ability to drive user-centered design consensus on your projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have an informal collegial work environment. We value our people greatly, and enable them to deliver achievable results against clear objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minneapolis is one of our nation&amp;rsquo;s most livable cities with a sophisticated cultural scene, great dining and entertainment. It has a vibrant city and bucolic suburban living atmosphere, easy commuting, and great schools and universities and healthcare. Housing is affordable and commuting times very acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This key new position includes relocation benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in human factors, psychology, user experience design or related degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years of experience in human factors  /  user experience design of products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding user experience design portfolio or concepts and commercialized products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation, and negotiation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent collaboration and teamwork attitude.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient interaction design skills, e.g., information architecture, workflows, wireframes, UI behaviors and patterns documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent with interaction design sketching and prototyping tools, e.g., Visio, Balsamiq, Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with design trends, benchmarking, forecasting and concept creation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with project planning, scoping and execution in a phase-gate environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graduate degree user experience design, human factors, interaction design or related discipline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To apply for this position, please go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.careersathoneywell.com/&quot;&gt;http://www.careersathoneywell.com/&lt;/a&gt; and enter requisition 216088..  You may also contact Judy Karasch directly at judy.karasch@honeywell.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an Equal Opportunity Employer, Honeywell is committed to a diverse workforce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-lead-user-experience-designer-honeywell-minneapolis-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-lead-user-experience-designer-honeywell-minneapolis-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic / Web Designer at BiG in Chanhassen, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;COMPANY DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From uniforms and apparel to enterprise recognition systems, Business Impact Group is a proven organization of brand product development using expert tools and techniques to recognize employees and celebrate customers. We strive every day to design, create and provide the very best products and recognition systems for our clients brand and business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are marketing and ad agencies that buy TV time and billboard space, but we know the real media impressions for our clients brand are everywhere else: on the street, the shop floors and on desks across the country and the world.   So think of BIG as an agency; just without the ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;BIG Careers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking growing exponentially and are looking for exceptional talent to join our teams.  BIG offers a collaborative, fast-paced entrepreneurial environment.  The ideal candidates will be flexible and adaptable to change.  Because we are a growing organization, we are looking for those who possess the entrepreneurial spirit; willing to work hard, embrace innovation and change, big picture thinkers, who can also focus on the details.  BIG offers a casual/business casual dress code, competitive compensation including nine paid holidays, flexible PTO, medical, dental, vision, 401k and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Browse our open positions and if you feel there is a potential match to your experience and skills, please apply.  Our recruiters will review your resume and reach out to you regarding your candidate status.   If you are not a fit for a current opening, please be sure to check back often as we are adding new positions frequently.  Thank you for your interest in BIG!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a creative forward-thinking individual to join our creative design team. This person will need to be flexible and adaptable to constant change.  The Graphic/Web Designer will be able to handle multiple projects simultaneously and within tight time constraints. The ideal candidate will be well-rounded with an ability to learn quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preferred candidates will be highly motivated self-starters with a passion for web design and incredible creativity. Strong technical skills with experience in multiple design applications is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The position will require a professional and polished person who is confident and able to be client facing. This role will interact with project managers, vaious organizational departments and client developers, and company stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exceptional design skills and attention to detail are a must. You will be responsible for the design, styling, implementation, content maintenance, configuration, and quality testing of externally facing projects. This position will entail supplying graphic services and technical demo website configurations to support pre and post sale client needs.  The Graphic/Web Designer will also use his/her creative skills and technical know-how to design marketing collateral including extensive PowerPoint presentations.  Candidate must enjoy a fast-paced, multi-tasking, customer service oriented environment. This role requires a strong communicator, who is organized, and understands the importance of quality and team work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Graphic/Web Designer for the eCommerce and Recognition Departments, you will take on a full-time regular position on-site and will be responsible for implementation of improvements and enhancements to graphic design and web design projects. You will be balancing multiple development projects and working with cross functional teams who are technically diverse, high performing, and collaborative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications: Required&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree or technical degree in Graphic / Web Design, Marketing or related field and/or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of Graphic Design and Web Wesign experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML4 (HTML5 highly desired), JavaScript (Advanced JavaScript highly desired), Flash, and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe CS 5.5 Suite, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, and related graphic programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate to Advanced proficiency with Microsoft Office; Word, PowerPoint, Outlook&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications: Desired&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with e-commerce platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B2B marketing experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating with enterprise systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL and database concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dreamweaver experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can-Do attitude with a strong work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong determination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work without a lot of supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong desire to learn and gain new skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with purchased software packages (ERP a plus) and custom developed software applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates will be required to take a skills assessment pre-hire.  You will also be requested to provide a design portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business Impact Group is an EEO employer.  All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines. NOTE: This job description is not all-inclusive.  Additional duties will be assigned according to business needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;NOTICE TO 3rd PARTY RECRUITERS AND AGENCIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business Impact Group does not accept solicitations from 3rd party recruiters or agencies.  All unsolicited resumes submitted either through the ATS or directly will become the property of BIG and no fee will be paid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-big-chanhassen-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-big-chanhassen-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Multimedia Designer at ShopNBC.com in Eden Prairie, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ShopNBC.com, the e-commerce arm of ShopNBC is looking for an extremely talented mid-level multimedia designer to support our consumer-oriented web stores. This person will be called on to design and create compelling designs for e-mail and web banner campaigns in a very fast paced, ever changing environment. Our website changes every day and so will the creative work this person produces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll do&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified candidates will be required to provide a portfolio showing previous concept-driven design work; proving proficiency in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Flash and knowledge of web development including HTML and CSS, Microsoft Office is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position requires a creative and artistic person who is motivated, detail-oriented and a willing contributor to a successful team. Must be able to juggle multiple projects simultaneously and meet productivity expectations while working closely with other designers and copywriters to produce a best in class solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Duties are varied, with room for growth. Your design skills will be applied to in-house materials for the ShopNBC.com website. Tasks include but are not limited to: banners, email communications, external partner site banners including affiliate ad banners and advertisements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits &amp;ndash; What you&amp;rsquo;ll get&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) match, Health, Dental, Vision, Life insurance, Paid Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team member discount&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual and quarterly recognition program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online team member auction every weekend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear growth opportunities within the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Career Path&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sr Multimedia Designer &amp;ndash;&gt; Interactive Art Director &amp;ndash;&gt; Creative Services Manager&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of experience required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with design software: Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash and Dreamweaver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehension of: HTML, CSS, Actionscript a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good sense of graphic composition and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly execute concepts under tight timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the creative process in a collaborative environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/multimedia-designer-shopnbc-com-eden-prairie-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/multimedia-designer-shopnbc-com-eden-prairie-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UX Designer at Digital River, Inc. in Minnetonka, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Digital River, founded in 1994, is a global leader in cloud commerce outsourcing that builds and manages online businesses for more than 40,000 software publishers, manufacturers, distributors, and online retailers. Its multi-channel commerce solution, which supports both direct and indirect sales, is designed to help companies of all sizes maximize online revenues as well as reduce the costs and risks of running a commerce operation. The comprehensive platform offers site development and hosting, order management, fraud prevention, export controls, tax management, physical and digital product fulfillment, multilingual customer service, advanced reporting and strategic marketing services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a publicly traded company (NASDAQ: DRIV) headquartered in Minneapolis, Minnesota, with offices and more than 1400 employees located across the United States, Europe and the Asia Pacific.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provide high-level and detailed interaction design documents (wireframes, UI specs, workflow diagrams, interactive prototypes) to product development teams working on a complex ecommerce web software application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather use cases and business requirements from product managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create solutions to difficult and complex design and product issues with little to no direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present and advocate for your solutions while educating the product team about the importance of usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure development teams adhere to the user interface requirements and pattern library.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with and mentor other UX designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the extensive user interface pattern library that we utilize regularly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct contextual inquiries, stakeholder interviews, and user research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have strong skills in user interface and page design and a solid background in information architecture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have 5+ years of experience in user experience design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy solving complex, multi-dimensional usability issues; are able to focus on form and function as well as look and feel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can roll with the punches without losing your passion to do great work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are able to rapidly design and prototype using Axure, Illustrator, Visio, and/or Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a portfolio of successful application solutions and interactive engagements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can articulate problems and solutions unique to your project work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are not afraid to influence product strategy and direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Agile methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to produce visual designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of JavaScript, CSS, XHTML, and jQuery for building of prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Digital River, Inc. offers a variety of perks such as an on-site fitness center, on-site full-service cafeteria, free on-site parking, casual dress every day, tuition reimbursement, employee referral program, domestic partner benefits, auto and homeowners discounts, on-site massage therapists and chiropractors, bring your dog to work day, pet insurance and all in a beautiful, Leed-certified, state-of-the-art building with scenic walking trails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Standard benefits include a competitive benefits package to all regular, full-time employees, a 401(k) plan with an aggressive company match, employee stock purchase plan, medical-dental-vision and life insurance, company paid short-term and long-term disability, a flexible spending/cafeteria plan, holiday and vacation days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital River, Inc. supports and embraces a diverse workforce as an Equal Employment Opportunity /Affirmative Action employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-digital-river-inc-minnetonka-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-digital-river-inc-minnetonka-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>