<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mn-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Multimedia Designer at ShopNBC.com in Eden Prairie, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ShopNBC.com, the e-commerce arm of ShopNBC is looking for an extremely talented mid-level multimedia designer to support our consumer-oriented web stores. This person will be called on to design and create compelling designs for e-mail and web banner campaigns in a very fast paced, ever changing environment. Our website changes every day and so will the creative work this person produces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll do&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified candidates will be required to provide a portfolio showing previous concept-driven design work; proving proficiency in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Flash and knowledge of web development including HTML and CSS, Microsoft Office is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position requires a creative and artistic person who is motivated, detail-oriented and a willing contributor to a successful team. Must be able to juggle multiple projects simultaneously and meet productivity expectations while working closely with other designers and copywriters to produce a best in class solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Duties are varied, with room for growth. Your design skills will be applied to in-house materials for the ShopNBC.com website. Tasks include but are not limited to: banners, email communications, external partner site banners including affiliate ad banners and advertisements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits &amp;ndash; What you&amp;rsquo;ll get&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) match, Health, Dental, Vision, Life insurance, Paid Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team member discount&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual and quarterly recognition program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online team member auction every weekend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear growth opportunities within the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Career Path&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sr Multimedia Designer &amp;ndash;&gt; Interactive Art Director &amp;ndash;&gt; Creative Services Manager&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of experience required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with design software: Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash and Dreamweaver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehension of: HTML, CSS, Actionscript a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good sense of graphic composition and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly execute concepts under tight timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the creative process in a collaborative environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/multimedia-designer-shopnbc-com-eden-prairie-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/multimedia-designer-shopnbc-com-eden-prairie-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UX Designer at Digital River, Inc. in Minnetonka, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Digital River, founded in 1994, is a global leader in cloud commerce outsourcing that builds and manages online businesses for more than 40,000 software publishers, manufacturers, distributors, and online retailers. Its multi-channel commerce solution, which supports both direct and indirect sales, is designed to help companies of all sizes maximize online revenues as well as reduce the costs and risks of running a commerce operation. The comprehensive platform offers site development and hosting, order management, fraud prevention, export controls, tax management, physical and digital product fulfillment, multilingual customer service, advanced reporting and strategic marketing services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a publicly traded company (NASDAQ: DRIV) headquartered in Minneapolis, Minnesota, with offices and more than 1400 employees located across the United States, Europe and the Asia Pacific.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provide high-level and detailed interaction design documents (wireframes, UI specs, workflow diagrams, interactive prototypes) to product development teams working on a complex ecommerce web software application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather use cases and business requirements from product managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create solutions to difficult and complex design and product issues with little to no direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present and advocate for your solutions while educating the product team about the importance of usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure development teams adhere to the user interface requirements and pattern library.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with and mentor other UX designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the extensive user interface pattern library that we utilize regularly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct contextual inquiries, stakeholder interviews, and user research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have strong skills in user interface and page design and a solid background in information architecture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have 5+ years of experience in user experience design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy solving complex, multi-dimensional usability issues; are able to focus on form and function as well as look and feel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can roll with the punches without losing your passion to do great work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are able to rapidly design and prototype using Axure, Illustrator, Visio, and/or Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a portfolio of successful application solutions and interactive engagements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can articulate problems and solutions unique to your project work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are not afraid to influence product strategy and direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Agile methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to produce visual designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of JavaScript, CSS, XHTML, and jQuery for building of prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Digital River, Inc. offers a variety of perks such as an on-site fitness center, on-site full-service cafeteria, free on-site parking, casual dress every day, tuition reimbursement, employee referral program, domestic partner benefits, auto and homeowners discounts, on-site massage therapists and chiropractors, bring your dog to work day, pet insurance and all in a beautiful, Leed-certified, state-of-the-art building with scenic walking trails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Standard benefits include a competitive benefits package to all regular, full-time employees, a 401(k) plan with an aggressive company match, employee stock purchase plan, medical-dental-vision and life insurance, company paid short-term and long-term disability, a flexible spending/cafeteria plan, holiday and vacation days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital River, Inc. supports and embraces a diverse workforce as an Equal Employment Opportunity /Affirmative Action employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-digital-river-inc-minnetonka-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-digital-river-inc-minnetonka-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>