<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mn-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic / Web Designer at BiG in Chanhassen, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;COMPANY DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From uniforms and apparel to enterprise recognition systems, Business Impact Group is a proven organization of brand product development using expert tools and techniques to recognize employees and celebrate customers. We strive every day to design, create and provide the very best products and recognition systems for our clients brand and business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are marketing and ad agencies that buy TV time and billboard space, but we know the real media impressions for our clients brand are everywhere else: on the street, the shop floors and on desks across the country and the world.   So think of BIG as an agency; just without the ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;BIG Careers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking growing exponentially and are looking for exceptional talent to join our teams.  BIG offers a collaborative, fast-paced entrepreneurial environment.  The ideal candidates will be flexible and adaptable to change.  Because we are a growing organization, we are looking for those who possess the entrepreneurial spirit; willing to work hard, embrace innovation and change, big picture thinkers, who can also focus on the details.  BIG offers a casual/business casual dress code, competitive compensation including nine paid holidays, flexible PTO, medical, dental, vision, 401k and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Browse our open positions and if you feel there is a potential match to your experience and skills, please apply.  Our recruiters will review your resume and reach out to you regarding your candidate status.   If you are not a fit for a current opening, please be sure to check back often as we are adding new positions frequently.  Thank you for your interest in BIG!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently looking for a creative forward-thinking individual to join our creative design team. This person will need to be flexible and adaptable to constant change.  The Graphic/Web Designer will be able to handle multiple projects simultaneously and within tight time constraints. The ideal candidate will be well-rounded with an ability to learn quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preferred candidates will be highly motivated self-starters with a passion for web design and incredible creativity. Strong technical skills with experience in multiple design applications is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The position will require a professional and polished person who is confident and able to be client facing. This role will interact with project managers, vaious organizational departments and client developers, and company stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exceptional design skills and attention to detail are a must. You will be responsible for the design, styling, implementation, content maintenance, configuration, and quality testing of externally facing projects. This position will entail supplying graphic services and technical demo website configurations to support pre and post sale client needs.  The Graphic/Web Designer will also use his/her creative skills and technical know-how to design marketing collateral including extensive PowerPoint presentations.  Candidate must enjoy a fast-paced, multi-tasking, customer service oriented environment. This role requires a strong communicator, who is organized, and understands the importance of quality and team work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Graphic/Web Designer for the eCommerce and Recognition Departments, you will take on a full-time regular position on-site and will be responsible for implementation of improvements and enhancements to graphic design and web design projects. You will be balancing multiple development projects and working with cross functional teams who are technically diverse, high performing, and collaborative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications: Required&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree or technical degree in Graphic / Web Design, Marketing or related field and/or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of Graphic Design and Web Wesign experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML4 (HTML5 highly desired), JavaScript (Advanced JavaScript highly desired), Flash, and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe CS 5.5 Suite, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, and related graphic programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate to Advanced proficiency with Microsoft Office; Word, PowerPoint, Outlook&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications: Desired&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with e-commerce platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B2B marketing experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating with enterprise systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL and database concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dreamweaver experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can-Do attitude with a strong work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong determination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work without a lot of supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong desire to learn and gain new skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with purchased software packages (ERP a plus) and custom developed software applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates will be required to take a skills assessment pre-hire.  You will also be requested to provide a design portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business Impact Group is an EEO employer.  All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines. NOTE: This job description is not all-inclusive.  Additional duties will be assigned according to business needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;NOTICE TO 3rd PARTY RECRUITERS AND AGENCIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business Impact Group does not accept solicitations from 3rd party recruiters or agencies.  All unsolicited resumes submitted either through the ATS or directly will become the property of BIG and no fee will be paid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-big-chanhassen-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-big-chanhassen-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Multimedia Designer at ShopNBC.com in Eden Prairie, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ShopNBC.com, the e-commerce arm of ShopNBC is looking for an extremely talented mid-level multimedia designer to support our consumer-oriented web stores. This person will be called on to design and create compelling designs for e-mail and web banner campaigns in a very fast paced, ever changing environment. Our website changes every day and so will the creative work this person produces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll do&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified candidates will be required to provide a portfolio showing previous concept-driven design work; proving proficiency in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Flash and knowledge of web development including HTML and CSS, Microsoft Office is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position requires a creative and artistic person who is motivated, detail-oriented and a willing contributor to a successful team. Must be able to juggle multiple projects simultaneously and meet productivity expectations while working closely with other designers and copywriters to produce a best in class solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Duties are varied, with room for growth. Your design skills will be applied to in-house materials for the ShopNBC.com website. Tasks include but are not limited to: banners, email communications, external partner site banners including affiliate ad banners and advertisements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits &amp;ndash; What you&amp;rsquo;ll get&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) match, Health, Dental, Vision, Life insurance, Paid Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team member discount&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual and quarterly recognition program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online team member auction every weekend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear growth opportunities within the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Career Path&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sr Multimedia Designer &amp;ndash;&gt; Interactive Art Director &amp;ndash;&gt; Creative Services Manager&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of experience required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with design software: Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash and Dreamweaver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehension of: HTML, CSS, Actionscript a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good sense of graphic composition and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly execute concepts under tight timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the creative process in a collaborative environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/multimedia-designer-shopnbc-com-eden-prairie-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/multimedia-designer-shopnbc-com-eden-prairie-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UX Designer at Digital River, Inc. in Minnetonka, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Digital River, founded in 1994, is a global leader in cloud commerce outsourcing that builds and manages online businesses for more than 40,000 software publishers, manufacturers, distributors, and online retailers. Its multi-channel commerce solution, which supports both direct and indirect sales, is designed to help companies of all sizes maximize online revenues as well as reduce the costs and risks of running a commerce operation. The comprehensive platform offers site development and hosting, order management, fraud prevention, export controls, tax management, physical and digital product fulfillment, multilingual customer service, advanced reporting and strategic marketing services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a publicly traded company (NASDAQ: DRIV) headquartered in Minneapolis, Minnesota, with offices and more than 1400 employees located across the United States, Europe and the Asia Pacific.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provide high-level and detailed interaction design documents (wireframes, UI specs, workflow diagrams, interactive prototypes) to product development teams working on a complex ecommerce web software application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather use cases and business requirements from product managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create solutions to difficult and complex design and product issues with little to no direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present and advocate for your solutions while educating the product team about the importance of usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure development teams adhere to the user interface requirements and pattern library.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with and mentor other UX designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the extensive user interface pattern library that we utilize regularly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct contextual inquiries, stakeholder interviews, and user research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have strong skills in user interface and page design and a solid background in information architecture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have 5+ years of experience in user experience design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy solving complex, multi-dimensional usability issues; are able to focus on form and function as well as look and feel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can roll with the punches without losing your passion to do great work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are able to rapidly design and prototype using Axure, Illustrator, Visio, and/or Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a portfolio of successful application solutions and interactive engagements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can articulate problems and solutions unique to your project work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are not afraid to influence product strategy and direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Agile methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to produce visual designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of JavaScript, CSS, XHTML, and jQuery for building of prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Digital River, Inc. offers a variety of perks such as an on-site fitness center, on-site full-service cafeteria, free on-site parking, casual dress every day, tuition reimbursement, employee referral program, domestic partner benefits, auto and homeowners discounts, on-site massage therapists and chiropractors, bring your dog to work day, pet insurance and all in a beautiful, Leed-certified, state-of-the-art building with scenic walking trails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Standard benefits include a competitive benefits package to all regular, full-time employees, a 401(k) plan with an aggressive company match, employee stock purchase plan, medical-dental-vision and life insurance, company paid short-term and long-term disability, a flexible spending/cafeteria plan, holiday and vacation days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital River, Inc. supports and embraces a diverse workforce as an Equal Employment Opportunity /Affirmative Action employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-digital-river-inc-minnetonka-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-digital-river-inc-minnetonka-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>