<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mn-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Creative Director at Best Buy in Richfield, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As an Associate Creative Director you will be part of the larger User Experience team responsible for creating the differentiated BestBuy.com user experience. The User Experience team is responsible for translating user and business needs into meaningful interactive experiences. The User Experience team partners with other digital teams within Best Buy to create seamless customer centric experiences that meet the needs and expectations of our customers based on where they are in their product purchase process or service experience with BestBuy.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Design team responsibilities within UX range from large-scale system and application development, to incremental site enhancements, to creation and support of communication campaigns around events and promotions. As an Associate Creative Director you will be working within a team of designers, writers, and information architects. The primary focus of the Associate Creative Director will be leading and directing the design team through thecreative process to best meet the evolving needs of our business partners, technology capabilities, and customer expectations. The ability to delegate, review, present, and administrate the necessary work streams within each project is critical to the Associate Creative Director role. The ACD will be responsible for identifying, sourcing, and assigning resources appropriate to staff projects. The project teams may be comprised of internal staff members, external agency or consultative resources, or both based on the needs of the project. As creative team lead the ACD is responsible for reviewing creative work to ensure that it is on-brand, solves for the marketing strategy needs at-hand, and covers a wide range of creative exploration. The ACD is also responsible for evolving the quality of the work product produced while expanding the capabilities of the design team. As an ACD your previous professional experience will be foundational to allow you to continuously develop a point of view on project deliverables, research methods, and web design best practices based on the needs and opportunities for the User Experience team at Best Buy. Your point of view will help shape and define the creation of new templates, features, and functions to evolve, enhance, and differentiate the Best Buy dotcom user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Graphic Design, MultiMedia, Information Architecture, Communication, Marketing, Journalism, Human Computer Interaction, Instructional or Graphic Design, related field or equivalent experience. or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years experience in strategic and conceptual creative development across multiple technology solutions. Proven creative ability required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years of e-Commerce UX experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years project and creative team management experience across multiple media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years experience building collaborative creative teams of designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years experience incorporating UX strategies, interactive design specifications, design models/prototypes and QA processes/use cases into the plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-creative-director-best-buy-richfield-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-creative-director-best-buy-richfield-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Life Time Fitness in Chanhassen, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provides full-service creative solutions to the Life Time Fitness organization. Upholds the fulfillment of the Life Time Fitness Mission Statement and 3E &amp;ndash; The Life Time Agency&amp;rsquo;s (3) three core competencies;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative Excellence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive Client Relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Great Culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Examples of Work Performed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates, designs, and supervises the production of marketing for communications to both internal and external customers (print, web, and interactive) translating marketing objectives into creative strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with team members, business units and external agency partners to translate user needs and business goals into actionable design strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Realizes the design strategy through mood and storyboard concepts to establish the visual design approach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverages the capabilities of Rich Internet Applications and other technologies to create intuitive and elegant user interactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs new and creative approaches to visualize data and present information that facilitates customer understanding and engagement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops experience style guides, including sustainable and maintainable visual design languages, interaction patterns, and design standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Articulates a graphic vision for the organization&amp;rsquo;s brand and create standards to support it based on market research and consumer insights data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with product line, loyalty and digital marketing team to make sure visual design communicates and functions successfully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interacts and networks with external professional organizations to remain current on new technology, software, trends and channels that LTF or its competitors may use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivers high quality work consistently and on deadline, while meeting business objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with the Creative team and external agency partners to develop communications that establish the LTF brand, creating concepts and visuals based on customer insights that drive engagement and lead to increases in acquisition and loyalty.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four-year degree in Communications, Visual Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three+ years in Creative communications or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agency Experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Licenses / Certifications / Registration:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills, Abilities and Other Characteristic&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi* task and learn quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent customer service skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle and resolve customer conflicts in a professional, tactful manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to build relationships with members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to operate a personal computer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of standard office procedures and computer software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to effectively multi* task with tight deadlines independently and within a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to define problems, collect and analyze data, establish facts, draw valid conclusions and recommend solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of all Adobe design software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-life-time-fitness-chanhassen-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-life-time-fitness-chanhassen-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Project Specialist at National Marrow Donor Program in Minneapolis, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Project Specialist &amp;ndash; Interactive position specializes in partnering with internal teams and outside vendors to provide strategic insights in the use of digital and interactive development to market to public audiences and for educational outreach. This role demands aptitude in both marketing communications and interactive development to ensure effective communication of messages to appropriate audience/customer groups for a superior interactive user experience. Responsibilities include strategic consulting, new projects initiation using defined request process(es), compiling status reports, coordinating project schedules, leading project meetings, identifying and resolving problems, and developing appropriate documentation. Collaboration with project owners is necessary. The person also develops Web analytics reports as a sound basis for incremental improvements in interactive communications strategies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelors degree in business/marketing or communication or related field. On evaluation, three years of direct experience in project management for web development, marketing, communications or related field, addition to the experience below may be substituted for the degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Four years of experience in interactive marketing communications.&lt;br/&gt;
Demonstrated ability to serve as project manager on complex projects with cross functional working groups. Project management professional certification preferred.&lt;br/&gt;
Demonstrated understanding of user experience design&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Knowledge:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strong understanding of interactive communications and user experience design to augment marketing communications to public audiences.&lt;br/&gt;
Demonstrated ability to manage complex Web, interactive or mobile development projects.&lt;br/&gt;
Solid technical understanding of web and e-communications development including responsive design and app development.&lt;br/&gt;
Understanding of principles of information architecture in relation to content writing and website development.&lt;br/&gt;
Understanding of social media and experience guiding the integration of advertising, PR, Web, social media and design strategies into holistic campaigns.&lt;br/&gt;
Up-to-date knowledge of digital industry trends.&lt;br/&gt;
Basic HTML knowledge a plus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demonstrated project management skills, with ability to lead cross functional teams and manage multiple projects having tight deadlines and complete projects according to schedule.&lt;br/&gt;
Ability to get results in a highly matrixed organization, often with ambiguous roles..&lt;br/&gt;
Advanced interpersonal, organizational, and communication skills and the ability to verbally translate technical information to non-technical people and to skillfully persuade in difficult situations.&lt;br/&gt;
Highly detail- and results-oriented, with excellent proactive problem definition and problem-solving skills.&lt;br/&gt;
Ability to collaborate and accept variable work direction in a fast-paced environment.
Demonstrated ability to define project metrics and develop effective reports.
Strong problem solving and analysis skills, combined with impeccable business judgment.
Strong attention to detail
Intermediate skills in Excel, Word and Powerpoint. Also, skilled in use of MS Project and Visio or comparable tool&lt;br/&gt;
Experience working with content management systems.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-specialist-national-marrow-donor-program-minneapolis-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-specialist-national-marrow-donor-program-minneapolis-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Creative Director at Best Buy in South Richfield, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As an Associate Creative Director you will be part of the larger User Experience team responsible for creating the differentiated BestBuy.com user experience. The User Experience team is responsible for translating user and business needs into meaningful interactive experiences. The User Experience team partners with other digital teams within Best Buy to create seamless customer centric experiences that meet the needs and expectations of our customers based on where they are in their product purchase process or service experience with BestBuy.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Design team responsibilities within UX range from large-scale system and application development, to incremental site enhancements, to creation and support of communication campaigns around events and promotions. As an Associate Creative Director you will be working within a team of designers, writers, and information architects. The primary focus of the Associate Creative Director will be leading and directing the design team through thecreative process to best meet the evolving needs of our business partners, technology capabilities, and customer expectations. The ability to delegate, review, present, and administrate the necessary work streams within each project is critical to the Associate Creative Director role. The ACD will be responsible for identifying, sourcing, and assigning resources appropriate to staff projects. The project teams may be comprised of internal staff members, external agency or consultative resources, or both based on the needs of the project. As creative team lead the ACD is responsible for reviewing creative work to ensure that it is on-brand, solves for the marketing strategy needs at-hand, and covers a wide range of creative exploration. The ACD is also responsible for evolving the quality of the work product produced while expanding the capabilities of the design team. As an ACD your previous professional experience will be foundational to allow you to continuously develop a point of view on project deliverables, research methods, and web design best practices based on the needs and opportunities for the User Experience team at Best Buy. Your point of view will help shape and define the creation of new templates, features, and functions to evolve, enhance, and differentiate the Best Buy dotcom user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Graphic Design, MultiMedia, Information Architecture, Communication, Marketing, Journalism, Human Computer Interaction, Instructional or Graphic Design, related field or equivalent experience. or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years experience in strategic and conceptual creative development across multiple technology solutions. Proven creative ability required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years of e-Commerce UX experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years project and creative team management experience across multiple media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years experience building collaborative creative teams of designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 or more years experience incorporating UX strategies, interactive design specifications, design models/prototypes and QA processes/use cases into the plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-creative-director-best-buy-south-richfield-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-creative-director-best-buy-south-richfield-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>