<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mn-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at AIC in Minneapolis, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts International Corporation is seeking a Front End Web Developer to join the IT team of one of our valued clients. We are an IT services company using our expertise, over 40 years of experience and industry resources to provide the highest quality custom staffing solutions.  The Front End Web Developer will be responsible for the design, development and testing of operating systems-level software, compilers, and network distribution software for computing applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Front End Web Developer you will&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modify existing databases and database management systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write and code logical and physical database descriptions and specify identifiers of database to management system or direct others in coding descriptions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work as part of a project team to coordinate database development and determine project scope and limitation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review project requests describing database user needs to estimate time and cost required to accomplish project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code (without the aid of WYSIWYG tools) high quality cross-browser compatible HTML, JavaScript, CSS, jQuery, and JSP code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Front End Web Developer position is a great match for a candidate with the following skill set&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript Developer experience is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing direct to production,A/B testing,Analytics (tracking and tags, Content,Accessibility,Creative Services/Solutions,Media Networks (google ads, etc and video plays), Version control concepts – SVN and Git, Agile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We value our employees' hard work and dedication to quality. In addition to a positive environment with opportunities for growth and advancement we offer a competitive salary and benefits package.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental, vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long / short term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock purchase plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-aic-minneapolis-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-aic-minneapolis-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at DealDash in Minneapolis, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;DealDash&amp;rsquo;s mission is to be the fun &amp;amp; social marketplace for deals. The 4-year-old startup has quickly grown its user base to 1,500,000+ customers. DealDash started as the risk-free, fair &amp;amp; honest alternative to pay-to-bid auction sites and today helps major retailers efficiently move overstock inventory while saving Customers money in a fun &amp;amp; social way. The fact that you can buy the item you were bidding on for its regular price and get a full refund on the bids spent trying to win a great deal differentiates DealDash from the other &amp;lsquo;shady&amp;rsquo; operators in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then DealDash has added patent pending game-mechanics and achieved record social context with more than 1 million Facebook fans. With 1.5 million US shoppers that complete more than 2.000,000 paid transactions / day we are recognized as a leader in our category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our rapidly growing team is now looking for a new team member who shares the company’s vision and is genuinely enthusiastic about being a part of our fast growing international company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Role:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who will focus on front-end web development, creating prototypes and optimizing existing systems. You will work closely with our UX and visual designer to hand over ready-made front end material to our engineering team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Our Ideal Candidate:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong understanding of current web standards and multi-browser compatibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are at your best when working closely with a UX and visual designer, allowing you to focus on front-end implementation and cross-browser compatibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create strong, production ready code, but able to deliver in situations that require (not-production-quality) rapid prototyping.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years experience with HTML, JS, CSS, Ajax&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recent experience with HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Responsive Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be located in Minneapolis or willing to relocate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Bonus Points:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have professional experience working in an Agile/Scrum environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What We Offer:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great salary, health insurance, and all required equipment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to be part of something great, and create products used by over a million users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open, attractive offices at Coco Minneapolis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Working in DealDash means working in a fast and innovative environment where no day is the same as the previous. You will be working with skillful, enthusiastic and international teammates, with systematic working methods, in a metrics driven culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How To Apply:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your application with your CV and salary request in an email titled “Front-end Web Developer” to careers@dealdash.com  and make sure to let us know in your application why you would be an asset to the team! The postion will be filled as soon as the right candidate is found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about DealDash, please visit http://www.dealdash.com/careers/.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All applications will receive a response.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All applications are kept strictly confidential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is for in person work at our Minneapolis office ONLY &amp;ndash; No contractors &amp;ndash; No recruiters &amp;ndash; No remote work&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-dealdash-minneapolis-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-dealdash-minneapolis-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer-Designer at Essnova Solutions, Inc. in Minnetonka, MN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Pine River Capital Management L.P. (“Pine River”) is a global asset management firm founded in 2002 by Brian Taylor to pursue opportunities in relative value trading. The firm employs over 300 people globally and provides solutions to qualified clients across three actively managed platforms: hedge funds, separate accounts and publicly-listed investment vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The qualified candidate will be responsible for the development and design of major and minor Web applications and components for internal and external users. The developer will design, develop, test and deliver web sites, applications and components, as well as provide enhancements and defect resolution on an ongoing basis.  Candidate is required to have experience in programming, graphics, layout, scripting, presentation and reporting.  Flexibility, adaptability and ability to learn quickly in various technical and creative environments, while delivering quality work by tight deadlines, are important attributes of this role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and development of web applications and components, such as web pages, graphics, GUIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operates effectively as a member of the development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functions effectively as an individual for quick turnaround of enhancements and fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet expectations and deliver on time and in high quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate effectively in both technical and business environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of experience in web design and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end and some back-end development and integration experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding and practical experience utilizing some or all of the following: ASP.NET, C#, VB, HTML, XML, JavaScript, MS SQL Server, Excel VBA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with some degree of data aggregation, client reporting and presentation methodologies, including data grids, dashboards, portals, SQL Server Reporting Services (SSRS), Online Analytic Processing (OLAP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of application development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative, technical and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS / BA degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-designer-essnova-solutions-inc-minnetonka-mn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-designer-essnova-solutions-inc-minnetonka-mn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>