<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mo-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. Designer - Art Director at Express-Scripts in Missouri</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Advance your career with the company that makes it easier for people to choose better health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Express Scripts is a leading healthcare company serving tens of millions of consumers. We are looking for individuals who are passionate, creative and committed to creating systems and service solutions that promote better health outcomes. Join the company that Fortune magazine ranked as one of the &amp;ldquo;Most Admired Companies&amp;rdquo; in the pharmacy category. Then, use your intelligence, creativity, integrity and hard work to help us enhance our products and services. We offer a highly competitive base salary and a comprehensive benefits program, including medical, prescription drug, dental, vision, 401(k) with company match, life insurance, paid time off, tuition assistance and an employee stock purchase plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT THE DEPARTMENT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marketing &amp;amp; Corporate Communications works strategically with Sales and Account Management across all divisions to manage relationships, win new business and retain existing clients. We also provide strategic planning and communications counsel for key corporate initiatives, as well as tactical and creative support for areas throughout the organization, including Product Management, Human Resources and Information Systems. Broadly, we are responsible for all corporate messaging and communications management. Other areas of responsibility include:&lt;br/&gt;
* Corporate proposal database
* Commercial and Labor proposal operations
* Public affairs and media relations
* Corporate events and experiential marketing
* Employee, client and member communications&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Express Scripts is seeking an in-house Senior Graphic Designer with the experience and talent to produce engaging visual communications for both internal and external audiences. Innovative thinking and outstanding creative and software skills are a must. The Senior Designer is proficient in the design and execution of communications materials including print and digital sales collateral, internal training materials, meeting presentations and events graphics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The candidate must be a well-rounded designer who thrives on contributing ideas, utilizes proficient knowledge of the most current industry standards, and possesses exemplary presentation skills to share concepts and final executions with internal clients. The ideal candidate also has the ability to comprehend diverse and complex ideas and translate them into clear and cogent visual communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Essential Functions:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop innovative concepts, create compelling design solutions and follow through to final delivery on a wide variety of B2B and B2C marketing projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Creative Directors and Copywriters to create attention-getting work for consumer lead generation, retention, and engagement initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide graphic design support to field force effectiveness initiatives, including; sales collateral design, presentation design and design of internal training materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate effectively with Express Scripts marketing managers, strategic planners, and product owners/managers from across the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years proven experience within the discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Graphic Design/Communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Adobe Creative Suite including InDesign and Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual thinker, strong familiarity with print and digital production and media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated, curious, and driven to succeed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to take direction and to work independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to manage multiple projects and demanding timelines, and to thrive in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior time management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail-oriented, organized, strives for flawless execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimistic, can-do attitude, and acts with integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of healthcare, managed care, and/or pharmacy benefits management industry is desired but not mandatory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EEO STATEMENT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Express Scripts is an Equal Employment Opportunity employer and does not discriminate in employment opportunities or practices on the basis of race, creed, color, religion, sex, national origin, nationality, ancestry, age, disability or status as a disabled veteran or veteran of the Vietnam era, pregnancy, affectional or sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, marital status, status with regard to public assistance, veteran status, citizenship or membership in any other legally protected class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;None of the questions in this application are intended to elicit information regarding any protected characteristics, nor imply any limitation, illegal preferences or discrimination based upon non-job-related information or protected characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants must be able to pass a drug test and background investigation and, depending on position requirements, a Department of Defense background investigation.  AA/EOE.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-designer-art-director-express-scripts-missouri</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-designer-art-director-express-scripts-missouri</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>