<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mo-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Art Director at DDB in St. Louis, MO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Rodgers Townsend | DDB St. Louis is seeking a Digital Art Director to develop original digital creative designs and oversee projects from design through execution in an open and collaborative environment. The successful candidate will be excited about helping to develop digital marketing and advertising strategies. They also must provide evidence of best-in-industry work and be able to create award-winning work in web and mobile. Candidate must be comfortable managing creative work and keeping projects on budget and on schedule by providing clear creative direction, timely and useful feedback and effectively managing individual and team time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept and create inspiring and groundbreaking digital experiences to support client goals and objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe and defend fresh, original digital concepts and strategies to internal and external audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support ongoing creative innovation by actively participating in and supporting the agency culture of collaboration, positivity, excellence and creative problem-solving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively monitor and manage projects from concept through production, prioritizing creative teamwork and resources according to short- and long-term deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of creative agency experience, minimum of 3 years of digital experience and managing the creative development process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evidence of award-winning work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in all aspects of digital and conventional design: identity, advertising, marketing, user experience, collateral, brand development, interactive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth, current knowledge of emerging digital platforms and related mediums, and ongoing monitoring of developments therein.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal communication and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rodgers Townsend | DDB is a nationally acclaimed, full-service marketing communications agency. Founded in 1996, the agency provides strategic planning, advertising, direct/one-to-one marketing, digital marketing and design services to a wide range of clients both nationally and regionally, including: AT&amp;amp;T, BASF, Enterprise Holdings, The Hartford, The Magic House, Missouri Baptist Medical Center, Nawgan Alertness Beverage and Saint Louis University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To view our internationally award-winning creative, see our work at &lt;a href=&quot;http://rodgerstownsend.com&quot;&gt;http://rodgerstownsend.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-art-director-ddb-st-louis-mo</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-art-director-ddb-st-louis-mo</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>