<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mo-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Second Street in St. Louis, MO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Second Street provides private-label web based SaaS products for media companies nationwide. Some of our leading-edge products include online contests, daily deal software, photo e-commerce, email marketing and more. Our software solutions are relied upon by more than 2,000 media and marketing companies across North America, including CBS, Clear Channel, The Washington Post and hundreds of others. This is a unique opportunity to obtain a vital role with a major emerging firm producing software used by millions. We are seeking candidates that are tech savvy, learn quickly, are passionate about technology and are motivated to succeed. If you are seeking an opportunity to build a career in a high tech organization with fun and exciting culture &amp;ndash; this is your opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About This Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love the web, design and the ever-expanding world of combining the two? Second Street is looking for a front-end developer that is passionate about their work and has a constant drive to make the user experience better and better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to knowledge in front-end technologies such as HTML5, CSS and JavaScript to build web and mobile interfaces, the ideal candidate will have experience in user-centered-design and have a passion for discussing the ideal solution to any problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full time position in St. Louis, MO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Job Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the UX team to design easy and fun to use interfaces that will be used by our partners and their consumers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update our existing table-based HTML to modern responsive HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help our partners customize our interfaces to meet their needs and work with their existing brand presence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive HTML knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive CSS knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Javascript, AJAX and libraries like jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing for mobile web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interested candidates will be required to show a sample of solid, recent work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MVC experience a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-second-street-st-louis-mo</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-second-street-st-louis-mo</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Web Developer at DDB in St. Louis, MO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Rodgers Townsend is seeking a creative web developer with a specialty in digital, mobile, social and back-end online experiences. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for people with strong interpersonal skills who are able to work well within a quickly growing team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with producers, art directors, and other internal and external developers to create Web-based experiences including corporate websites, landing pages, microsites, mobile optimized sites, banners and other web or mobile based applications where needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receive graphic source files and implement front end layout which may include subtle animations or integration with video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop mobile web, and native iOS applications for phone and tablet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the development of requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform iterative Quality Assurance testing procedures for both front end (browser, mobile, tablet) as well as back-end (database scripting, monitoring, test procedures etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot technical problems, fix bugs, and update content across the Application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide input and assist in evaluating new or alternative tools, technologies, standards, guidelines, and policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct and be part of peer reviews to ensure projects are consistent with established guidelines, policies, and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Competencies Required:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced and commanding knowledge of HTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing responsive, and adaptive websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of video integration with HTML5 and / or Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JQuery and JQuery UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience authoring custom JavaScript classes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using social network APIs (Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Understanding of Object-Oriented development processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of PHP and Wordpress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Flash / ActionScript 3.0 preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the SiteFinity, Expression Engine CMS considered a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the Subversion source control system considered a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SQL Server and MySQL Reporting Services considered a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in related field or equivalent education/training preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborative mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to stay in front of technology and bring fresh ideas to our efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior agency experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to achieve great things and continually learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professionalism and accountability for oneself required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-web-developer-ddb-st-louis-mo</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-web-developer-ddb-st-louis-mo</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer / Front-End Developer at Delta Systems in Columbia, MO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Delta Systems is looking for another self-motivated and enthusiastic web designer / front-end developer to join our team. You will be responsible for designing and developing websites and user interfaces for web-based applications. Strong creative and design sense, ability work efficiently in a team, and ability to communicate directly with the client are key. You will be expected to read and interpret client design briefs, translate their ideas into complete website mock-ups, and cut and code those designs into static HTML/CSS templates. Anything you can do beyond that is gravy. And we love gravy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will have real passion for the web and always keeps an eye on emerging technologies. You will be working closely in a team of highly skilled web developers that are scattered across the United States. If you can design it, they can make it a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong web design portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in something (if it’s something related to graphic/interactive design, even better!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience designing for client needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of User Interface (UI)/User Experience (UX) principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written &amp;amp; verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand and practice web standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a modern CMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience templating for WordPress is a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript / jQuery / YUI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of HTML5/CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PHP would be nice, but not expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know your way around Basecamp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are used to keeping detailed, client-friendly time records&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a dribbble.com account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a GitHub account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work Environment:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since 1986, Delta has been building tracking systems for everything from napkins to insurance policies, from golf courses to hot dog ingredients, from horse ailments to yoga certifications, and from blood donors to paddlefish.
Building online applications and data management systems that are intuitive yet powerful is our specialty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read about Delta in the Columbia Daily Tribune&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delta Systems has been named “one of Mid-Missouri’s foremost web design and support firms” by the Columbia Daily Tribune and “a premier providers of computing solutions” by the Columbia Business Times. Our employees enjoy many freedoms and benefits. We do group coding weekly for reviews and single-project focusing to knock out features, do some spec work, or just to put an app together to find and fix issues quickly. Free lunch-and-learn sessions provide opportunities for ongoing training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delta builds award winning websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delta Systems employees exemplify professionalism in every aspect of client relations and work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Typical daily activities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work along other senior developers to provide PHP programming and functionality for a wide variety of consumer related websites, intranets, extranets, and web-based applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be challenged on a daily basis to solve problems in new and creative ways&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, evaluate, update, and maintain object oriented applications in PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, evaluate, update, and maintain complicated database schemas in PostgreSQL and SQL Server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share your opinions and insights with business leaders on a daily basis in order to affect rapid decision cycles and effective solutions to business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid by the hour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flex time – If you like working from 7am to 3pm or 3pm to 11pm great!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Insurance, 90% paid by employer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SIMPLE retirement plan with corporate matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid sick leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AFLAC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free soda, tea, coffee and occasional lunches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development environments: Ubuntu, Windows, or Mac, whichever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’ll pay for applicable certification exams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subscription to O’Reilly Media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy “Virtual Tuesdays”; you can work from anywhere you want without meeting interruptions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dress is casual – jeans and t-shirts are just fine. When meeting with clients, we expect business appropriate attire and demeanor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-front-end-developer-delta-systems-columbia-mo</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-front-end-developer-delta-systems-columbia-mo</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr Front-End Developer at H&amp;R Block in Kansas City, MO</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for a place where your hard work can be FUN and APPRECIATED?  Come join H&amp;amp;R Block!  This is your chance to join our organization and become part of a known and respected brand.  H&amp;amp;R Block is America’s 4th largest retail organization.  Due to our exciting plans for the future, we have several career opportunities available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB SUMMARY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sr Front End Developer is responsible for guiding and assisting in the development of H&amp;amp;R Block interactive projects.  This role will guide user interface development and help define the direction for front end UI development for H&amp;amp;R Block’s digital products and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DUTIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be the conduit from User Experience to Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take the lead and mentor other developers on how to deliver UX designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with visual design and interaction design to develop the front end components and functions as defined then work closely with IT to implement these designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and implement standards and guidelines for all front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with visual design with bulk e-mail projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains data and most current standards, including writing of documentation, procedures, and definitions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluates functional design and tests technical usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translates visual and interaction design into a dynamic user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;JOB REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor degree in computer science or equivalent experience.  Masters degree a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6+  years of experience with front-end development and delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of iOS experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Android experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative and has a keen eye for clean user interface implementation and knowledge of web site design best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with maintaining data and UI standards, including writing of documentation, procedures, and definitions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written, and interpersonal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project management skills a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good organizational skills, attention to detail, and strong QA skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated proficiency with iOS and web design and implementation (e.g., iOS/XCODE, HTML 5, CSS 3, Android a plus, Perl, PHP, Javascript etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross browser &amp;amp; platform compatibility (IE &amp;amp; Fire fox on Win &amp;amp; OSX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;WHY SHOULD YOU WORK FOR H&amp;amp;R BLOCK?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Competitive compensation and benefits package, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary and incentive compensation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Time Off including&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sick time, including short-term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Benefit options for you and your eligible dependents, including:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical / Prescription Drug&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Savings Account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental / Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life / AD&amp;amp;D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long Term Disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Accounts – medical and dependent care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hyatt Legal Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional benefits include:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) plan, including a company match of $1 for $1 up to 4% and immediate vesting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Stock Purchase Plan with a discount purchase price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition Reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adoption Assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tax Preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buy and Save associate discount site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are dedicated to doing the right thing for our People, Clients and Shareholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High Ambition- we focus on setting our goals high, bring out the best in our people and celebrate success.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile- we anticipate the changing needs of the marketplace and quickly adjust to what our clients need today.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;H&amp;amp;R Block is a progressive company dedicated to looking at our clients’ lives through taxes and finding ways to help.   Our vision is to become the leading global consumer tax company, bringing tax and related solutions to clients year-round.  If you meet the above requirements and would like to explore a career with H&amp;amp;R Block, please log onto our career website at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hrblock.com&quot;&gt;http://www.hrblock.com&lt;/a&gt; and submit your resume and profile.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-h-and-r-block-kansas-city-mo</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-h-and-r-block-kansas-city-mo</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>