<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/mt-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at WebFilings in Bozeman, MT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;WebFilings is a rapidly growing company that builds collaborative, cloud-based applications for financial and executive teams. We are seeking talented Interaction Designers to work alongside our world-class development team to design and prototype amazing experiences for the highest levels of the largest companies. WebFilings deeply understands the importance of user experience and the value of this role in the product development process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll be doing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be working directly with a team of world-class product managers, developers, and other UX professionals to make our products simple and intuitive. Your responsibilities will include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing how our products work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing personas and modeling user behavior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lean user experience design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-fidelity rapid prototyping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iterating on your designs based on data, not opinions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we&amp;rsquo;re looking for&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mad Skillz (must have link to portfolio on resume)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intense passion for design and user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience designing for interactive Flash and/or HTML applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prototype what you design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subpixel attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to influence and inspire your team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication skills to clearly articulate and defend design decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivation and excellent problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S./M.S. in Human-Computer Interaction, Computer Science, Design or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in an Agile development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a geographically distributed team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-webfilings-bozeman-mt</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-webfilings-bozeman-mt</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>