<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nc-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Full Stack Web Developer at ReverbNation in Durham, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ReverbNation is looking for a Senior [insert ninja archetype] Full Stack Web Developer to join our growing team in Durham, NC. As a web developer, your role would include interfacing with both the product and infrastructure teams to bring sweet pixely nectar to over 1.7 million artists and live performers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You definitely should&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have lengthy (5+ years) experience building consumer-facing websites from front to back&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have 3+ years of experience with Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience with persistent and non-persistent backing stores (SQL, Redis)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have used popular libraries for development (jQuery, SASS, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience with (sold your soul to) an MVC web framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love wrangling all 4 major browsers on each OS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get your energy from a fast-paced team environment (supplemented with Pretzel M&amp;amp;Ms)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dream and fight for all browsers having equal opportunity to HTML5 and CSS3 standards compliance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;It would be best if you&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know your way around a *nix box&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have worked with AWS or other similar hosted solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can sing (we really need a singer for our band)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;In return, you&amp;rsquo;ll get&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The satisfaction of watching your friends use your work when they&amp;rsquo;re out in public&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to work with some of the most talented leaders, designers and developers in the Triangle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary with possibility of equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great benefits package that includes company contribution towards medical and 100% company paid dental and vision, 401(k) match, 18 PTO days/year + 7 company holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new hoss of a machine and leather executive chair with lumbar support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very casual work environment where jeans, tees and sneakers are encouraged&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular company outings with your awesome co-workers that include bulls games, cookouts and trips to our local breweries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great office location in Durham that is walking distance to lots of local restaurants and shops&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-full-stack-web-developer-reverbnation-durham-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-full-stack-web-developer-reverbnation-durham-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at 3-C Institute for Social Development in Cary, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have experience building and maintaining web applications using cutting-edge technologies like HTML5, jQuery, AJAX and object-oriented PHP? If so, 3-C Institute for Social Development wants to hear from you! We currently have three openings for web developers and are looking for a developer like you to help build a next-generation application for managing behavioral research projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re the right candidate for this mid-level position, you have experience with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working on a team of developers tasked with building great applications using proven technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing clean and readable HTML and CSS that works across all browsers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with PSD files produced by our graphic designers to produce exciting user interfaces for the web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using jQuery to send and receive AJAX requests to and from our web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object-oriented PHP development to map objects to our functional requirements and database structures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic MySQL or relational database experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning new technologies and understanding how they can be applied to our diverse suite of application offerings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Salary &amp;amp; Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary is based on education and experience level.  3-C ISD offers all of the traditional benefit packages plus fun extras like yoga classes and lunch parties!  Salaries and benefits are competitive with the central NC area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Company Information:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3-C ISD is a small but growing company with a progressive attitude and a positive mission to develop research-based tools to foster the health and well-being of children and families. We have a laidback, fun office environment where we work hard but always remember to have fun along the way! Take advantage of our in-office fitness room! Set your own schedule! Wear what you want (within reason)! Work with some of the coolest, most creative people in the Research Triangle. Plus, we trust you to get your work done. No visits from the boss every half-hour asking ofr &amp;ldquo;TPS Reports&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Information:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you&amp;rsquo;re a web developer looking to make a difference in a different atmosphere, shoot us your resume today at careers@3cisd.com!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About 3-C Institute for Social Development:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3-C ISD offers a collaborative, flexible, and family-friendly work environment with colleagues who value teamwork, self-motivation, and commitment to results. 3-C ISD is a rapidly expanding research institute located in Cary, NC. We specialize in development of research-based tools to foster the health and well-being of children and families. Please see www.3CISD.com for more information&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-3-c-institute-for-social-development-cary-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-3-c-institute-for-social-development-cary-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>