<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nc-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at The Cliffs Communities in Greenville, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;JOB SUMMARY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The Graphic Designer will assist the Club Marketing Team in delivering high quality visual solutions to communicate The Cliffs’ messages, utilizing a blend of creative skills, commercial awareness, and brand savvy. Develops and implements graphic standards for the Cliffs brand across a spectrum of applications including: electronic communications, magazines, posters, websites, logos, brochures and other marketing collateral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A graphic designer will develop a visual language to positively position Member events and products. The design work demands creative ability, up-to-date knowledge of graphic trends, latest industry software, and professional approach to time, costs and deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DUTIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role will involve managing more than one design project at a time, allocating the relevant amount of time according to the value of the job. Typical work activities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meets with project manager to discuss the objectives and requirements of the job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interpret the objectives and develop a concept to suit the purpose&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think creatively to produce new ideas and concepts within the constraints of cost and time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present ideas and concepts to project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within a wide range of media including photography, illustration, and computer-aided design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proofread to produce accurate and high-quality work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep abreast of developments in IT, particularly design programs such as InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Acrobat, Dreamweaver and Flash
*Work as part of a team with printers, copywriters, photographers, other designers, project managers, web developers and marketing specialists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create designs, concepts, and sample layouts based on knowledge of layout principles and esthetic design concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;BACKGROUND/EXPERIENCE:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree in Graphic Arts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ experience in Desktop Publishing/Layout/Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of principles of graphic and visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Macromedia, In Design, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe PhotoShop, Adobe Acrobat. Knowledge of Dreamweaver and Flash a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent grammatical, spelling and proofreading skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Microsoft Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented, strong organizational skills and can manage multiple projects in time-sensitive environment (work load varies from 5-25 design projects per week)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate initiative, work independently, meet deadlines and maintain collaborative professional relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photography skills a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PHYSICAL REQUIREMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess mobility to work in a standard office setting and to use standard office equipment, including a computer, stamina to maintain attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strength to lift and carry files weighing up to 10 pounds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision to read printed materials and a computer screen, and hearing and speech to communicate in person and over the telephone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-the-cliffs-communities-greenville-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-the-cliffs-communities-greenville-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer - Temporary at North Carolina State University in Chapel Hill, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position includes but not limited to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supporting marketing functions, marketing initiatives for different programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;providing technical support for blogs and web support (modifying text or approving blogs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;graphic design work in photo shop and InDesign, creative visual designer and basic support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Experience/Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 1 year of Graphic Design experience. Must have a portfolio or some samples of work to provide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Departmental Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite-Good digital design and creative skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic web support skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly organized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self starter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Productive and proactive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;AA/EOE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AA/EEO In addition, NC State welcomes all persons without regard to sexual orientation or genetic information. Persons with disabilities requiring accommodations in the application and interview process please call (919) 515-3148. Final candidates are subject to criminal &amp;amp; sex offender background checks. Some vacancies also require credit or motor vehicle checks. If highest degree is from an institution outside of the U.S., final candidates are required to have their degree verified at www.wes.org. Degree must be obtained prior to start date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Supplemental Questions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have at least 1 year of Graphic Design and can show a portfolio of work?
* Yes
* No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Materials Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Required Documents&lt;/em&gt;: Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optional Documents&lt;/em&gt;: Cover Letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-temporary-north-carolina-state-university-chapel-hill-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-temporary-north-carolina-state-university-chapel-hill-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>