<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nc-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>eCommerce Web Designer at MSC Industrial Supply in Davidson, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Web Designer is responsible for contributing to, and implementing the style guide specifications with respect to the layout, visual appearance and usability of the Company websites, while working closely with the Marketing department to ensure that brand continuity is maintained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;DUTIES and RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the Content Manager on all applicable design projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce web designs by using prototypes for concept design, mock-up creation and final design &amp;ndash; obtaining proper feedback and approvals throughout the process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently work with customers to validate the designs and customer experience for usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain the overall design standards, integrity and consistency for MSC’s websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the marketing team to provide creative support for online marketing collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update current web pages as necessary and appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current on industry design trends and technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform proofing and QA of own work to ensure flawless execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish excellent workflow and customer navigation experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create easy-to-use interfaces out of complex material&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate Requirement Documents into a visually pleasing interface that meets the requirements, provides an excellent customer usability experience and stays within the appropriate style guide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct research into new user interface design techniques and leverage as able&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foster the MSC Culture in the department and throughout the company to ensure unity of purpose and fulfillment of MSC’s mission&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in special projects and perform additional duties as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EDUCATION and EXPERIENCE:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree or equivalent work experience required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 Years working in web design is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert proficiency with Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Dreamweaver (hand coding) and other web design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High proficiency with HTML and CSS required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong portfolio that demonstrates a keen eye for user interface design and problem solving through web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with javascript (AJAX, jQuery, Dojo, etc.) creation, maintenance and modification required; proficient/expert level a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conscious of maintaining design consistency across the entire web site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A comprehensive understanding of the role of design in supporting the content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A comprehensive understanding of the design related issues surrounding large transaction volume websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An innate understanding of human-computer interaction and user flow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accountability for maintaining the design integrity of a highly dynamic and constantly evolving web site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for staying on top of web design trends and the latest techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;SKILLS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to effectively communicate with individuals at all levels in the Company and with various business contacts outside of the Company in an articulate, professional manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously while maintaining quality​&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive and Self Motivated – exhibits strong sense of ownership and proactively identifies what needs to be done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team Player – ability to work in a team environment and build strong working relationship across departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;EOE&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ecommerce-web-designer-msc-industrial-supply-davidson-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ecommerce-web-designer-msc-industrial-supply-davidson-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at New Breed Logistics in High Point, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS in Design, Visual Communication, Communication Information Sciences or equivalent field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience supporting Business Communications, Marketing, and/or Business Development activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very high level of proficiency with Adobe’s suite of design products (Illustrator, Photoshop, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of proficiency using MS Office applications (Word, PowerPoint, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated skill in supporting messaging/branding efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated skill in communicating complex technical and business processes  via visual media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage time to accommodate multiple projects and multiple deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task and transition rapidly and efficiently from one project to another&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to incorporate feedback/input/constructive criticism from a wide-ranging group of peers and project stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work both independently with little direction and as part of various teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a PC-based environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to support written communication efforts (proposals, presentations, business letters, etc.) by editing drafts, writing material, consolidating input, formatting, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of business to business sales processes and efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the requirements needed to succeed in a project-based work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-new-breed-logistics-high-point-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-new-breed-logistics-high-point-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Sports Endeavors, Inc. in Hillsborough, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Web Designer will participate in the creation, production, and maintenance of high-profile e-commerce web sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an integral member of the Online Properties Department, their responsibilities will be quite varied; a flexible, positive attitude will be essential. Multi-tasking and the ability to handle a wide variety of assignments and deadlines will be vital. Content creation, maintenance and ability to execute work within specific design parameters will be a priority for the Designer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The ideal candidate will command a thorough knowledge of:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, CSS and Javascript/jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of emerging standards like CSS 3 and HTML 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI/UX Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the principles of user centered interface design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with both producing and utilizing interface wireframes and mockups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-browser compliance, usability principles and testing practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Additional Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with design of e-commerce sites, particularly Websphere Commerce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Compass or other SASS-based tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CMS Customization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP or Java exposure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-sports-endeavors-inc-hillsborough-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-sports-endeavors-inc-hillsborough-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at BB&amp;T Human Systems in Raleigh, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor?s degree in graphic design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor?s degree or equivalent education and related training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four to five years of experience in graphic design for consumer-facing web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write source code for advanced HTML and advanced CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience in graphic design and multimedia techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid communication and problem-solving/analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work as a member of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced experience with: Photoshop, Dreamweaver, HTML, CSS, cross-browser coding and w3c guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash at intermediate to advanced level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail (unit-testing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with usability concepts and user-centered design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to travel as needed, occasionally overnight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and create custom layouts and templates for all websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create images and other graphical elements in accordance with branding standards and guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in iterative design of prototypes with multiple core team members and incorporate feedback from team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop concepts for applications, websites, demos and online marketing pieces with input from core team before development begins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct research on existing and emerging delivery technologies and products for purposes of delivering a richer client experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in development of Web Design processes and procedures and documentation of current branding and site specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review and provide feedback on time estimates, project requirements and specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-bb%26t-human-systems-raleigh-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-bb%26t-human-systems-raleigh-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at Wireless Generation in Durham, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Wireless Generation creates innovative tools, systems and services that help educators teach with excellence. With its solutions, educators can easily apply research-based, proven practices such as frequent progress monitoring and needs diagnosis, data-informed decision-making, differentiated instruction, and professional collaborations across classrooms, grades, and schools. The company has helped educators address and solve some of the most pressing challenges in teaching and learning. Wireless Generation currently serves more than 200,000 educators and three million students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wireless Generation is seeking a User Experience Designer to create intuitive and innovative user experiences for next generation educational applications. We?re looking for creative leaders interested in contributing to a variety of interactive and mobile based initiatives. UX Designers at Wireless Generation work across the user experience domain, including research (user interviews, ethnography, persona development), design (sketching, group ideation, information architecture, interaction design, prototyping), documentation (wireframing and specification writing), and user testing. The successful candidate will serve as the glue between Stakeholders, Users, and the engineers that build the designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities of UX Designer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute user requirements gathering, conceptual modeling, onsite and offsite usability testing and competitive landscape analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and specify user interfaces and information architecture using participatory and iterative design techniques including customer interviews, usability testing, and other forms of requirements discovery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce user requirements specifications, personas, storyboards, scenarios, prototypes, wireframes, functional specifications, and design specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate research findings, conceptual ideas and detailed design rationale both verbally and visually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help manage the interaction design process, drive decisions, track issues, and assist in estimating resource needs and schedules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate as a contributor to an interdisciplinary team that includes visual designers, project managers, product strategists, and developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designers need to be able to both discuss and document their designs and design decisions effectively to varied audiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements of UX Designer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience developing interactive products as an Information Architect, Interaction Designer, Product Designer, User Experience Designer or Usability Engineer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive and creative problem solver with an intellectual interest in current and new technologies and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-organized, with attention to detail and excellent follow-through skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional written and verbal communication skills and collegiality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelors Degree is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position may be funded, in whole or in part, through American Recovery &amp;amp; Reinvestment Act funds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wireless Generation is an Equal Opportunity Employer, M/F/D/V.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-wireless-generation-durham-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-wireless-generation-durham-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at The Cliffs Communities in Greenville, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;JOB SUMMARY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The Graphic Designer will assist the Club Marketing Team in delivering high quality visual solutions to communicate The Cliffs’ messages, utilizing a blend of creative skills, commercial awareness, and brand savvy. Develops and implements graphic standards for the Cliffs brand across a spectrum of applications including: electronic communications, magazines, posters, websites, logos, brochures and other marketing collateral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A graphic designer will develop a visual language to positively position Member events and products. The design work demands creative ability, up-to-date knowledge of graphic trends, latest industry software, and professional approach to time, costs and deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DUTIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role will involve managing more than one design project at a time, allocating the relevant amount of time according to the value of the job. Typical work activities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meets with project manager to discuss the objectives and requirements of the job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interpret the objectives and develop a concept to suit the purpose&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think creatively to produce new ideas and concepts within the constraints of cost and time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present ideas and concepts to project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within a wide range of media including photography, illustration, and computer-aided design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proofread to produce accurate and high-quality work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep abreast of developments in IT, particularly design programs such as InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Acrobat, Dreamweaver and Flash
*Work as part of a team with printers, copywriters, photographers, other designers, project managers, web developers and marketing specialists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create designs, concepts, and sample layouts based on knowledge of layout principles and esthetic design concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;BACKGROUND/EXPERIENCE:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree in Graphic Arts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ experience in Desktop Publishing/Layout/Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of principles of graphic and visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Macromedia, In Design, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe PhotoShop, Adobe Acrobat. Knowledge of Dreamweaver and Flash a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent grammatical, spelling and proofreading skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Microsoft Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented, strong organizational skills and can manage multiple projects in time-sensitive environment (work load varies from 5-25 design projects per week)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate initiative, work independently, meet deadlines and maintain collaborative professional relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photography skills a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PHYSICAL REQUIREMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess mobility to work in a standard office setting and to use standard office equipment, including a computer, stamina to maintain attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strength to lift and carry files weighing up to 10 pounds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision to read printed materials and a computer screen, and hearing and speech to communicate in person and over the telephone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-the-cliffs-communities-greenville-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-the-cliffs-communities-greenville-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer - Temporary at North Carolina State University in Chapel Hill, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position includes but not limited to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supporting marketing functions, marketing initiatives for different programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;providing technical support for blogs and web support (modifying text or approving blogs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;graphic design work in photo shop and InDesign, creative visual designer and basic support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Experience/Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 1 year of Graphic Design experience. Must have a portfolio or some samples of work to provide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Departmental Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite-Good digital design and creative skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic web support skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly organized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self starter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Productive and proactive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;AA/EOE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AA/EEO In addition, NC State welcomes all persons without regard to sexual orientation or genetic information. Persons with disabilities requiring accommodations in the application and interview process please call (919) 515-3148. Final candidates are subject to criminal &amp;amp; sex offender background checks. Some vacancies also require credit or motor vehicle checks. If highest degree is from an institution outside of the U.S., final candidates are required to have their degree verified at www.wes.org. Degree must be obtained prior to start date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Supplemental Questions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have at least 1 year of Graphic Design and can show a portfolio of work?
* Yes
* No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Materials Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Required Documents&lt;/em&gt;: Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optional Documents&lt;/em&gt;: Cover Letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-temporary-north-carolina-state-university-chapel-hill-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-temporary-north-carolina-state-university-chapel-hill-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>