<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nc-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Art Director - Digital at MedThink Communications in Raleigh, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Senior Art Director-Digital is responsible for creating, developing, and generating “game-changing” interactive creative work. You will be responsible for motivating and leading your creative team from concept to completion on digital initiatives. This position will help elevate creative thinking by partnering with senior creative and web development teams to turn the “can’t be done” into “wow.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be both a hands-on and high-level position &amp;ndash; creating design work as well as directing a team. The proven ability to balance multiple projects successfully and collaborate across strategy, media, account and technology disciplines is critical in our cross-functional environment. The Senior Art Director requires excellent interpersonal and presentation skills, including the ability to communicate designs effectively with clients and internal team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of a Bachelor’s degree, and five-seven years’ graphic design with no less than two years in a supervisory position &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Art Direction skilled to expertise in Adobe Creative Suite. Also, experience in a healthcare corporate communications environment and a strong design background  in visual and interaction design &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with outside vendors such as agencies (brand/digital), illustrators, photographers and stock photo companies  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An articulate, friendly, “whatever-it-takes” approach, along with an extremely strong work ethic (a good sense of humor helps, too.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A willingness to learn and stay on top of emerging trends and technologies and pursue opportunities to enhance the skills required to be successful in this role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet aggressive deadlines, juggle multiple priorities, and thrive in an environment of rapid change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Painstaking attention to detail, accuracy and quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazing design acumen and “stands out from the rest” creative portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to translate client business requirements, user needs and technical capabilities into designs that are visually exciting, easy to use and emotionally engaging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design skills that fit brand strategy, and the ability to create/evaluate own work and the work others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design, usability, functionality and understanding of information architecture is essential; however, a portfolio of strong design and conceptual work is a key deciding factor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a strong working knowledge of design tools common to design and Web development, such as Photoshop, Fireworks, Flash and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with healthcare and pharmaceutical marketing and/or print advertising&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and understanding of user experience and user interface principles and processes (utilizing static designs, site maps, page flows, wireframes and prototypes to guide design concepts)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall, must ensure the agency’s creative product is well designed, strategically on target, tactically optimized and utilizes proven online/offline techniques for generating highly effective and results-oriented creative work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demonstrates behavior expected of a professional member of the organization, including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to strategic solutions with the Creative Director and Account team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance visual aesthetic for a project while maintaining the brand identity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for overseeing the design process on assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self motivated, organized and accountable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains and promotes design consistency of look, tone and feel to assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads critiques of work in group and individual sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is able to articulate the benefits of the creative approaches, internally and to clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of capabilities and limitations of Web/Digital technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of informational architecture practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to interpret strategic objectives into tactics that a design team can execute&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think in abstract terms; can make connections between unrelated notions; can formulate innovative ideas where others can not; seen as original and value-added in brainstorming sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-digital-medthink-communications-raleigh-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-digital-medthink-communications-raleigh-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Art Director - Digital at MedThink Communications in Raleigh, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Senior Art Director-Digital is responsible for creating, developing, and generating “game-changing” interactive creative work. You will be responsible for motivating and leading your creative team from concept to completion on digital initiatives. This position will help elevate creative thinking by partnering with senior creative and web development teams to turn the “can’t be done” into “wow.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be both a hands-on and high-level position &amp;ndash; creating design work as well as directing a team. The proven ability to balance multiple projects successfully and collaborate across strategy, media, account and technology disciplines is critical in our cross-functional environment. The Senior Art Director requires excellent interpersonal and presentation skills, including the ability to communicate designs effectively with clients and internal team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum of a Bachelor’s degree, and five-seven years’ graphic design with no less than two years in a supervisory position&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Direction skilled to expertise in Adobe Creative Suite. Also, experience in a healthcare corporate communications environment and a strong design background
in visual and interaction design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience working with outside vendors such as agencies (brand/digital), illustrators, photographers and stock photo companies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;An articulate, friendly, “whatever-it-takes” approach, along with an extremely strong work ethic (a good sense of humor helps, too.).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A willingness to learn and stay on top of emerging trends and technologies and pursue opportunities to enhance the skills required to be successful in this role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet aggressive deadlines, juggle multiple priorities, and thrive in an environment of rapid change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Painstaking attention to detail, accuracy and quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazing design acumen and “stands out from the rest” creative portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to translate client business requirements, user needs and technical capabilities into designs that are visually exciting, easy to use and emotionally engaging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design skills that fit brand strategy, and the ability to create/evaluate own work and the work others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design, usability, functionality and understanding of information architecture is essential; however, a portfolio of strong design and conceptual work is a key deciding factor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a strong working knowledge of design tools common to design and Web development, such as Photoshop, Fireworks, Flash and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with healthcare and pharmaceutical marketing and/or print advertising&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and understanding of user experience and user interface principles and processes (utilizing static designs, site maps, page flows, wireframes and prototypes to guide design concepts)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall, must ensure the agency’s creative product is well designed, strategically on target, tactically optimized and utilizes proven online/offline techniques for generating highly effective and results-oriented creative work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demonstrates behavior expected of a professional member of the organization, including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to strategic solutions with the Creative Director and Account team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance visual aesthetic for a project while maintaining the brand identity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for overseeing the design process on assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self motivated, organized and accountable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains and promotes design consistency of look, tone and feel to assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads critiques of work in group and individual sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is able to articulate the benefits of the creative approaches, internally and to clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of capabilities and limitations of Web/Digital technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of informational architecture practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to interpret strategic objectives into tactics that a design team can execute&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think in abstract terms; can make connections between unrelated notions; can formulate innovative ideas where others can not; seen as original and value-added in brainstorming sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-digital-medthink-communications-raleigh-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-digital-medthink-communications-raleigh-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director Digital Strategy &amp; Content at Pace Communications in Greensboro, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Pace Communications, one of the largest content marketing agencies in the country, is now accepting resumes for a Director, Digital Strategy &amp;amp; Content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pace is one of the largest and most successful agencies of its type in the world – our people are recognized as leaders in the field and our account list includes some of the North America’s most successful brands – including Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts, Southwest Airlines, USAirways,Verizon Wireless, Wells Fargo and Walmart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pace is seeking a Digital and Content Strategist to work on key digital projects across multiple platforms (web, mobile, etc.) and for a portfolio of world class, Fortune 100  brands. This role will lead teams in developing and executing actionable, data-driven content strategies on user-focused platforms and in collaboration with editorial, design, development and analytic teams. This position will help lead editorial approach &amp;amp; content planning from initial strategy and solutions to implementation and post-launch optimization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Content Strategist will fuse the technical focus of content strategy (emphasis on content systems, organization and structure, metadata modeling) with audience definition (attribute modeling, persona design).  The successful candidate has experience leveraging multiple data sources (Simmons, AdWords, etc) for customer insights and facilitating interactive workshops to define audience types and expectations as well as have substantive experience in structuring content to support the delivery of personalized messages in diverse environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibility&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing unique content strategies based on business objectives and defined user needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determining a program’s overall content requirements and potential content sources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining target personas and customer journeys&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining KPIs for tracking success of digital content experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing innovative solutions for content presentation, including content management, workflow, and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating content taxonomy and metadata frameworks for content structure and relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auditing existing and legacy content that will inform overall content strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing content mapping and instructional documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;No phone calls please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer m/f/d/v&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-digital-strategy-and-content-pace-communications-greensboro-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-digital-strategy-and-content-pace-communications-greensboro-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>