<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nc-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Director Digital Strategy &amp; Content at Pace Communications in Greensboro, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Pace Communications, one of the largest content marketing agencies in the country, is now accepting resumes for a Director, Digital Strategy &amp;amp; Content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pace is one of the largest and most successful agencies of its type in the world – our people are recognized as leaders in the field and our account list includes some of the North America’s most successful brands – including Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts, Southwest Airlines, USAirways,Verizon Wireless, Wells Fargo and Walmart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pace is seeking a Digital and Content Strategist to work on key digital projects across multiple platforms (web, mobile, etc.) and for a portfolio of world class, Fortune 100  brands. This role will lead teams in developing and executing actionable, data-driven content strategies on user-focused platforms and in collaboration with editorial, design, development and analytic teams. This position will help lead editorial approach &amp;amp; content planning from initial strategy and solutions to implementation and post-launch optimization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Content Strategist will fuse the technical focus of content strategy (emphasis on content systems, organization and structure, metadata modeling) with audience definition (attribute modeling, persona design).  The successful candidate has experience leveraging multiple data sources (Simmons, AdWords, etc) for customer insights and facilitating interactive workshops to define audience types and expectations as well as have substantive experience in structuring content to support the delivery of personalized messages in diverse environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibility&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing unique content strategies based on business objectives and defined user needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determining a program’s overall content requirements and potential content sources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining target personas and customer journeys&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining KPIs for tracking success of digital content experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing innovative solutions for content presentation, including content management, workflow, and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating content taxonomy and metadata frameworks for content structure and relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auditing existing and legacy content that will inform overall content strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing content mapping and instructional documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;No phone calls please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer m/f/d/v&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-digital-strategy-and-content-pace-communications-greensboro-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-digital-strategy-and-content-pace-communications-greensboro-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>