<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nc-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Ashe Avenue in Chapel Hill, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Ashe Avenue is looking for an experienced Front-end Developer responsible for producing HTML markup, CSS and client-side engineering solutions for websites and web applications. The position requires extensive knowledge and understanding of HTML, CSS and JavaScript. This role is production focused with a commitment to client success through a balance of quality, prioritization, creativity and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a collaborative environment and communicate effectively to other members of the team both verbally and in written documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop using the latest client-side web technologies, specifically HTML5, CSS and JavaScript (jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remain current on new technologies and design trends for web, mobile and social media platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with design, development and client services teams to maintain creative and efficient production processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the estimating and scoping process for new work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and contribute to coding standards to promote best practices and community building both internally and externally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommend timely, researched, high-quality solutions and services to clients to further business objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest areas for improvement in internal processes, along with possible solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work in Brooklyn, NY or Chapel Hill, NC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;These attributes are pretty essential:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands the application of and demonstrates expert knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses excellent working knowledge of the Adobe Creative Suite, specifically Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrives in a team environment and facilitates effective team interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with source control principles and comfortable with Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with coding and deploying applications in a cross-platform and cross-browser environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CMS integration and maintenance, especially Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with MVC frameworks such as Yii, Rails, Symphony and CodeIgniter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PHP, Ruby and other Web programming languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with integrating websites and web applications with social media platforms and third party APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in becoming a part of this great and rapidly growing team, please send us your resume, cover letter and work samples.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ashe-avenue-chapel-hill-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ashe-avenue-chapel-hill-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Ashe Avenue in Chapel Hill, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Ashe Avenue is looking for an experienced Front-end Developer responsible for producing HTML markup, CSS and client-side engineering solutions for websites and web applications. The position requires extensive knowledge and understanding of HTML, CSS and JavaScript. This role is production focused with a commitment to client success through a balance of quality, prioritization, creativity and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a collaborative environment and communicate effectively to other members of the team both verbally and in written documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop using the latest client-side web technologies, specifically HTML5, CSS and JavaScript (jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remain current on new technologies and design trends for web, mobile and social media platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with design, development and client services teams to maintain creative and efficient production processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the estimating and scoping process for new work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and contribute to coding standards to promote best practices and community building both internally and externally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommend timely, researched, high-quality solutions and services to clients to further business objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest areas for improvement in internal processes, along with possible solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work in Brooklyn, NY or Chapel Hill, NC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;These attributes are pretty essential:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands the application of and demonstrates expert knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses excellent working knowledge of the Adobe Creative Suite, specifically Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrives in a team environment and facilitates effective team interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with source control principles and comfortable with Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with coding and deploying applications in a cross-platform and cross-browser environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CMS integration and maintenance, especially Drupal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with MVC frameworks such as Yii, Rails, Symphony and CodeIgniter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PHP, Ruby and other Web programming languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with integrating websites and web applications with social media platforms and third party APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in becoming a part of this great and rapidly growing team, please send us your resume, cover letter and work samples.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ashe-avenue-chapel-hill-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ashe-avenue-chapel-hill-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Caktus Consulting Group, LLC in Carrboro, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Caktus is a team of sharp web developers and designers who build high quality web applications. We are based in Carrboro, NC and we love collaborating on projects with our clients, who range from small non-profits (State Educational Technology Directors Association) to universities (UNC, UChicago) and large organizations (UNICEF, Mozilla, and CBS). We especially enjoy education and health focused work. Our passion is creating high quality, custom products. And we do it well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a professional user experience designer and front end web developer who enjoys working on a team and is excited to make beautiful, user friendly websites. Our front end web developers design in code and collaborate directly with the development team. They are hybrids: designers with a deep understanding of code and implementation. The ideal team member is also motivated to learn and work on new and diverse projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your work will involve:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading the design and front-end development efforts on your projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Branding, prototyping and designing pages for small and large web apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloning project repositories and running Django locally for development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating mockups and wireframes of proposed designs and user stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Converting PSDs into standards compliant HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performing front-end JavaScript and jQuery development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with and incorporating feedback from clients, project managers and developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of professional web design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong command of HTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of jQuery and other JavaScript frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intimate knowledge of cross-browser compatibility, web standards and SEO best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of template libraries (e.g. Django, jinja2, liquid, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of JSON, XML and interacting with public APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of usability and user experience (UX) design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good eye for layout, composition and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with distributed version control (Git, Mercurial)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always learning new web technologies and is active in the open source world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoys a fast pace, dynamic, challenging and team-oriented work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing mobile-optimized web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points For&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some Python experience is a plus, Django is even better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in this position, email jobs+website@caktusgroup.com with your resume. Kindly include a brief letter stating why you think you&amp;rsquo;d be a great fit for this opportunity.  Please include a few links to GitHub or Bitbucket repositories with examples of your work, detailing your involvement in each project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caktus is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary commensurate with experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confidentiality is ensured.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-caktus-consulting-group-llc-carrboro-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-caktus-consulting-group-llc-carrboro-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer - Internship at Caktus Consulting Group, LLC in Carrboro, NC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Come be a part of a small team of developers and designers passionate about creating fun and interactive web applications. Caktus is looking for someone who is excited about emerging technologies, creating compelling user experiences and enjoys writing Python. As a member of the Caktus team, you’ll be involved in every aspect of development, from brainstorming to prototyping, Django development, and front-end HTML/CSS and JavaScript work. You’ll learn and collaborate directly with a great group of talented developers and designers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;This summer experience includes:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position: A 12 week summer internship in Carrboro, NC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure: Great experience and education in current web development techniques and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentorship: At Caktus, you’ll get to work with some of the best and brightest minds in the Django community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You will do some or all of the following during the summer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Caktus developers on Django-powered web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform front-end development in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript (jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on internal Caktus projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in design and code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create mockups and wireframes of proposed design ideas and user stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with usability and user experience (UX) design (Don’t Make Me Think!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become familiar with Linux (Debian-flavor) desktop and server environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about test driven development and other agile methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use relational databases, such as PostgreSQL or MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;We’d love to meet someone who (not all required):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience developing rich applications with HTML/CSS/JS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is familiar with Django/Python or a similar framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is excited to work with HTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively uses Github or BitBucket to collaborate and share code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has an design eye for simplicity and user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is comfortable using Photoshop and/or InDesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is actively engaged in open source communities and learning about new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience with rapid prototyping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the full-time 12-week position, we will pay a fixed amount, commensurate with experience, that is pro-rated and paid monthly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How to Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in this position, email jobs+website@caktusgroup.com with your resume. Kindly include a brief letter stating why you think you&amp;rsquo;d be a great fit for this opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caktus is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary commensurate with experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confidentiality is ensured.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-internship-caktus-consulting-group-llc-carrboro-nc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-internship-caktus-consulting-group-llc-carrboro-nc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>