<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ne-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at Boar's Head in Lincoln, NE</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a user experience designer, you will be working on designing new products using the various concepts of interaction and user experience design. You will work closely with the product managers and software engineering to create an enhanced customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;External requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strong HTML and JavaScript (AJAX, DOM, JSON) and Java skills
CSS experience
SVN or source management experience
Java, Servlets and JSP/JSTL experience
Knowledge of the Structured Query Language (SQL), relational database principles and JDBC connection technology
Prototype and Scriptaculous experience
Strong User Interfacing knowledge
Database experience (e.g., MySQL, IBM DB2)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;External responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with back-end developers to find ways to push the limits of existing Web technology in service of creating the best*  possible user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive the User Experience by translating requirements into defined User Interface (UI) Specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create UI Designs, interaction diagrams, mock-ups and prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate business requirements into innovative applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain the visual style guide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate new UI technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create innovative UI solutions to solve complex interaction issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with product management team to establish user experience vision and guiding principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independently able to manage design process, project and schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritize and manage multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to solve both strategic and tactical UI issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years experience in HTML and JavaScript (AJAX, DOM, JSON) and Java skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year experience in Java, Servlets and JSP/JSTL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year experience in SVN or source management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years experience in User Interfacing knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English: Fluent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years experience in HTML and JavaScript (AJAX, DOM, JSON) and Java skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years experience in User Interfacing knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;IBM is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, disability, age, or veteran status.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-boar%27s-head-lincoln-ne</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-boar%27s-head-lincoln-ne</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>