<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nh-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile UI Designer at Bottomline Technologies in Portsmouth, NH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bottomline Technologies is seeking an experienced mobile UI Designer for our mobile group. This is an exciting opportunity to join a talented and dynamic team of mobile and web UI/UX professionals. The Mobile UI Designer will be designing native applications that are used globally for banking, healthcare, insurance activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is based in our Portsmouth, NH office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and translate complex web application tasks for appropriate mobile experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create full lifecycles of application design from storyboards through final design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan and facilitate user experience research and testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find innovative solutions by using mobile capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage native platform interaction principles for platform specific applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate native mobile design efforts with web-based application efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years hands on design in Mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In depth knowledge of iOS UI Guidelines and Android Design Principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated comfort in both reinventing the wheel and leverage existing UI models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in an Agile Scrum Development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B.A or B.S degree in Graphic Design, Interaction Design, Human Computer Interaction, Human Factors or other design related fields&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Bottomline Technologies:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottomline Technologies provides collaborative payment, invoice and document automation solutions to corporations, financial institutions and banks around the world. The company&amp;rsquo;s solutions are used to streamline, automate and manage processes involving payments, invoicing, global cash management, supply chain finance and transactional documents. Organizations trust these solutions to meet their needs for cost reduction, competitive differentiation and optimization of working capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serving industries such as financial services, insurance, health care, technology, communications, education, media, manufacturing and government, Bottomline provides products and services to approximately 80 of the Fortune 100 companies and 70 of the FTSE (Financial Times) 100 companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottomline is a participating employer in the Employment Verification (E-Verify) program EOE/AA/M/F/V/D/E-Verify Employer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottomline Technologies is an Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please Note: Bottomline Technologies does not accept resumes submitted by recruiting firms unless specifically requested by Human Resources. Unsolicited resumes will be ineligible for referral fees.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-ui-designer-bottomline-technologies-portsmouth-nh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-ui-designer-bottomline-technologies-portsmouth-nh</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>