<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nh-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Developer at Dyn in Manchester, NH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a Front-End/UI Developer, you will be responsible for creating new and improved User Interfaces for our Managed DNS platform.  You will work closely with Product Management and UI/UX Design to create and maintain a library of styles and controls through rapid prototyping and iteration. If you have a strong sense of consumer design, want to work hard in a fast paced environment for a rapidly growing company and would like to see some of the largest internet companies benefit from the results of your work then this is the job for you. You will be constantly collaborating with Product Management and Engineering to shape our products. We know that our ability to motivate and educate customers drives efficient results, so we use our insights from customer research to design engaging products that inspire real, positive action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage User Experience assets including (but not limited to) wireframes, user flows, information architectures, site map and taxonomy to produce functionally and structurally accurate user interfaces; approve UX assets to ensure UI can be produced on time and within budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage Creative Design compositions and mockups to strive for &amp;ldquo;pixel perfect&amp;rdquo; user interfaces; provide feedback where necessary to ensure proposed creative assets can be executed on time and within budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive the direction of the DynECT DNS user interface, clearly representing it as the leading product in the IaaS industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage expertise in the most powerful UI technologies available, such as HTML5, JavaScript, CSS, and AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with engineers to create a best-in-class UI that is conducive to the capabilities and limitations of the DynECT DNS business layer and data layer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work across functions to solve design challenges and accurately communicate expectations by seeking input from Product Management, Architecture, Development, and UX/UI colleagues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with UI/UX Teams to maintain and establish UI best-practices, patterns, and development frameworks within the DNS team and across teams for all products with a focus on Test-Driven Development and Test Automation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;General Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven analytical and problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good interpersonal skills &amp;ndash; you like working with a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in XHTML, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, and RESTful web services (JSON, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience planning and coding interfaces with flexible layouts using Responsive Design techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience developing web applications as a part of a product development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, CSS, or Javascript as technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Perl&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interest in creating great user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Other Desirable Skills&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile app development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing interfaces for data visualization and analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of or experience within other layers of the development stack: Linux, SQL variants, PHP, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual UI design skills (Photoshop comps)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-developer-dyn-manchester-nh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-developer-dyn-manchester-nh</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>