<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nj-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Experienced PHP Magento Developer at Triveni IT in North Bergen, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are a Web Application Development Company based in New Jersey (about 10 mins from NYC). Our team is looking for experienced PHP Developer with background in Magento Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;This full-time position will encompass the following responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Back-end web application developer (eCommerce, CRM/ERP feature development)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end user experience developer (feature development / web design implementation)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key holder of IT architecture (IDE, source control, performance monitoring)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web developer to help support, build and develop Web application solutions (internet, extranet, and internet)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather and analyze the business requirement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, customize and implement high-quality Magento ecommerce web solutions and custom web applications using PHP inclusive of testing, deployment, and documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan and coordinate Magento release maintenance for support packages and notes by evaluating and recommending support stacks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with Magento migration/upgrades&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create custom Magento modules or other new functionality using object-oriented PHP and the Magento APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand and effectively communicate Magento features and limitations with regard to design and development decisions on new projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and execute the Test Scenario/Test Scripts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work effectively in a team environment, providing knowledge transfer as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communications skills, ability to interact with business resources and comfortable operating at all levels of the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Background/skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor in Information Systems, Computer Science, or related field, or academic equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magento administration and development, including web development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Linux, Apache web server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Search Engine Optimization (SEO).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience in configuring and supporting Magento implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of RDBMS- MySQL Server and SQL query&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Employee Type:  Full-Time Employee
Experience Required:    0 Years
Degree Required:    Not Specified
Travel Required:    Not Specified&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum Pay:    Not Specified
Average Bonus:  Not Specified
Average Commission:     Not Specified
Other Compensation:     Not Specified&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Company Website:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.triveniit.com&quot;&gt;http://www.triveniit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/experienced-php-magento-developer-triveni-it-north-bergen-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/experienced-php-magento-developer-triveni-it-north-bergen-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Rutgers University in Camden, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Law IT is seeking a strong and experienced candidate to design and develop innovative web applications for a variety of university constituencies. This position, under the Director of Information Technology, will work closely with faculty, staff and students to design, develop, code, test, implement and maintain web based applications using a combination of coding and productivity tools. This position will also provide advanced support to users of our content management systems in both Drupal and Wordpress. Strong experience with relational database design and web programming is essential. This position will also participate as a member of the Law IT help desk team and will provide basic helpdesk support to faculty, staff and students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor’s degree in information technology, computer science or related field, or equivalent work experience with 3 or more years of programming experience with solid knowledge of current programming languages and methodologies. In addition to technical skill, the developer must be able to collaborate and communicate effectively with all levels of university faculty, staff and administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Preference will be given to candidates with the following areas of experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coding HTML, JavaScript and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scripting with PHP/Perl&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing relational databases using MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supporting Drupal and Wordpress, including module/plugin development and multi-site configuration and management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Programming Web 2.0 application development using dynamic JavaScript libraries (jQuery, Prototype, etc..)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrating SOAP or RESTful API web services into advanced web projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and develop web applications for standard and mobile web sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with faculty, staff and students to analyze site requirements and develop fully featured web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop project scope, deliverables and schedules for website projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other designers and programmers to complete web projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, develop and maintain new modules and themes for Drupal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and secure current web properties by applying patches and updates, re-working older code and transitioning to new development frameworks as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide basic PC &amp;amp; Mac desktop support as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-rutgers-university-camden-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-rutgers-university-camden-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>