<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nj-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at StreamWIDE Inc in New Jersey</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;UX designer will be part of StreamWIDE Marketing department inside the User Interface Team. He(she) will be responsible for User experience x design and ergonomics for StreamWIDE applications interfaces (mobile  and web apps)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designer is responsible for carrying ergonomics studies and recommendations, delivering written functional specifications, UI maps, wireframes, storyboards, application’ prototypes and implementation guidelines for development teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concerned interfaces range from consumer-oriented services delivered on smartphones to interfaces to back-office/administration-oriented web GUI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile interfaces design will take in account the different mobile OS constraints and specificities, whether Android, iOS, Windows Phone or Blackberry native development up to HTML5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting directly to the marketing director, designer interacts closely with marketing, artistic direction and product development teams and is likely to interact also with sales and top management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PROFILE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years experience in similar duties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Mobile UX design and ergonomics is mandatory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates focusing on visual part of specifications only and afraid of writing detailed use cases or scenarios should not apply&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with complex telecom services/apps is a +&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in prototyping software such as Axure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interest for high-tech environments, ability to understand what’s “behind the app”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English and French (mandatory), 3rd language would be an additional asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interface with development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-energy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication and empathy skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;JOB LOCATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paris or New Jersey
Job can imply travels (less than 20%).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;REMUNERATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be determined according to experience and profile&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-streamwide-inc-new-jersey</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-streamwide-inc-new-jersey</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at MRM Worldwide in Princeton, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Responsible for all aspects of client’s online and offline advertising. Design and production art and layouts for material to be presented by visual communications media such as digital media, publications, television, packaging and client presentations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and Production in a wide variety of styles for online and offline media (Digital: Banners, Email, Mobile and other Online Media. Print: Brochures, POS, Packaging, Inserts, etc. Presentation: Keynote, PowerPoint).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interaction with Graphic Services, Production, Creative, Account, Technology, Medical Editing, Strategy, Operations and Executive Teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for designs that are on strategy and reflect brand’s personality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitors projects through all phases of production, including Concepting, Production, Quality Control, Quality Assurance, Presentation and Release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides input, direction and communication to all involved disciplines throughout design and production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adheres design and projects to budgets and time constraints.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivers presentations to team and/or senior personnel and clients as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhibits expertise on all design trends and historic design influences and adheres to client branding and design styles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs skills within each individual project’s parameters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains time sheets and project budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for supporting leadership within department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complies to quality standards for the team as set forth by the department head&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with supervisor to foster innovative solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Builds relationship at appropriate client/vender level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works closely with upper management to identify and suggest solutions on how to improve departmental and team morale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps abreast of current trends and the latest technological advances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps to elevate department’s role in the whole advertising process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate’s Degree or equivalent from a two-year college or technical school required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five or more years of related work experience and/or training or equivalent combination of education and experience required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of printing and digital processes. Knowledge of photography, illustration, typography and digital formats preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding and experience of Digital Production Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding and experience of Print Production Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem solving skills and detail oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organization skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to listen and take direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;COMMUNICATION ABILITY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to read and interpret.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write reports and simple correspondence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to speak effectively before groups and other employees of the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REASONING ABILITY and ABILITY TO LEARN QUICKLY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to apply common sense understanding to carry out instructions furnished in written, oral or diagram form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to deal with problems involving several concrete variables in standardized situations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to grasp learning new skills and Applications with the constant advancement of emerging technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;COMPUTER SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outstanding knowledge of Macintosh Operating System and Expertise in the following Applications:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite 5.5+:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;InDesign: Must be at expert level and know major points of application when applied to Print and Digital. InDesign is a major work tool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop: Must be at expert level and know major points of application when applied to Print and Digital. Must be familiar with using application for web productivity, including Smart Objects, Layer Comps and Applying Effects (Having Retouching capabilities a plus+)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrator: Must be at expert level and know major points of application when applied to Print and Digital.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash: Having Flash Skills a plus+. Candidate would work with Motion Graphics team to assist and advance skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other: Having Skills in other applications a plus+.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having knowledge of other application or tools that can advance the capabilities of the work environment a plus+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowing other Applications in Adobe Creative Suite a plus+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowing Video Applications a plus+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having Coding Skills a plus+&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;MS Office:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Word: Must have basic application skills. Advanced skills a plus+ (Style Sheets, Long Documents, Formatting, MAC and PC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excel: Must have basic application skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PowerPoint: Must have basic application skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Skills a Plus+ (Full Presentations, Builds, Design, PC and MAC environment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keynote: Having Skills a plus+. Advanced Skills a Plus+ (Full Presentations, Builds, Transitions, Design)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Many other applications are used and may be learned already or applicant will receive needed training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;WORK ENVIRONMENT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normal office environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PHYSICAL DEMANDS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While performing the duties of this job, the employee is regularly required to talk or hear. The employee is frequently required to walk; sit and use hands to finger, handle, or feel. The employee is occasionally required to stand; reach with hands and arms; stoop, kneel, crouch, and crawl. The vision requirements include: ability to adjust focus and close vision and be color proficient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While performing the duties of this job, the employee is occasionally exposed to fumes or airborne particles and toxic or caustic chemicals.
Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-mrm-worldwide-princeton-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-mrm-worldwide-princeton-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>