<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nj-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer - Web &amp; Print at eMaint Enterprises in Marlton, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;While the job title is Graphic Designer, this is really a visual communicator who excels in graphic and image asset creation. If you can read something that describes a technology product or service, and can add attention-grabbing appeal, you&amp;rsquo;ll be the right person for this career opportunity. The person who fills this position will deliver consistent and compelling designs across a variety of media including our websites, emails and print collateral. You should be passionate about combining written content with graphics that best convey our message in a consistent and professional fashion. At eMaint we are a team in everything we do, so your ability to work collaboratively is essential. This position reports to the Director of Marketing while providing support for multiple teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graphic Designer will be responsible for creating content for websites, email, print collateral and external advertising campaigns. This position will play a central role from end-to-end as a design and production resource for the management of all websites. Primary responsibilities include designing website and print concepts and working closely with the marketing team to perform implementation. Additional responsibilities include various corporate identity, print and interactive projects and presentation designs. Must have a strong eye for layout and graphic design and experience in a deadline-driven agency or corporate setting. We are looking for a team player willing to bring new ideas to the table, but also somebody who executes production work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of original and compelling designs for online and offline marketing assets including website design mockups, website banners, email campaigns, direct mail, newsletters, brochures, signage and event materials for a variety of projects and campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with marketing and executive teams to understand strategy and objectives of each project and deliver concepts that are not only visually appealing but meet strategic objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide graphics support for marketing, customer communications and product teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once designs are approved, be able to move quickly to turn concepts into fully expedited web pages or print-ready pieces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage several jobs simultaneously in an organized manner, and work quickly and efficiently to deliver per established deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the identification of website enhancements by suggesting navigation and content improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain style guide for consistency in branding across all marketing channels (online and offline).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep current with emerging digital trends and share innovations with team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Arts in Graphic Design or related field, and/or 3+ years of relevant print &amp;amp; web design supplemented by a strong portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of HTML, CSS and Adobe Creative Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with standards compliant web design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of creating your own graphic assets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a deadline-driven, results-oriented ad agency or corporate setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct marketing experience in a BTB environment a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a self-starter and passionate about his/her job. Constantly strives to develop innovative solutions that result in enhanced results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design portfolio required. Be prepared to speak about the results of your work &amp;ndash; response rates, email open rates, page conversion rates, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly conceptualize and iterate designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of XML, PHP and JavaScript a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative vision with an eye for detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong graphic, typography, and design skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ideal candidate not only has a strong sense of design and understands usability, but is also on top of cutting edge trends for web and mobile interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to translate business goals and user needs into actionable branding, visual and digital designs while meeting deadlines and expectations for quality, creativity and accuracy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of video editing software is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-web-and-print-emaint-enterprises-marlton-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-web-and-print-emaint-enterprises-marlton-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director / Designer at RITTA in Englewood, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We need an experienced art director / designer with many talents. If you have the right combination, you can unlock the door to a fantastic opportunity!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are that designer, you totally understand and adhere to corporate and product branding. But that doesn’t stop you from having fun creating a wide range of branded content across all media platforms – print, packaging, digital, video, experiential, etc. We will look to you to help create innovative online design for websites, banners, landing pages, emails, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because you’ll be working closely with your teammates, you play well with others. Better yet, you inspire creativity in others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You are…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to judge and organize information for idea/concept generation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to sell your work internally and to the client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident and professional.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly organized, with attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A self-starter able to prioritize multiple work assignments and meet deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop and Dreamweaver. (Any knowledge of HTML, CSS and JavaScript earns brownie points.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You also have…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A unique, original portfolio of diverse creative work demonstrating a strong understanding of online trends, technology and design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating branded micro-sites for products and content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of industry best practices in web design, interactive design, and social media trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An affinity for marketing high-end and luxury brands, and an enthusiasm for promoting automotive, consumer electronics and home appliance products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years’ agency experience – especially working with brand style guides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you have the key talents we need, don’t wait. Email your resume with a cover letter detailing your experience, salary history, and salary requirements. You just may open the door to your dream future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-designer-ritta-englewood-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-designer-ritta-englewood-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at MRM Worldwide in Princeton, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;You Should Be Able to:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceive and execute visual solutions consistent with the agreed strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce interface design adhering to best practices in UX design and color theory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell visual stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be  responsible for original visual conceptions and typographical and visual treatments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry an established tone and manner forward and vary as needed for different formats, from print, to digital, to social or mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the technology we design for, from mobile devices, to web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under the direction, and with the approval of their supervisior see work through to finished production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work productively and harmoniously as a teammate with copywriters and production/producers who share responsibility on the given assignment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comply to quality standards for the team as set forth by the department head&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with supervisor to foster innovative solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep abreast of current trends and the latest technological advances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop concepts and/or comps that adhere to the platforms and channels agreed to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meet with Account and Project Management to review work in progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revise recommendations based on any client comments and share approved recommendations with all departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debrief and present project team with key findings at the conclusion of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in weekly departmental staff meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps supervisor apprised of the status of work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You Should Have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talent, judgment and imagination for creation and arrangement of visual and interface design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience as a Designer/Art Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio required to demonstrate creative and technical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have 1+ years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produced print materials, interface designs, for multiple paged web site, mobile, applications, and other forms of digital marketing communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, both written and oral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem solving skills and detail oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latest Adobe Photoshop CS6, Adobe Illustrator CS6, Adobe Image Ready, Acrobat, Microsoft Word, Photo retouching, Basic illustration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A plus is, knowledge of basic Code writing &amp;amp; editing: for Flash (AS3 &amp;amp; 2; HTML; &amp;amp; XML);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A plus is, knowledge of api’s &amp;amp; vendor languages such as: Eyeblaster, Pointroll, Eyewonder, Atlas, Gigya, Clearspring, Facebook, Myspace, igoogle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-mrm-worldwide-princeton-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-mrm-worldwide-princeton-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Advanced Group in Wayne, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About the Organization:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client, a leading consumer product/retail company is seeking a Freelance Senior Graphic Designer.  To be considered for this role you must be able to create designs, logos, store visuals/signage, catalogs and other ad related  materials.  You must be able to execute accurate work under a fast pace and tight deadline that require minimal art direction.  You should also be skilled at managing multiple projects while meeting all deadlines and work closely with Creative Director, Copywriters, Illustrators and design team to collaborate in creating great designs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe InDesign, Illustrator and Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 plus years in a Design role with a portfolio that reflects technical skills as well as original designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio must possess logos and strong type layout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be conceptual and have the ability to translate briefs into clear visual designs within our clients brand look and feel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail work strongly preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This role is a temporary, full time, onsite 3-month assignment.  The chosen candidate will be eligible for WunderLand&amp;rsquo;s benefits package and will receive unmatched customer service and support from their WunderLand representatives!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We thank you for considering WunderLand, your destination for digital and traditional communications staffing &amp;amp; recruiting!  We&amp;rsquo;ve built and continue to maintain long-term relationships with some of the most desirable companies and with highly-skilled and talented design, marketing, advertising, digital, and communications professionals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please apply today with resume &amp;amp; samples for immediate consideration, and also follow us on: Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/#!/WunderLandGroup&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/#!/WunderLandGroup&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp;  Linked in &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.linkedin.com/company/353356?trk=tyah&quot;&gt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/353356?trk=tyah&lt;/a&gt;, Like us on Facebook &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.facebook.com/wunderlandgroup&quot;&gt;http://www.facebook.com/wunderlandgroup&lt;/a&gt; and visit us at www.wunderlandgroup.com today!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-advanced-group-wayne-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-advanced-group-wayne-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at NICE Systems in Paramus, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage all projects from start to finish — concept ideation, art direction, design, pre-press,  production and quality control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the graphic design needs of the marketing, sales, client service and product development department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish and apply brand standards across multiple channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consult with in-house clients to analyze project requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, layout and format projects on a Mac platform, including — but not limited to — HTML emails, banner and print advertisements, web pages, landing pages and microsites, videos, brochures, white papers, sales sheets and presentations, trade show displays and signage, product documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visually integrate typographic, photographic, and illustrative elements to create high-impact designs that engage the target audience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop or search/acquire the imagery used in all materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photo retouching/resizing/color correction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce leading edge marketing material including print collateral, event merchandising and internal sales tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates storyboards for demos, animations, videos or presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sketch preliminary concepts &amp;amp; “put ideas to paper” based on management input&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure final art meets specifications and is prepped for its target medium (i.e. web, print)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Design, Graphic Design, Fine Arts, Industrial Design and/or related area required; a combination of education and experience may substitute for a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience with proven ability to lead and direct Design styles and efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience in a global high-tech company &amp;amp; a corporate marketing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be highly proficient with interactive web technologies, software or web applications, as well as print and branding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of user interface design, wireframes, layout and typography, branding, color processes, print production/pre-press and production for online&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in print graphic design including:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collateral design: Brochures, Rollup banners, Datasheets, Ads, Posters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documentation design: White Papers, case studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PPT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design – to support regional and local changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency with standard and dynamic design software packages (Photoshop, Flash, etc.) required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic support during trade shows and company events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Service oriented- working with company global headquarters to support global and local needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills along with ability to meet deadlines in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess strong attention to detail and be able to work as a team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-nice-systems-paramus-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-nice-systems-paramus-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at StreamWIDE Inc in New Jersey</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;UX designer will be part of StreamWIDE Marketing department inside the User Interface Team. He(she) will be responsible for User experience x design and ergonomics for StreamWIDE applications interfaces (mobile  and web apps)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designer is responsible for carrying ergonomics studies and recommendations, delivering written functional specifications, UI maps, wireframes, storyboards, application’ prototypes and implementation guidelines for development teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concerned interfaces range from consumer-oriented services delivered on smartphones to interfaces to back-office/administration-oriented web GUI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile interfaces design will take in account the different mobile OS constraints and specificities, whether Android, iOS, Windows Phone or Blackberry native development up to HTML5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting directly to the marketing director, designer interacts closely with marketing, artistic direction and product development teams and is likely to interact also with sales and top management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PROFILE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years experience in similar duties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Mobile UX design and ergonomics is mandatory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates focusing on visual part of specifications only and afraid of writing detailed use cases or scenarios should not apply&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with complex telecom services/apps is a +&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in prototyping software such as Axure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interest for high-tech environments, ability to understand what’s “behind the app”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English and French (mandatory), 3rd language would be an additional asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interface with development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-energy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication and empathy skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;JOB LOCATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paris or New Jersey
Job can imply travels (less than 20%).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;REMUNERATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be determined according to experience and profile&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-streamwide-inc-new-jersey</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-streamwide-inc-new-jersey</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at MRM Worldwide in Princeton, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Responsible for all aspects of client’s online and offline advertising. Design and production art and layouts for material to be presented by visual communications media such as digital media, publications, television, packaging and client presentations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and Production in a wide variety of styles for online and offline media (Digital: Banners, Email, Mobile and other Online Media. Print: Brochures, POS, Packaging, Inserts, etc. Presentation: Keynote, PowerPoint).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interaction with Graphic Services, Production, Creative, Account, Technology, Medical Editing, Strategy, Operations and Executive Teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for designs that are on strategy and reflect brand’s personality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitors projects through all phases of production, including Concepting, Production, Quality Control, Quality Assurance, Presentation and Release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides input, direction and communication to all involved disciplines throughout design and production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adheres design and projects to budgets and time constraints.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivers presentations to team and/or senior personnel and clients as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhibits expertise on all design trends and historic design influences and adheres to client branding and design styles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs skills within each individual project’s parameters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains time sheets and project budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for supporting leadership within department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complies to quality standards for the team as set forth by the department head&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with supervisor to foster innovative solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Builds relationship at appropriate client/vender level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works closely with upper management to identify and suggest solutions on how to improve departmental and team morale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps abreast of current trends and the latest technological advances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps to elevate department’s role in the whole advertising process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate’s Degree or equivalent from a two-year college or technical school required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five or more years of related work experience and/or training or equivalent combination of education and experience required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of printing and digital processes. Knowledge of photography, illustration, typography and digital formats preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding and experience of Digital Production Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding and experience of Print Production Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem solving skills and detail oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organization skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to listen and take direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;COMMUNICATION ABILITY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to read and interpret.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write reports and simple correspondence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to speak effectively before groups and other employees of the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REASONING ABILITY and ABILITY TO LEARN QUICKLY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to apply common sense understanding to carry out instructions furnished in written, oral or diagram form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to deal with problems involving several concrete variables in standardized situations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to grasp learning new skills and Applications with the constant advancement of emerging technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;COMPUTER SKILLS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outstanding knowledge of Macintosh Operating System and Expertise in the following Applications:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite 5.5+:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;InDesign: Must be at expert level and know major points of application when applied to Print and Digital. InDesign is a major work tool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop: Must be at expert level and know major points of application when applied to Print and Digital. Must be familiar with using application for web productivity, including Smart Objects, Layer Comps and Applying Effects (Having Retouching capabilities a plus+)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrator: Must be at expert level and know major points of application when applied to Print and Digital.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash: Having Flash Skills a plus+. Candidate would work with Motion Graphics team to assist and advance skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other: Having Skills in other applications a plus+.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having knowledge of other application or tools that can advance the capabilities of the work environment a plus+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowing other Applications in Adobe Creative Suite a plus+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowing Video Applications a plus+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having Coding Skills a plus+&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;MS Office:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Word: Must have basic application skills. Advanced skills a plus+ (Style Sheets, Long Documents, Formatting, MAC and PC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excel: Must have basic application skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PowerPoint: Must have basic application skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Skills a Plus+ (Full Presentations, Builds, Design, PC and MAC environment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keynote: Having Skills a plus+. Advanced Skills a Plus+ (Full Presentations, Builds, Transitions, Design)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Many other applications are used and may be learned already or applicant will receive needed training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;WORK ENVIRONMENT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normal office environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PHYSICAL DEMANDS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While performing the duties of this job, the employee is regularly required to talk or hear. The employee is frequently required to walk; sit and use hands to finger, handle, or feel. The employee is occasionally required to stand; reach with hands and arms; stoop, kneel, crouch, and crawl. The vision requirements include: ability to adjust focus and close vision and be color proficient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While performing the duties of this job, the employee is occasionally exposed to fumes or airborne particles and toxic or caustic chemicals.
Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-mrm-worldwide-princeton-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-mrm-worldwide-princeton-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>