<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nj-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Creative Director at JK Design in Hillsborough, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;JK Design &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jkdesign.com&quot;&gt;http://www.jkdesign.com&lt;/a&gt;, is a full service marketing agency with a 28+ year history. NJBiz has ranked us as one of their Top 50 New Jersey Internet Technology Firms annually since 2003! Our office is located in a relaxed environment located next to a pond in central New Jersey. Most of our clients are also in central NJ. However some are as far as Denver, Wisconcin, Connecticut and Maryland. You would be required to work on-site at our Hillsborough NJ office, and on occasion meet with our clients in our NYC office or at their locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Interactive team creates small to large Websites, applications for Mobile Devices, and Video Productions mixing Animated Motion Graphics with Live Footage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have an immediate need for a full-time Interactive Creative Director, to join our Interactive Team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would report to the VP of Interactive, with a dotted line to the Creative Director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attends some client business development and project meetings, representing design aspect and capabilities of JK Design and projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with creating Wire Frames for some projects, guiding producers/project managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze Site Maps and Wire frames and discuss with producers/project managers and subsequently determine design approaches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create graphical user interface designs for Websites using Adobe Photoshop, Flash Animation &amp;amp; Games, Email Marketing Designs, iPad Interfaces, and CD/DVD interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create storyboards and treatments for initial video/motion graphic concepts. Create subsequent Motion Graphics using Adobe After Effects, integrating live action or stock footage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Art directs other designers relating to layout, tone, style, color, interactive and animation techniques for Web, Mobile, Video, Animation, Touch Screens/Kiosks, CD/DVD etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervise the work of Interactive Artists, Animators and Flash Designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews, requests revisions and approves all interactive designs and motion graphic videos, prior to presenting to the client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with account managers, producers/project managers, design staff and programmers to ensure a high level of usability in the end product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takes into account opinion of account managers and producers, but in conjunction with the Creative Director (Jerry), makes the final decision on designs and interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommends new software tools that may improve upon design quality and effects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a self starter, have high standards, be able to work independently and on a team to meet aggressive deadlines, even if requiring extended work hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience Required:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing Interactive Web sites using Adobe Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating Motion Graphics using Adobe After Effects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be comfortable using a Macintosh as your workstation operating system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of basic HTML5 and CSS3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Strong Plusses (but not required):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating Flash Animation with ActionScript 3 using Object Oriented coding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating Flash applications that retrieve data using a server side language such as PHP and/or parse XML with Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to build Flash and HTML5 Video Players and how to create and optimize video files for streaming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Adobe Air.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video Editing Skills (Adobe Premiere, Avid system or Apple Final Cut Pro).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary commensurates with experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In your cover letter, please include your portfolio links, salary history and salary requirements, and indicate that you are applying for the &amp;ldquo;Interactive Art Director&amp;rdquo; position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-creative-director-jk-design-hillsborough-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-creative-director-jk-design-hillsborough-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at The Marcus Group, Inc. in Little Falls, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for an all-star creative director to help our clients achieve their communication goals. Being creative is only part of the job here – the ideal person has a knack for understanding and developing strategies to meet client objectives, enjoys the challenge of producing great work in short timeframes and thrives on figuring out smart solutions to fit any budget. Communicating a message effectively is the main priority at our agency, so we are looking for a CD that has experience working in all types of mediums. You won’t find pool tables or video game lounges here – just a great group of people that thrive on bright ideas and doing great work.  Agency experience is a must with at least a few years of experience in B2B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The right candidate is able to multitask, working on multiple accounts and projects with tight deadlines. You are able to develop and execute concepts and designs in a variety of mediums including print, broadcast, out-of-home and web/digital. You have experience working with and directing graphic designers to assist in the production of materials and can deliver strategic communication solutions that help our clients achieve their marketing and communications objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that our high quality of creative and production is upheld, maintaining consistently high standards for him/herself and others on the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listen, prioritize and translate client situation, marketing goals and information into strategic brand concepts, voice, messages and rationales&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate and contribute to the creative process as a leader of a creative team, and as a member of the account team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Co-lead the unified creative/account management process in order to execute on client projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write and present cohesive and persuasive rationales for campaign approaches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the unified process of marketing/concept/design and post-production execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the unified process of marketing/concept/design and interactive/web/video/motion graphics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Primary Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively with partners, participate in company strategizing, and make recommendations for changes to the creative function to meet market changes, competitive threats or to support strategic plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the agency’s strategic goals and brand; analyze the creative team, environment, processes, technologies, etc., to determine areas needing improvement; and build and direct a creative function aligned with and supportive of those goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make decisions on a daily basis that ensure both profitability and creative quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set expectations and standards (build a culture) for creative team attitude, behavior, teamwork and professional development. Lead accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and oversee client budgets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With the account lead, assure that internal and client presentations are on time, professional, engaging, persuasive and supported by a sound rationale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assure that timely and informative communication takes place between the creative function and the partners, account team and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage art direction, design, copywriting and production of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quality control, including proofing/reviewing creative output and confirm deadlines are met.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Secondary Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually learning, evaluating and implementing new marketing communications technologies within the agency and for client campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work toward the constant improvement of the agency’s creative quality and capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the strategic and creative development of the agency’s marketing and branding efforts for new business development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure self and staff development in web-based and interactive marketing capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Functional Competencies:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior leadership and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior problem solving and decision-making skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellence in managing and motivating staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and persuasion skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior understanding of advertising and marketing principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior understanding of marcom strategies and tactics, including technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated talent for high-caliber creative concepting and writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to judge creative concepts and copy, and clearly communicate creative direction to others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of clients and their business/industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of art direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of on and offline marcom elements production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, planning, time-management and follow-through skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of Quark and/or InDesign and Adobe Acrobat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Microsoft Office, Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of interactive media production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-the-marcus-group-inc-little-falls-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-the-marcus-group-inc-little-falls-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>