<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nj-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Software Developer (Android) at CommVault Systems in Oceanport, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have an outstanding career opportunity for a Mobile Software Developer (Android) in our Oceanport, NJ office.  This individual will be responsible for performing all or part of the full life-cycle development process, ranging from user analysis, design, and development to implementation and support. The developer will be involved in developing and maintaining native Android application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop Apps for Android and other mobile platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect, design, and develop high quality software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain, support and enhance existing software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively to solve complex software problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advice and assist other developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with other teams to deliver scalable, reliable software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in computer science, computer information systems, or a related study (Master&amp;rsquo;s degree preferred).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of relevant experience Strong Programming experience developing mobile applications in Android SDK (versions 2.3 nd higher)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working XML/JSON and familiarity with REST/SOAP methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience integrating 3rd party open source libraries/Google APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have one or more apps deployed on play store (please send us the links)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Knowledge on Object Oriented design and principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing, testing, and maintaining applications from conception to launch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical and troubleshooting skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good writing and communications skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-software-developer-android-commvault-systems-oceanport-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-software-developer-android-commvault-systems-oceanport-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Configuration Management, Inc. in Hackensack, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Join a dynamic team responsible for the development of user-facing client software running on multiple platforms and play a pivotal role in its future development. The Senior iOS Developer will work on complex software infrastructure as well as client application user interface for iOS. You will primarily be using C, C++ and Objective-C for development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities may include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New feature design and implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration of newly available technologies and devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimizations to existing infrastructure and algorithms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unit tests and issue resolution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven development experience with at least 2 years of commercial UI applications on iOS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing interactive end-user communication applications or services (chat, audio, video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of 3-5 years with C/C++ programming for large and complex systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with interactive voice and/or video communications over IP a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Linux, MacOS or Android an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CS/EE degree with at least 5 years of industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-configuration-management-inc-hackensack-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-configuration-management-inc-hackensack-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>