<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nj-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Representative at Rearden Commerce, Inc. in Secaucus, NJ</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Rearden Commerce,reator of the Deem™ commerce platform, is transforming commerce on behalf of buyers and sellers. Through a suite of interoperable smart applications, the Deem platform is designed to leverage big data, analytics and semantics technology to optimize the exchange of goods, services, and information with personalization and repeat value to drive customer loyalty. Deem is distributed globally by more than 40 strategic partners including American Express and JPMorgan Chase — connecting millions of consumers and over 35,000 business customers across every market segment to more than 1.2 million merchants. Rearden Commerce is headquartered in Foster City, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Deem commerce platform is designed to connect buyers and sellers via Absolute Relevance™ technology. Deem leverages big data, social collaboration, game-mechanics, semantics and advanced machine learning to optimize the exchange of goods, services and information between buyers and sellers, resulting in the web&amp;rsquo;s most personalized one-to-one marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor transaction queue &amp;amp; take action on pending transactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical support to customer help desks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide end user support &amp;amp; training to customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical support to Ground field personnel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Log all customer contacts into call tracking system so that recurring problems can be analyzed, reported to product development and resolved&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Triage and resolve usability and technical issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help identify and define usability improvements for better customer experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop working knowledge of company products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively support achievement of team goals and objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic technical project planning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years Technical Support experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal skills required to function both in a team environment and to build relationships with our valued customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid general technical background with demonstrated sound problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate time managementskills and ability to multi-task and prioritize in a fast paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated individual with the ability to work under minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task, prioritize, and be flexible – able to adapt plans and react to change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion and desire to work at a company trying to change the world and a goal driven achiever with high productivity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technical Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Outlook), Microsoft Visio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Windows 2008, Windows XP, Windows 7 experience and operationally literate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel automation experience including GDS systems integration such as Sabre, Apollo/Galileo, or Worldspan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft SQL Server, Crystal Reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team Foundation Server (TFS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Test Case manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-representative-rearden-commerce-inc-secaucus-nj</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-representative-rearden-commerce-inc-secaucus-nj</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>