<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nm-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at HSC Communications in Albuquerque, NM</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The HSC Office of Communications and Marketing is seeking a qualified graphic designer who, under general supervision, designs electronic and printed materials, exhibit elements, and/or illustrations for a variety of university publications, displays, and other media, as appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a benefits eligible position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The University of New Mexico provides a comprehensive package of benefits including medical, dental, vision, and life insurance. In addition, UNM offers educational benefits through the tuition remission and dependent education programs. See the Prospective Employee page for a more complete explanation of UNM benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;High school diploma or GED; at least 3 years of experience that is directly related to the duties and responsibilities specified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years graphic design experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years working with or for a Marketing team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Adobe Creative Suite (v.6).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple projects with competing deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Posting Date:   03/20/2013&lt;br/&gt;
For Best Consideration:     03/26/2013&lt;br/&gt;
Closing Date:   Open Until Filled&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application type required for this position:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staff/UNMTemps Employment Application&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Additional requirements for this position:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are selected for an interview, please be prepared to present official transcripts of your highest level of education completed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates for this position must be eligible for employment as verified by the US Department of Health and Human Services Office of Inspector General (OIG) and the Government Services Administration (GSA); those individuals on the OIG/GSA Exclusion Lists will not be considered for hire. Once hired, periodic checks will be made for eligibility of continued employment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Applicant Documents:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resume&lt;br/&gt;
Cover Letter&lt;br/&gt;
Other&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Special Instructions to Applicants:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please provide examples of graphic design work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Links to work featured in online publications, blogs, etc. are acceptable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-hsc-communications-albuquerque-nm</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-hsc-communications-albuquerque-nm</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>