<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nv-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Digital Designer at MGM Resorts International in Las Vegas, NV</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan, design and develop web-based and application-based interfaces, both interactive and non-interactive, from concept to completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain applications and related content in a high profile production environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meet corporate, department and property operations expectations of budgets and deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface with internal teams to communicate project status, project timelines and resolve project issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop application software models following Object Oriented Programming standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anticipate and solve design and development problems with internal teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current in design and development trends and styles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize and maintain Multimedia Services archives and libraries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully understand department job processes and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other job related duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;JOB REQUIREMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have working knowledge and application of user interface design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have working knowledge and application of Object Oriented Programming standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have working knowledge and application of design patterns with emphasis in the Model-View-Controller.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong working knowledge and application of web development languages including, but not limited to HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery, AJAX, PHP, SQL and AS3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational skills to function effectively under time constraints and within established deadlines with particular attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent customer services skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have interpersonal skills to deal effectively with all business contacts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional appearance and demeanor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work varied shifts, including weekends and holidays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High School diploma or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of Mac OS X, Linux and Windows operating systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of Adobe Creative Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to communicate effectively in English, in both written and oral forms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate Degree and/or Bachelor Degree in related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience working in a similar resort setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-digital-designer-mgm-resorts-international-las-vegas-nv</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-digital-designer-mgm-resorts-international-las-vegas-nv</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>