<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/nv-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. Front-End Developer at Zappos.com in Las Vegas, NV</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Why join us?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our unique culture has made Zappos.com, Inc. and its subsidiaries one of FORTUNE’s 100 Best Companies to Work For 5 years straight. Find out why: &lt;a href=&quot;http://money.cnn.com/magazines/fortune/best-companies/&quot;&gt;http://money.cnn.com/magazines/fortune/best-companies/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why else?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer an extensive benefits package for all full-time employees, including medical, dental, vision and 401k!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And &amp;hellip; we&amp;rsquo;re hiring like crazy right now and looking for smart, forward-thinking problem solvers to join our world-class and fairly wacky team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and one more thing! Cover letters are cool, but do you know what’s even cooler?! Show us who you are with a cover letter VIDEO! You will be able to upload one when applying for this position. (Video cover letters are not required, but if you wanna do one, we wanna see it!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for highly skilled, senior-level, front-end developers who live and breathe web standards. You will have strong experience with standards-compliant, semantic HTML and CSS, extensive knowledge of native JavaScript, DOM scripting and familiarity with JavaScript frameworks like JQuery, Mustache, etc. We work with a lot of *nix based technologies so experience with shell scripting and GNU tools will be very beneficial, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be tackling large and small projects that are fun, challenging and span the spectrum of front-end development.  There are multiple opportunities within our team. Depending on your background and strengths, the focus of your particular position may be any one of a number of Zappos Development’s websites, such as: Zappos.com, 6pm.com or vip.zappos.com.  Sometimes the deadlines are tight, but that&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re looking for people with great personalities who are team players. When a project is done, we&amp;rsquo;ll celebrate, enjoy the view and look forward to the next project wiser and stronger than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a casual dress, fun, thriving dot-com with a great work environment and plenty of growth in our future. If we&amp;rsquo;ve sparked your interest, drop us an email with a cover letter, your resume and a nice portfolio of sites developed and we&amp;rsquo;ll talk. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include but are not limited to:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Semantic HTML/CSS coding/updating for assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript/DOM scripting to build interactive but accessible interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with FreeMarker templates and JSON or XML files to expose data to the front-end&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interaction with UX team and business users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily maintenance/updates to existing sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to relocate to Las Vegas area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree in Web Development, Computer Science or combined equivalent of education and/or experience is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create layouts using advanced and semantic HTML5 and CSS3, as well as previous HTML and CSS specs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of DOM scripting with native JavaScript and JS frameworks such as jQuery, Mustache, Handlebars; LABjs and async loaders; Create.js, Raphael and canvas-focused frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong understanding of JavaScript performance optimization techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive use of APIs and a strong understanding of HTTP and REST architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong understanding of modern web practices to create an efficient user-experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong web portfolio required** (showcasing the aforementioned skills)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a *nix environment and using GNU tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistent with and exemplifies our Core Values&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a team player and open to change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fun and friendly attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Freemarker templating&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with object-oriented JavaScript or programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Version Control; primarily GitHub&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with server-side scripting languages like PHP, Python or Ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the Drupal CMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years eCommerce experience with a larger retailer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Along with your resume, please provide a cover letter explaining why you are interested in the company and this position. In the cover letter, please tell us what your favorite HTML tag or CSS property is and why you find it the most exciting. Also, please include an online portfolio showcasing the projects you’ve developed – this is very important! We get a lot of applications, so without a cover letter and portfolio, your application may not be considered. Please show off those awesome skills you have – we wanna see them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a position for someone that is passionate about modern front-end web development. While we will consider all qualified candidates, this is not a position for back-end developers that happen to know some front-end coding. (We have plenty of other Development positions for you to apply to.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zappos IP, Inc. is an equal opportunity employer and drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-zappos-com-las-vegas-nv</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-front-end-developer-zappos-com-las-vegas-nv</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>