<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Linium Resources in Brooklyn, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for a capable, driven Web Engineer. Candidates should be strong web developers with front-end and back-end skills who work well independently and in pairs.  We love people who love to make things, so tell us about what you’ve made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Areas of Responsibility&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frontend/Backend development of new functionality and site designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debugging and bugfixes in existing and new code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working within 3rd party frameworks like Magento and WordPress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of internal tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing awesome code that you can be proud of&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level knowledge of Perl, PHP, Python, and/or Ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level knowledge of HTML, CSS and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level knowledge of MySQL and query optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functional knowledge of MVC / distributed architectures / eCommerce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience architecting and implementing backend systems (from database on up)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of transforming design mockups into HTML/CSS templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skills with cloud computing tools and services such as Chef, Amazon’s EC2, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing eCommerce sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with 3D printing / digital fabrication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good front-end design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-linium-resources-brooklyn-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-linium-resources-brooklyn-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Boxee in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re hard at work building the next generation of products at Boxee.  Our new platform will target many different devices using diverse technologies.  Users will soon be able to experience Boxee on mobile, tablet, web and of course Boxee Box. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting environment to work in for an engineer.  There&amp;rsquo;s always something new to learn&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some stuff we&amp;rsquo;re using in our web stack: ruby, rails, node.js, mongodb, mysql, redis, ember.js, jquery and php&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe in hiring smart, creative and passionate developers.  Our interview process is friendly and casual but in-depth, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for the best and brightest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have experience scaling products quickly, building beautiful user experiences, processing lots of bits or other relevant experience?  We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-boxee-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-boxee-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at 360i in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Award-winning digital advertising agency (and 2-year Best-Place-To-Work recipient), 360i (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.360i.com&quot;&gt;http://www.360i.com&lt;/a&gt;) is looking for a Web Developer to support our growing development needs in New York, NY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This candidate will have the opportunitiy to develop some of the coolest social and mobile applications, pushing the boundaries of what&amp;rsquo;s new in digital marketing, for some of the most iconic brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate must be hands-on, a superb communicator, and have experience working in a fast-paced and collaborative environment. A passion for quality, an eye for detail, and the hunger to develop &amp;ldquo;never-been-done-before&amp;rdquo; solutions are also required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 360i &amp;ndash; Over a Decade of Digital Innovation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a next generation digital agency rooted in innovation and drive. We develop everything from enterprise-level websites to highly complex social apps to innovative rich media campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes us different is our highly experienced technical and design teams and our passionate and collaborative culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re sharp, creative, and forward-thinking &amp;ndash; and if complacency isn&amp;rsquo;t in your vocabulary &amp;ndash; drop us a line. It takes a special kind of person to work here, and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strong experience using modern web standards (CSS3, HTML5) and Javascript Strong experience with
Strong experience PHP LAMP-stack), with solid understanding of object-oriented programming (OOP)(BR&gt; Experience integrating with APIs (such as Facebook or Google Maps)
Experience with MySQL database design and integration
Familiarity with version control systems (such as SVN or Git)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Additional skillset considered a plus:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience leveraging front-end libraries, such as Raphael and JQuery, for web animations Experience building mobile web applications Experience with RESTful and SOAP-based web service models Experience with PHP frameworks, such as Zend or Symphony Experience with caching strategies (such as Memcached or APC) Please add code samples and examples of work&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-360i-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-360i-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Theatre Communications Group (TCG) in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About The Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theatre Communications Group (TCG), the national organization for the American theatre is seeking a full-time ColdFusion Web Developer to assist with the implementation of new applications, maintenance of existing platforms, and project specification reviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About You&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the development team, you will support an environment with systems that cross a wide array features and functionality such as ecommerce, subscription-based models, reporting, survey building, and content management. The ideal candidate for this position is an experienced developer who works well within a team and has the ability to work on projects with minimal supervision in a deadline oriented situations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Technologies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ColdFusion(8,9,10),HTML5, XHTML, DHTML, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, XML/XSLT, IIS6 &amp;amp; 7, CSS, ActiveX, ODBC, JDBC, SQL Server 05/08/10/12, Transact-SQL, MS Access. Visio, UML, T.O.A.D, Crystal Reports 9, Dreamweaver MX, HomeSite 5+. Windows 2008 server, XP, UML&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience designing, coding, and deploying CF applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience database development including DDL (tables, views, stored procedures) and DML (analyzing and optimizing existing SQL code, writing new queries)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience working with JavaScript, jQuery (Ajax development).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience working with frameworks such as Model Glue, ColdBox or FuseBox.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong customer service skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can demonstrate proficiency in application development life cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient oral and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to plan, prioritizes, and complete projects and tasks in deadline oriented environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsibilities include code and unit testing of project rollouts and application enhancements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other responsibilities include trouble shooting, solution modeling and testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In addition to strong hands-on technical skills, the candidate must show proficiency in communicating technical concepts in understandable terms and convert complex business objectives into tangible products. Must work closely with executive level individuals and shown an ability to communicate effectively across multiple groups.   Candidate must show a propensity for leadership, knowledge sharing, and technical growth essential to producing high-level enterprise applications in deadline-oriented situations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;To Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email your cover letter including salary requirements, code and database samples and resume to: itjobs@tcg.org. No calls please. We will respond only to those resumes in which we have interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About TCG&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For over 50 years, Theatre Communications Group (TCG), the national organization for the American theatre, has existed to strengthen, nurture and promote the professional not-for-profit American theatre. TCG’s constituency has grown from a handful of groundbreaking theatres to nearly 700 member theatres and affiliate organizations and more than 12,000 individuals nationwide. TCG offers its members networking and knowledge-building opportunities through conferences, events, research and communications; awards grants, approximately $2 million per year, to theatre companies and individual artists; advocates on the federal level; and serves as the US Center of the International Theatre Institute, connecting its constituents to the global theatre community. TCG is North America’s largest independent publisher of dramatic literature, with 11 Pulitzer Prizes for Best Play on the TCG booklist. It also publishes the award-winning AMERICAN THEATRE magazine and ARTSEARCH®, the essential source for a career in the arts. In all of its endeavors, TCG seeks to increase the organizational efficiency of its member theatres, cultivate and celebrate the artistic talent and achievements of the field and promote a larger public understanding of, and appreciation for, the theatre. For more information, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tcg.org&quot;&gt;www.tcg.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-theatre-communications-group-%28tcg%29-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-theatre-communications-group-%28tcg%29-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>