<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Perl Developer at Nature Publishing Group in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Nature Publishing Group (NPG), the leading name in Science, Technology &amp;amp; Medical (STM) publishing, has a vacancy within the Application Department for an Perl Applications Developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role will be responsible for supporting projects that involve the development, implementation and deployment of applications to NPG. Also involves is support of new and existing applications. Applications may be internally developed or externally sourced from 3rd parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will have prior application development / programming experience, including web-based applications and documentation. Ideally they will also have knowledge of the software development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software systems development, conversion, implementation and maintenance for the Manuscript Tracking system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing and maintaining applications for various other company-wide systems and projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation of technical and user documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation and maintenance of databases for project work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advise, recommend and specify improvements to systems and technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum 3+ years of professional experience in online Application Development with specific focus on:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perl/OO Perl development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration of front-end technologies (such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Prototype/JQuery, DHTML, AJAX) into functional websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object oriented coding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience researching, developing and applying new technologies and methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apache/Mod_Perl, UNIX/Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SQL, working experience with MSSQL 2005&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using and creating web services (SOAP, REST, etc) with past experience with developing reusable components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working practice with XML/JSO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scripting knowledge (Unix Shell, Perl)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of CVS and Git Version Control Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and documentation of code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong command of the English language, both oral and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent self-tasking skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent teamwork skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and manage multiple projects simultaneously in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Experience of Tracking Systems, STM publishing and language skills are desirable, but not essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role is based in our New York offices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nature Publishing Group is an Equal Opportunity Employer. To learn more about our company, please visit our web site at www.nature.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please complete our short application by clicking the link below.&lt;br/&gt;
Website for more information:   home.eease.adp.com&lt;br/&gt;
Contact information:    Maureen Long&lt;br/&gt;
Email: m.long@us.nature.com
Phone: 212-451-8494
Phone: 212-451-8494&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/perl-developer-nature-publishing-group-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/perl-developer-nature-publishing-group-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at The Bachrach Group in Melville, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Position Title: Web Developer 1- 2 yrs exp.
Reports to: COO&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working in concert with Operations, Marketing, Sales and IT, tie together both design and back-end functionality for all web-based and social media communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;In terms of benefits, we offer the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life Insurance ( company paid)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional Voluntary life insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FSA/DCA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LTD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AFLAC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you have additional questions. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Roles and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of robust and user-friendly web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Routine daily maintenance of existing sites and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on projects including web layout enhancements, website enhancements, web-based applications, and database-backed websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Application/Framework design as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay up to date on latest trends and emerging technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills and Specifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of major operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects in a changing, multitasking environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of common programming languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience and knowledge in PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Wordpress. Ability to work in an Adobe environment a must and graphic design skills is a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in HTML5 / CSS3, experience with Ruby on Rails, JQuery, a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Mobile Platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of web application development processes, from the layout/user interface to relational database structures to full implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organization skills to manage multiple projects and complete tasks thoroughly and quickly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to communicate clearly and timely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work independently without direct supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four-year college degree followed by at least three years as a front-end web developer, producing professional websites and/or web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated expertise in creating cross-browser user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Design experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with mobile device browsers is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing automated tests a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of accessibility requirements a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-the-bachrach-group-melville-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-the-bachrach-group-melville-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Concordia Publishing House in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our client in NYC is seeking a Senior Web Developer.  Ideally for someone to create and maintain systems written (primarily) in PHP.   The successful candidate will have over five years experience working in an open source ( LAMP) environment .  Being able to develop scalable object-oriented PHP5 code in a deadline-driven environment. The company is looking for innovative approaches and high growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your skills and background include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years professional open source development, primarily using PHP and MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web development experience including HTML, CSS, and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of MVC frameworks (e.g. Code Igniter, Symfony) and experience using a debugger&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of MySQL, Apache, Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and teamwork skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree in Computer Science or Engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior search-related experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MySQL configuration and performance tuning a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In this role you will work with a team of internal and external developers collaboratively building out and maintaining the Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For immediate consideration please email your resume to application@ezrah.org&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-concordia-publishing-house-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-concordia-publishing-house-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Back-End Web Developer at Analog Method in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Analog Method is looking for a junior to mid-level on-site Web Developer skilled in server-side programming, scripting and databases to develop high quality websites and Web applications. This is a full-time position with great benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your Profile&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are super smart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your passion for web technology is unmatched.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong desire to make the world a better place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing good code makes you happy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You care about quality more than anyone you know.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analog Method is a dynamic New York City web development shop committed to delivering quality work that&amp;rsquo;s cutting-edge and creative. We make the world a better place by creating superior web sites and web applications that are useful and user friendly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll want to work for us because:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The work is fun, varied and challenging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll never stop learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will have ownership of your projects and will get to make critical technical decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the design, information architecture, quality assurance, technical and account teams to successfully develop, launch and maintain websites and web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create Content Management Systems and other database-driven web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement interactivity using AJAX and various JavaScript libraries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with sales to discuss development approaches and create work estimates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to support requests and ensure customer satisfaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document work and development processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Candidate Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player with excellent written and verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized with attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer science or digital media degree, or at least 3 years of industry experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of at least one major server side scripting language, PHP, Python or C# preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database savvy (MySQL or Microsoft SQL Server).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with a passion for the Web and technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to work on-site at our office in midtown Manhattan, conveniently located near Grand Central and Penn Station.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send an email with your resume to dev0312@analogmethod.com. In your email subject, you must use the keyword &amp;ldquo;dev0312&amp;rdquo; for us to consider you for employment.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/back-end-web-developer-analog-method-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/back-end-web-developer-analog-method-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Linium Resources in Brooklyn, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for a capable, driven Web Engineer. Candidates should be strong web developers with front-end and back-end skills who work well independently and in pairs.  We love people who love to make things, so tell us about what you’ve made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Areas of Responsibility&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frontend/Backend development of new functionality and site designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debugging and bugfixes in existing and new code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working within 3rd party frameworks like Magento and WordPress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of internal tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing awesome code that you can be proud of&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level knowledge of Perl, PHP, Python, and/or Ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level knowledge of HTML, CSS and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level knowledge of MySQL and query optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functional knowledge of MVC / distributed architectures / eCommerce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience architecting and implementing backend systems (from database on up)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of transforming design mockups into HTML/CSS templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skills with cloud computing tools and services such as Chef, Amazon’s EC2, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing eCommerce sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with 3D printing / digital fabrication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good front-end design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-linium-resources-brooklyn-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-linium-resources-brooklyn-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Boxee in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re hard at work building the next generation of products at Boxee.  Our new platform will target many different devices using diverse technologies.  Users will soon be able to experience Boxee on mobile, tablet, web and of course Boxee Box. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting environment to work in for an engineer.  There&amp;rsquo;s always something new to learn&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some stuff we&amp;rsquo;re using in our web stack: ruby, rails, node.js, mongodb, mysql, redis, ember.js, jquery and php&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe in hiring smart, creative and passionate developers.  Our interview process is friendly and casual but in-depth, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for the best and brightest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have experience scaling products quickly, building beautiful user experiences, processing lots of bits or other relevant experience?  We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-boxee-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-boxee-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at 360i in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Award-winning digital advertising agency (and 2-year Best-Place-To-Work recipient), 360i (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.360i.com&quot;&gt;http://www.360i.com&lt;/a&gt;) is looking for a Web Developer to support our growing development needs in New York, NY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This candidate will have the opportunitiy to develop some of the coolest social and mobile applications, pushing the boundaries of what&amp;rsquo;s new in digital marketing, for some of the most iconic brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate must be hands-on, a superb communicator, and have experience working in a fast-paced and collaborative environment. A passion for quality, an eye for detail, and the hunger to develop &amp;ldquo;never-been-done-before&amp;rdquo; solutions are also required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 360i &amp;ndash; Over a Decade of Digital Innovation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a next generation digital agency rooted in innovation and drive. We develop everything from enterprise-level websites to highly complex social apps to innovative rich media campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes us different is our highly experienced technical and design teams and our passionate and collaborative culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re sharp, creative, and forward-thinking &amp;ndash; and if complacency isn&amp;rsquo;t in your vocabulary &amp;ndash; drop us a line. It takes a special kind of person to work here, and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strong experience using modern web standards (CSS3, HTML5) and Javascript Strong experience with
Strong experience PHP LAMP-stack), with solid understanding of object-oriented programming (OOP)(BR&gt; Experience integrating with APIs (such as Facebook or Google Maps)
Experience with MySQL database design and integration
Familiarity with version control systems (such as SVN or Git)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Additional skillset considered a plus:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience leveraging front-end libraries, such as Raphael and JQuery, for web animations Experience building mobile web applications Experience with RESTful and SOAP-based web service models Experience with PHP frameworks, such as Zend or Symphony Experience with caching strategies (such as Memcached or APC) Please add code samples and examples of work&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-360i-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-360i-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Theatre Communications Group (TCG) in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About The Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theatre Communications Group (TCG), the national organization for the American theatre is seeking a full-time ColdFusion Web Developer to assist with the implementation of new applications, maintenance of existing platforms, and project specification reviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About You&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the development team, you will support an environment with systems that cross a wide array features and functionality such as ecommerce, subscription-based models, reporting, survey building, and content management. The ideal candidate for this position is an experienced developer who works well within a team and has the ability to work on projects with minimal supervision in a deadline oriented situations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Technologies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ColdFusion(8,9,10),HTML5, XHTML, DHTML, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, XML/XSLT, IIS6 &amp;amp; 7, CSS, ActiveX, ODBC, JDBC, SQL Server 05/08/10/12, Transact-SQL, MS Access. Visio, UML, T.O.A.D, Crystal Reports 9, Dreamweaver MX, HomeSite 5+. Windows 2008 server, XP, UML&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience designing, coding, and deploying CF applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience database development including DDL (tables, views, stored procedures) and DML (analyzing and optimizing existing SQL code, writing new queries)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience working with JavaScript, jQuery (Ajax development).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience working with frameworks such as Model Glue, ColdBox or FuseBox.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong customer service skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can demonstrate proficiency in application development life cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient oral and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to plan, prioritizes, and complete projects and tasks in deadline oriented environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsibilities include code and unit testing of project rollouts and application enhancements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other responsibilities include trouble shooting, solution modeling and testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In addition to strong hands-on technical skills, the candidate must show proficiency in communicating technical concepts in understandable terms and convert complex business objectives into tangible products. Must work closely with executive level individuals and shown an ability to communicate effectively across multiple groups.   Candidate must show a propensity for leadership, knowledge sharing, and technical growth essential to producing high-level enterprise applications in deadline-oriented situations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;To Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email your cover letter including salary requirements, code and database samples and resume to: itjobs@tcg.org. No calls please. We will respond only to those resumes in which we have interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About TCG&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For over 50 years, Theatre Communications Group (TCG), the national organization for the American theatre, has existed to strengthen, nurture and promote the professional not-for-profit American theatre. TCG’s constituency has grown from a handful of groundbreaking theatres to nearly 700 member theatres and affiliate organizations and more than 12,000 individuals nationwide. TCG offers its members networking and knowledge-building opportunities through conferences, events, research and communications; awards grants, approximately $2 million per year, to theatre companies and individual artists; advocates on the federal level; and serves as the US Center of the International Theatre Institute, connecting its constituents to the global theatre community. TCG is North America’s largest independent publisher of dramatic literature, with 11 Pulitzer Prizes for Best Play on the TCG booklist. It also publishes the award-winning AMERICAN THEATRE magazine and ARTSEARCH®, the essential source for a career in the arts. In all of its endeavors, TCG seeks to increase the organizational efficiency of its member theatres, cultivate and celebrate the artistic talent and achievements of the field and promote a larger public understanding of, and appreciation for, the theatre. For more information, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tcg.org&quot;&gt;www.tcg.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-theatre-communications-group-%28tcg%29-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-theatre-communications-group-%28tcg%29-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>