<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Back-End Developer - Freelance at NoFavorite in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMS setup and integration of pages created by the Front End team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of MVC paradigm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of HTML/CSS/Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Server­side Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Framework experience (Cake, RoR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are looking for someone creative who stays up to date with new web trends and understands the possibilities and limitations of front end development. Attention to detail and clean, organized code are absolute requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strong communications skills in dealing with team members and clients is essential. This is a freelance position with possibility of turning into full time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think you would be a good fit and want to work in a fun, creative environment, please email jobs@nofavorite.com with a link to your portfolio. Submissions without portfolio links will not be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compensation for the position is to be determined based on work quality and experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/back-end-developer-nofavorite-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/back-end-developer-nofavorite-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Application Developer at JOOR in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Creates user information solutions by developing, implementing, and maintaining Internet/intranet applications. Designs and develops user interfaces to Internet/intranet applications by setting expectations and features priorities throughout development life cycle; determining design methodologies and tool sets; completing programming using languages and software products; designing and conducting tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tackle complex problems and identify new ways to build extensible technology platforms that will support sophisticated product search, social networking and global transactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommends system solutions by comparing advantages and disadvantages of custom development and purchase alternatives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrates applications by designing database architecture and server scripting; studying and establishing connectivity with network systems, search engines, and information servers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completes applications development by coordinating requirements, schedules, and activities; contributing to team meetings; troubleshooting development and production problems across multiple environments and operating platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push code to production within weeks of completion and QA testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate passion for the product and for delivering a best-in-class, innovative and engaging, user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years extensive experience in web application development and OOP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of the web stack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong technical skills in PHP, MySQL, HTML, JavaScript, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with an MVC framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technology Organization&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our technology department is composed of autonomous teams comprising back and front end engineers, QA and designers. Everyone on a team is expected to own the team’s goals and objectives. Our projects are tied to the retail industry&amp;rsquo;s seasonally buying period and are comprised of two week iteration cycles with release comprised of no more than four sprints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About JOOR&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Featured in Fortune, Cool Hunting and Business Insider as one of the “20 Innovative Start-ups of 2011” JOOR is a business-to-business, venture capital backed startup based in NYC. We&amp;rsquo;re revolutionizing the wholesale fashion marketplace by connection brands and buyers digitally through disruptive and innovative mobile and web applications. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-joor-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-joor-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Application Developer at JOOR in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Creates user information solutions by developing, implementing, and maintaining Internet/intranet applications. Designs and develops user interfaces to Internet/intranet applications by setting expectations and features priorities throughout development life cycle; determining design methodologies and tool sets; completing programming using languages and software products; designing and conducting tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tackle complex problems and identify new ways to build extensible technology platforms that will support sophisticated product search, social networking and global transactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommends system solutions by comparing advantages and disadvantages of custom development and purchase alternatives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrates applications by designing database architecture and server scripting; studying and establishing connectivity with network systems, search engines, and information servers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completes applications development by coordinating requirements, schedules, and activities; contributing to team meetings; troubleshooting development and production problems across multiple environments and operating platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push code to production within weeks of completion and QA testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate passion for the product and for delivering a best-in-class, innovative and engaging, user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years extensive experience in web application development and OOP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of the web stack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong technical skills in PHP, MySQL, HTML, JavaScript, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with an MVC framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technology Organization&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our technology department is composed of autonomous teams comprising back and front end engineers, QA and designers. Everyone on a team is expected to own the team’s goals and objectives. Our projects are tied to the retail industry&amp;rsquo;s seasonally buying period and are comprised of two week iteration cycles with release comprised of no more than four sprints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About JOOR&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Featured in Fortune, Cool Hunting and Business Insider as one of the “20 Innovative Start-ups of 2011” JOOR is a business-to-business, venture capital backed startup based in NYC. We&amp;rsquo;re revolutionizing the wholesale fashion marketplace by connection brands and buyers digitally through disruptive and innovative mobile and web applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-joor-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-developer-joor-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Developer at BNY Mellon in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a User Interface Engineer with front-end development expertise and a strategic approach to deliver best-in-class user interfaces across multiple device types.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role is based at the BNY Mellon offices in New York City as part of the Architecture &amp;amp; Engineering group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To succeed in this role you will demonstrate expert knowledge in the technical design and implementation of front end user interfaces using Bootstrap frameworks. You have a strong passion for technology and have a track record of success working in a collaborative, team-based environment. Experience with a broad range of Open Source software components/frameworks will be advantageous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Range of Activities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Collaborate on definition, expansion and rollout of a pattern-based framework to optimize interface functionality and display across multiple device formats (web, mobile, rich desktop)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Design, coding and testing of a range of Asset Management application and services &amp;ndash; including a range of components to support a Service Oriented “Integration As A Service” model and white label Web UI Framework&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Partner with team members to identify and resolve usability and technology issues&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provision of expertise to other Asset Management development groups on how to adopt a MV* based methodology for UI design and integration&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provision of support, guidance and training for other technology groups within Asset Management regarding development best practices&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research into new and emerging technology for introduction into the development stack for Asset Management wide usage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participation in Agile scrum based software development model&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 &amp;ndash; 8 years experience required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technology Skills &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience developing UIs for enterprise applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in JavaScript MVC/MV*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript libraries like jQuery, DoJo, Ext-JS or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great HTML5 and CSS skills, with knowledge of LESS and/or SASS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AMD architecture (Require.js, Common.js)
Hands-on experience with WebSockets (such as SocketIO, Sock.js, Kaazing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with popular application frameworks (such as Backbone, Spine, Angular)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience developing scalable, rich internet applications
Adept with web standards; mindful of browser and device compatibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with TDD/BDD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile-first development experience and knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocate of agile engineering principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with multi-modal UI, including voice and gesture input, is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Skills &amp;amp; Personal Qualities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated, confident and enthusiastic team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to mentor and develop junior staff with evidence of strong leadership skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivery focused with history of achieving deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to create a dynamic, collaborative and engaging work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communicator, both face to face and remote&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovative and enthusiastic approach to solving technology problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interact with the business to understand requirements and perform technology analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive approach to problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disciplined, thorough attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiastic in a pressurised environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seeking professional career development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The successful candidate will have a strong Computer Science related Degree or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience within an Investment Management company is an asset, but not required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternative industry experience will be considered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-developer-bny-mellon-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-developer-bny-mellon-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Javascript Engineer / UI Developer at Integral Ads in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a strong Javascript programmer with a good design sense. (To be clear, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who knows how to program in Javascript, not just someone who can hack together some jQuery plug-ins.) The Javascript Engineer / UI Developer Reports to the Director of User Experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research, design and develop for our industry-leading client-facing user interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovate and develop for our core javascript ad tag technology (think ultra-low latency, 1.3 billion+ calls daily)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All the usual stuff: smart, gets things done, detail oriented, self-starter, good communication skills, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with sql, hadoop &amp;amp; big data processes is a plus, as is a strong design portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We use Eclipse, SVN, Adobe CS5 and Omnigraffle &amp;ndash; so should you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end tech stack includes: jQuery, Backbone, Marionette, D3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Big plus: you play an instrument or a sport, or both&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enter your name, this position, a cover letter, and upload your resume using the form to the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a growing ad-tech start-up with a great culture. Nice, casual, Union Square office. Free lunch on Fridays; stocked snacks in the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/javascript-engineer-ui-developer-intergral-ads-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/javascript-engineer-ui-developer-intergral-ads-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP Back-End Developer at LocalVox Media Inc. in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;LocalVox Media Inc is a local, social and mobile marketing platform that helps local businesses publish and promote their business, events, announcements and deals to a range of online channels including NearSay.com, social media channels, search, local directories email messaging and to their own web sites. LocalVox Media Inc. has been named the #3 start up to watch in 2012 by Business Insider, and was recently featured on Fox News as the #1 Tech Tool for Entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who We Are Looking For:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced PHP backend developer who thrives on finding clever solutions to knotty problems to help us build a suite of web applications that are lightning fast and built to scale in the cloud to be an anchor member of a fast-growing development team. You&amp;rsquo;ll be starting with a Drupal 7 code base, but should expect to work toward migrating away from Drupal to achieve these goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Candidates Should Possess:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong debugging and general analytical skill and the ability to work in a fast-paced environment juggling multiple tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years of experience working on high-volume, high transaction, commercial web applications in multi-server, load-balanced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very strong PHP skills. You should be able to write basic CRUD for an object with nothing more than a text editor and access to a web server running stock Apache, PHP, and MySQL in 15 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very strong HTML skills. This is not a front-end position, but we expect you to be comfortable writing clean, syntactic HTML.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in the MVC pattern and Object-Oriented development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sufficient comfort with Apache and MySQL to be able to manage your own dev environments and assist with other environments when needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Drupal a plus, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-back-end-developer-localvox-media-inc-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-back-end-developer-localvox-media-inc-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mid-Senior Level Web Developer at Downtown Manhattan Area in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Rapidly growing web technology firm with a passion for creating efficiencies to help companies achieve dramatic growth is seeking a mid-senior level web developer. This position will allow for tremendous growth and work-life balance. Not only will you collaborate with a top-tier team of incredibly intelligent technologists, you will play an integral role in the growth of this organization. Must have &amp;ldquo;Git&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;shell&amp;rdquo; program experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This opportunity promises opportunities for learning new frameworks and skills, and coming to a job that never feels like work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in a modern, high level language (PHP, Python or Ruby)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for front end technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JS libraries and frameworks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Framework experience (Drupal, CakePHP, Ruby on Rails, Django, Wordpress, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with using RESTful services and HTTP APIs (Facebook, Twitter, PayPal, Google, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with windows and linux server administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with version control systems (SVN and GIT)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable in the command line interface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of MVC architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working knowledge of Drupal would be super helpful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Python with Django or a desire to learn them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magento&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;work well with others in a fast paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be able to work closely with other team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be able to deliver on time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;meticulous and curious by nature, enjoy reading between the lines in a specification document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please contact me as soon as possible if you are interested in this opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mid-senior-level-web-developer-downtown-manhattan-area-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mid-senior-level-web-developer-downtown-manhattan-area-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP Developer at Creative Solutions Services, LLC in Port Washington, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;our client in port washington, ny is looking for a PHP Developer to work on the development and enhancements of several PHP/Joomla web sites. if interested, please apply to this ad or send your resume and contact details with the job title in the subject line to recruiter@css-llc.net&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join a friendly, team environment that is full of enthusiasm, talent and challenging opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate and interface with Marketing Leads and/or Product Owners to help understand and size User Stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and enhance Joomla/PHP web sites (actual coding)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure proper tracking of tasks and ensuring Spring Story commitments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Creative Development to get desired UI updates deployed on live site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on selected critical defects or Production issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree in a software development technology discipline required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years of web programming with PHP and MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge working with Joomla and Zend frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insight into proper setup and configuration of the Apache web server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Unix/Linux environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years experience working with front-end technologies ie Javascript, HTML, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled at using RESTful api’s, JSON, and XML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using JIRA and Agile Methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using SVN for versioning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-developer-creative-solutions-services-llc-port-washington-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-developer-creative-solutions-services-llc-port-washington-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Bloomberg in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg Businessweek has been delivering the market&amp;rsquo;s sharpest insight and
analysis to business leaders for more than 80 years. Join our fast moving team
within the Bloomberg R&amp;amp;D Consumer Websites group, where every day we take on
and surmount the industry&amp;rsquo;s greatest challenges around content delivery,
consumer engagement and content personalization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking well rounded full stack developer, who is passionate about building high profile, large scale web applications, to lead our front end web development. You will be a key participant and contributor throughout the entire SDLC. Channel your creative energy and contribute to a team building fast, engaging and responsive websites for a multi platform user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate should have a passion for design/building high traffic web apps and be proficient in multiple programming languages (front-end and back-end), have a solid understanding of web development trends.
The person chosen for this role must be able to communicate and collaborate effectively with a diverse set of colleagues in different disciplines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS or MS in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in building high traffic consumer facing websites using Ruby on Rails (3+ years professional experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, SASS/SCSS, grid-systems, responsive web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for UI performance debugging and benchmarking, cross browwer testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write high-performance, readable/reusable code for UI components which work across multiple browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with object oriented design, Ruby, test driven development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience with SQL and NoSQL databases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in working with `Comps¿ provided by design partners and break it down into tasks and work effort estimates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong team player with passion for constantly improving the product, user experience, code quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding interpersonal skills, intellectual curiosity, and an entrepreneurial spirit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg, the global business and financial information and news leader, gives influential decision makers a critical edge by connecting them to a dynamic network of information, people and ideas. The company&amp;rsquo;s strength &amp;ndash; delivering data, news and analytics through innovative technology, quickly and accurately &amp;ndash; is at the core of the Bloomberg Professional service, which provides real time financial information to more than 310,000 subscribers globally. Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s enterprise solutions build on the company&amp;rsquo;s core strength, leveraging technology to allow customers to access, integrate, distribute and manage data and information across organizations more efficiently and effectively. Through Bloomberg Law, Bloomberg Government, Bloomberg New Energy Finance and Bloomberg BNA, the company provides data, news and analytics to decision makers in industries beyond finance. And Bloomberg News, delivered through the Bloomberg Professional service, television, radio, mobile, the Internet and two magazines, Bloomberg Businessweek and Bloomberg Markets, covers the world with more than 2,300 news and multimedia professionals at 146 bureaus in 72 countries. Headquartered in New York, Bloomberg employs more than 15,000 people in 192 locations around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Legal Terms:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree that my submission of this employment application does not obligate the Company (Bloomberg L.P., its subsidiaries, divisions and any affiliated entities, collectively &amp;ldquo;the Company&amp;rdquo;) to employ me, or to offer me employment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree that if I am hired for a position in the United States of America, I will be employed on an at-will basis, which means that: (a) my employment and compensation are not guaranteed for any definite period, and can be terminated, with or without cause, and with or without notice, by either the Company or myself, and (b) there is no written or oral agreement or representation that can alter my at-will status except an individual written agreement signed by the Chief Executive Officer of Bloomberg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree that the information on this application (and accompanying documents, if any) is true and complete to the best of my knowledge. I am responsible for ensuring that the information I submit is accurate and up-to-date. I may review or update my personal information at any time using this site or by entering a request via Careers- Feedback . I also agree that any misstatement, false information, or omission deemed significant by Bloomberg may disqualify me from consideration, and/or may be reason for discharge if discovered after an offer of employment has been extended to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree that I am not party to any agreement, or subject to any legal obligation, that would in any way restrict me, or interfere with me from fully performing the requirements of the job for which I am applying, and that I must disclose to the Company any such agreement or obligation before the Company considers my application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand that if I am selected to proceed with the application process, I may be given or obtain access to non-public information that the Company considers to be of a confidential, proprietary, or trade secret nature (&amp;ldquo;Confidential Information&amp;rdquo;). I agree that I will not directly or indirectly disclose the Confidential Information to any third party, and that I will not use the Confidential Information for my own benefit or for the benefit of any third party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, I agree that if I am offered employment at Bloomberg, that such offer, and continued employment, is contingent on the results of a reference check and background investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand that the Company is an equal employment opportunity/affirmative action employer, and that the application process will be conducted in accord with applicable EEO/affirmative action requirements where the relevant position is located. I understand and agree that Bloomberg may use any personal information submitted in my application for the purpose of considering my suitability for employment, as well as for general statistical analysis and reporting purposes, including candidate activity and demographic reports. Bloomberg will process my information in compliance with applicable laws on privacy and data protection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree that if Bloomberg does not employ me at this time, Bloomberg may retain and use the information that it obtains as part of the application process to consider my application later if a suitable position becomes available and, if appropriate, to refer back to this application if I apply again. If at any time I no longer want Bloomberg to consider my application for employment, I understand I must enter a request via Careers- Feedback, in which case the information will be stored securely for no more than one year from the date of notification, and access to it will only be made to the extent necessary for legal and regulatory purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand that Bloomberg is a global company and that it will process my information on its servers in the United States of America. Bloomberg is committed to compliance with its privacy obligations and for that reason will apply the Safe Harbor Privacy Policy, to the extent applicable, when processing my information on its US servers. I further agree that if I am applying for a position outside the EEA and US, Bloomberg may also process my information on its servers in the country in which the relevant position is located and comply with the privacy legislation in that country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand my information may be disclosed to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or third parties where required and where necessary to comply with legal or regulatory obligations or requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By continuing with this application, I voluntarily consent to the above terms, and recognize that my agreement to these terms is legally binding and enforceable to the same extent as if I had signed my name.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-bloomberg-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-bloomberg-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Perl Developer at Nature Publishing Group in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Nature Publishing Group (NPG), the leading name in Science, Technology &amp;amp; Medical (STM) publishing, has a vacancy within the Application Department for an Perl Applications Developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role will be responsible for supporting projects that involve the development, implementation and deployment of applications to NPG. Also involves is support of new and existing applications. Applications may be internally developed or externally sourced from 3rd parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will have prior application development / programming experience, including web-based applications and documentation. Ideally they will also have knowledge of the software development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software systems development, conversion, implementation and maintenance for the Manuscript Tracking system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing and maintaining applications for various other company-wide systems and projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation of technical and user documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation and maintenance of databases for project work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advise, recommend and specify improvements to systems and technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum 3+ years of professional experience in online Application Development with specific focus on:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perl/OO Perl development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration of front-end technologies (such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Prototype/JQuery, DHTML, AJAX) into functional websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object oriented coding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience researching, developing and applying new technologies and methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apache/Mod_Perl, UNIX/Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SQL, working experience with MSSQL 2005&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using and creating web services (SOAP, REST, etc) with past experience with developing reusable components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working practice with XML/JSO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scripting knowledge (Unix Shell, Perl)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of CVS and Git Version Control Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and documentation of code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong command of the English language, both oral and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent self-tasking skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent teamwork skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and manage multiple projects simultaneously in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Experience of Tracking Systems, STM publishing and language skills are desirable, but not essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role is based in our New York offices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nature Publishing Group is an Equal Opportunity Employer. To learn more about our company, please visit our web site at www.nature.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please complete our short application by clicking the link below.&lt;br/&gt;
Website for more information:   home.eease.adp.com&lt;br/&gt;
Contact information:    Maureen Long&lt;br/&gt;
Email: m.long@us.nature.com
Phone: 212-451-8494
Phone: 212-451-8494&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/perl-developer-nature-publishing-group-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/perl-developer-nature-publishing-group-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>