<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Pink in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;POSITION DESCRIPTION:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide excellent individual design and to allocate and coordinate assignments among graphic design staff, providing direction as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design lead for specific creative projects, from concept to execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contract and direct outside creative for product photography, illustration, as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with visual presentation to create innovative in-store marketing that enhances the clients shopping experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Train and develop designers and artists to achieve team objectives and personal growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with production team to execute all projects in a timely manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present creative ideas to management for assigned projects. Influence decision-making process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain state-of-the-art knowledge of design trends and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up with current trends in fashion and marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College degree in graphic design or experience equivalent to preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4-5 years graphic design experience in a related field. Retail preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership experience preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to use Macintosh computer programs. Specifically- In Design, Photo Shop, Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PINK, a member of the Limited Brands family, is the dominant aspirational lifestyle brand for the collegiate girl. VS Pink celebrates campus life through its assortment of sleepwear, loungewear and bras and panties designed to appeal to the spirit, humor, optimism and self-confidence of the girl who wears, loves and lives PINK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-pink-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-pink-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS/Mobile Designer at BuzzFeed in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;BuzzFeed is looking for a Mobile Designer to design applications for iOS. We&amp;rsquo;re a new kind of media company for the social world. Our technology powers the social distribution of content, detects what is trending on the web, and connects people in realtime with the hottest content of the moment. Our site is a rapidly growing hub for media that reaches over 40 million monthly unique visitors and our network tracks an additional 300M uniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This job is based in our NYC offices, and we offer competitive compensation and stock option program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a key role in bringing mobile products to life from idea to execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create pixel perfect visual designs based on UX wireframes and specs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain, contribute and adhere to our best practices and brand guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to complete and juggle multiple projects and responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing simple and intuitive mobile user interfaces for iPhone and iPad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong visual and user focused design skills and an eye for detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in iOS UI conventions, best practises, and latest app trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a version control system (Specifically Git)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a small, agile product and development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About BuzzFeed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BuzzFeed is the leading social news organization, intensely focused on delivering high-quality original reporting, insight, and social content across a rapidly expanding array of subject areas. BuzzFeed’s technology powers the social distribution of content, detects what is trending on the web, and connects people in real-time with the hottest content of the moment. BuzzFeed.com is growing rapidly and reaches more than 40 million monthly unique visitors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jonah Peretti, founder &amp;amp; CEO of BuzzFeed, is an MIT Media Lab grad who previously co-founded the Huffington Post. Ben Smith is its Editor-in-chief, Google alum Jon Steinberg is President and COO, and Huffington Post co-founder Kenneth Lerer serves as Executive Chairman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BuzzFeed is backed by: NEA, Softbank, Hearst, RRE, Lerer Ventures, SV Angel and Founder Collective.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-mobile-designer-buzzfeed-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-mobile-designer-buzzfeed-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at New York Islanders in Uniondale, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Marketing and Creative Services Department operates in conjunction with the organizations’ Sponsorship, Sales, Communications and Game Operations departments to create collateral as well as promote programs and events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The department develops concepts and executes pieces to be distributed through the following media: web, print, television and radio. All deliverables are created under a strict production schedule to ensure proper execution and to meet required deadlines internally and externally for the client/sponsor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong production and design sense&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite 6, strong in the following programs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;InDesign CS6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop CS6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrator CS6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash CS6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work well under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must present a portfolio that shows talent, taste and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position requires minimum 2 years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Note:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you apply for this job online, you will be required to answer the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you have two or more years of graphics experience?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you have strong knowledge of the following programs: Adobe Creative Suite 6, InDesign CS6, Photoshop CS6, Illustrator CS6 and Flash CS6?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-new-york-islanders-uniondale-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-new-york-islanders-uniondale-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile UI/UX Designer at SKMedia Inc. in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SKMedia specializes in custom software solutions for mobile and web applications that solve real world problems for consumers and businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a freelance mobile UI/UX designer to help with designing the user interface and user experience of a real time location based application that will change the way people use ground transportation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing a highly functional interface for our mobile application that is easy for end users to perceive, learn, and act upon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design visual mockups based on specifications with the ability to recommend revisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with our business and development team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make recommendations and decisions on design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong background in designing for iOS, Android, and web UI/UX and their respective design principles is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to account for differences between newer &amp;amp; older versions of mobile OSes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong background in Adobe Creative Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to produce mockups, prototypes, and variations quickly &amp;amp; on time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work collaboratively and interpret direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to handle some changing requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, written &amp;amp; verbal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work remotely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-ui-ux-designer-skmedia-inc-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-ui-ux-designer-skmedia-inc-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Boys Apparel GraphicDesigner (DKNY/Lucky/LRG) at Justice in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;To create graphics (placement art and repeats) for boys sportswear apparel lines, sizes NB-20.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PRINCIPAL ACCOUNTABILITIES-&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To create new graphic elements based on Design direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To modify and adjust graphic elements from corporate office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present research and develop graphic themes for each season/delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop graphic artwork for screen prints, embroideries, appliqués, patches, trims, labels, packaging and accessories to be implemented on apparel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Template each graphics to be production ready.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually search and shop for graphic elements applicable to the apparel line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Planning and Organization:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life cycle of season from sku plan to development to final product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;KNOWLEDGE AND EXPERIENCE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To qualify, candidates must have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-7 years experience in boys or mens sportswear apparel market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of computer graphic technology specifically: Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop. (a level above proficient is required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hand skill: Sketching, drawing, rendering ability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good color sense.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and understanding of graphic printing techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to receive and follow through on design direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adhere to deadlines set by Head Designer/Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate and work well with others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College degree is a plus but not necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/boys-apparel-graphicdesigner-dkny-lucky-lrg-justice-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/boys-apparel-graphicdesigner-dkny-lucky-lrg-justice-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Cigna in New York</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our client in NYC is seeking a Senior Graphic Designer to join the  fast-paced, in-house marketing and design team. Candidate should be a skilled and creative designer, with a minimum of 3 years experience. Attention to detail, problem-solving and communication skills, and the ability to work under pressure are critical (lots of production work along with the creative staff).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Projects range from print (posters, postcards, brochures, advertising), to design for web, social media, and other digital outlets&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA (in Design or equivalent, but a good portfolio is most important)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced ability with Adobe CS5 (especially InDesign, Photoshop and Illustrator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of/experience with print production and basic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;web/digital technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently and multi-task in a fast-paced, deadline-driven environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create marketing materials for hundreds of programs, including fliers, posters, invitations, brochures, postcards, newsletters/direct-mail pieces, outdoor phone and bus kiosk advertisements, print advertising and their extension to web/digital&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be able to handle working on multiple jobs at the same time in a fast-paced environment, communicating well with the marketing account reps and clients&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with web developers to coordinate artwork for web and digital&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain relationships with print vendors, find new vendors &amp;ndash; request print estimates on larger or unique jobs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Art directing photography a few times a year; experience photo editing/retouching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor junior designer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For immediate consideration please email resume to application@ezrah.org&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-cigna-new-york</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-cigna-new-york</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at Technosoft Corporation in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Forbes Creative division is seeking a highly motivated and creative individual to join our design team within the conferences and live media group. The right candidate must possess innovative design skills, be proactive, a problem-solver, be able to multi-task and work under tight deadlines in a fast paced environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This candidate will support the conference sales director and planning group in developing and executing sales and marketing materials in both print and digital platforms. The Graphic Designer will execute a wide-variety of projects including presentations, digital ad units, in-magazine sections, high-impact ad unit mockups, email blasts, as well as direct mail pieces and conference collateral that focus on bringing our brand message to consumers and potential sponsors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Graphic Design or related discipline from an accredited college or university, or equivalent training and/or experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 or more years professional experience with a clear understanding of best practices in print production and web design. Publishing experience is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software expertise should include but not limited to: InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash, Dreamweaver (HTML/CSS), Keynote, PowerPoint, Microsoft Word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video Editing software knowledge a plus, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a team player who thrives in a collaborative environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess strong organizational and time management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be comfortable following direction and implementing changes, while balancing strong design and tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to absorb and synthesize complex branding and style requirements from clients and account managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-technosoft-corporation-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-technosoft-corporation-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer at Salesforce in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1999,  salesforce.com  is the enterprise cloud computing company that is leading customers in their transformation to become social enterprises. Social enterprises are able to connect with customers, partners and employees in entirely new ways. Based on  salesforce.com &amp;rsquo;s real-time, multitenant architecture, the company&amp;rsquo;s platform and application services give customers the tools to create a true social front office and revolutionize the way they sell, service, market, collaborate, work, and innovate. With more than 9,000 employees, the first enterprise cloud computing company to exceed $2.5B in annual revenue run rate, and more than 100,000 customers worldwide, we are proud to contribute to the success of companies of all sizes and industries, around the globe. We&amp;rsquo;re also one of the &amp;ldquo;Best Places to Work&amp;rdquo; (FORTUNE). If you&amp;rsquo;re passionate about innovation, come help revolutionize how companies collaborate and communicate with customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Marketing Cloud is not only about technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about changing the customer experience—making it personal, and really relevant, fast.  The Marketing Cloud unites the capabilities of Buddy Media, the world&amp;rsquo;s #1 social marketing solution, with the world&amp;rsquo;s #1 social listening platform, Radian6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the team:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team plans, designs and builds product demonstrations and prototypes on top of the salesforce.com platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team supports product launches, prospect/customer meetings and major events with demos that amaze audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work is showcased both internally and externally, and is a critical part of ideating and selling software to our clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Scope of Job:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a scripted user flow that showcases particular features, utilizing user personas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production of wireframes and designs of each screen, by leveraging and improving an existing library of reusable UI elements to create full-page designs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with a front end developer, who will  take the script and designs and produce coded prototype/demo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on multiple projects simultaneously, requiring attention to detail and working within constrained timelines; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product team to understand the direction of the Marketing Cloud products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Ideal Qualities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates who are great story tellers;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love working on prototypes for shows/demos;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive on fast-paced environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a Prototyping/vision mindset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know when to defend design choices; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to find and reference other solutions you’ve seen before.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio demonstrating a deeply grounded background in modern interface design;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience delivering UI artifacts, including: style and color guides; UI element library; organized, multi-layer PSDs of full-page designs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with business stakeholders and engineers;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working knowledge of Semantic xHTML and limitations of CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Applicants Should Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio of past work, preferably including application UI &amp;amp; form design; user personas, and scripts.  Anything that best demonstrates your skillset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-salesforce-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-salesforce-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer On-Site Freelance at Lugh Studio in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;COMPANY DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lugh Studio, Inc. is a branding and graphic design studio that provides focused and effective branding strategies. In over 15 years of business, Lugh Studio has worked with clients in a variety of industries ranging from Fortune 100 companies to small start-ups.  Our multi-lingual onsite staff, as well as our extensive network of freelance talent, enable us to work effectively in different media and languages, domestically and internationally. Located in downtown Brooklyn with a spectacular view of the harbor and New York skyline, Lugh Studio offers a uniquely creative, diverse, and dynamic work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a graphic designer who will collaborate with the rest of our team to conceptualize, develop, and execute highly compelling brand identities for our clients. This position will be on-site freelancer with the potential to go full-time. We will also consider highly qualified individuals to work off-site on a case by case basis. The successful candidate will have the ability to understand the needs of the client, and to creatively and efficiently deliver the solution to those needs. This candidate absolutely must have the ability to pay close attention to detail, self-manage, follow directions, and meet deadlines under pressure. Lugh Studio needs a team player who is quick, efficient, and knows how to manage his or her time. The candidate should have a good attitude, be able to work flexible hours, and be willing to do whatever needs to get done. If you feel this describes you, please submit your resume, portfolio, and references.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative concepts for branding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design print collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production &amp;amp; edits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magazine design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Adobe InDesign, Illustrator, and Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in HTML, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum two years of experience in a related position&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a boutique design firm based in Brooklyn specializing in visual branding and web design. Our team consists of graphic designers who work in both web and print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our projects range from start-ups looking for create an image, to established businesses needing to bolster their web presence. Our services include all things digital and print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our office is located in downtown Brooklyn with a spectacular view of the harbor and New York skyline.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-onsite-freelance-lugh-studio-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-onsite-freelance-lugh-studio-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer, Travel+ Leisure at American Express in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Job of the Designer in the T+L Art Department is two-fold: This person designs pages for the magazine and tablet editions and provides administrative support to this very busy art department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;DESIGN RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs and sees through to printer and tablet release the entire edit/production process of all Front-of-Book layouts including Contents pages, Contributors, In Box, T+L Digital, Letters, Mastheads and Back Page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Along with the Design Director, conceptualizes idea for the Point of View essay every month and commissions illustrations accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps out designing for our tablet editions each month and digital premiums.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in the color correction process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADMINISTRATIVE/DESIGN DEPARTMENT SUPPORT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enters all illustration commissions into an editorial tracking system. Handles flow of contracts and invoicing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hangs the wall every month and helps to update the wall for various meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports the Design Director with extra projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps magazine subscriptions up to date and coordinates ordering supplies for the department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps the Design Director file expenses every month.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have some previous consumer magazine print experience, knowledge of illustrators and a sophisticated eye for photography and typographic details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a proactive, self-starter with a collaborative spirit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous tablet experience is a huge plus. An inherent love for print magazines is appreciated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A. in graphic design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of full Adobe Creative Suite (CS5 or CS6) is a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Woodwing is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some web design experience is appreciated, but not a requirement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-travel%2B-leisure-american-express-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-travel%2B-leisure-american-express-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>