<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer at Salesforce in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1999,  salesforce.com  is the enterprise cloud computing company that is leading customers in their transformation to become social enterprises. Social enterprises are able to connect with customers, partners and employees in entirely new ways. Based on  salesforce.com &amp;rsquo;s real-time, multitenant architecture, the company&amp;rsquo;s platform and application services give customers the tools to create a true social front office and revolutionize the way they sell, service, market, collaborate, work, and innovate. With more than 9,000 employees, the first enterprise cloud computing company to exceed $2.5B in annual revenue run rate, and more than 100,000 customers worldwide, we are proud to contribute to the success of companies of all sizes and industries, around the globe. We&amp;rsquo;re also one of the &amp;ldquo;Best Places to Work&amp;rdquo; (FORTUNE). If you&amp;rsquo;re passionate about innovation, come help revolutionize how companies collaborate and communicate with customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Marketing Cloud is not only about technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about changing the customer experience—making it personal, and really relevant, fast.  The Marketing Cloud unites the capabilities of Buddy Media, the world&amp;rsquo;s #1 social marketing solution, with the world&amp;rsquo;s #1 social listening platform, Radian6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the team:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team plans, designs and builds product demonstrations and prototypes on top of the salesforce.com platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team supports product launches, prospect/customer meetings and major events with demos that amaze audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work is showcased both internally and externally, and is a critical part of ideating and selling software to our clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Scope of Job:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a scripted user flow that showcases particular features, utilizing user personas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production of wireframes and designs of each screen, by leveraging and improving an existing library of reusable UI elements to create full-page designs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with a front end developer, who will  take the script and designs and produce coded prototype/demo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on multiple projects simultaneously, requiring attention to detail and working within constrained timelines; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product team to understand the direction of the Marketing Cloud products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Ideal Qualities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates who are great story tellers;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love working on prototypes for shows/demos;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive on fast-paced environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a Prototyping/vision mindset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know when to defend design choices; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to find and reference other solutions you’ve seen before.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio demonstrating a deeply grounded background in modern interface design;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience delivering UI artifacts, including: style and color guides; UI element library; organized, multi-layer PSDs of full-page designs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with business stakeholders and engineers;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working knowledge of Semantic xHTML and limitations of CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Applicants Should Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio of past work, preferably including application UI &amp;amp; form design; user personas, and scripts.  Anything that best demonstrates your skillset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-salesforce-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-salesforce-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer On-Site Freelance at Lugh Studio in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;COMPANY DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lugh Studio, Inc. is a branding and graphic design studio that provides focused and effective branding strategies. In over 15 years of business, Lugh Studio has worked with clients in a variety of industries ranging from Fortune 100 companies to small start-ups.  Our multi-lingual onsite staff, as well as our extensive network of freelance talent, enable us to work effectively in different media and languages, domestically and internationally. Located in downtown Brooklyn with a spectacular view of the harbor and New York skyline, Lugh Studio offers a uniquely creative, diverse, and dynamic work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a graphic designer who will collaborate with the rest of our team to conceptualize, develop, and execute highly compelling brand identities for our clients. This position will be on-site freelancer with the potential to go full-time. We will also consider highly qualified individuals to work off-site on a case by case basis. The successful candidate will have the ability to understand the needs of the client, and to creatively and efficiently deliver the solution to those needs. This candidate absolutely must have the ability to pay close attention to detail, self-manage, follow directions, and meet deadlines under pressure. Lugh Studio needs a team player who is quick, efficient, and knows how to manage his or her time. The candidate should have a good attitude, be able to work flexible hours, and be willing to do whatever needs to get done. If you feel this describes you, please submit your resume, portfolio, and references.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative concepts for branding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design print collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production &amp;amp; edits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magazine design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Adobe InDesign, Illustrator, and Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in HTML, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum two years of experience in a related position&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a boutique design firm based in Brooklyn specializing in visual branding and web design. Our team consists of graphic designers who work in both web and print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our projects range from start-ups looking for create an image, to established businesses needing to bolster their web presence. Our services include all things digital and print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our office is located in downtown Brooklyn with a spectacular view of the harbor and New York skyline.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-onsite-freelance-lugh-studio-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-onsite-freelance-lugh-studio-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer, Travel+ Leisure at American Express in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Job of the Designer in the T+L Art Department is two-fold: This person designs pages for the magazine and tablet editions and provides administrative support to this very busy art department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;DESIGN RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs and sees through to printer and tablet release the entire edit/production process of all Front-of-Book layouts including Contents pages, Contributors, In Box, T+L Digital, Letters, Mastheads and Back Page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Along with the Design Director, conceptualizes idea for the Point of View essay every month and commissions illustrations accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps out designing for our tablet editions each month and digital premiums.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in the color correction process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADMINISTRATIVE/DESIGN DEPARTMENT SUPPORT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enters all illustration commissions into an editorial tracking system. Handles flow of contracts and invoicing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hangs the wall every month and helps to update the wall for various meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports the Design Director with extra projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps magazine subscriptions up to date and coordinates ordering supplies for the department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps the Design Director file expenses every month.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have some previous consumer magazine print experience, knowledge of illustrators and a sophisticated eye for photography and typographic details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a proactive, self-starter with a collaborative spirit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous tablet experience is a huge plus. An inherent love for print magazines is appreciated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A. in graphic design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of full Adobe Creative Suite (CS5 or CS6) is a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Woodwing is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some web design experience is appreciated, but not a requirement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-travel%2B-leisure-american-express-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-travel%2B-leisure-american-express-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior UX Designer at Pine River Capital Management in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;A lead / senior UX Designer at Pod1 will combine strategy, creativity and technology to design interfaces that deliver the ultimate digital experience which meet the needs of the consumer and business objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Roles and Responsibilities;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in the brainstorming of and creation of concepts for best-in-class user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate abstract concepts into simple and elegant user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create concept models, user interface sketches, and detailed schematics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with fellow creatives and developers to ensure the solidity of design systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with clients to make the best work, finding the intersection between business and user goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Represent User Experience in pitch work and business development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan for, delegate, oversee, and polish all UX project deliverables (such as strategic vision briefs, concepts, wireframes, site maps, content inventories, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding and demonstration of user centered design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of what types of experiences are made possible by current digital technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to develop simple and elegant design approaches to complex design problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to collaborate actively as part of a multi-disciplinary team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In possession of excellent interpersonal communication skills, analytical and leadership potential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be organized, able to act independently, and able to switch rapidly between different projects in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work with grace under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated thought leadership in at least one of the following domains; product design, commerce, mobile, branding, retail, and social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3+ years experience in an Experience Design role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Axure, OmniGraffle or other tools for generating wireframes and specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Courses or further education in HCI, UI or design considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;How to apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please write an email to nicky.conti@pod1.com with a short resume and saying why you&amp;rsquo;re interested in the job.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-pine-river-capital-management-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ux-designer-pine-river-capital-management-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Product Designer at Blackstone in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Product designers collaborate with other members of the design team, product managers, and engineers to deliver great experiences for local merchants and their customers. Product designers cultivate deep empathy for their users, and translate this understanding into inventive and delightful product designs that cross channels and devices (email, web, mobile, and tablet).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User research, from in-home and in-store interviews to screen-sharing usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sketching, concept generation, and other ideation exercises to push the boundaries of what we build&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workflows, wireframes, and other elements of making explicit the functional and systems core of a product’s design, across all relevant channels and devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Craft prototypes of proposed product designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute ideas to improve existing products, both in and outside personal expertise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product managers and engineers to complete projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First and foremost, applicants should be awesome, empathetic design thinkers who can engage in an end-to-end experience, from vision to production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio featuring examples of product and interaction work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think about high-level product vision and contribute a vision of a fantastic user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong, clean visual design sense, valuing usability, simplicity, and consistency (cats optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great design communication skills; able to tell the story of a design from end to end&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid grounding in fundamentals of HCI, human cognition, and user-centered design principles and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with qualitative user research methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to follow interface guidelines, style guides, and best practices when designing for new platforms, and an ability to intelligently challenge and improve them when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience designing for the modern, highly interactive web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort working in fast-moving, agile development environments
Healthy sense of humor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-designer-blackstone-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-designer-blackstone-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at Blackstone in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;To keep our company on the fast track we need the very best talent to lead the way. The Senior User Experience Designer will be involved in all phases of the development process. The UX Designer will work in a highly collaborative environment with other skilled software professionals to deliver exceptional software and tools to help them improve the customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop user interfaces that are clean, easy and intuitive, which incorporate the latest technologies, customer feedback, and UX best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and scale wireframes and sitemaps for web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate requirements into UX deliverables that meet business objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create first rate graphic assets in a fast paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct usability analysis and testing, and make recommendations for improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Who we are looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands basic web-based and client/server architectures, including how systems interface with each other&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building e-commerce and mobile web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and passion for responsive web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of UX Design and building web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of HTML, CSS, Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work collaboratively with cross-functional teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Careful attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-blackstone-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-blackstone-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at Blackstone in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We work in a highly empowered work environment where managers are very involved in planning and generating ideas for improvement. You will be supported and surrounded by some of the best and brightest people in the industry. People who care about our customers and care about helping them achieve the results they seek.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Marketing Manager, the Sr Graphic Designer is responsible for designing and developing marketing collateral and graphics to support relay sales growth objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES INCLUDE:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, develop and update relay marketing collateral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify needs and develop the visual communication messaging for marketing collateral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide graphics support for Electrical Division content on Littelfuse.com, and LF Resource Center.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor and ensure proper brand representation through different media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA in Communication, Marketing, Graphic Design or other related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7-10 years of experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-blackstone-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-blackstone-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Bloo Circle in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bloo Circle, is a leading full-service interactive agency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We own and
operate numerous internet businesses serving both businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT THE JOB&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our company is growing quickly and we are looking for a number of web designers both experienced designers with years of working on large-scale sites as well as recent grads who are looking to get their feet wet. Our design work ranges from designing new large-scale consumer sites to designing simple but critically important banner and email ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We pay a competitive salary and this is a great opportunity to work directly with our Vice-president of Operations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-bloo-circle-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-bloo-circle-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at Lot18 in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Join Lot18, and help us improve the wine-buying experience for our customers. There&amp;rsquo;s a ton of opportunity to build new things and improve everything we already have, and we need someone with a great eye for user experience design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in user research efforts, including usability testing and listening labs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create intuitive navigation and interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document those designs with wireframes, user flows and site maps Work hand-in-hand with Product Managers, Developers, and Web Designers to deliver projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide a final layer of user acceptance testing and quality assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Characteristics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS/MA/MS in HCI, interaction design, computer science, psychology preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years experience in IA/UX design for the web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ecommerce or transactional experience a plus Coding is not necessary, but a solid knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript capabilities is desirable An eye for good web design, and a passion for creating it Excellent communication skills, both written and verbal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-lot18-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-lot18-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Designer at Shutterstock in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Company&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shutterstock is a global marketplace for digital imagery. We help creative people around the world bring their projects to life with millions of photos, illustrations, and footage clips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The People&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a trailblazing New York tech company, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for talented people who believe in working hard and having fun. Our ideal candidates are curious and passionate about finding creative solutions to complex problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Agile product and tech teams get to build a lot of really cool systems at scale using Perl, JavaScript / Node.js, PHP, Ruby, Solr, Apache, Nginx, Puppet, Chef, Selenium, and MySQL. Check out our open source projects at &lt;a href=&quot;http://code.shutterstock.com&quot;&gt;http://code.shutterstock.com&lt;/a&gt; and our tech blog at &lt;a href=&quot;http://bits.shutterstock.com&quot;&gt;http://bits.shutterstock.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Office&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re headquartered in New York City, but we&amp;rsquo;re truly a global company with customers in over 150 countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Fun Stuff&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know that the trick to keeping awesome people happy is by creating a fun, comfortable environment. This includes competitive pay for top talent, full medical benefits, plus:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocked beverage fridges, free breakfasts &amp;amp; snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lunchtime Yoga&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pizza &amp;amp; Massage Fridays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy hours and killer Summer &amp;amp; Holiday parties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Want to know more about us? Check out our blog, Facebook page or follow us on Twitter. Think you have the right stuff to be part of the team? Check out our open positions below or submit a general application and let us know how you can make an impact at Shutterstock!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-designer-shutterstock-design</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-designer-shutterstock-design</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>