<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Designer at Gilt Groupe Inc in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Gilt Groupe is looking for a Mobile Visual Designer to join our fun, progressive, rapidly growing ecommerce team. The Mobile Designer will report into the Head of Creative while working as a member of the mobile team to create innovative and intuitive mobile shopping experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mobile Designer will partner with product, engineering, and user experience to define new concepts, tools, and experiences from initial concept to final implementation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design visually attractive and thoughtful mobile interfaces based on principles of design and usability while taking into consideration the unique needs of each mobile platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a deep understanding of Gilt’s visual design principles and how they can be adapted and applied across multiple mobile platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain visual guidelines to ensure consistent representation of the Gilt’s brand across each individual device and application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a strong point of view about visual design and how it can improve the user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuously collaborate with UX, product, and engineering as a core member of the mobile team in the agile development of Gilt’s mobile products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or equivalent in graphic design or interaction design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio demonstrating innovative mobile design work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience designing for mobile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about reinventing how people shop on mobile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication, collaboration, and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly proficient in Photoshop and Illustrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a very collaborative, creative, fast paced, and agile environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable sharing concepts and taking feedback from a very passionate and involved team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously and to keep abreast of innovative design trends and technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-designer-gilt-groupe-inc-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-designer-gilt-groupe-inc-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Graphic Designer at Corr-Jensen in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Fast growing health and wellness nutraceuticals company seeking a creative, passionate, and entrepreneurial addition to the team in our SoHo office beginning as soon as possible! We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a rockstar candidate to support our growing design team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think you have the motivation, creativity, and flexibility to juggle the demands of a vibrant work environment in the heart of SoHo, drop us a line &amp;ndash; and include your portfolio!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will be comfortable creating 3D renderings, web banners, print ads and product labels. Knowledge of HTML, CSS or PHP a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare work by following previously established brand standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create banners and graphics for the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload content via our CMS or FTP as scheduled&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create accurate, print-ready files according to specs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in creating templates for sales and marketing collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete projects by managing and tracking due dates, material needed, etc. in close collaboration with the Art Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Skills/Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe CS6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet tight deadlines and multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keen attention to detail and excellent organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 years of creative design experience creating print and web designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work hard and have fun!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Competitive; Depending on Experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please tell us why you&amp;rsquo;d be a fit and please submit a link to your portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Corr-Jensen:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About Us: Corr-Jensen is a health and lifestyle company that strives to provide the highest quality products to meet a variety of nutritional needs in the most natural way possible. With a portfolio of brands including AbCuts, Skinnygirl Daily, and Training Day, Corr-Jensen has experienced expansive growth in the dietary and nutritional supplements industry since its founding in 2008 and continues to rapidly evolve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For More Information, please visit our websites:
* &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.revolutionlifestyle.com&quot;&gt;http://www.revolutionlifestyle.com&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.skinnygirldaily.com&quot;&gt;http://www.skinnygirldaily.com&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trainingday.com&quot;&gt;http://www.trainingday.com&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thedominant1.com&quot;&gt;http://www.thedominant1.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-graphic-designer-corr-jensen-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-graphic-designer-corr-jensen-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Product Designer at Kickstarter.com in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our small and passionate design team is growing. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone equal parts designer and developer to help shape the tools people use to bring new projects to life. As a part of our team, you&amp;rsquo;ll work with engineers, editors, product managers, and our community team to define how project creators and backers interact. We&amp;rsquo;re constantly shipping features and iterating, so expect a hands-on, collaborative environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel as comfortable in Photoshop as you do writing CSS? Obsess over grid systems as much as you do media queries? If you&amp;rsquo;re a self-starter, sweat the details, and want to have a visible impact on the lives of people in the creative community, we want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to code your work (we use Haml and Sass)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version control systems like Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-browser testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with mobile design and dev (responsive, mobile sites, and/or native iOS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JS and DOM scripting, ideally with jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a Rails environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-designer-kickstarter-com-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-designer-kickstarter-com-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Graphic Designer at JPMorgan Chase in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. (NYSE: JPM) is a leading global financial services firm with assets of $2 trillion and operations in more than 60 countries. The firm is a leader in investment banking, financial services for consumers, small business and commercial banking, financial transaction processing, asset management, and private equity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JPMorgan Chase is seeking an experienced and dynamic Graphic Designer to join the Corporate Marketing and Communications team. The candidate will join the group that is responsible for designing and producing the firm&amp;rsquo;s Annual Report; developing and enforcing the firm&amp;rsquo;s brand guidelines; maintaining and updating the jpmorganbrand.com site; designing and producing sponsorship ads for various groups in the firm; supporting the graphic needs of the Chase Communications team; overseeing and updating the jpmorganchase.com website; managing updates for the stationery ordering site; ensuring that gift items, which carry our logos, are correctly branded; designing and producing printed and online materials for the various sponsorships the firm underwrites, among them the J.P. Morgan Corporate Challenge; and providing general design support for various corporate groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team&amp;rsquo;s key responsibility is to maintain, develop and support the JPMorgan Chase brand, which includes some support for the marketing brands, Chase and J.P. Morgan, as well.  Projects include, but are not limited to, identity development, print, web and motion-based designs. The ideal candidate will possess innovative and creative thinking skills, as well as an ability to translate strategic ideas into visual concepts. The candidate should have a minimum of 5-10 years of experience, worked for an in-house design department or agency. The job opening is a full-time position  based in New York City reporting to the Head of Corporate Branding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs high quality and innovative concepts, including but not limited to brochures, Annual Reports, web sites and other electronic media, and events-related materials such as identities, invitations, posters, electronic screens, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and edits documents using templates and style sheets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with design team members on complex or special projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages and provides quality control over multiple projects from concept through completion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrates a commitment to high-quality design and accuracy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates and contributes in brainstorming sessions with marketing teams, creates concepts that bring ideas to life, and articulates creative concepts clearly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applies consistent design vision across multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepares final print-ready art files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures that all communications, whether online or offline, follow brand guidelines and that they are delivered to printers and web developers in the desired formats, free of errors and within designated deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works quickly and purposefully to complete the desired output according to instructions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interfaces with external printers and other vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocates excellent design and positively impacts the work environment for the long term growth of the design discipline in the firm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acts as a resource for our marketing colleagues to help develop communications materials and prototypes that communicate the JPMorgan Chase positioning as the best in class leader in the industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BFA or MFA in Graphic Design or similar discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio of work required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of hands-on design experience in both print and web, with proficiency in graphic design software; candidates without this experience will not be considered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong skills in Adobe CS suite products, in particular InDesign, Illustrator and Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in MS Word and PowerPoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of printing processes, pre-press development and production standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of html a plus, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design aesthetic in layout, composition and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled in developing and applying branding guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to effectively function independently or in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meticulous attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English language proficiency required and excellent writing skills are considered a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong project- and time-management and organizational skills with the ability to multi task and meet tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the financial industry is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presents facts, thoughts and ideas in a clear, concise, convincing and organized manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops and sustains effective and cooperative working relationships with peers, all levels of management in the firm and external stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to be flexible and adapt to change in direction based upon team and stakeholder consensus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Apply today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-graphic-designer-jpmorgan-chase-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-graphic-designer-jpmorgan-chase-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at JPMorgan Chase in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About J.P. Morgan Corporate &amp;amp; Investment Bank&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J.P. Morgan&amp;rsquo;s Corporate &amp;amp; Investment Bank is a global leader across banking, markets and investor services. The world&amp;rsquo;s most important corporations, governments and institutions entrust us with their business in more than 100 countries. With $18 trillion of assets under custody and $393 billion in deposits, the Corporate &amp;amp; Investment Bank provides strategic advice, raises capital, manages risk and extends liquidity in markets around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;User Experience and User Interface designer for ICOLive! Portal project&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications required:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strong UI / UX design experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Desired:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;infrastructure experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Necessary Technology or Application Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perl / Python / Java programming&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;work experience requirement&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. offers an exceptional benefits program and a highly competitive compensation package.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. is an Equal Opportunity and Affirmative Action Employer, M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job&lt;/strong&gt; Technology&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Primary Location&lt;/strong&gt; US-NY-Work At Home&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Organization&lt;/strong&gt; Investment Bank&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Schedule&lt;/strong&gt; Full-time&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Job Type&lt;/strong&gt; Standard&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Shift&lt;/strong&gt; Day Job&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Employee Status&lt;/strong&gt; Regular&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Corporate Brand&lt;/strong&gt; J.P. Morgan&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-jpmorgan-chase-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-jpmorgan-chase-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Experience Designer at R/GA in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in the brainstorming of and creation of concepts for best-in-class user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate abstract concepts into simple and elegant user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create concept models, user interface sketches, and detailed schematics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with fellow creatives and developers to ensure the solidity of design systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Several examples of successfully launched projects which demonstrate strategic, conceptual and creative thinking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3+ years experience in an Experience Design role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding and demonstration of user centered design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of what types of experiences are made possible by current digital technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to develop simple and elegant design approaches to complex design problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to collaborate actively as part of a multi-disciplinary team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In possession of excellent interpersonal communication skills, analytical and leadership potential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be organized, able to act independently, and able to switch rapidly between different projects in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work with grace under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated thought leadership in at least one of the following domains; product design, commerce, mobile, branding, retail, and social media a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-experience-designer-r-ga-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-experience-designer-r-ga-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at 360i in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a next generation digital agency rooted in innovation and drive. We don&amp;rsquo;t walk; we run. We don&amp;rsquo;t follow; we lead. We dream, and then we do. Our ideas are big, but our results are bigger. Bigger still is our collective pursuit of positive change &amp;ndash; the innovations that will move our industry forward in new and exciting directions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The digital world changes fast &amp;mdash; and our employees are just as dynamic. We&amp;rsquo;re continuing to evolve our marketing capabilities, having gone from specialty agency to digital AOR in just 5 years. We have an incredible track record of selling in and executing the ideas we pitch. And we&amp;rsquo;ve more than doubled in size over the last 2 years while doing work for world-class brands like Coke, Oreo and other Kraft Foods brands, Smirnoff, Guinness, Fisher-Price, NBC Universal and jcpenney.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come join the #2 Agency, and help make us #1 in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;You are:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Graphic Designer at Content Studio at 360i. You transform creative vision into eye-popping on and off-line digital experiences for our diverse range of clients. You see opportunity in every project, whether a chance to show off your skills or an invitation to learn new ones. You don&amp;rsquo;t hold back and you don&amp;rsquo;t shut down. New directions and new ideas are what motivate you, flawless execution is what satisfies you. You&amp;rsquo;re clever, efficient, and something else that people can&amp;rsquo;t quite put their finger on, but whatever it is&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s awesome and it needs to create cool stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;You will:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Creative/Design/Art Directors and Copy Writers to compose engaging online experiences, digital advertising, social content and internal promotional/sales material.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Articulate and defend creative decisions, take feedback and push beyond expectations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research, demonstrate and report on new tools, trends and techniques that can help expand the capability, creativity and expertise of you and the 360i:Recess team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore opportunities and ideas to bring digital into the physical world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and uphold the highest standards of quality, efficiency and organization with regard to creative execution, production and file/asset management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help foster a culture of ideas, experimentation and collaboration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;You must have or be:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion: Your significant-other thinks you have A.D.D. (and you might), because the ideas never stop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisdom: You have a solid grasp of complex design principles including grid systems, typography, color etc. and can explain them to those that don&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curiosity: You&amp;rsquo;re addicted to knowledge and inspiration and you&amp;rsquo;re always looking for the next fix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast and flexible: Because getting through the stuff we HAVE to, lets us focus on the stuff we WANT to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weapons Expertise: You have a masterful knowledge of creative software and a true understanding of its place within the arsenal. You also know what a pencil is, and aren&amp;rsquo;t afraid to use it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MacGyver: You can solve problems with whatever you have on hand. A font or a color swatch is really all you need to stay &amp;ldquo;on-brand&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mechanical Ability: You love figuring out how things work and fixing them when they don&amp;rsquo;t because its the key to making them better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organization: You understand that the only way to a balance your A.D.D. is with a healthy dose of O.C.D.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident: You can speak and write but usually don&amp;rsquo;t need to because your work does most of the talking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personality: A strong sense of humor is an absolute must. Seriously. We&amp;rsquo;re not kidding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent: Be able to work independently and in a team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chops: A kick-ass portfolio that embodies all of the above and says &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re stupid if you don&amp;rsquo;t hire me!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Hobby: You absolutely MUST do something interesting that helps define who you are outside of the office. Sports, Music, Woodworking, Metalworking, Knitting, Cooking, Wine Making ANYTHING!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;It would be nice if you can:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrate in 2 and/or 3D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Animate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shoot/edit video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take amazing photographs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-360i-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-360i-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Software Developer / UX-UI Designer at Shindig in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Help build paradigm shifting web platform with application in social web, gaming, distance learning, and online events. Currently in stealth mode, company just closed its ‘Series A’ round and now seeks superstar Software Developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone hates video chat and we figured out why. Our innovative technology combines elements of design from gaming, video conferencing, and rich interactive applications to enable revolutionary new types of web experiences including online events, a next generation gaming platform, better online learning, and other dramatically enhanced purposeful online activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a software developer who has experience creating applications for the web and who can contribute to the creative vision of our products. The ideal individual for this position will have a solid software development background, with particular expertise in Flex and Java. They should have the ability to rapidly build Flash/Flex prototypes, develop PHP-based sites and accompanying databases, and be comfortable utilizing code management systems. Experience with web conferencing, VOIP, digital goods, or game design &amp;amp; development a big plus!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the central skill for this position is programming, as a small organization we are looking for a versatile player who can also help with UX design, articulate clear product specifications for other members of the team, and interact closely with our development partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time or part-time opportunity with significant growth potential. We&amp;rsquo;re housed in a great office environment near Union Square.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Company&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO is a serial entrepreneur and longtime angel tech investor. Among prior career highlights, he founded and led the largest US independent music company with some 30 Gold, Platinum, and Multi platinum artist releases to its credit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To apply, send a cover letter and your resume to Info@ShindigEvents.com. Please include the job title in your email&amp;rsquo;s subject line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/software-developer-ux-ui-designer-shindig-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/software-developer-ux-ui-designer-shindig-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Product Designer at Refinery29 in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;COMPANY DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refinery29 is the cornerstone of fashion, beauty, and shopping for a new generation. Combining daily local newsletter editions and a website that serves as a global style hub, Refinery29 offers the only 360-degree source for shopping, exclusive deals, trends, beauty news, local hot-spots, and at-home sneak-peeks of fashion&amp;rsquo;s finest. At Refinery29, great style isn&amp;rsquo;t just a one-way obsession—it&amp;rsquo;s a fast-changing world where readers talk, designers, brands, and shop-keepers engage, and great fashion influences everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a senior product designer who loves to solve interesting problems, create meaningful interactions, and design the slickest products. If you think you might be the one, we are eager to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Some responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping to define the user interface and visual design for new and existing Refinery29 products and features. This will include being the “keeper of consistency,” across all Refinery29 products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building, maintaining and improving the experience of the entire suite of Refinery29 products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translating business objectives and end-user needs into design strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working collaboratively with project teams under the supervision of the Director of User Experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participating in brainstorming sessions and concept sketching [we love working on Paper]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Please read carefully. You must:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have 2-3 yrs of experience in building large scale websites for commerce products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have prior experience in being an IA advocate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a master at Visual Design, love Typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have an un-satiated passion for new ways to design an interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have expert knowledge of Adobe suite products and Wireframing/Prototyping tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be an advocate of Lean UX methods, experience in Persona Research and User Testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Pluses:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Html/CSS experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to produce high fidelity prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education in Human Computer Interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does this sound like you? Let us know why we should meet. Please submit your resume along with an online portfolio.(EOE)day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-designer-refinery29-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/product-designer-refinery29-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer Internship at Pearson in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the Program
The Pearson Education Internship Program (PEIP) is a national internship program across various locations, functions, and businesses in Pearson North America. The program offers competitively compensated ten-week summer internships from June 3 – August 9, 2013 to students and recent college/university graduates (graduation date between January 2012 and June 2014).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the Pearson Education Internship Program (PEIP) visit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pearsonstudents.com/get-involved/internships/index.html&quot;&gt;http://www.pearsonstudents.com/get-involved/internships/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a complete list of internship opportunities visit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://jobs.pearson.com/go/internship-jobs-at-pearson-education/333372/&quot;&gt;http://jobs.pearson.com/go/internship-jobs-at-pearson-education/333372/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To Apply: Only applications submitted to this website will be considered. If you are applying for multiple internships, you must submit a separate application for each position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Department Overview&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tablets are changing education around the globe and Pearson is at the forefront of this revolution. Whether it’s Android tablets under $50 in Indian high schools, Nook tablets in powerless schools in Kenya or next generation gamification tools for Californian students &amp;ndash; we’re passionate about them all&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our group’s remit within Pearson is to be the one stop shop for our businesses to provide the platforms, guidance and support to build beautiful mobile products that are loved by billions of users. In that role, our responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building consumer products that are not only loved by the end users, but become a serious revenue stream for our businesses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supporting the larger Pearson-wide education projects that will establish Pearson as the clear leader in the digital transformation of education globally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building great enterprise mobile products that make the work lives of our colleagues more productive and efficient&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Internship Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role is responsible for supporting the creative needs of the products created by the Mobile &amp;amp; Gaming group, including product presentations for different stakeholders. S/he will be responsible for innovative, inspired and beautiful web, mobile and digital design that communicates the core message of the group effectively. The Graphic Designer Intern will work directly with the Lead Designer and/or Senior Product Managers on assigned projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Internship Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide and prepare graphic design files for all assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for functions such as proofreading, final project check/quality control and ensuring that projects are properly prepared for web or print output&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Internship Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and design innovative and effective visual designs for mobile apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and organize the creative process within each project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to everyday discussions and ideas that pertain to existing and new projects with creative solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;General Requirements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graduation date between January 2012 – June 2014&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3.2 GPA or above&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to participate in ten-week internship session: June 3 – August 9, 2013&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proper authorization to work in the U.S. or Canada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Required Technical Skills&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the Adobe Suite is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for creative design, technology and education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently and cooperatively in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open to constructive feedback directly from internal customers and is willing to make requested changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and good organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good stakeholder management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Skills (optional)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with designing for mobile apps is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated interest in digital/mobile design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Ideal Intern&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ideal intern will be pursuing a graduate or undergraduate degree in the NYC area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Candidates will be requested to provide a website link or a pdf of recent work for review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Segments:&lt;/strong&gt; Intern, Graphic Design, Proofreading, Copy Editor, Temporary, Entry Level, Creative, Contract&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-internship-pearson-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-internship-pearson-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>