<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Project Manager - Digital Projects at Project One in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our Broadcast/ Digital Media client, who own and operate some of the top TV Stations and digital experiences in the world, is seeking a Technical Project Manager to join their Entertainment Group and lead multiple projects across this interactive department.  These projects will cover everything Digital, from website &amp;amp; mobile redesign to new development efforts (both web and mobile).  There will also be interaction with the product side of new Television shows and initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage concurrent technical projects, in an Agile environment, dealing extensively with interactive &amp;amp; digital initiatives (web redesign, mobile development, streaming video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, track, and remove impediments to project success&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review project requests and participate in the green-light process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitate the creation of a well-defined Project Backlog or Project Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage Sprint and Release planning or development cycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with offshore development teams to tightly integrate them into their project work streams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze risk and mitigation accordingly, including establishing contingency plans and initiating corrective action&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track and report key project metrics and capital budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate participation of different tech and business groups in requirements gathering, specifications, design, development and implementation of key projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn, understand, and actively use project management software to effectively manage project deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 + years experience managing technical projects, specifically dealing with digital and web-based initiatives in the Media or Interactive Industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a Project Manager in an Agile environment, with an excellent understanding of sprints and running Scrum meetings; Understanding of more traditional PM Methodologies would be extremely helpful as well&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading projects involving website or mobile redesigns, streaming video or mobile initiatives, mobile applications, or in-depth product-centric initiatives (building a full web/mobile campaign around a TV show)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand technologies applicable to a chosen project and facilitate resolution of technical issues as they arise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable superb written and verbal communications and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A willing team member who enjoys working collaboratively across all business units&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Alison Landau
Direct: (212) 792-6368&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Northeast (NY): (212) 268-5800
Nationwide: (877) 677-6566&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-project-manager-digital-projects-project-one-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-project-manager-digital-projects-project-one-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Strategy Director at Razorfish Healthware in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Razorfish Healthware is a key partner for health and wellness companies who want to grow their business by engaging with and improving the lives of their customers.  With a focus on creating brand experiences that build our clients’ business, we leverage our unique mix of insight, technology, creativity, and industry savvy to transform the health and wellness community so that our clients can build healthy relationships that last. Headquartered in Philadelphia, Razorfish Healthware is a brand of Razorfish, and a member of the Paris-based Publicis Groupe S.A. the world’s third largest communications group, second largest media counsel and buying group, and a global leader in digital and healthcare communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re the Strategy department of Razorfish Healthware, part of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest interactive agency. Within the Strategy department, Digital Strategists are responsible for the successful planning and implementation of digital solutions for our clients. They help to create overall advertising and marketing tactics that bridge web, mobile, email, and other digital media. They direct how brands are expressed through digital interactions and how those interactions fit into broader consumer and health care provider experiences. Our strategists play a lead role in developing digital strategies for a number of our agency’s top clients, and partner closely with the agency’s account service teams and discipline leads in media, creative, UX and Technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Strategy Director’s primary responsibility is to help our cross-functional teams develop and evolve digital solutions in the healthcare space driven to address unmet needs of consumers and/or health care Providers and drive a brand’s business forward. This requires evaluating consumer and industry research, brand information, digital trends and relevant technical and user requirements in order to recommend digital solutions. Their thought leadership and strategy will guide digital implementation executed by multi-disciplinary teams throughout the life of a project.
Specific Responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the account services, media and creative disciplines in developing and presenting overall analyses of client needs and digital marketing solutions to meet existing and new business client’s needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in and/or drives the design and development of online measurement solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides insights and develops recommendations based on measurement reporting and analysis and where appropriate to improve business, website and/or marketing program performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with the analytics team to design research plans and manage execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze and interpret information from multiple data sources as needed (database, primary research and syndicated) through knowledge and application of various qualitative and quantitative methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains functional expertise in digital marketing, integrated channel marketing (including online based channels such as websites, banners, email and search), analytics tools and, techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and facilitation of client workshops that make use of brainstorming and prioritization sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of social media strategies and oversight of social media monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writes POVs and authors white papers on various topics related to Digital Strategy and how the channel impacts business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interface and work in conjunction with a wide range of team members across various disciplines and departments is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of online (web) metrics, hands-on experience with tools of trade, and knowledge of relevant web measurement technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A command of digital marketing best practices, with an ability to incorporate them into implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in client-facing roles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexibility to travel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of integrated marketing and customer relationship management disciplines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possession of excellent written, oral communication, project management and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience working on strategies targeted to health care providers is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience with offline channels is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10+ years experience in digital communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience in a digital strategist or equivalent role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years in marketing or advertising.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/strategy-director-razorfish-healthware-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/strategy-director-razorfish-healthware-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director, Planning and Strategy at WNET New York Public Media in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;American Masters, Thirteen/WNET’s award-winning biography series, celebrates our arts and culture. Created and launched in 1986 by Executive Producer Susan Lacy, the series set the standard for documentary film profiles, accruing widespread critical acclaim – 50 Emmy nominations and 23 awards – including for Outstanding Primetime Non-Fiction Series in 1999, 2000, 2001, 2003, 2004, 2008, 2009 and 2011 – the 2012 Producers Guild Award for Outstanding Producer of Non-Fiction Television; an Oscar, three Grammys and 12 Peabody Awards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;American Masters has produced an exceptional library of 180 titles, bringing unique originality and perspective to exploring the lives and illuminating the creative journeys of our most enduring writers, musicians, visual and performing artists, dramatists and filmmakers – those who have “left an indelible impression on our cultural landscape.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Executive Producer of American Masters, this newly created position is responsible for devising and implementing short- and long-range strategies for enlarging and stabilizing the American Masters franchise, with a senior role in both external and internal (WNET) initiatives and communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Director will be responsible for developing innovative thinking and forging relationships to further the reach and scope of the series beyond broadcast into the digital space, publishing, creative partnerships with universities, libraries and other organizations; for evaluating and activating renewed and original exploitation of the assets of the American Masters archive; for considering and planning new spin-offs, sub-sets, mini-series etc. based on existing and future American Masters programming &amp;ndash; all with an eye to maximizing the educational,digital, social media and revenue producing possibilities for both the existing library and future productions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This effort will entail developing media and other creative partnerships&amp;mdash;both digital and analog, in film, production, literary and visual media&amp;mdash;as well as potential funding partners&amp;mdash;individuals, philanthropic and corporate&amp;mdash;including developing promotional tie-in and event opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Director’s role will also entail coordination of all grant proposals to foundations, governmental organizations and PBS, collaborating closely with WNET Development staff. This individual will manage internal communications between the series and all relevant departments at WNET—the VP Programming, Interactive Engagement, Law, Human Resources, Station Relations, Communications, Program Publicity and especially Development and Major Gifts &amp;ndash;  and will be primarily responsible for working with Communications to coordinate press efforts, press releases and events, including screenings, station outreach events and the TCA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to strengthening the reach of the series through potential digital partnerships, this position will entail continued and expanded work with WNET&amp;rsquo;s in-house on-line and web department to enhance the work currently being done with the series programs, especially in the area of educational materials, DLOs etc. &amp;ndash; including finding the funding to support these expanded efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To qualify, candidates must possess a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Broadcast Communications, Production, or a related field, and at least 10 years experience in senior broadcast/production/arts production or managerial roles with direct supervisory responsibility for staff. Candidates must also have thorough knowledge of budgets and budget management; of rights and clearance issues; excellent oral and written communication skills; strong planning, organizational and relationship-building skills; knowledge of the independent production community; and ideally, some experience in fundraising. Familiarity with digital and online would be very desirable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates with solid experience as executive or senior producer or in a development &amp;amp; planning role, in network, cable or independent production, with a successful history of developing projects, creating alliances, and fundraising – are preferred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is not a position for an active film-maker or would-be producer for American Masters – though film and production experience will be essential.  Rather, this is a critical senior administrative role in planning, strategy, communications and development.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Broadcast Communications, Production, or a related field, and at least 10 years experience in senior broadcast/production/arts production or managerial roles with direct supervisory responsibility for staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thorough knowledge of budgets and budget management; of rights and clearance issues; excellent oral and written communication skills; strong planning, organizational and relationship-building skills; knowledge of the independent production community; and ideally, some experience in fundraising.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-planning-and-strategy-wnet-new-york-public-media-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-planning-and-strategy-wnet-new-york-public-media-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Director at Innovation in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;360i (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.360i.com&quot;&gt;http://www.360i.com&lt;/a&gt;) is looking for a Technical Director to help build our growing technology team in New York, NY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This person will work closely with our VP, Technology and the rest of the Technology group to scope, plan, and lead the development of digital marketing project that include web sites, social apps, and mobile apps. Additionally, this person will participate in the ideation process along with creative and strategy team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate must be hands-on, a superb communicator, and have experience working in a fast-paced and collaborative environment. A passion for quality, an eye for detail, and the hunger to bring great ideas to life is also required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About 360i &amp;ndash; Over a Decade of Digital Innovation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a next generation digital agency rooted in innovation and drive. We develop everything from enterprise-level websites to highly complex social apps to innovative rich media campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes us different is our highly experienced technical and design teams and our passionate and collaborative culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re sharp, creative, and forward-thinking &amp;ndash; and if complacency isn&amp;rsquo;t in your vocabulary &amp;ndash; drop us a line. It takes a special kind of person to work here, and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience in technical project management, including scoping and cost and timeline estimation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with social media platforms and APIs (such as Facebook, Twitter, and YouTube)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of the development lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough front-end and back-end development skills (we are not looking for a coder, but rather someone who can read and understand code, conduct code reviews, and drive and enforce coding conventions)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with database design, including basic understanding of SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to architect a complete technical solution given a set of business or creative requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform quality assurance tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest and ability to participate in creative ideation and strategy sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-director-innovation-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-director-innovation-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director of Analytics and Insight at Integrated Media Solutions in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At IMS, data driven advertising strategy is paramount to our clients’ success. From understanding market conditions and consumer behaviors, to evaluating
conversion efficiency across digital and offline media channels, The Senior Data Strategist will be responsible for finding the insights that matter most. In
addition to inspirational analytics that shape media and creative direction, you will be responsible for enabling our clients with clear, highly visual, eagerly
anticipated scorecards and optimization reports. This position will require a continuous, big picture understanding of “how we’re doing” along with a
specialized expertise in digital analytics. The SDDS will work closely with SEM, SEO, and emerging media experts in our Digital group to develop our digital
reporting and measurement offering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Summary of Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Optimization and Reporting: Development of a suite of offerings (products and processes) that optimize our digital efforts and provide performance visibility to our clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage the Marin platform to customize and automate the optimization and testing cycle as well as client and internal reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Analytics: From identifying the right questions to presenting the insights that impact the bottom line and all steps in-between (data
identification and gathering, coordinating with internal and client teams, broad analysis, summarized analysis)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Visualization and Advanced Reporting: Assist with moving away from Excel centric reporting by creating interactive, web-based reporting built with best-in-class data visualization software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 &amp;ndash; 10 years experience in marketing analytics and / or research including&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in a digital marketing role (search, display, mobile), experience with Marin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable strategic thinking and analysis skills, as well as the ability and confidence to make conclusions and recommendations from a business perspective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and client relationship skills with a proven history of building and maintaining relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to translate results into clear, concise presentations, written reports, and data visualizations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resourceful and creative — must bring fresh insights and not be stymied when all the data is not readily available&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Technical Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Excel skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SEM tracking platforms, Marin is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relational databases (SQL, Access)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Direct Marketing media warehouse platforms is a plus (Mediabank)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visualization software (Tableau, Domo, Qlikview, Spotfire, Roambi, Microstrategy, Crystal Reports)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-analytics-and-insight-integrated-media-solutions-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-analytics-and-insight-integrated-media-solutions-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Art Director at Rosetta in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Associate Project Manager&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is looking for an Associate Project Manager to drive cross-functional project teams, project budgets and project schedules. Individuals in this role have considerable client exposure and must demonstrate the ability to work on both business and technology projects with companies across a broad range of industries. The Associate Project Manager must have considerable experience in a fast-paced, dynamic environment and demonstrate a degree of project ownership and accountability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who We Are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is a consulting-centered interactive agency engineered to transform marketing for the connected world. We are focused on helping progressive marketers drive material business impact by translating deep consumer insights into personally relevant brand experiences across touch points and over time. Our differentiated capabilities and structure have enabled us to become a market leader, operating as an independent brand in the Publicis Groupe of global agencies. Rosetta is ranked by Ad Age among the top U.S. digital agencies and was recently named the #1 Agency to Watch in Ad Ageâ€™s Agency A- List.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role will be responsible for leading and designing projects, communicating with clients/internal teams, directing creative brainstorming sessions and, most importantly, promoting a culture of fun and excellence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and management of project timelines and project plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assurance that projects achieve desired business and technical objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of internal project team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identification and mitigation of project risks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validation and presentation of project deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of project financials, with a focus on optimizing efficiency and project margin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishment of close working relationships with client project team and internal development managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2-3 years of project management experience in a technology organization or professional services company working on mid-sized projects with 5+ team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, organization, interpersonal and writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to multi-task and interact with a large number of customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business process planning and implementation planning experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS in communications, business or technology-related field (or commensurate experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience with the MS Office suite, including MS Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in web design and interactive technology preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rosetta is an equal opportunity employer M/F/V/D&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-rosetta-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-art-director-rosetta-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>