<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Project Manager at Havas Worldwide New York in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The role is a combination of traditional project management and modern digital product design. Working on digital projects requires the ability manage projects that develop applications and digital experiences for the most savvy customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The environment is very collaborative, sometimes agile/scrum, and you should have the ability to work well in a mix of designers, UX, developers, strategists, writers and others. Experience or familiarity with agile is a plus but not a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role is also very hands-on, so you will need to be able to direct others and produce work yourself. Ultimately, you should have a passion for creating work that redefines the modern expression of a timeless brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively manage projects from planning and estimating to post-project review, working with the client, creative, strategy and account management to drive project design and execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with account, creative, strategy and technical teams to deliver projects on time and within budget with an eye toward exceeding client expectations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage third-party vendors and partners (i.e. social channel development teams)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with and manage execution of work with client selected partner agencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage web site development, mobile and tablet applications, social channel applications, strategy assignments (and a small amount of banner campaigns).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the legal review processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor project status, reporting in to team all accomplishments, issues and risks for appropriate client communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-facing communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage resources, planning, project work, communicating tasks required. Manage budgets including ability to develop estimates for projects, monitor project “burn” and produce “actuals” upon project completion. Work with other project managers to minimize resource conflicts across many client teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years of digital project management experience with the ability to manage digital projects in an autonomous manner from initiation through to completion in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of creative development and digital technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of technology platforms. (You will not be the technical lead, but you will need to be able to liaise with technology lead with client-selected technology partner.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of financial management and budget process &amp;amp; tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of trends in the interactive industry, e.g. loyalty programs, multimedia, new channel platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid PC skills and proficiency in Microsoft software (Project, Word, Excel, PowerPoint)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience managing timelines and resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be responsible, dedicated, positive, reliable, dynamic, and enthusiastic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong writing, communication and organizational skills, be self-motivated with the ability to work independently and as a team-player, and accept creative suggestions openly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must work well under pressure, able to manage multiple projects and prioritize projects according to changing deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be solutions and results-oriented, a fast learner and accepting of change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Common sense approach is absolutely necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-havas-worldwide-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-havas-worldwide-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at RAPP in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Directors of the client projects – the people who know how to make things happen. They are the masters of the execution and process from project initiation to delivery. They are also passionate about the space from print, to web to gaming to mobile and broadcast. This person must also be creative, solutions-driven, organized, and have exceptional people skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Principal Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages account-related meetings including weekly producer/account status meetings, internal reviews, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scope Management &amp;ndash; Authors all and reviews project SOW’s and estimate documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages multiple producers and simultaneous projects assigned to a particular account(s) within budgetary and schedule constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is a champion of the agency process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps projects moving smoothly, under budget and on schedule, while maintaining the required level of quality through every step of the delivery process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with disciplines across the agency to deliver world-class work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All levels should expect to juggle multiple projects and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All levels should have a desire to create the best customer experiences in the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project plans (goals, budget, schedule, and scope), oversight of project development, and participation in strategic development of brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of live action shoots, talent issues and licensing technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Needs to be capable of respectful, strong working relationships with internal team(s) from Client Service to developers to the Creative on a project as well as external partners and vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient with programs such as Visio, Excel, and MS Project, and have strong written and oral skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AtTask a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acts as the liaison and coordinator with internal team and management in other departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project documentation samples are required (SOW and Project Plan)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-6+ years experience in online producing and project management experience at media, entertainment or creative brand interactive advertising agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in multiplatform content extensions and original content production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge and understanding of web technologies, including HTML, DHTML, Flash, XML, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess an established track record of successful accomplishment with clients / teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;WE ARE an Equal Opportunity Employer Statement
* RAPP is an equal opportunity employer and all employment decisions are made on the basis of valid job qualifications regardless of race, color, creed, sex, age, national origin, ancestry, religion, medical condition, sexual orientation, marital status, physical handicap or veteran status&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-rapp-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-rapp-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Innovation in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Equal parts strategist, creative maverick, and business mind. If that&amp;rsquo;s you, this is the perfect spot. We want to win awards (who doesn&amp;rsquo;t) but we&amp;rsquo;re also focused on finding better ways to build connections (between brands and consumers) and do things differently. We&amp;rsquo;re not mired by politics or egos, just driven by the idea that we can redefine the marketing landscape for some of the biggest global brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 360i &amp;ndash; Over a Decade of Digital Innovation We&amp;rsquo;re a next generation digital agency rooted in innovating at the forefront of a redefined marketing landscape. We don&amp;rsquo;t walk; we run. We don&amp;rsquo;t follow; we lead. We dream, and then we do. Our ideas are big, but our results are bigger. Bigger still is our collective pursuit of positive change &amp;ndash; the innovations that will move our industry forward in new and exciting directions. The digital world changes fast &amp;mdash; and our employees are just as dynamic. Our backgrounds and strengths are diverse, yet we&amp;rsquo;re all fueled by an innate curiosity that inspires us to blaze new trails and a shared belief in the power of the web to forge deeper relationships between brands and consumers. If you&amp;rsquo;re sharp, creative and forward-thinking &amp;ndash; and if complacency isn&amp;rsquo;t in your vocabulary &amp;ndash; drop us a line. It takes a special kind of person to work here, and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years experience Art Directing in the digital marketing space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to concept ideas that will move the needle for our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong presentation skills: the ability to articulate, present, and sell ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with and/or passion for social/emerging media and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven innovation, creativity, &amp;ldquo;big idea&amp;rdquo; conceptual ability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong, stimulating design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio that demonstrates the above skill set&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player &amp;ndash; high energy level, and willingness to do &amp;ldquo;whatever it takes&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you have an entrepreneurial spirit, get excited about finding smarter ways to do things, and have a burning desire to be part of a winning team where you can truly make a difference, we want to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-innovation-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-innovation-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. Director Of Product at MTV in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Music Group Digital, a division of Viacom Media Networks, aims to create innovative digital products for today&amp;rsquo;s tech savvy generation.  Currently, we are seeking experienced product developers with an execution mindset to take on some of our ambitious initiatives in the TV shows, music, movie, news, and events domains.  If you have an outstanding track record of designing and delivering successful digital consumer products and are excited about the future of media experience for the web, mobile, and emerging platforms such as social and interactive TV, we want to talk to you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The right candidates will join a team of seasoned product developers that have developed and managed products for startups, media companies, and interactive agencies.  This hands-on role blends business, technology, design, and production.  In an average day you might be immersed in UI designs, testing new features, analyzing usage data, specing out technical requirements, or evaluating a startup&amp;rsquo;s technology.
Our top areas of focus are news and blogs.  We operate dozens of blog properties and MTV News that are some of the top destinations for celebrity and entertainment news.  If you work in top notch news and blogs outlets where you work with various editors and writers and create tools and processes to support an efficient network of content producing entities, we would love to hear from you.  From a tech standpoint, expertise in the latest and biggest including Wordpress, Chartbeat, text analytics and natural language processing, social, recommendation systems, and search are necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The successful candidate will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate user needs and business objectives into intuitive and compelling consumer products used by millions of users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct and influence an interdisciplinary team of design, engineering, business, marketing, ads, and research to hone and iterate on your ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create product roadmaps and identify, analyze and prioritize new features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strive for agility, but build with practicality, reusability, and scalability in mind.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain awareness of trends and advancements in the digital consumer space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-8+ years of product experience.  Preferably for a media company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS required. Computer science/engineering majors ideal (MS/MBA/PhD a plus).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on and detailed oriented approach.  You can lead teams and show clear paths and goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results:  You have a successful record of defining and launching digital consumer products.  Even better, they resulted in cost savings, new revenue, or new market positioning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Techie Cred:  You are highly technical and have worked with designers/tech significantly.  You prototype with / understand the latest tools including JavaScript, HTML5/CSS, NoSQL, AWS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User-driven.  You test with users before building heavily.  You care about design details including UX, layout, typography.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interdisciplinary.  You work with design, engineering, business, marketing, ads, and research.  You can navigate large company with ease.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process Minded.  You have a strong sense of best practices for product management.  You are comfortable with both traditional development methodologies and agile development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative and Innovative.  Dreaming up and studying new products are your hobbies.  You always know how to make your products better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep.  You are an expert in one / more of these spaces: multi-platform (web/mobile/etc.), video/ad products, analytics, API, AI/personalization, SEO and social.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-director-of-product-mtv-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-director-of-product-mtv-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Blackstone in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager leads interactive marketing and Web development projects, oversees creative and technical project teams, interacts with business managers and is responsible for producing projects on time and on budget. The PM also contributes strategic and operational insight on client accounts to promote project efficiency and success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the creation, maintenance and delivery of detailed project plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies and scopes client requirements and deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create goals and milestones that correlate to billable events within a project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies, documents, and manages scope or deliverable change requests required whether initiated internally or by the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and maintains activity and progress reports for internal and external customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates daily tasks and assigns project resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracks all budget-related information, including billable hours and project expenses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the success of the project while remaining within the scoped time and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages and helps ensure client satisfaction in partnership with the internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Properly notifies the internal team of any risks, weaknesses or opportunities that could impact the success of the project, escalating to upper management as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plans for and controls quality by reviewing items before delivery to client; monitoring and enhancing internal and external deliverables/documents; working with internal teams on needed revisions/enhancements, and involving the Quality Assurance team at key project junctures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates and participates in periodic project and program reviews and strategy meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in and completes training and professional development as detailed within department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an understanding of the client’s operating environment and internal processes and procedures that may affect the project’s success; serves as point of contact for clients as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the use of best practices and apply lessons learned from previous projects; share lessons learned with other project management team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of relevant experience managing projects (preferably 2-4 years within an interactive, advertising or marketing agency environment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management principles, methods and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of financial concepts and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to demonstrate experience with professional services processes and tools including workflow development and management, milestone management and quality assurance practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of technical and creative design and development principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing resources, budgets and project timing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience analyzing complex data reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in MS Project, and the entire MS Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business analysis and requirements gathering skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-blackstone-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-blackstone-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Design Director at Bloomberg in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Role:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Internal Agency operates as a Marketing and Advertising Agency within Bloomberg, responsible for creating communication strategies and design solutions that solve business problems. It reports to the head of Global Brand Management. It is a diverse group of art-directors and specialist designers, collaboratively working on assignments for print, environmental, interactive and broadcast projects. The Internal Agency has both design and production capabilities. The design function has a strong hands-on approach to design, carrying out initial concept development and using external talent as well as internal support to achieve the best end results. The production function ensures concepts are carried through to execution, working with both our internal resources as well as external vendors to produce materials. The Internal Agency handles projects for the Central &amp;amp; Business Unit Marketing teams as well as other departments, e.g. Philanthropy, Internal Communications and Bloomberg Space. All departments may also use external design and brand consultancies and agencies to implement projects effectively. The Internal Agency will be measured on results from the campaigns they produce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a self-starting conceptual art director and designer to lead a small team of designers and bring original ideas and fresh, stylish approaches to each project. The candidate should be a 360 degree integrated thinker who is able to create and roll-out multi channel campaigns both internally and externally campaigns in partnership with copywriting resources. Candidate should show experience with art direction, large-scale branding efforts and cohesive campaigns, be familiar with working within and developing defined visual/brand systems as well as comfort in working closely with printers and seeing complicated jobs through production. The candidate should have a strong sense of style, excellent typographic skills, and a flair in working with photography. Finally have experience in working collaboratively with copywriters and art directors. The person should have managerial and/or leadership role experience with the ability to provide design/approval guidance and direction to others, have high level communication skills with the ability to handle strategic and marketing conversations and have experience in a global organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Specific&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong operating knowledge of Photoshop, Illustrator, In-Design, and Acrobat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A flair for delivering visual concepts in the context of defined strategies and copy approaches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of type, photography, and color management, evident in portfolio examples.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Industrial and environmental design experience, knowledge of motion graphics and web design, skills in art direction and team leadership, experience directing shoots, are all a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Education/Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10+ years experience in a similar role within a company or agency. NOTE Exception could be made on amount (number of years) of experience &amp;ndash; based on quality of candidate&amp;rsquo;s creative examples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree required. Candidates with a degree in Marketing, Graphic Design, Digital Media Design, Visual, Fine or Commercial Arts, Art Design or related field preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of print and collateral design and production processes and interactive communications and delivery systems as well as industry best practices required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of client communication and management preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg, the global business and financial information and news leader, gives influential decision makers a critical edge by connecting them to a dynamic network of information, people and ideas. The company?s strength delivering data, news and analytics through innovative technology, quickly and accurately is at the core of the Bloomberg Professional service, which provides real time financial information to more than 300,000 subscribers globally. Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s enterprise solutions build on the company?s core strength, leveraging technology to allow customers to access, integrate, distribute and manage data and information across organizations more efficiently and effectively. Through Bloomberg Law, Bloomberg Government and Bloomberg New Energy Finance, the company provides data, news and analytics to decision makers in industries beyond finance. And Bloomberg News, delivered through television, radio, mobile, the Internet and two magazines, Bloomberg Businessweek and Bloomberg Markets, covers the world with more than 2,300 news and multimedia professionals at 146 bureaus in 72 countries. Headquartered in New York, Bloomberg employs more than 13,000 people in 185 locations around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/design-director-bloomberg-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/design-director-bloomberg-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Project Managers at RAPP in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Principal Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages account-related meetings including weekly producer/account status meetings, internal reviews, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scope Management &amp;ndash; Authors all and reviews project SOW’s and estimate documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages multiple producers and simultaneous projects assigned to a particular account(s) within budgetary and schedule constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is a champion of the agency process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps projects moving smoothly, under budget and on schedule, while maintaining the required level of quality through every step of the delivery process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with disciplines across the agency to deliver world-class work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All levels should expect to juggle multiple projects and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All levels should have a desire to create the best customer experiences in the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project plans (goals, budget, schedule, and scope), oversight of project development, and participation in strategic development of brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of live action shoots, talent issues and licensing technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Needs to be capable of respectful, strong working relationships with internal team(s) from Client Service to developers to the Creative on a project as well as external partners and vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient with programs such as Visio, Excel, and MS Project, and have strong written and oral skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AtTask a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acts as the liaison and coordinator with internal team and management in other departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project documentation samples are required (SOW and Project Plan)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-6+ years experience in online producing and project management experience at media, entertainment or creative brand interactive advertising agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in multiplatform content extensions and original content production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge and understanding of web technologies, including HTML, DHTML, Flash, XML, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess an established track record of successful accomplishment with clients / teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WE ARE an Equal Opportunity Employer Statement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RAPP is an equal opportunity employer and all employment decisions are made on the basis of valid job qualifications regardless of race, color, creed, sex, age, national origin, ancestry, religion, medical condition, sexual orientation, marital status, physical handicap or veteran status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-project-managers-rapp-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-project-managers-rapp-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director of Product Management / Senior Product Manager at StyledOn in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;StyledOn.com is a VC-backed startup based in NY and LA focused on creating the largest style centric social network — we are well on our way, but we need help!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a marriage of fashion and technology. If this sounds appealing to you, check our current openings and see if your skill set matches. However, if you don’t see something that matches your skills or tickles your fancy, and you think you are good enough for us to create a job for you, we invite you to send us your resume with an email on why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are all busy here at StyledOn, so don’t send us fluff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The more creative, the more thoughtful, the better your chances! Email positions@styledon.com with your proposed title in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How we define Product Management:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product Management brings our ideas to fruition. This takes a supernatural ability to be both technical and creative, and, most importantly, to project manage to successful launch. StyledOn is creating a social network that is laser focused on “style”, and we are looking for individuals who are masters at creating, managing, and nurturing both online social mediums and mobile products. Product management is our guiding light as to what our market wants/craves/needs and helps our marketing department in positioning, packaging, and promoting the products that are created—after all, no one is more passionate than the creator!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The role: Director of Product Management / Senior Product Manager&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;StyledOn is looking for a Product Jedi Master. We are in the troughs of re-launching our online properties and creating our mobile applications and we need a hard-nosed, battle-tested technologist who knows how to bring to market a hatched idea. He/she needs to be ambitious and self-managed with a proven track record of defining, creating and managing market leading interactive products in a consumer-facing environment. We employ both internal shared resources and outsourced development houses to accomplish our product goals, so we are looking for someone who also has experience managing a diverse development environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities boiled down:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a deep understanding of the competitive landscape in our vertical through analysis, user research and site testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead usability tests, feasibility studies, review web analytics and conduct user research to deliver high-quality products that meet user needs, or, better yet, create new user “needs”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own and manage every aspect of the product lifecycle and user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clearly define requirements at a functional and technical level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scope project strategies, initiatives, budgets and resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop project plan and resource allocation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain overall product and feature roadmap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze and present hard data and metrics to back up assumptions and feature concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define, monitor and report progress against key success metrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate product strategies and objectives into specific tactical plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And, most importantly, EXECUTE on plan and hit timelines and targets!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS in Computer Science or a related technical field preferred (MS or Ph.D is a plus).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5-8 years of product design and management experience in web-based businesses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working on online content businesses, and in particular, experience in building online communities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in product design and management of mobile products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product management record (e.g. writing MRDs and PRDs, performing competitive analysis, creating product roadmaps, creating presentations that communicate product features &amp;amp; benefits, defining user interfaces, creating wireframes).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical thinker with exceptional verbal and written skills; this individual is the communication hub of product-related matters and must be able to communicate effectively with different roles in the company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong business acumen and grasp of business fundamentals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical, organizational, and problem solving skills with ability to interpret data into key learnings and product strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter and team player.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of comfort with working closely with developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High integrity and a record of excellence in your work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A true passion for product design and user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of the “social sphere” space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational and analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong technical abilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project managing outsourced development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;How to apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We receive hundreds of resumes and we can’t read them all. If you are interested in this position, and consider your skill set a good fit, do more than just send us your resume. If you are serious about being considered and want us to spend our time in reviewing your qualifications, then you should spend your time in presenting to us why you are a good fit. Include in your email something, anything that separates you from the crowd. Get creative! Get inventive! Give us your ideas of a product roadmap. Tell us where we are falling short. Give us your idea on a mobile app. We dare you to come up with something that makes us salivate so we can’t wait to hire you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email positions@styledon.com with “Director of Product Management / Senior Product Manager” in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing your idea(s)!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-product-management-senior-product-manager-styledon-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-product-management-senior-product-manager-styledon-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Project Manager - Digital Projects at Project One in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our Broadcast/ Digital Media client, who own and operate some of the top TV Stations and digital experiences in the world, is seeking a Technical Project Manager to join their Entertainment Group and lead multiple projects across this interactive department.  These projects will cover everything Digital, from website &amp;amp; mobile redesign to new development efforts (both web and mobile).  There will also be interaction with the product side of new Television shows and initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage concurrent technical projects, in an Agile environment, dealing extensively with interactive &amp;amp; digital initiatives (web redesign, mobile development, streaming video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, track, and remove impediments to project success&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review project requests and participate in the green-light process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitate the creation of a well-defined Project Backlog or Project Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage Sprint and Release planning or development cycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with offshore development teams to tightly integrate them into their project work streams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze risk and mitigation accordingly, including establishing contingency plans and initiating corrective action&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track and report key project metrics and capital budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate participation of different tech and business groups in requirements gathering, specifications, design, development and implementation of key projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn, understand, and actively use project management software to effectively manage project deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 + years experience managing technical projects, specifically dealing with digital and web-based initiatives in the Media or Interactive Industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a Project Manager in an Agile environment, with an excellent understanding of sprints and running Scrum meetings; Understanding of more traditional PM Methodologies would be extremely helpful as well&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading projects involving website or mobile redesigns, streaming video or mobile initiatives, mobile applications, or in-depth product-centric initiatives (building a full web/mobile campaign around a TV show)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand technologies applicable to a chosen project and facilitate resolution of technical issues as they arise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable superb written and verbal communications and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A willing team member who enjoys working collaboratively across all business units&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Alison Landau
Direct: (212) 792-6368&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Northeast (NY): (212) 268-5800
Nationwide: (877) 677-6566&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-project-manager-digital-projects-project-one-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-project-manager-digital-projects-project-one-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Strategy Director at Razorfish Healthware in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Razorfish Healthware is a key partner for health and wellness companies who want to grow their business by engaging with and improving the lives of their customers.  With a focus on creating brand experiences that build our clients’ business, we leverage our unique mix of insight, technology, creativity, and industry savvy to transform the health and wellness community so that our clients can build healthy relationships that last. Headquartered in Philadelphia, Razorfish Healthware is a brand of Razorfish, and a member of the Paris-based Publicis Groupe S.A. the world’s third largest communications group, second largest media counsel and buying group, and a global leader in digital and healthcare communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re the Strategy department of Razorfish Healthware, part of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest interactive agency. Within the Strategy department, Digital Strategists are responsible for the successful planning and implementation of digital solutions for our clients. They help to create overall advertising and marketing tactics that bridge web, mobile, email, and other digital media. They direct how brands are expressed through digital interactions and how those interactions fit into broader consumer and health care provider experiences. Our strategists play a lead role in developing digital strategies for a number of our agency’s top clients, and partner closely with the agency’s account service teams and discipline leads in media, creative, UX and Technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Strategy Director’s primary responsibility is to help our cross-functional teams develop and evolve digital solutions in the healthcare space driven to address unmet needs of consumers and/or health care Providers and drive a brand’s business forward. This requires evaluating consumer and industry research, brand information, digital trends and relevant technical and user requirements in order to recommend digital solutions. Their thought leadership and strategy will guide digital implementation executed by multi-disciplinary teams throughout the life of a project.
Specific Responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the account services, media and creative disciplines in developing and presenting overall analyses of client needs and digital marketing solutions to meet existing and new business client’s needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in and/or drives the design and development of online measurement solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides insights and develops recommendations based on measurement reporting and analysis and where appropriate to improve business, website and/or marketing program performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with the analytics team to design research plans and manage execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze and interpret information from multiple data sources as needed (database, primary research and syndicated) through knowledge and application of various qualitative and quantitative methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains functional expertise in digital marketing, integrated channel marketing (including online based channels such as websites, banners, email and search), analytics tools and, techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and facilitation of client workshops that make use of brainstorming and prioritization sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of social media strategies and oversight of social media monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writes POVs and authors white papers on various topics related to Digital Strategy and how the channel impacts business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interface and work in conjunction with a wide range of team members across various disciplines and departments is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of online (web) metrics, hands-on experience with tools of trade, and knowledge of relevant web measurement technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A command of digital marketing best practices, with an ability to incorporate them into implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in client-facing roles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexibility to travel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of integrated marketing and customer relationship management disciplines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possession of excellent written, oral communication, project management and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience working on strategies targeted to health care providers is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience with offline channels is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10+ years experience in digital communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience in a digital strategist or equivalent role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years in marketing or advertising.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/strategy-director-razorfish-healthware-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/strategy-director-razorfish-healthware-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>