<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Group Project Director at MRY in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a brilliant/dynamic Group Project Director New York office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put all the pieces in place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of different places, actually. Creatives here. Clients there. Ideas and budgets and deadlines everywhere. But that’s a good thing, because a sharp tack like you is coordinating the action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep projects moving every step of the way, from strategy to implementation to end-of-project learnings—and do it all on time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring together a team of IAs, designers, copywriters, developers and technical leads—and make it look easy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage project scope, schedules, meetings, milestones, budgets and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empathize. Build relationships. Relationships are everything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be proactive. Be accountable. Be flexible. Collaborate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn. Fail. Learn. Succeed. Repeat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee and manage project scopes, deliverables, schedules and resource needs on large engagements across multiple brands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successfully partnering with Client Services to ensure proactive client communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balance the needs of the client with team, resource and schedule needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Involve team at the optimal levels for project success and overall account utilization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead efficient meetings and conference calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clearly communicate and mitigate project issues and solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be passionate about client success and delivering quality work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years project management experience in a digital client service environment, simultaneously managing multiple large-scale web/interactive projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a multidisciplinary environment and the ability to directly manage and mentor a team of Project Managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to partner with client services, strategy, creative and technology disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with C-level executives at the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to accurately track and communicate project status to client and internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and proficiency in structuring and executing large-scale (over $4 million) projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to accurately forecast timing and associated costs across a range of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A comprehensive understanding of the lifecycle of web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to identify and manage project risks and solid change control experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management principles, processes and software, including Microsoft Project, PowerPoint and Excel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent, clear written and oral communication skills; solutions-oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/group-project-director-mry-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/group-project-director-mry-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Project Manager- Interactive/Web Dev at TMP in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a great time to join TMP – we’re seeking a Digital Project Manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Digital Project Manager, you will manage the entire project lifecycle to deliver comprehensive digital solutions to our client base.  In addition to excelling in scope, time and budget management, Project Managers also must possess a thorough understanding of digital development in all its forms (design, IXD, content, UI development,engineering and quality assurance) and the ability to facilitate dialog that represents our company’s development efforts and methodologies to clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run point on several projects at once, managing all communications, scope, timeline and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and communicate project performance throughout development to all stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and update all project plan documentation from initiation to execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading cross-functional teams to deliver high quality deliverables on time and on budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working as a member of an interactive development team researching and executing emerging solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing detailed project plans and collecting client information for development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;accurately identify and mitigate project risk, forecast development timelines and budget accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitating communication among team members – internally and with the client – via regular team meetings and the project website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project Management certification and/or  3-5 years experience with formal project management methodologies, including various forms of project documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience managing projects involving website development, video, mobile sites, apps,  social media and etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills and ability to produce enough project documentation, business requirements documentation and functional specifications to drive successful development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must possess an understanding of basic site usability and architecture principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some previous experience withfacilitating projects involving content management systems, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Flash and otherweb technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a digital agency a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have experience in a range of client management situations (i.e. multiple industries and corporate structures, projects of varying duration and complexity).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent negotiation and interpersonal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong knowledge of MS Office including Microsoft Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About TMP Worldwide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMP Worldwide Advertising &amp;amp; Communications, LLC &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tmp.com&quot;&gt;http://www.tmp.com&lt;/a&gt; is a global, tech-enabled talent acquisition company that leverages software, advertising and creativity to develop and deploy our clients' employer brands across digital, social and mobile outlets. Our client base of over 1,200 companies spans every sector in business and government. Headquartered in New York City, with offices throughout North America, Europe and Asia with affiliates around the globe, TMP continues to set the standard for measurable and cost-effective HR communications. We are also honored to be recognized, once again, among AdAge&amp;rsquo;s Top US Digital Agencies, ranking #33 for 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMP Worldwide is committed to providing a safe workplace for all employees. It is the policy of TMP Worldwide to conduct a background check for all candidates who accept an offer of employment with us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-project-manager-interactive-web-dev-tmp-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-project-manager-interactive-web-dev-tmp-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Creative Director at Edelman in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Associate Creative Director needed for Edelman Digital. This is an amazing opportunity to work on national brands in a close-knit, empowering environment. Best of all, it’s a great place to grow your talent: You&amp;rsquo;ll be challenged to find the innovative solutions we need to create the next generation of relevant, motivating consumer engagements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edelman Digital is the world’s first and largest global social agency. We leverage the industry’s best talent, combining insight driven business strategy, creative problem solving and flawless execution. This leads to measurable results for our clients and tangible value for their stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We focus on the intersection of culture, commerce and media, assisting brands in leveraging digital and social tools to further engage their markets in ways that lead to improved relevance, affinity and preference….and ultimately, revenue. We combine deep digital expertise with Edelman’s incredible communication credentials to create integrated and effective communications and experiences for our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are at a critical juncture in communications where the online market conversation has never been louder, further reaching, nor more active.  Social media and digital marketing are now not “nice to haves” in the communications mix, they are essential to a brand’s overall image and success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting direction and lead ideation of on-brand, forward-thinking creative solutions across all digital media (online, mobile, social) to meet business objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating and concepting campaign strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recognizing great ideas and pushing them forward&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentoring teams and direct reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributing to the new business development process – from ideation to pitch presentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The associate Creative Director must have at least eight years of relevant experience in public relations and/or related fields including research, advertising, management consulting, media and publishing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of creative experience, working on interactive projects such as web sites, online advertising, social media, mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong copy background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to inspire and motivate co-workers, colleagues and others, to be a team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the creative team, you’ll work in a highly collaborative environment with respected colleagues in Art/Design, Account Management, Strategy and Project Management. Your natural desire to take ownership of each assignment will need to be balanced by the patience and creative flexibility to revise your work as directed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our company is growing and looking for talented creatives with an innovative turn of mind. Sound like anybody you know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Edelman&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edelman is the world’s largest public relations firm, with 66 offices and more than 4,500 employees worldwide, as well as affiliates in more than 30 cities. Edelman was named Advertising Age’s top-ranked PR firm of the decade in 2009 and one of its “A-List Agencies” in both 2010 and 2011; Adweek’s “2011 PR Agency of the Year;” PRWeek’s “2011 Large PR Agency of the Year;” and The Holmes Report’s “2011 Global Agency of the Year” and its 2011 “North American Large Agency of the Year.” Edelman was named one of the “Best Places to Work” by Advertising Age in 2010 and 2012 and among Glassdoor’s top five “2011 Best Places to Work.” Edelman owns specialty firms Edelman Berland (research), Blue (advertising), A&amp;amp;R Edelman (technology), and agencies Edelman Significa (Brazil), and Pegasus (China). Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.edelman.com&quot;&gt;http://www.edelman.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information.  Edelman is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-creative-director-edelman-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-creative-director-edelman-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Project Manager at Havas Worldwide New York in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The role is a combination of traditional project management and modern digital product design. Working on digital projects requires the ability manage projects that develop applications and digital experiences for the most savvy customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The environment is very collaborative, sometimes agile/scrum, and you should have the ability to work well in a mix of designers, UX, developers, strategists, writers and others. Experience or familiarity with agile is a plus but not a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role is also very hands-on, so you will need to be able to direct others and produce work yourself. Ultimately, you should have a passion for creating work that redefines the modern expression of a timeless brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively manage projects from planning and estimating to post-project review, working with the client, creative, strategy and account management to drive project design and execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with account, creative, strategy and technical teams to deliver projects on time and within budget with an eye toward exceeding client expectations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage third-party vendors and partners (i.e. social channel development teams)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with and manage execution of work with client selected partner agencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage web site development, mobile and tablet applications, social channel applications, strategy assignments (and a small amount of banner campaigns).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the legal review processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor project status, reporting in to team all accomplishments, issues and risks for appropriate client communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-facing communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage resources, planning, project work, communicating tasks required. Manage budgets including ability to develop estimates for projects, monitor project “burn” and produce “actuals” upon project completion. Work with other project managers to minimize resource conflicts across many client teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years of digital project management experience with the ability to manage digital projects in an autonomous manner from initiation through to completion in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of creative development and digital technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of technology platforms. (You will not be the technical lead, but you will need to be able to liaise with technology lead with client-selected technology partner.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of financial management and budget process &amp;amp; tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of trends in the interactive industry, e.g. loyalty programs, multimedia, new channel platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid PC skills and proficiency in Microsoft software (Project, Word, Excel, PowerPoint)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience managing timelines and resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be responsible, dedicated, positive, reliable, dynamic, and enthusiastic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong writing, communication and organizational skills, be self-motivated with the ability to work independently and as a team-player, and accept creative suggestions openly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must work well under pressure, able to manage multiple projects and prioritize projects according to changing deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be solutions and results-oriented, a fast learner and accepting of change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Common sense approach is absolutely necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-havas-worldwide-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-havas-worldwide-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at RAPP in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Directors of the client projects – the people who know how to make things happen. They are the masters of the execution and process from project initiation to delivery. They are also passionate about the space from print, to web to gaming to mobile and broadcast. This person must also be creative, solutions-driven, organized, and have exceptional people skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Principal Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages account-related meetings including weekly producer/account status meetings, internal reviews, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scope Management &amp;ndash; Authors all and reviews project SOW’s and estimate documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages multiple producers and simultaneous projects assigned to a particular account(s) within budgetary and schedule constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is a champion of the agency process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps projects moving smoothly, under budget and on schedule, while maintaining the required level of quality through every step of the delivery process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with disciplines across the agency to deliver world-class work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All levels should expect to juggle multiple projects and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All levels should have a desire to create the best customer experiences in the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project plans (goals, budget, schedule, and scope), oversight of project development, and participation in strategic development of brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of live action shoots, talent issues and licensing technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Needs to be capable of respectful, strong working relationships with internal team(s) from Client Service to developers to the Creative on a project as well as external partners and vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient with programs such as Visio, Excel, and MS Project, and have strong written and oral skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AtTask a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acts as the liaison and coordinator with internal team and management in other departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project documentation samples are required (SOW and Project Plan)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-6+ years experience in online producing and project management experience at media, entertainment or creative brand interactive advertising agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in multiplatform content extensions and original content production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge and understanding of web technologies, including HTML, DHTML, Flash, XML, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess an established track record of successful accomplishment with clients / teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;WE ARE an Equal Opportunity Employer Statement
* RAPP is an equal opportunity employer and all employment decisions are made on the basis of valid job qualifications regardless of race, color, creed, sex, age, national origin, ancestry, religion, medical condition, sexual orientation, marital status, physical handicap or veteran status&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-rapp-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-rapp-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Innovation in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Equal parts strategist, creative maverick, and business mind. If that&amp;rsquo;s you, this is the perfect spot. We want to win awards (who doesn&amp;rsquo;t) but we&amp;rsquo;re also focused on finding better ways to build connections (between brands and consumers) and do things differently. We&amp;rsquo;re not mired by politics or egos, just driven by the idea that we can redefine the marketing landscape for some of the biggest global brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 360i &amp;ndash; Over a Decade of Digital Innovation We&amp;rsquo;re a next generation digital agency rooted in innovating at the forefront of a redefined marketing landscape. We don&amp;rsquo;t walk; we run. We don&amp;rsquo;t follow; we lead. We dream, and then we do. Our ideas are big, but our results are bigger. Bigger still is our collective pursuit of positive change &amp;ndash; the innovations that will move our industry forward in new and exciting directions. The digital world changes fast &amp;mdash; and our employees are just as dynamic. Our backgrounds and strengths are diverse, yet we&amp;rsquo;re all fueled by an innate curiosity that inspires us to blaze new trails and a shared belief in the power of the web to forge deeper relationships between brands and consumers. If you&amp;rsquo;re sharp, creative and forward-thinking &amp;ndash; and if complacency isn&amp;rsquo;t in your vocabulary &amp;ndash; drop us a line. It takes a special kind of person to work here, and we hope that&amp;rsquo;s you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years experience Art Directing in the digital marketing space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to concept ideas that will move the needle for our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong presentation skills: the ability to articulate, present, and sell ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with and/or passion for social/emerging media and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven innovation, creativity, &amp;ldquo;big idea&amp;rdquo; conceptual ability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong, stimulating design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A portfolio that demonstrates the above skill set&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player &amp;ndash; high energy level, and willingness to do &amp;ldquo;whatever it takes&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you have an entrepreneurial spirit, get excited about finding smarter ways to do things, and have a burning desire to be part of a winning team where you can truly make a difference, we want to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-innovation-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-innovation-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. Director Of Product at MTV in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Music Group Digital, a division of Viacom Media Networks, aims to create innovative digital products for today&amp;rsquo;s tech savvy generation.  Currently, we are seeking experienced product developers with an execution mindset to take on some of our ambitious initiatives in the TV shows, music, movie, news, and events domains.  If you have an outstanding track record of designing and delivering successful digital consumer products and are excited about the future of media experience for the web, mobile, and emerging platforms such as social and interactive TV, we want to talk to you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The right candidates will join a team of seasoned product developers that have developed and managed products for startups, media companies, and interactive agencies.  This hands-on role blends business, technology, design, and production.  In an average day you might be immersed in UI designs, testing new features, analyzing usage data, specing out technical requirements, or evaluating a startup&amp;rsquo;s technology.
Our top areas of focus are news and blogs.  We operate dozens of blog properties and MTV News that are some of the top destinations for celebrity and entertainment news.  If you work in top notch news and blogs outlets where you work with various editors and writers and create tools and processes to support an efficient network of content producing entities, we would love to hear from you.  From a tech standpoint, expertise in the latest and biggest including Wordpress, Chartbeat, text analytics and natural language processing, social, recommendation systems, and search are necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The successful candidate will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate user needs and business objectives into intuitive and compelling consumer products used by millions of users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct and influence an interdisciplinary team of design, engineering, business, marketing, ads, and research to hone and iterate on your ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create product roadmaps and identify, analyze and prioritize new features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strive for agility, but build with practicality, reusability, and scalability in mind.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain awareness of trends and advancements in the digital consumer space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-8+ years of product experience.  Preferably for a media company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS required. Computer science/engineering majors ideal (MS/MBA/PhD a plus).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on and detailed oriented approach.  You can lead teams and show clear paths and goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results:  You have a successful record of defining and launching digital consumer products.  Even better, they resulted in cost savings, new revenue, or new market positioning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Techie Cred:  You are highly technical and have worked with designers/tech significantly.  You prototype with / understand the latest tools including JavaScript, HTML5/CSS, NoSQL, AWS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User-driven.  You test with users before building heavily.  You care about design details including UX, layout, typography.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interdisciplinary.  You work with design, engineering, business, marketing, ads, and research.  You can navigate large company with ease.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process Minded.  You have a strong sense of best practices for product management.  You are comfortable with both traditional development methodologies and agile development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative and Innovative.  Dreaming up and studying new products are your hobbies.  You always know how to make your products better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep.  You are an expert in one / more of these spaces: multi-platform (web/mobile/etc.), video/ad products, analytics, API, AI/personalization, SEO and social.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-director-of-product-mtv-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-director-of-product-mtv-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Blackstone in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager leads interactive marketing and Web development projects, oversees creative and technical project teams, interacts with business managers and is responsible for producing projects on time and on budget. The PM also contributes strategic and operational insight on client accounts to promote project efficiency and success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the creation, maintenance and delivery of detailed project plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies and scopes client requirements and deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create goals and milestones that correlate to billable events within a project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies, documents, and manages scope or deliverable change requests required whether initiated internally or by the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and maintains activity and progress reports for internal and external customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates daily tasks and assigns project resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracks all budget-related information, including billable hours and project expenses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the success of the project while remaining within the scoped time and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages and helps ensure client satisfaction in partnership with the internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Properly notifies the internal team of any risks, weaknesses or opportunities that could impact the success of the project, escalating to upper management as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plans for and controls quality by reviewing items before delivery to client; monitoring and enhancing internal and external deliverables/documents; working with internal teams on needed revisions/enhancements, and involving the Quality Assurance team at key project junctures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates and participates in periodic project and program reviews and strategy meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in and completes training and professional development as detailed within department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an understanding of the client’s operating environment and internal processes and procedures that may affect the project’s success; serves as point of contact for clients as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the use of best practices and apply lessons learned from previous projects; share lessons learned with other project management team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of relevant experience managing projects (preferably 2-4 years within an interactive, advertising or marketing agency environment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management principles, methods and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of financial concepts and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to demonstrate experience with professional services processes and tools including workflow development and management, milestone management and quality assurance practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of technical and creative design and development principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing resources, budgets and project timing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience analyzing complex data reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in MS Project, and the entire MS Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business analysis and requirements gathering skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-blackstone-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-blackstone-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Design Director at Bloomberg in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Role:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Internal Agency operates as a Marketing and Advertising Agency within Bloomberg, responsible for creating communication strategies and design solutions that solve business problems. It reports to the head of Global Brand Management. It is a diverse group of art-directors and specialist designers, collaboratively working on assignments for print, environmental, interactive and broadcast projects. The Internal Agency has both design and production capabilities. The design function has a strong hands-on approach to design, carrying out initial concept development and using external talent as well as internal support to achieve the best end results. The production function ensures concepts are carried through to execution, working with both our internal resources as well as external vendors to produce materials. The Internal Agency handles projects for the Central &amp;amp; Business Unit Marketing teams as well as other departments, e.g. Philanthropy, Internal Communications and Bloomberg Space. All departments may also use external design and brand consultancies and agencies to implement projects effectively. The Internal Agency will be measured on results from the campaigns they produce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a self-starting conceptual art director and designer to lead a small team of designers and bring original ideas and fresh, stylish approaches to each project. The candidate should be a 360 degree integrated thinker who is able to create and roll-out multi channel campaigns both internally and externally campaigns in partnership with copywriting resources. Candidate should show experience with art direction, large-scale branding efforts and cohesive campaigns, be familiar with working within and developing defined visual/brand systems as well as comfort in working closely with printers and seeing complicated jobs through production. The candidate should have a strong sense of style, excellent typographic skills, and a flair in working with photography. Finally have experience in working collaboratively with copywriters and art directors. The person should have managerial and/or leadership role experience with the ability to provide design/approval guidance and direction to others, have high level communication skills with the ability to handle strategic and marketing conversations and have experience in a global organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Specific&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong operating knowledge of Photoshop, Illustrator, In-Design, and Acrobat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A flair for delivering visual concepts in the context of defined strategies and copy approaches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive understanding of type, photography, and color management, evident in portfolio examples.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Industrial and environmental design experience, knowledge of motion graphics and web design, skills in art direction and team leadership, experience directing shoots, are all a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Education/Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10+ years experience in a similar role within a company or agency. NOTE Exception could be made on amount (number of years) of experience &amp;ndash; based on quality of candidate&amp;rsquo;s creative examples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree required. Candidates with a degree in Marketing, Graphic Design, Digital Media Design, Visual, Fine or Commercial Arts, Art Design or related field preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of print and collateral design and production processes and interactive communications and delivery systems as well as industry best practices required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of client communication and management preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg, the global business and financial information and news leader, gives influential decision makers a critical edge by connecting them to a dynamic network of information, people and ideas. The company?s strength delivering data, news and analytics through innovative technology, quickly and accurately is at the core of the Bloomberg Professional service, which provides real time financial information to more than 300,000 subscribers globally. Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s enterprise solutions build on the company?s core strength, leveraging technology to allow customers to access, integrate, distribute and manage data and information across organizations more efficiently and effectively. Through Bloomberg Law, Bloomberg Government and Bloomberg New Energy Finance, the company provides data, news and analytics to decision makers in industries beyond finance. And Bloomberg News, delivered through television, radio, mobile, the Internet and two magazines, Bloomberg Businessweek and Bloomberg Markets, covers the world with more than 2,300 news and multimedia professionals at 146 bureaus in 72 countries. Headquartered in New York, Bloomberg employs more than 13,000 people in 185 locations around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/design-director-bloomberg-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/design-director-bloomberg-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Project Managers at RAPP in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Principal Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages account-related meetings including weekly producer/account status meetings, internal reviews, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scope Management &amp;ndash; Authors all and reviews project SOW’s and estimate documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages multiple producers and simultaneous projects assigned to a particular account(s) within budgetary and schedule constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is a champion of the agency process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps projects moving smoothly, under budget and on schedule, while maintaining the required level of quality through every step of the delivery process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with disciplines across the agency to deliver world-class work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All levels should expect to juggle multiple projects and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All levels should have a desire to create the best customer experiences in the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project plans (goals, budget, schedule, and scope), oversight of project development, and participation in strategic development of brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of live action shoots, talent issues and licensing technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Needs to be capable of respectful, strong working relationships with internal team(s) from Client Service to developers to the Creative on a project as well as external partners and vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient with programs such as Visio, Excel, and MS Project, and have strong written and oral skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AtTask a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acts as the liaison and coordinator with internal team and management in other departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project documentation samples are required (SOW and Project Plan)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-6+ years experience in online producing and project management experience at media, entertainment or creative brand interactive advertising agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in multiplatform content extensions and original content production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge and understanding of web technologies, including HTML, DHTML, Flash, XML, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess an established track record of successful accomplishment with clients / teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WE ARE an Equal Opportunity Employer Statement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RAPP is an equal opportunity employer and all employment decisions are made on the basis of valid job qualifications regardless of race, color, creed, sex, age, national origin, ancestry, religion, medical condition, sexual orientation, marital status, physical handicap or veteran status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-project-managers-rapp-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-project-managers-rapp-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>