<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director-Digital Media at A&amp;E Television Network in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Creative Art Director will the lead the Lifetime digital design team to strategize, concept and oversee brand management, creative direction and re-designs for all of the Lifetime Digital platforms including mylifetime.com, mobile, tablet, smartphones, social media and emerging platforms. He/she will work collaboratively across design, production, technology and marketing teams to define and synthesize project requirements and assist in product road map and design resource planning. This role will report to the Vice President of Production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with keen multitasking skills, the ideal candidate must maintain a critical eye for design details while managing the project’s overall scope and direction. The position requires keeping up-to-date on emerging platforms and technologies, as well as design and interaction trends and best practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with VP of production to understand and manage project priorities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage all phases of creative work from conceptualization to execution across all Lifetime Digital platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategize for new digital and interactive experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create seamless integration between on-air and digital creative across all platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate overall vision on projects with design, production, and technology teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop creative concepts with brand integration that are sponsorable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage design project schedules and deliverables for the team of digital designers and freelancers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring latest design trends and technical innovations across all digital platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of related experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An exceptional portfolio of work showcasing web, mobile, social, application solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior communication and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent managerial and leadership abilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keen multi-tasking skills and strong attention to design detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in all CS5 applications such as Photoshop and Illustrator, Flash. Proficient in CSS, HTML5 and Wireframe Development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A Interaction Design or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-digital-media-aande-television-network-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-digital-media-aande-television-network-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at LBi Health in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking an experienced Project Manager to join MRY.  Experience with a diverse mix of health care clients ranging from health publishers and hospitals to pharmaceutical and bio-tech firms, is highly desired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our project managers are very much the heart of our projects and the glue that holds our development efforts together.  While a project manager may be adept at scheduling, coordinating project efforts, resourcing and budgeting, our project managers must also possess a visceral understanding of creative development in all its forms.  They must also have the ability to both facilitate creative dialogue and faithfully represent our creative efforts and methodologies to clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in defining  and managing  project scope, deliverables, schedule, resource needs and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Often serve as client interface on projects, clarify strategic requirements, explain complex ideas clearly, and manage expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a dual role of client advocate and internal team advocate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep projects on track through clear task lists, issue tracking, status reports, and meeting notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Involve team at the optimal levels for project success and overall account utilization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead efficient meetings and conference calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clearly communicate project issues and solutions-oriented resolution to the client and internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be passionate about client success and delivering the highest quality work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years project management experience in a client service environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health industry and domain experience, including some experience with a pharmaceutical or bio-tech client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive industry experience a must&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knows project management principles, processes and software, including Microsoft Project, PowerPoint and Excel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a multidisciplinary environment and the ability to direct a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respects and understands the strategic, creative and technology disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and proficiency handling client contact for all project-level communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurately tracks and communicates project status to client and internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurately forecasts timing and associated costs across a range of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a comprehensive understanding of the lifecycle of web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies and manages project risks and solid change control experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-lbi-health-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-lbi-health-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at R/GA in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Direct creative development &amp;amp; implementation of interactive digital marketing campaigns &amp;amp; transactional experiences for Fortune 500 clients. Design &amp;amp; oversee design of digital eco-systems &amp;amp; interfaces, including mobile, website, &amp;amp; tablet experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Translate concepts into effective designs. Incorporate business strategy &amp;amp; customer insights into designs. Direct staff of Experience Designers in designing interfaces &amp;amp; components of a project, such as site maps &amp;amp; wireframes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conduct adaptive &amp;amp; responsive web design, rapid prototyping, &amp;amp; agile product development. Serve as strategic partner to clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Reqs:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master’s degree in Applied Mathematics, Human Computer Interaction, Product Design, Graphic Design, Communication, or closely related field, &amp;amp; 3 yrs of exp in position offered or in an interaction design role at a digital agency, OR Bachelor’s degree in Applied Mathematics, Human Computer Interaction, Product Design, Graphic Design, Communication, or closely related field, &amp;amp; 5 yrs of exp in position offered or in an interaction design role at a digital agency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Req’d exp must have included developing interactive digital marketing campaigns &amp;amp; transactional experiences for Fortune 500 clients, &amp;amp; conducting adaptive &amp;amp; responsive web design, rapid prototyping, &amp;amp; agile product development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact: P. DeSouza, Sr. HR Manager, R/GA Media Group Inc., 350 W. 39th St., NY, NY 10018.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-r-ga-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-r-ga-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Director of Online, Creative Design at Estee Lauder in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The primary focus of this position is to support the Executive Director, Online in the creative development and implementation of all online and new media projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Director, Online is responsible for the look-and-feel of all global M·A·C Cosmetics sites. M-commerce, online retailers, as well as a strong focus on social media channels. They are also responsible for the conceptualization and implantation of exclusive online programs, Pro.com and associated print collateral for stores and events, Globe Comm assets and training material. This person must be highly knowledgeable in understanding online consumer behavior (particularly for luxury brands), the nuances of online functionality, marketing, emerging technology and trends and incorporate into designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain visual and conceptual consistency with offline brand strategy for collections and apply to all interactive mediums.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize and design assets for all M·A·C Cosmetics web sites, mobile sites, partner sites (i.e. online retailers, online advertisers and magazine web sites) and social media sites that adhere to M·A·C’s global branding standard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop collection and marketing concepts for m-commerce globally.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for all Pro and Pro.com material.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate design goals and messages to creative participants, ensuring integration of design requirements into all phases of production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversees production process for all global online assets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop or refine the design process to reflect technical requirements of delivery platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and analyze industry trends and maintain knowledge of emerging technologies and its creative applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA or BFA preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+  Years of direct Design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough working knowledge of Photoshop, Flash, Illustrator, InDesign and experience in motion graphics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full understanding of HTML, CSS and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a very fast paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of current fashion/cultural/technological trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drawing/Illustration/Typography skills are highly desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong brand translation and superior organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EEO&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-online-creative-design-estee-lauder-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-online-creative-design-estee-lauder-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at Konrad Group in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Konrad Group is dedicated to creating an environment filled with innovation. We have an open, collaborative office, and a team of tech enthusiasts who are passionate about making amazing software. What really sets us apart, is how encourage the free exchange of new ideas and reward self-motivation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a Creative Director to lead UI + UX design initiatives for some of the most innovative projects in mobile and across the web.  These are major projects ranging from consumer facing apps to enterprise solutions, and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone with experience working on various large-scale web and mobile projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KG Creative Director will be one of the senior members of our NYC Creative team and be responsible for concepts and will work alongside the Technology and Strategy teams to oversee project design all the way through execution.  He or she is also responsible for presenting work to client stakeholders and representing KG’s Solution Design Process at all stages of an engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of interactive experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience in a leadership  position or higher&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A well-rounded UX professional who connects the dots between business needs and good design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interface with clients and defend the creative vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-konrad-group-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-konrad-group-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Project Manager - Digital Experience at iCrossing in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;iCrossing is looking for an Associate Project Manager for their New York office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Associate Project Manager helps to manage an account and is responsible for helping the team achieve the clients’ objectives. They handle day-to-day client and internal team communications and assists with producing client deliverables.  The Associate Project Manager supports senior Project Management team resources on large projects or manages small-scale projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps manage day-to-day client and internal project team communications; provides a high level of service to clients and internal departments to ensure effective dissemination of information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports members of the Project Management team to develop project plans and timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports Account Director on account deliverables, including account plans, project briefs, proposals and presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps cross-disciplinary internal team track and prioritize client requests; reports status to senior-level team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sets up and coordinate internal and client meetings and conference calls; develops agendas; writes and distributes meeting notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews and reports on hours burned by team members on projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops expertise in online marketing and proprietary technology solutions; helps identify solutions relevant for clients*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of relevant work experience, preferably in an interactive marketing agency environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nice to have but not a requirement, familiarity with SEO and SEM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience supporting web site development process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Microsoft Office suite of programs, including Outlook, Word, Excel and PowerPoint; experience with Microsoft Project is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills, both verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unswerving attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work in a dynamic, fast-paced environment and manage multiple simultaneous tasks and projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-project-manager-digital-experience-icrossing-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-project-manager-digital-experience-icrossing-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Jr Digital Project Manager Interactive Web at TMP Worldwide in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a great time to join TMP – we’re seeking a Digital Project Manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Digital Project Manager, you will manage the entire project lifecycle to deliver comprehensive digital solutions to our client base. In addition to excelling in scope, time and budget management, Project Managers also must possess a thorough understanding of digital development in all its forms (design, IXD, content, UI development,engineering and quality assurance) and the ability to facilitate dialog that represents our company’s development efforts and methodologies to clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run point on several projects at once, managing all communications, scope, timeline and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and communicate project performance throughout development to all stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and update all project plan documentation from initiation to execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading cross-functional teams to deliver high quality deliverables on time and on budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working as a member of an interactive development team researching and executing emerging solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing detailed project plans and collecting client information for development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;accurately identify and mitigate project risk, forecast development timelines and budget accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitating communication among team members – internally and with the client – via regular team meetings and the project website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years experience with project management methodologies, including various forms of project documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience managing projects involving website development, video, mobile sites, apps, social media and etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills and ability to produce enough project documentation, business requirements documentation and functional specifications to drive successful development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must possess an understanding of basic site usability and architecture principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some previous experience withfacilitating projects involving content management systems, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Flash and otherweb technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a digital agency a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have experience in a range of client management situations (i.e. multiple industries and corporate structures, projects of varying duration and complexity).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent negotiation and interpersonal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong knowledge of MS Office including Microsoft Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About TMP Worldwide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMP Worldwide Advertising &amp;amp; Communications, LLC (www.tmp.com) is a global, tech-enabled talent acquisition company that leverages software, advertising and creativity to develop and deploy our clients' employer brands across digital, social and mobile outlets. Our client base of over 1,200 companies spans every sector in business and government. Headquartered in New York City, with offices throughout North America, Europe and Asia with affiliates around the globe, TMP continues to set the standard for measurable and cost-effective HR communications. We are also honored to be recognized, once again, among AdAge&amp;rsquo;s Top US Digital Agencies, ranking #33 for 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMP Worldwide is committed to providing a safe workplace for all employees. It is the policy of TMP Worldwide to conduct a background check for all candidates who accept an offer of employment with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMP Worldwide is an Equal Opportunity and Affirmative Action Employer, M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-digital-project-manager-interactive-web-tmp-worldwide-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-digital-project-manager-interactive-web-tmp-worldwide-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Project Manager at IOMEDIA in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;IOMEDIA is looking for a motivated Digital Project Manager with 3-5 years professional digital advertising or marketing experience, who possesses a strong understanding of the creative development process. You should have experience within a creative environment creating project plans, estimates, timelines, risk plans, etc. You should be a proponent of process, and willing to learn to work within our agency’s specific processes and workflow. Ability to function in a fast paced creative environment is a must. Healthcare Communication/Pharmaceutical Agency experience is a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a tight-knit team at IOMEDIA, and seek individuals who are enthusiastic and strong team players. This is a full-time salaried position (with benefits) for immediate hire into IOMEDIA’s Healthcare team in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;AREAS OF JOB RESPONSIBILITY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain project calendars, kick-off meetings, status reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform day-to-day functions, including creating build matrices and linking matrices, spec documents, necessary documentation for program delivery, med legal submissions, ad trafficking, quality control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for weekly/daily internal communications for assigned projects, including scrums, hot sheets, status reports, and follow up internal meetings with contact reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with department leads to secure and manage workflow through various internal departments and off-site and external development partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage budget against project scope, elevate scope changes and execute change orders as needed, mitigate risk, and elevate conflicts to upper management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to proposal building and track project burn rate with upper management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of professional project management experience in digital creative environment or interactive advertising agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in related marketing field a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be responsible, detail-oriented, organized, dedicated, maintain a positive attitude, reliable, dynamic, enthusiastic, and able to stay calm in high-pressure situations. Must have good communication skills, be self-motivated with the ability to work independently and as a team-player, accept suggestions and critique openly, work well under pressure, be able to manage multiple projects and prioritize projects according to changing deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of proficiency with Microsoft Office [Word, Excel, Power Point, Project]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for new technologies and knowledge of best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of proficiency with Project Management oriented software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of HTML and/or healthcare/pharmaceutical agency experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT IOMEDIA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IOMEDIA is a creative agency focused on the bigger picture―strategy, concept, and execution of extraordinary digital visuals and brand-centric media experiences. For the past 15 years, IOMEDIA has offered a diverse outlook answering complex marketing challenges with inspired concepts, campaigns, and media productions. The IOMEDIA team is comprised of visual and brand specialists, interactive strategists, designers, architects, animators, 3D artists, illustrators, writers, and producers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;ABOUT THE IOMEDIA HEALTHCARE STUDIO – www.io-media.com&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IOMEDIA creates impactful, award winning, visual communications for the Healthcare, Pharmaceutical, and Scientific community. Our mission is to strategically execute visual imagery that is informative, dynamic, and educational.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The innovative use of dynamic and rich media to engage and educate an audience is of primary concern to the Healthcare Studio at IOMEDIA. Complex problems and visual solutions are our core strengths, feeling right at home with scientists, researchers, medical and creative directors. By focusing on the power of imagery with motion, sound and interaction we have found a medium that best communicates concepts macro, micro, and sophisticated chains of events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IOMEDIA’s capabilities include the strategic development of custom 3D Animation, Storyboarding, Medical Illustration, Interactive CD-ROMS &amp;amp; DVDs, Web-based Applications, Exhibit Design, and HD Film &amp;amp; Video Productions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your resume, cover letter with salary requirements and any other relevant information (e.g. web link) to pmcareers@io-media.com .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applications submitted without relevant professional experience will not be accepted.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-project-manager-iomeda-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-project-manager-iomeda-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Project Manager Interactive\Web Dev at TMP Worldwide in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a great time to join TMP – we’re seeking a Digital Project Manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Digital Project Manager, you will manage the entire project lifecycle to deliver comprehensive digital solutions to our client base. In addition to excelling in scope, time and budget management, Project Managers also must possess a thorough understanding of digital development in all its forms (design, IXD, content, UI development,engineering and quality assurance) and the ability to facilitate dialog that represents our company’s development efforts and methodologies to clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run point on several projects at once, managing all communications, scope, timeline and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and communicate project performance throughout development to all stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and update all project plan documentation from initiation to execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading cross-functional teams to deliver high quality deliverables on time and on budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working as a member of an interactive development team researching and executing emerging solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing detailed project plans and collecting client information for development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;accurately identify and mitigate project risk, forecast development timelines and budget accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitating communication among team members – internally and with the client – via regular team meetings and the project website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience with project management methodologies, including various forms of project documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience managing projects involving website development, video, mobile sites, apps, social media and etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills and ability to produce enough project documentation, business requirements documentation and functional specifications to drive successful development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must possess an understanding of basic site usability and architecture principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some previous experience withfacilitating projects involving content management systems, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Flash and otherweb technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a digital agency a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have experience in a range of client management situations (i.e. multiple industries and corporate structures, projects of varying duration and complexity).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project Management certification a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent negotiation and interpersonal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong knowledge of MS Office including Microsoft Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About TMP Worldwide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMP Worldwide Advertising &amp;amp; Communications, LLC (www.tmp.com) is a global, tech-enabled talent acquisition company that leverages software, advertising and creativity to develop and deploy our clients' employer brands across digital, social and mobile outlets. Our client base of over 1,200 companies spans every sector in business and government. Headquartered in New York City, with offices throughout North America, Europe and Asia with affiliates around the globe, TMP continues to set the standard for measurable and cost-effective HR communications. We are also honored to be recognized, once again, among AdAge&amp;rsquo;s Top US Digital Agencies, ranking #33 for 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMP Worldwide is committed to providing a safe workplace for all employees. It is the policy of TMP Worldwide to conduct a background check for all candidates who accept an offer of employment with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TMP Worldwide is an Equal Opportunity and Affirmative Action Employer, M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-project-manager-interactive-web-dev-tmp-worldwide-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-project-manager-interactive-web-dev-tmp-worldwide-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at ScrollMotion in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with Project Managers and Account Managers to create project scopes, schedules, and road maps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requirements gathering, user profiles and audience definition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan for, delegate, oversee, and polish all UX project deliverables (such as strategic vision briefs, concepts, wireframes, site maps, content inventories, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and present the aforementioned deliverables if necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with 3rd party partners, including client agencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Champion user-centered design principals, while balancing business objectives carefully&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+5 years experience creating interfaces, large scale web sites, and mobile experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Committed to creating great user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly skilled using the Adobe Design Suite, and productivity applications such as Office, iWork, Google Docs, Assembla, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful track record leading design teams to producing high quality products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focused attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with usability and HCI literature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand the “big picture” for a client’s business and design for phased implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven client management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid communication and presentation skills, both written and visual&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience working within visual design departments, and experience managing other designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing for interactive applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loves solving complex problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable managing 2-3 projects at any given time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If interested and available to start immediately, please send introductory email, résumé, and samples of work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-scrollmotion-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-scrollmotion-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>