<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UI / UX Developer - JavaScript at Project One in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our client, a an innovative Online Multimedia Entertainment company, is seeking a seasoned Front-End Developer to join a very collaborative team for development projects across the organization.  You&amp;rsquo;ll be responsible for developing &amp;ldquo;front-end&amp;rdquo; components in JQuery and Custom JavaScript code.  This is a PHP / LAMP environment with Akamai CDN (Content Distribution Network) in place.  This Developer must have excellent experience with Object-Oriented JavaScript and building suites with JQuery.  The Developer will also be responsible for Unit Testing and documentation of their work, and truly take pride in their development.  This is a very collaborative, growing company with an excellent environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities &amp;amp; Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience with extensive coding with both Object-Oriented JavaScript Structures and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years hands on experience with XML, JSON, Selenium and building suites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to Unit Test and Document own work; must be familiar and have experience with Rich, evolving content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Selenium and integration with Front-End Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Eclipse or GIT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Back-end teams to ensure that users are getting content, seamlessly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness of headers and ESI (Edge Side Includes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile/Scrum Development experience is mandatory; must be comfortable in a fast-paced environment where you take full responsibility and pride in your work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for high-level redesigns and wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 competency is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-developer-javascript-project-one-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-developer-javascript-project-one-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Front-End Developer at Viacom in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Front End Web Developer is about working on improving and enhancing Social Media enterprise web platform with state-of-the-art technologies and methods. This involves broad scope of activities: from being a contact point debugging issues to working on POCs and prototypes to mentoring/overviewing off-shore team of web developers. Position also involves daily communication with team members on- and off-shore: Developers, Team leads, PMs, Product owners, Designers, Technical managers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PRINCIPAL RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance and maintenance of front end components of web platform (widgets, various javascript frameworks/SDKs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze, design and develop front end components for platform solutions in Social Media realm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in all phases of software development, ensure the proper usage of best practices, patterns and development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in product requirements analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide input and influence front end decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review staging and production environments client side performance and pro-actively improve it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with developers on a daily basis in order to implement best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with other teams within company structure to achieve better integration of Social Media platform into other products/solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure web development follows responsive paradigm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Product/Design team to build POC and/or prototype&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical input on decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver ready sites/pages within couple days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Mobile first” mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Progressive Enhancement, Responsive Design Techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS/XHTML/Javascript (including CSS3 and HTML5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AJAX, JSON(P)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fiddler (or Charles)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to debug and fix issues in production environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EXPERIENCE:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in designing and implementing enterprise web solutions is A MUST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with cross-browser hell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe Photoshop – should be able to use mocks from Designer and cut all necessary resources from it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EDUCATION:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least Bachelor degree in Computer Science&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Desired Qualification:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of Facebook/Twitter integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of web components as part of platform solution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-developer-viacom-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-developer-viacom-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Lugh Studio in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Lugh Studio, Inc. is a branding and graphic design studio that provides focused and effective branding strategies. In over 15 years of business, Lugh Studio has worked with clients in a variety of industries ranging from Fortune 100 companies to small start-ups.  Our multi-lingual onsite staff, as well as our extensive network of freelance talent, enable us to work effectively in different media and languages, domestically and internationally. Located in downtown Brooklyn with a spectacular view of the harbor and New York skyline, Lugh Studio offers a uniquely creative, diverse, and dynamic work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for front-end developers who can work on-site. This position will be on-site freelancer with the potential to go full-time. We want someone who not only is technically capable of the programming but who also is attentive to the design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Your skills should include:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML &amp;ndash; including understanding of the new HTML5 semantic tags&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS &amp;ndash; including CSS3 properties and media queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of Javascript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic PHP and MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordpress theme creation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic Photoshop and/or Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PLUSES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SEO best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drupal experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML email platforms (i.e. MailChimp)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a boutique design firm based in Brooklyn specializing in visual branding and web design. Our team consists of graphic designers who work in both web and print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our projects range from start-ups looking for create an image, to established businesses needing to bolster their web presence. Our services include all things digital and print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our office is located in downtown Brooklyn with a spectacular view of the harbor and New York skyline.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-lugh-studio-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-lugh-studio-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Forbes, Inc in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Front End Web Developer develops media and business solutions by designing, developing and supporting web solutions for forbes.com. New solutions are developed in HTML5 in coordination and collaboration with the Systems team, the Operations team, Template developers, Product Management, QA and Project Managers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews and influences ongoing designs, standards and methods for forbes.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops innovative media and business solutions for stable, secure, high-volume web-based applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Committed to continually learning through actively participating in code reviews and solution demonstrations, participating in educational opportunities, reading professional publications, maintaining personal networks, and participating in professional organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uses Jira for Bug reporting and Mantis for production roll out requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document progress , code migrations and status on work assignments and communicates these updates during daily standups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On call support of front end solutions for forbes.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides complete technical documentation, code comments, and readable code that is properly stored in a version control system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses an intense drive to learn how to improve our core products and services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTML5, XML, XSL and JS libraries, specifically jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with UI/UX on critical, large scale web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing and troubleshooting front end solutions across multiple browsers and devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of the behavior of web and mobile application security issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multitask and grow in a fast paced development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-forbes-inc-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-forbes-inc-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Blackstone in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an experienced Front-End Developer to join our User Experience Team. The ideal candidate should be able to quickly hand-code clean HTML and CSS from Comps and Wireframes. You will report to the Manager of Front-end Development. You will take on new development initiatives and platform enhancements on Grainger.com focusing on front-end development and client-side interactions using HTML, XHTML, CSS, XML, JavaScript, and other related interactive technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Major responsibilities and duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate and maintain front-end code (HTML / CSS / JavaScript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working to improve site performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain reusable code libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurately estimating and tracking your time across multiple simultaneous projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a team of developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn and adapt to new software/hardware technology and incorporate into production process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;collaborating on new design concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Core Competencies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert HTML, XHTML, DHTML, CSS, XML programming skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create clean, precise browser-compatible code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in JavaScript / Dojo / jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Adobe Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of interaction design and user-centered design methods &amp;amp; practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience collaborating with design and development teams on large-scale projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and track multiple tasks across multiple projects, under tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy working closely with others, and respectful of other perspectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert conflict resolution skills and being able to negotiate with stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to switch gears quickly and be flexible to work on concurrent projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the Agile development methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Education and Experience&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 2 to 3 years experience of hands-on web development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience Web Accessibility Standards a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Broad Vision, Hybris, JSP, Swing, Struts a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Marketing, Visual Communication, Graphic Arts, Computer Science or related area a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-application-developer-blackstone-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-application-developer-blackstone-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Lot18 in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Lot18 is revolutionizing the way America buys wine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re an agile technology startup based in New York City. We connect wineries and retailers with our members nationwide. The wine, glassware, and other epicurean products we offer are highly curated by teams on both coasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lot18 is a great place for smart people who know how to get things done &amp;ndash; and who want to work alongside likeminded teammates. Come make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Competitive Salaries, Full Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All positions are full time and based in New York, unless otherwise stated, and come with a comprehensive benefits package:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental and vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Top of the line computer setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fun office environment (foosball, XBOX360, turntables)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plenty of wine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work With Awesome People&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We run the gamut. Our people hail from companies such as Amazon, AOL, AT&amp;amp;T, Christie&amp;rsquo;s auction house, CollegeHumor/IAC, Merrill Lynch, J.P. Morgan, Sony Ericsson, Forbes, Gourmet, The French Laundry, The Waverly Inn, Benu, Ruth&amp;rsquo;s Chris Steak House, and many others. Lot18&amp;rsquo;s employees have over 150 years of combined experience in the technology and wine industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve gotten a perfect score on the SAT and graduated from top schools like Harvard, Oxford, and Princeton. But please don&amp;rsquo;t hold it against us! We&amp;rsquo;ve done things in the real world, too, like climbing Mt. Everest and sailing the Atlantic Ocean to winemaking, filmmaking for the 48 Hour Film Projects, studying cheese-making in Italy on a Fulbright, making videogames for Aerosmith, and playing with the Philadelphia Orchestra. In our spare time, we like to eat and drink, run marathons and compete in roller derby and dodgeball.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for well-rounded front-end developers that will write efficient code, snappy pixel precise interfaces and create an amazing user experience. You&amp;rsquo;ll bring new design perspectives and have an important say in how we design and build our product. You need to think like a user, be able to show the DOM who&amp;rsquo;s boss, be passionate about the front-end and excited to build and iterate on features that will help change the way people buy wine online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize, design and implement consumer-facing user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the delivery of a rich user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write complex JavaScript applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design interfaces that are quick and responsive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write tests and participate in code reviews to ensure quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to product and implementation discussions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with UI/UX, product and web application teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 and CSS3 fluency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript mastery and experience working with a JS library (jQuery ftw!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience or willingness to learn an interpreted programming language, like PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to use the Adobe creative suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General understanding of version control (we use git)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A/B and multivariate testing experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write reusable code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The patience to make things work in Internet Explorer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial spirit and a preoccupation with staying on top of industry technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Why you should come work with us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock options. Medical, dental, vision and cell phone paid in full&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Top of the line computer setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10% time to work on projects outside of your daily responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well funded by top tier venture firms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many technical and business challenges to solve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plenty of wine to drink and a fun office environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-lot18-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-lot18-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX/Front-End Web Developer at Analog Method in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Analog Method is looking for a junior to mid-level on-site UX/Front-End Web Developer skilled in wireframing, HTML/CSS, and JavaScript to develop high quality websites and Web applications. This is a full-time position with great benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your Profile&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are super smart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your passion for web technology is unmatched.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong desire to make the world a better place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing good code makes you happy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You care about quality more than anyone you know.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analog Method is a dynamic New York City web development shop committed to delivering quality work that&amp;rsquo;s cutting-edge and creative. We make the world a better place by creating superior web sites and web applications that are useful and user friendly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll want to work for us because:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The work is fun, varied and challenging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll never stop learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will have ownership of your projects and will get to make critical technical decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the design, strategy, quality assurance, technical, project management and account teams to successfully develop, launch and maintain websites and web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop user flows, site maps and wireframes for websites, Content Management Systems and other database-driven web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create web pages using well-structured CSS and HTML/HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement interactivity using AJAX and various JavaScript libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with sales to discuss development approaches and create work estimates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to support requests and ensure customer satisfaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document work and development processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Candidate Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player with excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized with attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer science or digital media degree, or at least 1 year of industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of CSS, HTML/HTML5 and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General understanding of responsive web design techniques, media queries and mobile web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of at least one major server side scripting language, Python, PHP or C# preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with a passion for the Web and technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to work on-site at our office in midtown Manhattan, conveniently located near Grand Central and Penn Station.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send an email with your resume to fedev0312@analogmethod.com. In your email subject, you must use the keyword &amp;ldquo;fedev0312&amp;rdquo; for us to consider you for employment.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-front-end-web-developer-analog-method-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-front-end-web-developer-analog-method-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Web Developer at Steven Alan in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Steven Alan, a multi-brand retailer carrying a curated collection of clothing, accessories, apothecary, and home items for both men and women, is searching for a Junior Web Developer to join the eCommerce team. Located in the TriBeCa neighborhood of New York City, this person will report to the Director of eCommerce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and review outsourced technical resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate proficiency across all coding techniques and web technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain project schedules, while working closely with in-house designers as well as external partners to ensure timely deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with web team to develop online content, implement web design updates and oversee and/or implement other front-end project requests while maintaining department budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree and 1-3 years related experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of XHTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySQL, HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to convert designs into pixel perfrect, standards compliant ZHTML/CSS Dreamweaver and ability to hand code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Demandware&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work with a number of MVC Frameworks and write strong scalable code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Ecommerce solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SEO Awareness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player with excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly organized and detail-oriented multi-tasker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compensation package includes competitive salary, medical and dental insurance, 401k plan, gym membership reimbursement, vacation and holidays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steven Alan is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-developer-steven-alan-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-developer-steven-alan-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Front End Developer at The New York Public Library in Manhattan, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York Public Library is re-imagining how archival materials can be used on the web. We are seeking a talented, user-focused developer to join the NYPL Labs team and, working closely with staff from the Manuscripts and Archives Division, assist us in building dynamic web applications to facilitate discovery, access and use of archival and manuscript collections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About NYPL Labs:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based at the landmark central branch on 42nd Street, NYPL Labs is an award-winning design and technology team working to weave The New York Public Library&amp;rsquo;s vast collections into the Internet. Labs technologists work closely with curatorial staff to develop imaginative collections-based apps and services, often engaging the public directly in the work of improving, organizing or remixing library data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Position is grant-funded for 18 months with possibility of extension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop dynamic presentations for archival descriptions, including finding aids (building in part on pre-existing prototypes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design search and discovery interfaces for archives and manuscript materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop image viewer (building on existing open source projects) appropriate to the presentation of archival materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and develop tools to enable interaction between users and NYPL archivists and to facilitate research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with members of NYPL’s Web team to integrate new archival access systems with the Library’s website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other NYPL Labs developers on crowdsourcing projects involving archival records and manuscripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the development of other archives-related applications as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Web Development, Computer Science, Digital Design, or a related field (or equivalent experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least three years' experience developing public-facing web sites and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced skills in HTML and CSS, including experience with Sass and Less&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Javascript skills, including experience with JQuery and Backbone.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing web applications in Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience interacting with data via RESTful web APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with source/version control systems such as Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent skills in visual design and typography for the Web, and familiarity with current trends in web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-the-new-york-public-library-manhattan-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-the-new-york-public-library-manhattan-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End UI Developer at Boxee in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You will own the front end development of the Boxee client. You will work in the Boxee R&amp;amp;D and in close collaboration with the Boxee Product and Design team. This position is in NYC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have skinned for XBMC or similar product you know the lay of the land. If not, being a UI developer means having a creative spark but a pixel level attention to detail and the ability to constantly improve and solve UX problems to make the product better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skinning or HTML/JS/CSS experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop/Illustrator/GIMP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eye for good product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Savvy Boxee/XBMC and TV tinkerer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please send us links to screenshots or videos of UI work you have created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-boxee-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-boxee-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>