<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer - Freelance at NoFavorite in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Implementing modern, semantically structured layouts based on designs provided by our design team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Javascript frameworks (jQuery, YUI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of Adobe CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating device­ specific layouts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design sensibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of back end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of source control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of best practices, design principles, and web standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are looking for someone creative who stays up to date with new web trends. Responsive design skills are a major plus. Knowledge of Photoshop and image optimization methods are a requirement.
Strong communications skills in dealing with team members and clients is essential. This is a freelance position with possibility of turning into full time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think you would be a good fit and want to work in a fun, creative environment, please email jobs@nofavorite.com with a link to your portfolio. Submissions without portfolio links will not be considered&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compensation for the position is to be determined based on work quality and experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-nofavorite-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-nofavorite-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Direct Brands in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Direct Brands is looking for creative, versatile, problem-solving front-end developers to join our team. A new management team recently kicked-off an ambitious effort to reinvent how the business serves its customers.  As part of this effort, our Developers will work closely with the rest of the product marketing team to redesign and re-platform our consumer web experience. The developer will also play a critical role in training and building the team going forward, providing tremendous opportunities for growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You Should Be Prepared to&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with our designers to transform Adobe CS files into beautiful, fast web pages that users love.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Day 1 you&amp;rsquo;ll work primarily in a static HTML and CSS environment, but overtime you will dig deeper into the stack, utilizing interactive design with Javascript to Magento&amp;rsquo;s back-end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with internal and external back-end developers to align front-end and back-end development needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help recruit and evaluate more people like you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide consumer web technology expertise and advice across the business as our team and capabilities continue to evolve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Must Haves:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level understanding of hand-coded, semantic HTML/HTML5, CSS 3 and legacy browser compliance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level understanding of jQuery (and other JS libraries and JS).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and maintaining CSS and JS libraries for use across our 24 sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design and UI instincts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can teach yourself almost anything. You use whatever resources are at your disposal to find an answer.  You search on Google, call friends, read stack overflow, experiment, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have excellent communication skills and you&amp;rsquo;re well liked by others. You enjoy and have experience teaching other people about your area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You value content and want to build products which provide people enjoyable media experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Located in NY, NY&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Major Bonus Points…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Magento&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable skill in writing high-quality, server-side code (preferably in PHP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven history of working on interesting side-projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love to read and have an innate interest in and strong understanding of at least one of our core genres: popular fiction, mystery, romance, science fiction, cooking, crafting, home decor, history, military, Christian, children&amp;rsquo;s, spirituality/wellness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;We Look for People Who&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love content &amp;mdash; web, books, tech, movies, music, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess an intense intellectual curiosity and unwavering work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive in uncertain environments with small, high-energy teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Care about work and want to make an impact, but also like to have fun.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-direct-brands-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-direct-brands-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Warby Parker in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Some front-end devs started out as designers and then learned to code. Others started out as programmers and then fell in love with design. And the rest tackled the full stack at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However you came to it, we’re looking for someone who loves building great user experiences and is skilled in the tools necessary to build them. If that sounds like you, we should talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re hiring ASAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with our designers to transform Adobe CS files into beautiful, fast web pages that make a user’s day better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll be working through most of our web stack  — from static HTML and CSS to interactive designs with a lot of JS to the site’s Magento back end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain JS and CSS libraries to use throughout our site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll love about working here:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The company is reshaping the eyewear industry. That industry is massive, and we&amp;rsquo;re growing fast. We love being here to see that happen, and we love working hard to speed it along. It&amp;rsquo;s an electrifying climate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be work on a very small team, and you&amp;rsquo;ll own a lot of the projects that you work on. We often release important, high-visibility features that were done by just one developer. That developer often will be you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our location in the heart of Soho. We&amp;rsquo;re in the Puck Building, which is lucky enough to have its own Wikipedia entry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have delicious catered lunches three days a week and a steady supply of snacks in the kitchen. And for when that all catches up with you, we offer free membership at the 24 Hour Fitness across the street from the office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Necessary attributes:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong, well-formed opinions about what makes for a good user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience implementing those opinions in user-facing work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert-level skill in hand-coded HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meaningful real-world experience writing jQuery and vanilla JS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable skill in writing high-quality server-side code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talent as a writer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort with the Adobe CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Useful attributes:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A track record of building interesting and/or challenging side projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magento experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing web sites for iOS and Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The gift of flight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-warby-parker-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-warby-parker-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Interactive Developer at mcgarrybowen in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, mcgarrybowen was built differently, on the simple premise that clients deserve better. So we built a company committed to delivering just that. A company that believes, with every fiber of its being, that it exists to serve clients, build brands, and grow businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;At Mcgarrybowen We Believe:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in taking things personally. In throwing ourselves into our work and being passionate about our ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in people. Our colleagues are a diverse, creative, outspoken, ambitious, character-rich ocean of talent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in collaboration. Great ideas come from all corners. And they’re burnished by discussion and teamwork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in decency. We love people who have passion, but aren&amp;rsquo;t egomaniacs or glory hogs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in personal growth. We teach, mentor, and grow the best and brightest, so they become leaders in the field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;mcgarrybowen is looking to fill the position of Junior Interactive Developer. In this role, the candidate will play a key role in delivering award winning, interactive experiences to our clients.  The core focus of this position will be on banner advertisement production on desktop and mobile devices.They will be responsible for working with a team of Technologists in the process of taking visual design concepts and converting those into high quality rich interactive experiences including websites, online advertisements and integrated social media programs for Fortune 500 clients. This individual will work directly with a Technology Lead and be responsible for assisting with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing standard and rich media banners (Flash &amp;amp; HTML5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code Email campaigns:   work with business teams to implement marketing &amp;amp; servicing emails consistent with the brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code digital assets:  work with agency teams to implement refreshed and invigorated marketing &amp;amp; servicing banners, personalization, micro sites, transaction-based offers and landing pages that demonstrate creative approaches to visualizing data and presenting information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboration with Design, IA, Content Management &amp;amp; Planning: meet project objectives and maintain schedules in a fast paced and changing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position will require the following Critical Competencies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of AS2/AS3 language, tweening libraries (such as tweenlite/max)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with media vendors such as doubleclick and mediamind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess quality code and timeline animation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML5/canvas, css and javascript are a plus.  Experience developing ads in HTML5 a major plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take direction and work in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professionalism, reliability, integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to details related to design and code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be accountable for the delivery of quality, well written code within agreed timelines and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be optimistic, ambitious, and eager to be a part of our growing development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;A bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree is preferred as well as an enthusiasm for working with front-end technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;mcgarrybowen is an equal opportunity employer and bases its employment decisions only on job-related criteria.  All applicants and employees are intended to enjoy the same rights and privileges with respect to recruiting, hiring, training, promotions, demotions, separations, compensation, and benefits regardless of their age, race, color, creed, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy-related status, marital status, veteran status, physical or mental disability, national or ethnic origin, or record of arrest, where the individual is otherwise qualified.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-interactive-developer-mcgarrybowen-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-interactive-developer-mcgarrybowen-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at weeSpring in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a front-end developer with an entrepreneurial bent to join our team. You&amp;rsquo;ll be crafting new page templates, emails, AJAX requests, user interactions, and rewriting the existing front end to match your high standards. You have free rein to use whatever libs and technology you want for this purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our development process is hyper agile, with continuous deployment to our development site, and we release new code to production several times a day. Our tech stack is Python using the Django framework and Jinja2 template engine, MySQL (Percona Server), Nginx, hosted on Amazon AWS. All pages are served in under 500 milliseconds&amp;hellip; without caching. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who can make our front end just as fast and responsive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a young company, and as such, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of room for you to grow and take on new responsibility. Our team is built upon mutual respect, autonomy, and a humble awareness and acceptance of our strengths and weaknesses. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone to work with us, not for us. That means competitive salaries and meaningful equity for the right candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are an HTML/CSS3, Javascript and jQuery ninja&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve worked with back end engineers before and you know what makes their life easier and how to plan a project with them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a thorough knowledge of cross-browser compatibility issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve got knowledge of cutting edge technologies, but more importantly, the common sense to know when to use them and when to stick with traditional methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re self-motivated, self-directed, and can work without supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You understand that done is better than perfect&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to have&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve worked with startups and/or small companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience building a mobile site and/or responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re familiar with and have an opinion on SASS/LESS, domain sharing, asynchronous loading, icon fonts, sprites, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know all the little graceful degradation tricks for the above techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re obsessed with page load times and seem to always have a waterfall graph open when you&amp;rsquo;re viewing a page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have an interest in taking on product and/or design responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Application Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the form at right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please do not include a formal cover letter.  Instead please use the cover letter space at right to tell us what you find interesting about weeSpring and provide us three suggestions for improving weeSpring&amp;rsquo;s user experience or design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-weespring-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-weespring-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer - Internship at weeSpring in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a front-end developer with an entrepreneurial bent to join our team. You&amp;rsquo;ll be crafting new page templates, emails, AJAX requests, user interactions, and rewriting the existing front end to match your high standards. You have free rein to use whatever libs and technology you want for this purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our development process is hyper agile, with continuous deployment to our development site, and we release new code to production several times a day. Our tech stack is Python using the Django framework and Jinja2 template engine, MySQL (Percona Server), Nginx, hosted on Amazon AWS. All pages are served in under 500 milliseconds&amp;hellip; without caching. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who can make our front end just as fast and responsive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a young company, and as such, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of room for you to grow and take on new responsibility. Our team is built upon mutual respect, autonomy, and a humble awareness and acceptance of our strengths and weaknesses. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone to work with us, not for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are an HTML/CSS3, Javascript and jQuery ninja&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve worked with back end engineers before and you know what makes their life easier and how to plan a project with them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a thorough knowledge of cross-browser compatibility issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve got knowledge of cutting edge technologies, but more importantly, the common sense to know when to use them and when to stick with traditional methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re self-motivated, self-directed, and can work without supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You understand that done is better than perfect&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to have&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve worked with startups and/or small companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience building a mobile site and/or responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re familiar with and have an opinion on SASS/LESS, domain sharing, asynchronous loading, icon fonts, sprites, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know all the little graceful degradation tricks for the above techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re obsessed with page load times and seem to always have a waterfall graph open when you&amp;rsquo;re viewing a page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have an interest in taking on product and/or design responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Application Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the form at right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please do not include a formal cover letter. Instead please use the cover letter space at right to tell us what you find interesting about weeSpring and provide us three suggestions for improving weeSpring&amp;rsquo;s user experience or design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-internship-weespring-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-internship-weespring-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Jr. Front-End Developer at Plated in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Plated is looking for a junior front-end developer to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a NYC tech startup that is redefining the way we eat and reconnecting people to their food, one plate at a time. Plated was founded by two Harvard Business School graduates less than a year ago. Since then we have received funding from an exceptional group of investors (including one of the Facebook co-founders and well known NYC seed fund), been featured in the Wall Street Journal and New York Times, and been accepted into the most competitive startup accelerator in the world, TechStars. You will be joining a small and energetic team composed of the next big movers and shakers in tech; our co-founder Nick Taranto was recently featured in Forbes’ 30 Under 30.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As our young company is taking off, we need to rapidly expand our developer team – that’s where you come in! Why us? This is a wonderful opportunity for a junior front-end developer to learn and have an impact; you will gain back-end proficiency while working hand-in-hand with our senior developer who has over 15 years of experience. Beyond brute intelligence and problem solving skills, we are looking for hunger, passion, and a general craving to help us change the way people eat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and create new features for responsive website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop integrations between Plated website and 3rd party APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand and create an outstanding online experience for your target audience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy, Energy.  You really want to work with us and learn how to build a company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undergraduate degree or minimum of 1 year of hands-on front-end web development experience (or dev boot camp)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to self manage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technical Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in HTML, CSS and github.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong skills in Javascript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of how to connect to external APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to jQuery, Twitter Bootstrap and Ruby on Rails preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonus points for cloud services and Pivotal Tracking use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-front-end-developer-plated-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-front-end-developer-plated-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Front-End Developer at Viacom in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Front End Web Developer is about working on improving and enhancing Social Media enterprise web platform with state-of-the-art technologies and methods. This involves broad scope of activities: from being a contact point debugging issues to working on POCs and prototypes to mentoring/overviewing off-shore team of web developers. Position also involves daily communication with team members on- and off-shore: Developers, Team leads, PMs, Product owners, Designers, Technical managers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;PRINCIPAL RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance and maintenance of front end components of web platform (widgets, various   javascript frameworks/SDKs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze, design and develop front end components for platform solutions in Social Media   realm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in all phases of software development, ensure the proper usage of best practices,   patterns and development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in product requirements analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide input and influence front end decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review staging and production environments client side performance and pro-actively    improve it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with developers on a daily basis in order to implement best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with other teams within company structure to achieve better integration of Social Media platform into other products/solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure web development follows responsive paradigm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Product/Design team to build POC and/or prototype&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical input on decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver ready sites/pages within couple days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Mobile first” mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Progressive Enhancement, Responsive Design Techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS/XHTML/Javascript (including CSS3 and HTML5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AJAX, JSON(P)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fiddler (or Charles)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to debug and fix UI/javascript issues in production environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;EXPERIENCE:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in designing and implementing client side components for enterprise web solutions is A MUST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with cross-browser hell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe Photoshop – should be able to use mocks from Designer and cut all    necessary resources from it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;EDUCATION:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least Bachelor degree in Computer Science&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Desired Qualification:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of Facebook/Twitter integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of web components as part of platform solution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-developer-viacom-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-front-end-developer-viacom-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>(UI/UX) Developer/Designer at KegWorks in Buffalo, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;KegWorks is currently seeking an outstanding User Interface/Experience Designer to join our Marketing Team. The UI/UX Designer will work as part of our diverse team of copywriters, social media managers, SEO specialists, and graphic designers to create and maintain an intuitive and cohesive look, feel, and overall user experience for our website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is a brilliant problem solver, quick study, self-starter, and superb communicator who possesses a passion for creating a first-rate user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be working closely with a cross-functional team that includes personnel from IT, customer service, sales, purchasing, and product development. You’ll be responsible for design and markup deployment of website headers, banners, and graphics. Design and development of promotional emails with corresponding landing pages and homepage graphics will also be regular responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Responsibilities Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transactional email design and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Triggered email design and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI research, scope, and design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UX design and development (from global site processes to individual landing pages)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design for social media on an as-needed basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsite design and front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile site design and front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category and product organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Education &amp;amp; Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Successful candidates will have:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Digital Media Arts, Marketing, or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience designing interactive user experiences for rich web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications &amp;amp; Capabilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic design for print and web &amp;ndash; both raster and vector&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end development (HTML, CSS with PHP and JS familiarity) and SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intimate understanding of user-centered design disciplines and principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acute attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to grasp and distill highly complex user design issues into clean, understandable solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective time management and project management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to flourish in a fast paced, iterative, deadline-driven environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Print development experience and skills are highly preferred – B2B and B2C collateral, ads, catalogs, branding, and retail POP and signage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great aim with a nerf gun&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send an email to jobs@kegworks.com with the following included in the body of the email (NO ATTACHMENTS):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A well-written cover letter that explains exactly why you’re “the one”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A URL for your online portfolio (including recent UI and UX work to be considered)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-developer-designer-kegworks-buffalo-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-developer-designer-kegworks-buffalo-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Flavorpill in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Flavorpill is looking for a focused, multi-disciplined front-end developer to join a small but growing product development team. The right candidate is passionate about clean code, collaboration, and ever-improving UX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Covering arts and culture globally with a site reaching more than 1M uniques monthly and event coverage in 10 markets in the US and London, Flavorpill is evolving its web, email and mobile offering to give our readers a powerful tool to discover, save, and share culture &amp;ndash; providing them with worthwhile options for their limited free time. This work will involve an overhaul of the user experience, the integration of key web services, and the extension of a scalable CMS and site built in Ruby on Rails, through an iterative Agile process which takes heavily from Lean Startup practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The environment at Flavorpill is fast-paced, dynamic, and focused on developing impactful cultural content and tools for an engaged, creative audience. Although we are a dot-com veteran, formed in the early 2000s, we have a startup mentality, and every voice here is important. So is creating an environment for people to do amazing things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time position based out of our office in Soho, NYC. If you have the experience we’re looking for, please send us your resume, a short cover letter, and 2-3 code samples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Main Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code and deliver pages and features in HTML/CSS and Javascript based on Photoshop designs and/or interactive wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Properly test all code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help with QA (Selenium experience is a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage custom projects across multiple web platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Core Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong HTML/CSS, and Javascript skills, ability to write clean code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very comfortable with JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to profile and optimize code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working with Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating templates with third-party services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with backend web frameworks (preferably Ruby on Rails)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of basic SEO concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile dev experience a HUGE plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-flavorpill-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-flavorpill-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>