<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feeds/ny-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead Front-End Developer at Marqueed in Brooklyn, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marqueed makes it easy to work with others on visual projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are making a service that makes it easy for people working on visual projects to talk about images in a fun and visual way. It makes the collaboration faster and easier while secretly keeping you more organized and efficient . In a way, its image sharing for a purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We think it’s an awesome idea that could change the way the creative community interacts– and our investors agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the moment we are looking for a front-end developer who is bright and motivated to join the founding team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she would need to have proven front-end experience working on web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be comfortable in a rapid iterate and deploy environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review interactive strategies and recommend improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current with regard to web design trends, tools and best or emerging practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jquery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MySQL is a Big Plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary (Based on experience) + Equity&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 12:38:32 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-front-end-developer-marqueed-brooklyn-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-front-end-developer-marqueed-brooklyn-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at ZocDoc in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ZocDoc is seeking front end developers who love to build web pages that are exceptionally usable and universally astounding. You mostly live in the worlds of HTML, CSS and JavaScript, but you also understand the full stack because you know it makes you better at front end. You care about the quality of your code and the products you build more than anyone you know. You care deeply about the experience of using your product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Working at ZocDoc&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were recently named the Best Place to Work in New York City by Crain&amp;rsquo;s New York, which means that they asked everyone who works here how much they loved their job and everyone answered in the range of &amp;ldquo;a lot&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;a helluva lot.&amp;rdquo; The truth is, we have a lot of fun doing our job. We get excited about driving conversions and building slick UIs cool enough to blog about. We go on semi-annual hackathons to remote, exotic places (like the Catskills and Long Island!). Pizza and beer are never far away. Neither are granola and tea, for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Our Offices&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work in a massive loft-y space in the heart of SoHo. Devs get top-notch gear (24gb RAM, 4 monitor setups, etc) and interact a lot with the rest of the team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;We want someone who:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crafts beautiful cross-browser compatible pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is expert at Javascript (you write your own jQuery plugins)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is driven by an unknown force to change healthcare for the better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knows how to test the UX of what they build&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;As a ZocDoc employee you get:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A feeling of accomplishing something genuinely useful to humanity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation fees fully covered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free catered lunches every day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer-covered health insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A hoverboard&lt;em&gt;
&lt;/em&gt;subject to availability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like the gig for you, send us your resume and in your cover letter tell us what we should change to make our website, zocdoc.com, even better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 12:38:32 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-zocdoc-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-zocdoc-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Project One in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client, a global leader in omni-media, is seeking a highly motivated Front End Developer to join their development and digital team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in reviews of wireframe comps and evaluate the best approach for front end web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with designers to obtain and create all visual assets necessary for website production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop custom, dynamic user experience using JavaScript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with server side developers to facilitate UX on the front end using dynamic server side data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in development of best practices, shared standardized code libraries, and written documentation of all systems, tools, and processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-4 years of hands on front end development experience in a professional web environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-4 years of hands on experience with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with use-cases and/or scenario specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a team environment that uses concurrent application development systems such as code repositories, unit and integration testing, user acceptance testing, and deployments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 12:38:32 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-project-one-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-project-one-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>