<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Front End Developer at The New York Public Library in Manhattan, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York Public Library is re-imagining how archival materials can be used on the web. We are seeking a talented, user-focused developer to join the NYPL Labs team and, working closely with staff from the Manuscripts and Archives Division, assist us in building dynamic web applications to facilitate discovery, access and use of archival and manuscript collections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About NYPL Labs:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based at the landmark central branch on 42nd Street, NYPL Labs is an award-winning design and technology team working to weave The New York Public Library&amp;rsquo;s vast collections into the Internet. Labs technologists work closely with curatorial staff to develop imaginative collections-based apps and services, often engaging the public directly in the work of improving, organizing or remixing library data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Position is grant-funded for 18 months with possibility of extension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop dynamic presentations for archival descriptions, including finding aids (building in part on pre-existing prototypes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design search and discovery interfaces for archives and manuscript materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop image viewer (building on existing open source projects) appropriate to the presentation of archival materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and develop tools to enable interaction between users and NYPL archivists and to facilitate research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with members of NYPL’s Web team to integrate new archival access systems with the Library’s website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other NYPL Labs developers on crowdsourcing projects involving archival records and manuscripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the development of other archives-related applications as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Web Development, Computer Science, Digital Design, or a related field (or equivalent experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least three years' experience developing public-facing web sites and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced skills in HTML and CSS, including experience with Sass and Less&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Javascript skills, including experience with JQuery and Backbone.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing web applications in Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience interacting with data via RESTful web APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with source/version control systems such as Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent skills in visual design and typography for the Web, and familiarity with current trends in web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-the-new-york-public-library-manhattan-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-developer-the-new-york-public-library-manhattan-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End UI Developer at Boxee in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You will own the front end development of the Boxee client. You will work in the Boxee R&amp;amp;D and in close collaboration with the Boxee Product and Design team. This position is in NYC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have skinned for XBMC or similar product you know the lay of the land. If not, being a UI developer means having a creative spark but a pixel level attention to detail and the ability to constantly improve and solve UX problems to make the product better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skinning or HTML/JS/CSS experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop/Illustrator/GIMP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eye for good product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Savvy Boxee/XBMC and TV tinkerer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please send us links to screenshots or videos of UI work you have created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-boxee-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-boxee-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Developer at The New York Times in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The New York Times Company, a leading global, multimedia news and information company with 2011 revenues of $2.3 billion, includes The New York Times, the International Herald Tribune, The Boston Globe, NYTimes.com , BostonGlobe.com , Boston.com , and related properties. The Company’s core purpose is to enhance society by creating, collecting and distributing high-quality news, information and entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Interactive News Developer Opening&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York Times is seeking an experienced front-end multimedia developer to join its newsroom interactive team. This person will be expected to work with reporters, editors, producers and software developers to develop and support online storytelling tools such as our photo viewers, galleries and interactive timelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Interactive News team operates like a startup within a large media company, which means that, as a front-end multimedia developer, this person will have an extraordinary amount of creative freedom to explore new ways of presenting the news and the stories behind the news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The job requires solid coding skills and the ability to execute. Also critical is attention to detail, a pride in the quality of one&amp;rsquo;s work and the ability to meet news deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary commensurate with experience. This is an excluded position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert-level understanding of standards-driven CSS, HTML and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with photography, video and/or gaming platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive cross-browser and cross-device development experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with mobile development, including responsive design and touch capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of the principles of web accessibility and user-centered design/development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Ruby, Python or MySQL is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Internal and external applicants should send resumes to aron@nytimes.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York Times Company is an equal employment opportunity employer, and does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, gender, sexual orientation, marital status, age, disability, national origin, citizenship or any other protected characteristic. The New York Times Company is committed to diversity in its most inclusive sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Job Segments: Photography, Developer, Web Design, Programmer, Information Technology, Creative, Technology&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-developer-the-new-york-times-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-developer-the-new-york-times-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at 2U in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;2U is changing the way great students and great universities think about online higher education. Founded by a unique team of education veterans, 2U, Inc. is a private company that partners with preeminent institutions of higher education to deliver rigorous, selective degree programs online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We supply universities with the tools, expertise, and global recruiting needed to compete in a space currently dominated by unexceptional programs. 2U develops state-of-the-art technology platforms that enhance traditional offline curricula, while also providing key logistical components, including comprehensive student support services from enrollment through graduation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What We’re Looking For&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2U is looking for a rockstar front-end developer with a strong PHP background and Wordpress experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Front-End Developer will develop and maintain new and existing Wordpress websites and landing pages. The developer will work closely with a project manager to meet a series of critical deadlines.  On-going work may include custom HTML tabs for Facebook, and other marketing-related initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Things That Should Be in Your Background&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of Wordpress development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of Wordpress/Custom Theme Development/Plugins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong PHP and MySQL experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version control systems (Git preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appreciation of good design/UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Attributes That Will Help You in This Role&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player with a “can do” attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented, ability to prioritize efficiently and multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a diverse team in a fast-paced, entrepreneurial environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think out of the box and find creative, unorthodox solutions when needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness and interest in new marketing trends and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2008 by a unique team of education veterans with unparalleled experience, 2U, Inc., formerly known as 2tor, Inc., partners with preeminent institutions of higher education to deliver rigorous, selective degree programs online to students globally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2U supplies universities with the tools, expertise, capital, and global recruiting needed to build and support programs of quality and scale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology:&lt;/strong&gt; 2U develops state-of-the-art technology platforms that give universities the ability to deliver traditional offline curricula in a unique online learning environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructional Design:&lt;/strong&gt; Our instructional designers work closely with faculty to translate classroom courses into a compelling combination of synchronous and asynchronous online and real-world experiences, using the best educational and social technologies available. We work side-by-side with professors to evolve those courses.  We make improvements as usage and learning patterns emerge and new technologies become available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infrastructure:&lt;/strong&gt; 2U provides the support infrastructure and the logistical components of our partners’ online programs.  This includes comprehensive student support services from enrollment through graduation and beyond, as well as practical learning experiences in communities around the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources:&lt;/strong&gt; 2U makes an upfront investment of over $10 million in each of our partner programs.  By supplying capital and global marketing capabilities, we enable universities to give high-performing students around the world a transformational educational experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Since our founding, 2U has partnered with some of the most prestigious research universities to deliver groundbreaking online degree programs.   You can read about our partners here (www.2U.com/partners).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And if you’re ready to help our team (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.2U.com/team&quot;&gt;http://www.2U.com/team&lt;/a&gt;) build the next great movement in higher education, consider joining us (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.2U.com/careers&quot;&gt;http://www.2U.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why It’s Great to Join Our Team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of reasons, but here are a few:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Benefits – at 2U we offer a great benefits package including medical, dental, vision, life insurance, disability and 401k.  We also offer paid time off and company holidays.  That’s not all!  Admissions Counselors receive a 100% paid tuition benefit for themselves, their spouse and their legal dependants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Culture – We are a highly energetic, innovative start-up company with room to grow.  We don’t take ourselves too seriously, and strive to maintain a casual, professional and highly productive work environment for our team.  2U employees enjoy many perks, including the ability to wear jeans to work every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note:  The above statements are intended to describe the general nature and level of work performed by individuals assigned to this position. They are not intended to be construed as an exhaustive list of all responsibilities, duties, and skills required.  All employees may be required to perform duties outside of their normal responsibilities from time-to-time, as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2U is an equal opportunity employer that does not discriminate against applicants or employees and ensures equal employment opportunity for all persons regardless of their race, creed, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, national origin, age, marital status, disability, citizenship, military or veterans' status, or any other classifications protected by applicable federal, state or local laws. 2U’s equal opportunity policy applies to all terms and conditions of employment, including but not limited to recruiting, hiring, training, promotion, job benefits, pay, and dismissal.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-2u-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-2u-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interface Developer at AREA 17 in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We seek an Interface (front-end) Developer with a strong web portfolio that includes high traffic websites. The candidate must write clean, efficient and semantic code with a keen eye for pixel accuracy and a hardcore desire to implement tight designs. Most of the work we do requires advanced JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is passionate about the web and is (or aims to be) a respected contributor to the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: AREA 17 focuses solely on user-centered websites and platforms. We have little expertise in Flash and/or advertising/marketing campaigns. We appreciate and respect your experience in that domain, however we will only consider candidates that have experience in our domain of expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status – Full-time with benefits (or Freelance if necessary)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reports to – Technical Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary – Based on experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Application Integration (RoR, PHP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and Experimentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spec Writing and Documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience developing for the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of semantic HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to code cross-browser/platform gracefully&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respect of industry-accepted standards, specifications and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn new interface techniques as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to code iPhone and mobile-capable websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of RoR, PHP and related frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Flash, Flex, ActionScripting, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of server environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of JavaScript tempting engines (Mustache, Dust.js)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Canvas, SVG and building responsive websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Would be nice if you also did:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iPhone, iPad and Android app development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some backend development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Application Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover-letter with salary history or requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PDF Resume/CV with online portfolio or work examples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code examples will be later required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To apply for this job, we first ask you to send us a thoughtful cover-letter stating your intentions and a link to your portfolio, CV and/or work examples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NO RECRUITERS PLEASE&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interface-developer-area-17-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interface-developer-area-17-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at EXPO in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Profile&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right in the heart of Silicon Alley, EXPO is one of the success stories in New York&amp;rsquo;s booming start-up scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EXPO is a leading video commerce platform generating and distributing authentic consumer video for the world&amp;rsquo;s premier manufacturers and retailers. EXPO&amp;rsquo;s video community has built the largest catalog of product videos with over 300,000 user-generated product reviews covering electronics, home, parenting, and consumer packaged goods. The company provides manufacturers including Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, Colgate, Kraft, Philips, and LG Electronics with fresh, authentic videos and also distributes the informative video content to high-impact digital points of purchase. EXPO&amp;rsquo;s turn-key ecommerce syndication network has delivered over 40 million video views for leading sites such as Amazon.com, Walmart, Sears.com, and drugstore.com, social media sites such as Facebook and YouTube, manufacturer brand sites, and at www.expotv.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a fast-growing, venture capital-backed company based in Flatiron, and a great place for top talent to do their best work. We are looking to add a smart, creative, and experienced front-end coder to our development team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will be able to work on tight deadlines and keep up with our fast paced, ever-growing environment. You will work closely with product managers, backend developers and designers and should have strong communication skills. You will produce cross-browser, standards-compliant, front-end code (HTML, JavaScript, Ajax, CSS, etc.) to ensure that the user interface for our applications remains consistent across multiple platforms and browsers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills and Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience creating hand-coded, semantic (table-less) XHTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full understanding of CSS/CSS2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of browser capabilities and design constraints on the web, with expertise in developing and testing across multiple browsers and platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years experience in hand coding efficient, unobtrusive Javascript code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of DOM manipulation and AJAX/JSON/XML protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of various Javascript frameworks, particularly jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to convert graphic designs from PSD or vector graphics formats to efficient and standards-compliant HTML/CSS files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using versioning systems like SVN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Adobe Photoshop and image optimization techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for producing clean, standards-based semantic mark-up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for researching and learning emerging web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently, as well as in a team-oriented environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated and not afraid to ask questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferable Job Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic PHP and/or Smarty templating engine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Flash and Actionscript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Google Analytics or other web analytics systems (Omniture, CoreMetrics, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest and knowledge in HTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To apply, please email jobs@expotv.com with the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code samples or link to portfolio site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-expo-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-expo-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer – Web Application at GlobalLogic, Inc. in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a front-end developer to work on a large-scale web application in the TV space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal developer is highly skilled in JavaScript single-page web application development. The developer will work on-site in and will be required to periodically travel to the client site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under limited direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing single-page web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical expertise in JavaScript, CSS and HTML5 development with consideration for responsive web design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of objected-oriented analysis and design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of common software design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile/Scrum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript MVC frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AMD or commonJS modules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript test frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Sass CSS preprocessor and Compass CSS authoring framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with UNIX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decompose visual design comps into functional components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Prefered&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years developing single page web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Backbone.js in a large scale single page web application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience profiling and tuning JavaScript and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of JavaScript design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Mocha, Chai and Sinon JavaScript test frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-web-application-globallogic-inc-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-web-application-globallogic-inc-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Front-End UI / UX Developer at AOL in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The mission of AOL Technologies is to drive innovation, technical excellence and the best experiences to our 250 million customers every day. We succeed when our customers get the best products and services, and our teams get energized and have fun delivering value and top-notch performance to each and every one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AOL Services focuses on curating the best content, products, and services mirrored to real human behavior – what people need to make their digital lives as convenient as possible. We create an integrated experience that allows AOL consumers to feel like valued AOL Members, gaining access to the most useful content from some of the best brands, communication tools, and valuable services. Whether through communication products like AOL Mail and AIM, our mobile services, or our subscription packages, AOL Services is pivotal in driving traffic and user engagement across the AOL network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AOL Services engineering team builds and supports the applications and services we use at AOL to deliver features like Mail, AIM, Access and Commerce across all platforms (mobile, desktop, and web). We build the tools, frameworks and services that let people safely and securely access content and applications online.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-ui-ux-developer-aol-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-front-end-ui-ux-developer-aol-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-end Developer at Harvest in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The role that JavaScript plays at Harvest is growing every day. You&amp;rsquo;ll join our front-end team in solving problems, building new features and making Harvest better and better. If you have experience with a nimble team where things progress rapidly then you&amp;rsquo;ll feel right at home at Harvest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harvest is a distributed team. We have a lovely big office in New York City, but team members live all over the USA, Canada and Europe. Wherever you currently live, that&amp;rsquo;s where we want you to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did we mention a sense of humor yet? It&amp;rsquo;s important, we like to have fun while we work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who You Are&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have unrivaled attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You believe it&amp;rsquo;s worth doing some extra work to make life easier on the customer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You like writing CoffeeScript, but can write vanilla js without breaking a sweat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are familiar with Backbone and Ember and have an opion on what makes them good/bad/meh. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve even built projects in both.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know that performance is king and have optimized your code for a wide range of browsers and platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You write code in a modular, reusable fashion. Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve released open source code that demonstrates these qualities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You believe that a task is not complete until a test is written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;A Sample of Tasks and Projects You Might Work On&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new Harvest features and improve existing components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a select box plugin for use in Harvest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a cross-platform framework to support the mobile web component of Harvest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a state manager for CSS media queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please make sure you fit the descriptions above (see the brain!). You must be authorized to work in the United States (unless you intend to work remotely from your home country).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email us at careers@getharvest.com with the subject &amp;ldquo;Harvest Front-end Developer.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell us why you want to work with us, and why you&amp;rsquo;d make a good fit here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give us your thoughts on the eternal JavaScript debate: semicolons &amp;ndash; yes or no?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-harvest-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-harvest-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Web Developer at Downtown Community Television Center in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1972, DCTV is a 15-time Emmy Award winning, Academy Award nominated media arts center that fosters independent voices by providing professional media training and state-of-the-industry resources, and by creating and exhibiting outstanding documentary film productions, with the belief that diversity of expression strengthens our democracy and enhances civil society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DCTV is seeking a part-time junior web developer to work 16 hours/week. This position will report to DCTV&amp;rsquo;s website manager to assist with the development and maintenance of dctvny.org and other online projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities &amp;amp; Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform weekly HTML updates to our email blast templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add, update, and remove content from DCTV&amp;rsquo;s website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resolve technical issues through research and debugging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research, recommend, implement new website features and functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform other related duties or special projects as requested&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree and minimum of 2 years of web development experience in a professional work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PHP, MySQL, and Content Management Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Drupal is a major bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have an understanding of web standards and cross-browser compatibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe CS4 Creative Suite (Photoshop and Illustrator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated, organized, detail-oriented, creative problem-solver, team-player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in and familiarity with web analytics, SEO, and user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Details:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compensation: $18/hour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Part-Time Permanent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;DCTV is a 501 &amp;copy; 3 non-for-profit organization. DCTV is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For consideration please submit a cover letter and resume (HTML, Word, or PDF) to employment@dctvny.org. Please also include contact information for two references. Links to examples of your work online are appreciated. No phone calls please. We thank all applicants for their interest, but only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-developer-downtown-community-television-center-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-developer-downtown-community-television-center-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>