<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at App Partner Development in Brooklyn, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Here at App Partner, we originally focused our efforts on iOS development, but have finally made our long anticipated push into Android mobile app development and are currently looking for talented Android Developers to fill our ranks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like to create games, social networking apps, productivity apps, or anything Android-based and want to be with like-minded peers on the frontlines of the Android revolution, then this is the place for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why Pursue a Career in App Development at App Partner?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides being one of the hottest career fields in America, pursuing a job in app development at App Partner has a multitude of benefits that you can’t find anywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’re a young, diverse, and close-knit team based in the urban jungle of New York City while living the Silicon Valley dream. You can have it all!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you work at App Partner, you don’t climb the corporate ladder- you help build it. If you don’t believe us, ask our HR Director what position he started in when you meet him!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most importantly, when you have a job in mobile application development at App Partner, you have the opportunity to work on challenging and rewarding projects in an emerging field while learning the tricks of the trade from our seasoned vets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are constantly growing, so if you are interested in joining our team of New York app developers, designers, and artists who do some of the most interesting and edifying work in this burgeoning field, take a look at our open positions!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-app-partner-development-brooklyn-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-app-partner-development-brooklyn-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile Web Developer at Paperless Post in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an exceptional Mobile Web Developer to join our new mobile team. In this role you will work closely with our Product and Mobile team to help us shape, design, and build the mobile Paperless Post experience for our mobile customers across a variety of mobile devices, and browsers. This role is a great fit for an experienced web developer who is looking to move into the mobile space. You will tackle design and software architecture challenges as you make the rich Paperless Post web experience live on mobile browsers. The ideal candidate is an excellent programmer, user-focused, and passionate about the mobile opportunities for Paperless Post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop our mobile web application throughout the product lifecycle: code architecture, feature implementation, integration, and code verification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve complex technical problems under system constraints such as performance, form factors, and data service availability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and participate in code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the product, design, QA, and support teams to understand product requirements prior to implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure continuous high product quality through code testing, bug fixing, and feature changes based on consumers feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years of experience developing for web/mobile web platforms in JavaScript, HTML, CSS (Ruby, Ruby on Rails a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. / B.A. in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative with excellent problem solving and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for product quality and attention to details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a team player and effective collaborator with excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coding for multiple mobile platforms (Android, BlackBerry, Windows) is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send your resume to mobile_webdev@paperlesspost.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-developer-paperless-post-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-web-developer-paperless-post-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Custom Media Labs in Greece, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Required skillset:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;iOS, XCode, UlKit, Cocoa Touch, XML/JSON, iPhone/iPad Apps, fluent in English&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What skills are needed to apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Oriented Programming, with XCode, UIKit, latest SDK versions, Cocoa Touch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of Apple Human Interface guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working XML/JSON and familiarity with REST/SOAP methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with using server side services/web services; Maps, GPS services for iOS apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having strong knowledge/experience in iOS domain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In depth understanding of software development lifecycle and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage time and competing deadlines effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additionally:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of iOS development experience (iPhone/iPad)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding and experience querying against relational databases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Apple Push Notification Services, Foundation Framework and Memory Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in provisioning and publishing apps in iTunes/App Store with working knowledge of Apple Publishing Procedures and App review Process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in creating custom design interface elements from a Photoshop template file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using OpenGL in development and proficient in 3D programming (would be a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Cocos2D/Cocos3D would be a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Custom Media Labs&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a full-service agency that helps businesses thrive in a digital world. Our core DNA is digital, but we deliver strong brand solutions in every medium. We understand that to change the world, you need to inspire people. That’s why everything we do is human-centric: our ideas, our team, and our approach. customedialabs has offices in North America and Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please include a small description of yourself and a quick overview of your skills.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-custom-media-labs-greece-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-custom-media-labs-greece-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Principal iOS Developer at Razorfish Healthware in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Razorfish Healthware is a key partner for health and wellness companies who want to grow their business by engaging with and improving the lives of their customers.  With a focus on creating brand experiences that build our clients’ business, we leverage our unique mix of insight, technology, creativity, and industry savvy to transform the health and wellness community so that our clients can build healthy relationships that last. Headquartered in Philadelphia, Razorfish Healthware is a brand of Razorfish, and a member of the Paris-based Publicis Groupe S.A. the world’s third largest communications group, second largest media counsel and buying group, and a global leader in digital and healthcare communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re the Technology department of Razorfish Health, part of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest interactive agency. The only technology that’s relevant to us is the one we haven’t seen yet. We are seeking an entrepreneurial Senior Developer who prefers big ideas to best in class. We’re not all the way there yet, care to help?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Principal Developer supports the design and implementation of next generation mobile sites and applications. This position will require an experienced application designer, capable of leading a small development team. Individuals must demonstrate success and experience in each of the phases of software development; including requirements, design, coding and implementation, test and maintenance. Experience as a team leader supporting the design and coding of larger projects and systems integrations is also appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead a team of Developers in the design and coding phases of a software development project while functioning as the escalation or focal point to resolve technical obstacles to project completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide state of the art expertise in development technologies and coding languages; mentoring team members as may be necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide team leadership by assigning, monitoring and ensuring coding is addresses functional requirements and is compliant with any appropriate coding principles or standards to ensure delivery within project timeframes and budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in meetings with staff, team members, and other project stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in software development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical team leadership experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with project management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with web supporting technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to lead a team of 2 to 5 delivering development projects within schedule and costs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to serve as an escalation point of internal technical obstacles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise within the iOS Framework is important as well as full exposure to the software development life cycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience with key iOS concepts – core data, view controllers, ARC, storyboards, xib, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of deploying an app to the App Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong skills with the Objective-C programming language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated expertise in object oriented design and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the software requirements and development lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working with geographically disparate teams – onshore, near-shore and off-shore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated success in application design, inter-communication and coding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of software testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communications skills (both written and oral)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Droid, Blackberry, Windows Mobile a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with platforms such as PhoneGap and Appcelerator is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. or M.S in Computer Science or a related degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years success delivering software design and development projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience as team leader of a software development project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years developing mobile application including iOS apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-ios-developer-razorfish-healthware-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-ios-developer-razorfish-healthware-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>