<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Raretec Consulting in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities and essential functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of user interface and usability best-practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective problem solving skills, and the ability to follow a methodical implementation process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate with clients and gather technical requirements, if required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of Cocoa Touch and other iOS frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS is Computer Science or similar degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iPhone / iPad development, including implementing applications with standard UI components, creating custom UI components, connecting applications to back end services [HTTP and XML processing in the IOS application environment ]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XHTML/HTML, JavaScript, CSS, XML or other web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C or C++&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Objective-C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge with XCode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database / SQL experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using version control software in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-raretec-consulting-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-raretec-consulting-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Designer-Mobile Web or APP at Initiative in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Ansible is seeking a senior designer with 5+ years experience in digital design, preferably mobile web and app. The Senior Designer is a very senior level creative talent who has a good technical understanding, and is adept at translating business objectives to mobile interactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with the Creative Director to ensure that various aspects of design work meet both Ansible and clients’ expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept and design innovative, usable, technically feasible designs for our mobile website and application projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze and evaluate current front-end design/usability challenges and implement effective design solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with deliverables across the entire design lifecycle including, but not limited to: site maps, page flows, wireframes, prototypes, full screen comps, and asset delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work across a range of design needs including icons, layouts, templates, and navigation components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This candidate must be highly self-motivated, comfortable in fast-paced advertising environment and familiar with technical aspects of mobile site design, information architecture, and user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of fundamental design disciplines and principals and experience with typography, composition, and color&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Adobe Creative Suite applications including, Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Fireworks, Indesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advertising background and agency experience is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, XML/XSL is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of internet best practices including the web and the mobile web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven team player with the ability to work under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work independently with little direction and can own a project from beginning to end&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to present designs to clients and partners, address feedback, and set appropriate expectations with the tea&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-mobile-web-or-app-initiative-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-mobile-web-or-app-initiative-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Project Manager at Moving Interactive in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Moving Interactive is a fast growing interactive agency seeking a Sr. Project Manager to manage and successfully deliver high profile creative front-end projects. The Sr. Project Manager will provide strategic insight and direction into developing innovative solutions for our clients. The Sr. Project Manager will lead the project team to accurately delivery clients’ needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving Interactive is a consulting and product design firm that works with leading and emerging media brands on the development and launch of capabilities to maximize the opportunities of the digital age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 7 years of related experience in managing multiphased, complex front-end projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successfully delivered digital marketing and technology solutions on large sized projects through the entire lifecycle, with experience in a consulting environment highly preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to manage strategic projects with Fortune 500 clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading and motivating a cross-functional project team within budget and schedule constraints while exceeding client&amp;rsquo;s expectations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced multiple full-project lifecycles from business development to final delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to craft and define a strategic business solution based on broad client goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of web development including strategies, design, implementation, and user adoption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise knowledge of Project Management principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Microsoft Project and/or other standard project planning tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using software development lifecycle and agile development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree required, MBA / Master&amp;rsquo;s degree preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;With a team of over 100 professionals on four continents, Moving Interactive works with some of the worlds leading media brands such as Readers Digest, Conde Nast, Moodys and Bloomberg on the launch of their new digital products. Moving Interactive also provides platforms to accelerate the creation of social applications, websites and mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-moving-interactive-new-year-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-project-manager-moving-interactive-new-year-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior iOS Developer at Roundarch Isobar in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will be able to architect, develop and debug parts of, or complete apps utilizing Apple’s iOS SDK.  The candidate may need to take lead on projects and delegate tasks to other developers on the team.  They will be required to solve problems and assist in debugging issues with other developers.  Will need to estimate overall timelines and risks to management as well as participate in design meetings to speak to the feasibility of design requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The candidate will be responsible to see that the projects assigned to them are completed on time and as designed.  They will be required to spot problems and bring them to management’s attention as soon as possible.  They must be able to interact with other disciplines (creative, backend services, etc) and developers to clearly specify when required elements are due in order to deliver on schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Experience / Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the current version of the iOS SDK with at least two apps in the App Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with standard iOS interface components such as table views, navigation controllers, various button and control types, etc. as well as creating custom interface elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Core graphics and Core animations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete understanding of Cocoa programing methodologies and memory management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Interface Builder with at least one app created using Interface Builder as the primary UI tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with web services with either json or xml formatted return data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of block and/or multi-threaded based programing concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with source control systems such as svn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in software development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice to Have&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Apple’s enterprise developer accounts and ad-hoc distribution on standard developer accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AV media frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with networking frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Objective-C blocks and/or multi-threaded apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SQL based database systems and/or Core data technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-roundarch-isobar-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-roundarch-isobar-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Cocoa/Cocoa Touch Developer for iOS and OSX at Krossover in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Krossover is a cutting edge company bringing stats and analytics to the world of sports.  Think Moneyball meets Friday Night Lights.  We build and deliver digital products, games and services for coaches, athletes and fans at all levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an experienced developer to work on our iOS and OSX apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work in a small, agile team where everyone is involved from initial whiteboarding to launch.  It&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, and everyone has to wear different hats from time to time.  So if you want a job where you can get involved and see the difference you&amp;rsquo;ve made on the final product, keep reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements &amp;amp; Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven development experience of iOS apps (iPhone and iPad).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven development experience of Mac OSX apps (Lion and above).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing using Objective-C, C, and C++&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using the following frameworks and components:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AVFoundation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JSON serialization and deserialization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NSURL, NSURLConnection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Animation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Graphics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quartz2D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ARC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blocks and Grand Central Dispatch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StoreKit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push Notifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Science STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics) degree or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills (oral and written)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using a modern version control system (git, mercurial, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/cocoa-cocoa-touch-developer-for-ios-and-osx-krossover-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/cocoa-cocoa-touch-developer-for-ios-and-osx-krossover-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web / Mobile Producer at Syracuse Media Group in Syracuse, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This position offers you the opportunity to play a leading role in the syracuse.com newsroom and be part of an exciting initiative to form a sustainable digital news operation. As Web Mobile Producer and SEO Specialist, you will work to monitor the flow of content on syracuse.com. You&amp;rsquo;ll proactively highlight the best of the best, making changes to the website as breaking stories evolve and develop. If you’re versatile and have strong news judgment as well as an interest in local sports and entertainment, or someone who has already found success in the digital world, this is a prime opportunity to take an exciting step in your career. You&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy thinking outside of the traditional news box in order to make a direct and immediate impact on your audience. If you like the idea of being empowered to determine news placement on the website, working in a collaborative news environment and influencing the daily operation of your workplace, consider using your talents to build a cutting-edge career with Syracuse Media Group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;To be a good fit for the position of Web Mobile Producer, you will need to have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in journalism, communications or a related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of one to two years of journalism experience with a proven ability in reporting and writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience building, maintaining and engaging an active audience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of search engine optimization (SEO) practices and familiarity with Google trends, insights and other SEO tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using social media to source and promote content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with basic HTML or equivalent web language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent visual/design instincts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work independently under deadline pressure and prioritize tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click the &amp;ldquo;Apply&amp;rdquo; button for further details&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Syracuse Media Group is a digitally focused news and information company serving Central New York. Syracuse Media Group publishes and operates an extensive portfolio of digital and print products featuring comprehensive in-depth content from Central New York&amp;rsquo;s largest news organization. Syracuse Media Group&amp;rsquo;s flagship brands are syracuse.com, the leading website in the region and The Post-Standard newspaper which has served the community since 1829.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Syracuse Media Group is an Equal Opportunity Employer and does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, gender, national origin, age, physical or mental impairment, sexual orientation or any other category protected under federal, state or local law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Syracuse Media Group endeavors to make syracuse.com accessible to any and all users. If you would like to contact us regarding the accessibility of our website or need assistance completing the application process, please contact thawkins@dtoolbox.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-mobile-producer-syracuse-media-group-syracuse-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-mobile-producer-syracuse-media-group-syracuse-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at IBM in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;IBM Global Business Services &amp;ndash; Help Make the World Work Smarter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is getting smarter, triggering unprecedented change. IBM&amp;rsquo;s unparalleled ability to bring together deep business insight, advanced research, analytics, and technology enables IBM Global Business Services to help position its clients for the future. We leverage the proven roadmaps and frameworks that have been developed across 17 industries and the unique combination of skills and experiences of our teams in over 170 countries &amp;ndash; unmatched capabilities. When you join IBM, you&amp;rsquo;ll partner with our clients, and leverage these capabilities to deliver real business value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a member of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading and largest consulting organization, you&amp;rsquo;ll tap into resources that only a global leader like IBM can provide: access to a vast and diverse network of talented professionals; enjoy unparalleled career opportunities; be provided with ongoing training and education that you&amp;rsquo;ll need to succeed; and work on some of the most interesting projects on the planet, helping everyone from organizations to local governments, work smarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Objective C iOS developer to participate in the design and development of highly interactive iPhone and iPad projects for high profile projects. This position requires well-rounded development skills with strong front end development experience including HTML and the Apple iPhone SDK. This position also requires light system adminstration skills and experience with HTTP and messaging technologies. The ideal candidate will have iOS development experience in high profile interactive projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When working with other key stakeholders the candidate should be able to articulate deeply technical concepts in a customer friendly and understandable way. This would involve being able to assist with project managers, designers and information architects in scoping and pricing front end applications as well as working with a team of developers during the build, test and deployment phases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;People Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The candidate should have experience working with a variety of clients at all levels of an organization as well as a level of comfort presenting their work in workshops and client meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has developed relationships of mutual trust with people inside and outside of their organization based on respect, integrity, positive regard and an appreciation of the uniqueness of the individual.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position requires 75% travel. Valid passport to travel outside United States required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information on our world-class Application Innovation solutions and services, please visit: http://www-935.ibm.com/services/us/gbs/ais/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also expected that newly hired resources into the Global Business Services U.S. practice live within a reasonable commuting distance (generally 50 miles) of the following cities: Atlanta, GA; Boston, MA; Charlotte, NC; Chicago, IL; Cincinnati, OH; Columbus, OH; Cleveland, OH; Dallas, TX; Denver, CO; Detroit, MI; Hartford, CT; Houston, TX; Kansas City, MO; Los Angeles, CA; Miami, FL; New York City, NY and surrounding area; Philadelphia, PA; San Francisco, CA; and Washington, DC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help Build A Smarter Planet.
Visit ibm.com/start/consulting to learn more. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ibm.com/start/consulting/ais&quot;&gt;http://www.ibm.com/start/consulting/ais&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years experience in mobile development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years experience in Internet Industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years experience in HTML, JavaScript (including jQuery) and CSS development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge in Apple iOS development in Apple iPhone SDK for iPhone and/or iPad apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Readiness to travel Up to 4 days a week (home on weekends-based on project requirements)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English: Fluent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years experience in mobile development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years experience in Internet Industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years experience in Experience in full application lifecycle with UI integration from PhotoShop and Visio assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years experience in Apple iOS development in Apple iPhone SDK for iPhone and/or iPad apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge in Experience with standard LAMP stack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge in Familiarity with Apple HTTP Live Streaming for live video streaming (Apple HLS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge in Omniture and/or Flurry analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge in CDN networks including Akamai Media delivery, Akamai configuration and Akamai NetStorage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;French : Basic knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;IBM is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, disability, age, or veteran status.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-ibm-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-ibm-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at 9mmedia in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Love what you do? So do we, which is why 9mmedia has been building amazing things for over 10 years now. We mostly work with startups, and our culture mostly resembles a startup &amp;ndash; well, only the good parts, that is. We are a group of 20ish passionate, smart, nice, fun people who all love working together in our gorgeous NYC office. We’ve worked hard to create an inspiring space and culture that combines the best of both worlds &amp;ndash; the interesting technological challenges and excitement of a startup, and the stability and comfort of a lifestyle business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our clients are our partners, so if you like being an integral part of developing and starting businesses, you’ll love how we operate. We have a small handful of projects going at any given time, and you’ll get the opportunity to work on many projects over the years, each with its own unique challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If all that sounds good, we’d love to hear from you! We believe in giving all developers a lot of responsibility and control over what they do, and in treating people with trust and respect. We have no middle management, and you can make your own hours &amp;ndash; and no, that isn’t code for us expecting you to be in the office 24/7. We only care about people who can work hard, produce great apps, and get things done. You’ll get to learn lots of new technology, enhance your skills, and have a ton of influence over every product you touch here. We are looking for the sort of person who will speak up to help improve not only our products, but also our process, our technology and our company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a great iOS developer you already know what we’re looking for, but one must observe the forms:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid command of the iOS SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cocoa / Objective-C proficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Example code or working iOS app we can evaluate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-9mmedia-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-9mmedia-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead iOS Developer at ShowMe in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;An iOS developer with experience building beautiful, robust, and innovative apps. You must be not only technically proficient but also have a strong eye for UI design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT US&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ShowMe was started by a couple guys who wanted to change the way people learn. Today we have hundreds of thousands of users, and have received funding from an amazing group of investors (TechCrunch coverage).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work at General Assembly, the heart of the NYC startup scene, where we interact with entrepreneurs, investors, creatives, and other awesome people on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;SUMMARY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ShowMe&amp;rsquo;s iPad app has received tons of praise for its design and innovative functionality. But we&amp;rsquo;re just getting started. The next phase of our app development will marry content production with content discovery, while further simplifying user experience. If you&amp;rsquo;re up for the challenge, send us the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examples of projects you&amp;rsquo;ve worked on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Compensation is extremely competitive, and includes weekly happy hour drinks and the occasional free lunch. If you’re not in NYC, we’re willing to help get you out here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-ios-developer-showme-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-ios-developer-showme-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at App Partner Development in Brooklyn, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Min. Experience: Student (College)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here at App Partner, we originally focused our efforts on iOS development, but have finally made our long anticipated push into Android mobile app development and are currently looking for talented Android Developers to fill our ranks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like to create games, social networking apps, productivity apps, or anything Android-based and want to be with like-minded peers on the frontlines of the Android revolution, then this is the place for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why Pursue a Career in App Development at App Partner?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides being one of the hottest career fields in America, pursuing a job in app development at App Partner has a multitude of benefits that you can’t find anywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’re a young, diverse, and close-knit team based in the urban jungle of New York City while living the Silicon Valley dream. You can have it all!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you work at App Partner, you don’t climb the corporate ladder- you help build it. If you don’t believe us, ask our HR Director what position he started in when you meet him!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most importantly, when you have a job in mobile application development at App Partner, you have the opportunity to work on challenging and rewarding projects in an emerging field while learning the tricks of the trade from our seasoned vets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are constantly growing, so if you are interested in joining our team of New York app developers, designers, and artists who do some of the most interesting and edifying work in this burgeoning field, take a look at our open positions!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-app-partner-development-brooklyn-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-app-partner-development-brooklyn-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>