<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ny-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>IT Helpdesk Support Specialist at Edelman in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The candidate will provide Level 2 IT assistance to users in accessing and using computer systems and business applications. Will respond to and diagnose IT problems through a variety of means, such as phone, desk-side support or remote control technology. The candidate will conduct problem identification, research, isolation, resolution, and follow-up assuring the timely closeout of trouble tickets in the ticketing system. The candidate will coordinate additional support as needed to ensure problem resolution, customer satisfaction and quality assurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Record all IT requests and input problem information into ticketing system, focusing on first call resolution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot virus-related issues on end-user computers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Escalate/assign tickets as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install and troubleshoot minor hardware &amp;amp; software malfunctions  and correct them as directed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform password resets, disable user/computer accounts, group membership changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Image, configure, and deploy Mac and Windows computer equipment with required items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deploy office phone equipment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with office moves as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform root cause analysis on issues to prevent recurring issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep peers and management informed of trends, significant problems, and unexpected delays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add to IT knowledge-base as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop training documentation/user guides for common user issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setup and support audio/video equipment as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support web conferencing as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide basic smart phone support (iOS, Windows, Android, BlackBerry)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain knowledge of the principles, methods, and techniques used in information system troubleshooting and support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and exceptional organizational skills are a must for this task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resolve network related issues (internet connectivity, printers).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage user accounts through Active Directory (unlock account, password reset, update information)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote into user&amp;rsquo;s workstation to troubleshoot issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform hardware evaluations and make recommendations based on evaluations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure Service Level Agreement (SLA) scores are being met in all areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance and work leadership to less-experienced technicians&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in special projects as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After-hours support may be required occasionally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent customer service, interpersonal, oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years’ experience supporting Windows 7, Mac OS, MS Office, internet browsers , LAN connectivity and network printing in large environment is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience in relevant dedicated help desk customer support environment is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated troubleshooting skills for complex technical issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic administration of users in Active Directory and Exchange 2010&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to plan, organize and track tasks for team and self&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to quickly understand and solve customer issues using customer service best practices while maintaining a positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individual should be able to multi-task and establish priorities and have a genuine eagerness to learn new concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and organizational skills are required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inventory management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Edelman:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edelman is the world’s largest public relations firm, with 66 offices and more than 4,500 employees worldwide, as well as affiliates in more than 30 cities. Edelman was named Advertising Age’s top-ranked PR firm of the decade in 2009 and one of its “A-List Agencies” in both 2010 and 2011; Adweek’s “2011 PR Agency of the Year;” PRWeek’s “2011 Large PR Agency of the Year;” and The Holmes Report’s “2011 Global Agency of the Year” and its 2012 “Digital Agency of the Year.” Edelman was named one of the “Best Places to Work” by Advertising Age in 2010 and 2012 and among Glassdoor’s top ten “Best Places to Work” in 2011 and 2012. Edelman owns specialty firms Edelman Berland (research), Blue (advertising), A&amp;amp;R Edelman (technology), BioScience Communications (medical communications), and agencies Edelman Significa (Brazil), and Pegasus (China). Visit http://www.edelman.com for more information. Edelman is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/it-helpdesk-support-specialist-edelman-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/it-helpdesk-support-specialist-edelman-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Product Support Specialist at Canon USA in Babylon, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;For the technical support professional possessing customer focus, professional communication skills and a drive to continuously improve cutting-edge technology, this is the perfect opportunity to join NT-ware, a subsidiary of Canon USA, a provider of a full range of software and hardware solutions for the document imaging industry.  This highly visible position provides you a variety of responsibilities in product support and quality management, and will put you in a prime position to help us continue to grow the NT-ware brand in the U.S. market.  Take this chance to join a smart, fast paced and dynamic company where you will experience autonomy while you accelerate your career with hard work and excellent customer-focused service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join an exciting opportunity with one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most successful global brands. NT-ware, headquartered in Bad Iburg, Germany, a subsidiary of Canon Europe Ltd., NT-ware provides a full range of soft- and hardware solutions, based on the latest technologies, to manage and control all printing and copying processes. Our organization not only delivers printer management functionalities like printer accounting, copy accounting, and secure printing, but also production printing features like print room management, job ticketing, web submission and production management. It is our goal to help our customers increase their productivity, reduce costs, and optimize their print/scan workflows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our main  product, uniFLOW, NT-ware has entered in a strategic partnership with Canon USA Inc. This position, based in Babylon, NY is in support of the US client base. We are seeking talented IT professionals for our Product Support team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Sr. Product Support Specialist working in our office in Babylon, NY, your primary mission will be to provide customer support and technical product support (3rd level) including quality management, installation support, issue diagnosis, quality assurance, testing and training for our uniFLOW output management product.  After receiving thorough product training you will travel up to 25% of the time to our prospects' sites throughout the United States to assist with product installation and troubleshooting issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possessing strong experience on Microsoft Server, workstation operating systems, networking and SQL Server, as well as a strong understanding of client operating systems such as Windows XP, Windows Vista, Windows 7, Mac OS X, and Linux  will help you simulate and solve high-level customer issues in a lab environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apart from providing product support over the phone and email, you will be tasked with on-site support for strategic customer accounts, particularly in support of installations and technical training.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your ability to analyze network traffic using tools such as Wireshark and Netmon will allow you to hit the ground running.  Crucial to your success will be your ability to work in an autonomous environment and make independent decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is an outstanding role for the tech-savvy professional who enjoys client interaction and is looking for an opportunity to grow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent with a minimum of 7 years of relevant experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-product-support-specialist-canon-usa-babylon-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-product-support-specialist-canon-usa-babylon-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Specialist at Schoology in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Schoology is an award winning learning management platform based in New York City. It’s also one of the fastest growing education technology companies, with more than 2 million users across the world. We are looking for a talented Customer Support Specialist to join our rockstar customer support team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are located in a loft space in midtown NYC and we offer competitive salaries, full benefits, stock options, and an awesome office with a pool table, Pac-Man/Galaga arcade, soda machine with free drinks, and a fully stocked kitchen via weekly FreshDirect grocery deliveries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Customer Support Specialist is a key member of the Support Team, responsible for working with new clients as well as the general user base. By utilizing a strong understanding of product knowhow, you will answer questions, troubleshoot technical issues, and work internally with Schoology teams to address outstanding concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve the frontline of customer service for Schoology’s passionate user base by responding to issues via email, support systems, and phone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tackle basic-to-advanced technical questions as they arise in relation to support tickets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attain a deep understanding of the web-based product and iOS/Android applications, and keep abreast of latest changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the growing knowledge base of feature requests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide on-going, weekly assistance in testing for quality assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with maintenance of Help Center documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with the development of Schoology’s support strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage in overall business operations involving strategy meetings with senior management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The ideal candidate has:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An outgoing personality that resonates over the phone or in email&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to solve technical problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Patience to deal with complex issues and a variety of personalities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivation and desire to help others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Careful attention to details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational and prioritization skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong writing ability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor Degree or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years in a problem-solving environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with customer or technical support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foreign languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salaries + full benefits + generous stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly FreshDirect grocery delivery (full kitchen)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly office happy hour/party&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Private lounge with pool table&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Classic Pac-Man/Galanga machine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coca-Cola fridge stocked with free drinks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awesome co-workers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-schoology-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-specialist-schoology-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Director at Purpose in New York, NY</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Purpose creates 21st century movements. We deploy the collective power of millions of the world’s citizens and consumers to help solve major global problems. To do this, we develop and launch our own technology-driven social and consumer movements from concept to execution, using our model of movement entrepreneurship, and we partner with progressive businesses and existing organizations to create new initiatives at the intersection of mass participation, social innovation and the new economy. As pioneers in the development of cutting-edge techniques for mass digital participation, movement building and self-organization, we have built a rapidly growing business around this increasingly valuable expertise. Our work combines emerging technology with key insights from political organizing, behavioral economics, brand strategy, business strategy and visual and interaction design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Purpose was born out of some of the best-known and most successful recent experiments in mass participation. Our principals are co-founders of Avaaz, the world’s largest online political movement with more than 15 million members operating in 14 languages, and the creators of Australia’s GetUp!, an internationally recognized social movement phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Purpose is looking for a Creative Director who is a senior level problem solver and visionary with a passionate edge for wanting to help solve pressing social and political challenges and lead the creative department at one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most innovative new economy companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a dynamic individual that has the ability to lead and motivate a team with a mix of entrepreneurial drive and collaborative grace. He/She should be a talented manager and a hands-on creative practitioner, who is able to simultaneously internalize both the 30,000 foot strategic overview and the minute executional details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Creative Director is ultimately responsible for the creative output of Purpose, with oversight of the creative team and creative processes; the ideation, presentation and execution of movement branding and campaigns; the profitability and creative quality of client projects, and the operational readiness of the creative team, all in fulfillment of our brand promise to our clients. The role reports to the GM and is based in our downtown Manhattan office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Align the Creative Department’s mission so that the environment, culture, team, capabilities, tools, processes, expectations, work style and other elements support the strategic goals and brand of Purpose&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Strategy Directors and Senior Strategists to deliver strategic communication solutions that help our clients attain their marketing and communications objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With the account lead, assure that internal and client presentations are on time, professional, engaging, persuasive and supported by a sound rationale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assure that timely and informative communication takes place between the creative function and the partners, account team and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that the creative function operates in an efficient, profitable manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that our creative product remains leading edge and ahead of competition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead by example and ensure that the high quality of creative and production is upheld, maintaining consistently high standards for him/herself and others on the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Co-lead the unified creative/account management process in order to execute on client projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate client situation, marketing goals and information into strategic brand concepts, voice, messages and rationales&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the unified process of marketing, concept, design, interactive, web, video, and post-production execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage, mentor, and build a team of talented visual and interaction designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nurture the professional development of the creative team and build and maintain of culture of accountability, teamwork and high standards. Lead accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the evolution of the agency’s technology needs and digital marketing capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10+ years of design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience as a senior and director-level interactive designer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio of branding and interactive projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong conceptual thinker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deeply committed to our mission of building movements to help solve the world’s biggest social and political challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated talent for high-caliber creative concepting and writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to judge creative concepts and copy, and clearly communicate creative direction to others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and significant experience with interactive media production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Both a talented manager and hands-on creative practitioner who exhibits superior leadership and a commitment to collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent client facing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and persuasion skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Naturally entrepreneurial and able to execute visionary creative projects under constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low drama with the highest standards and professionalism and civility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus if you have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A global sensibility, foreign language skills, international policy expertise and/or work experience abroad.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social innovation or movement building experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;When applying, please include a cover letter and a link to your portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-purpose-new-york-ny</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-director-purpose-new-york-ny</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>