<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/oh-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Tween Brands in New Albany, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Tween Brands is a world-class specialty retailer that builds an exciting and powerful connection with our customer through well-defined fashion brands.  We believe we are creating one of the best work experiences in retail.  Tween Brands is a place where people can do great work and live great lives!  Each area in our company plays an important role in the delivery of quality products for tweens (7 thru 14 years of age).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll do:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Creates graphic design aspects of a product line and participates in presenting graphic concepts of the line each season.  Partners with Manager, Graphic Design and Senior Graphic Design to collaborate with the Design team to execute seasonal graphic line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researches seasonal information and assists senior staff to create inspiration boards to create inspiration boards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates artwork for brand and graphic applications.  Responsible for any changes or updates to existing artwork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for color pegging and information layouts.  Emails approved graphics for vendor use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in the presentation of graphic concepts of the line each session.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Are you Tween Brands material? We hope so. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we look for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individuals with a passion for fashion and strong customer intimacy knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individuals with intense fashion radar that allow them to translate trends that work for &amp;ldquo;our girl&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individuals that live in the marketplace and can apply their knowledge to our business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individuals that work collaboratively with internal and external partners to get the job done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individuals that possess the critical ability to translate customer knowledge into  actionable annual and seasonal business plan to achieve sales and profit plans for one or more merchandise categories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we value &amp;ndash; we are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focused: as the premier tween specialist, we put our customer first in everything we do!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Driven: we set goals, have high standards, and achieve results!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative: our girl is all about what&amp;rsquo;s new and what&amp;rsquo;s hot. We encourage innovation and support creativity because that&amp;rsquo;s what she expects from us.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ethical: simply put, our girl and her mom expect us to always do the right thing!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balanced: everyone needs to be rejuvenated &amp;ndash; we want you to enjoy life, have fun, and take care of you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree or Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Illustration Studies or Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Mac operating systems, including Freehand, Illustrator and Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the apparel industry, preferably working with tween customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of screen printing, embroidery and other applied techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-tween-brands-new-albany-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-tween-brands-new-albany-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at PSSI in Wilmington, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a Web Designer for a full time position in Wilmington, OH. This position will develop and maintain web solutions for our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be responsible for gathering the requirements and building solutions using standards, tools and methodologies to ensure a quality and effective product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a comprehensive a benefits package that includes health insurance, vacation, disability, 401(k) retirement plan and free vacation lodging at our employee resorts in Daytona Beach, FL, Big Bear Lake, CA and Pigeon Forge, TN. JOB REQUIREMENTS Desired&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in web design technologies including HTML, HTML5 and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript, ASP.NET and WordPress in a design role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with using grid design a plus Understanding of appropriate whitespace in design as well as the importance of User Experience (UX) and how it impacts a design is a plus Working knowledge of Adobe Photoshop and Dreamweaver is necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be team-oriented and able to work in a fast-paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must work together with team to build and maintain effective web solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be customer centric and aggressive in servicing your customers’ needs and getting them met.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills are required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ Years experience in key web technologies such as HTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop good rapport with technology staff and vendors to meet customer expectations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College BS or BA Information Technology Experience in the Transportation Industry Candidate should have 3-5 years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-pssi-wilmington-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-pssi-wilmington-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>