<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/oh-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Rosetta in Cleveland, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is seeking an Art Director to join our Creative and Customer Experience practice.  The Art Director will be responsible for creating compelling, insight-driven, customer-focused communications that drive results and enhance our clients’ consumer experience—for both online and offline channels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who We Are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is a consulting-centered interactive agency engineered to transform marketing for the connected world. We are focused on helping progressive marketers drive material business impact by translating deep consumer insights into personally relevant brand experiences across touch points and over time. Our differentiated capabilities and structure have enabled us to become a market leader, operating as an independent brand in the Publicis Groupe of global agencies. Rosetta is ranked by Ad Age among the top U.S. digital agencies and was recently named the #1 Agency to Watch in Ad Age’s Agency A-List.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with Copywriters to develop results-driven creative solutions that help clients develop and improve their consumers’ experience across print, Web and other interactive channels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for execution of assigned client projects as it pertains to design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use of comprehensive layouts with clear execution of strategy, design and synergy between concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with development teams to ensure that recommended visuals/formats can be executed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to execute own projects from concept through final mockup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for adhering to project budgets and estimates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present work internally and externally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build comps and boards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in corporate initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the work and development of other more junior team members on the visual design team and contribute to the pricing and estimation of work effort requirements for staffing purposes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay abreast of the latest software upgrades and be proficient in them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in an advertising or direct marketing agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years of print and interactive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in direct mail print&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Financial Services Industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to manage multiple projects with minimal supervision in a fast-paced work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear understanding of branding and direct marketing principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aptitude and desire to learn emerging web tools and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in HTML/DHTML/JavaScript, and stylesheets/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess good conceptual understanding of HTML, color, optimizing images, the capabilities of Web browsers across multiple platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;COMPUTER SKILLS and Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Acrobat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe InDesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quark Xpress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft PowerPoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in ImageReady and Dreamweaver or similar HTML editor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Rosetta is an equal opportunity employer M/F/V/D&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-rosetta-cleveland-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-rosetta-cleveland-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Resource in Columbus, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Reporting to an Associate Creative Director, the Art Director is responsible for creative leadership and ownership of multiple projects. Art Directors mentor, inspire and direct a team of Senior Designers, Designers, Interaction Designers and Production Designers from concept to implementation. Art Directors work closely with Strategy, Client Service and Technology partners to ensure creative concepts and execution meet the established business objectives. Art Directors are also required to effectively communicate with clients in both creative presentations and feedback meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Practice Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept creation and development, design direction, management and execution
of overall visual language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct Designers, Interaction Designers and Production Designers regarding interface design and visual hierarchy systems, establishing the design language, execution of design direction, visual asset creation, HTML production and presentation preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photo and video art direction and participation in both pre- and post-production process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining and extending current knowledge base as well as learning about new design tools and software relating to interactive media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ownership of design and functional continuity throughout the development phase of project work, consistently consulting Associate Creative Director for guidance and validation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-facing presentations of creative concepts and design progress throughout the course of project work and creative assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soliciting and assimilating design feedback, establishing priorities and directing/implementing design related revisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Client Delivery&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of the Resource creative process against established timelines and budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staffing of project teams with a close eye on utilization targets for team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active collaboration with Strategy and Creative Domains to ensure effective visual communications and overall functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Business Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to assist in Scoping &amp;amp; estimating projects accurately as well as review and comment on SOW’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in new business opportunity brainstorming and spec work creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s Degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 to 10 years experience in Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years experience in Interactive Marketing and Interface Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive training in graphic design, typography, interaction design and/or visual communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstration of successful leadership experience with a team of at least 5 direct reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding conceptual abilities and collaborative skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong team building and management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills with the ability to present information in verbal, written or visual form to a variety of audiences, from the internal team to client executives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent time management skills and the ability to effectively allocate resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth understanding of interactive usability principles, HTML, dHTML and capabilities
of web browsers across platforms is essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in the latest versions of design software including: Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash and InDesign. After Effects and sound editing is a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-resource-columbus-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-resource-columbus-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>