<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/oh-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience (UX) Developer at Ascendum Solutions in Cincinnati, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Ascendum Solutions is looking for a User Experience (UX) Developer to join our team of talented IT consultants for a client of ours in the Cincinnati, Ohio area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience and portfolio demonstrating front-end user interface design and development of rich web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-End development and web applications including HTML, javascript, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using Javascript frameworks and custom plug-in development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using AJAX/JSON/REST/XHR and development using Web 2.0 techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual design experience using Photoshop and related tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation of front-end HTML, Javascript, CSS and related artifacts for developer consumption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of UI prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with mobile user interfaces—including smartphones and tablets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-End Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS (experience with CSS extension libraries like LESS or SASS would be a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript Frameworks (jQuery, Prototype, Backbone.js, AngularJS, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AJAX, REST/JSON, XHR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual Design Tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop, Illustrator, related tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Ascendum provides:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and Dental benefits to all consultants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) Retirement plan with employer contribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid vacation and sick days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We welcome inquiries from applicants only (We will not accept third parties or agencies for this opportunity). Candidates must be authorized to work permanently in the United States. Due to the volume of resumes that we receive, only those candidates selected for review will be contacted. Ascendum is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pay Range: $85K &amp;ndash; 105K + Full Benefits&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Ascendum Solutions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ascendum is a global information technology (IT) solutions company that delivers &amp;ldquo;Technology Inspired Solutions to Business Driven Challenges.&amp;rdquo; Ascendum works with small, medium, and large firms, including many Fortune 1000 companies, to help them solve business challenges. Ascendum&amp;rsquo;s approach is built on the success of using the right combination of strategy, people, processes, technology, and infrastructure for each client situation, to meet specific business needs/challenges and deliver expected results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Headquartered in Cincinnati, Ascendum has delivery, sales, and support offices worldwide including its Asia/Europe HQ and an offshore development center in the heart of India&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Silicon Valley,&amp;rdquo; Bangalore, and a BPO Center in Ahmadabad, India. We also have strategic partnerships with technology and domain-expertise based consulting companies worldwide&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-ux-developer-ascendum-solutions-cincinnati-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-ux-developer-ascendum-solutions-cincinnati-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at American Chemical Society in Columbus, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CAS is seeking a Web Developer to contribute to the development of a mission critical customer facing web application, working within an Agile team to code and test features according to customer specifications.  They will be responsible for developing UI modules within a Web framework using GUI best practices according to agile methodology and recommending best approach for developing complex user interactions focusing on application performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional duties include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop both unit and acceptance tests (TDD &amp;amp; ATDD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide oral and written status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance to less experienced members of the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years of software development experience (HTML / CSS / JavaScript)  within an enterprise-wide environment, focusing on web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective communication, technical leadership and teaming skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Object Oriented Analysis &amp;amp; Design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development experience on Windows and UNIX (i.e. Linux) platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a team of application developers and source code repositories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Computer Science or related discipline or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant skills include front-end web development with JavaScript, CSS and HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-american-chemical-society-columbus-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-american-chemical-society-columbus-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>