<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/oh-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface Developer at OverDrive, Inc in Cleveland, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Website Developer / UI Developer’s responsibilities include building attractive, creative, technically sound library and retail websites. This position is responsible for working on multiple assignments at once and must be able to prioritize tasks based on deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years website development experience using standards-compliant HTML.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years experience implementing W3C compliant websites using xHTML, CSS, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to write clean, highly reusable, and easily maintainable code compliant with web standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in cross-browser functionality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient to expert user of Adobe Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creativity; the ability to develop intuitive and attractive websites with minimal or no customer input.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Written communication skills with the ability to convey complex information concisely and clearly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail-oriented and self-motivated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competent user of Microsoft Office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Experience/Background:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with HTML 5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please email your resume and cover letter to jobs@overdrive.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-developer-overdrive-inc-cleveland-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-developer-overdrive-inc-cleveland-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer/Web Developer at Expedient Data Centers in Columbus, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Expedient operates a network of eight nationwide Data Centers in six markets (Pittsburgh (2), Cleveland (2), Boston, Baltimore, Indianapolis and Columbus).  The company offers a suite of managed services include virtualization, cloud computing, remote backups, management of equipment; storage area networks (SAN), disaster recovery and more.  These proven managed services combined with reliable and redundant geographically-diverse SSAE-16 SOC 2 compliant data centers enable Expedient to deliver premier colocation, network and managed services to enterprise, commercial, education and government entities.  Expedient is a wholly owned by Continental Broadband, LLC which is owned by Landmark Media Enterprises of Norfolk, VA.  For more information, log on to www.expedient.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expedient is a leading provider of Data Center services and is entering a new stage of significant growth that has created the need for a Graphic Designer in the Cleveland or Columbus, Ohio marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As our in-house designer, this position will play a key role in all aspects of the design and production of our marketing initiatives. This role will ensure designs are seen through to completion by applying brand style guidelines, typography, composition, and layout across multiple elements. Build creative content using brand standards to multiple deliverables (sales and marketing collateral, websites, marketing automation platforms, social media, etc.) and ensure end products meet the defined technical and quality standards for artwork preparation. Additionally, you will organize, archive and maintain creative templates and assets. Being mindful of time and budget constraints, this position requires one to be proactive and well organized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This full time position offers a competitive base pay plus bonuses and benefits, including a 401(k) plan with a company match, medical, dental and vision plans, flexible spending accounts, basic and supplemental life/AD&amp;amp;D insurance, tuition reimbursement, paid time off and paid holidays.  The graphic designer reports to the Vice President of Sales and Marketing and will work collaboratively with other Expedient marketing and sales professionals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate the visual and graphic design as it relates to all the aspects of the marketing program outlined to include branding, program identities, print templates, web templates, data sheets, whitepapers, industry brochures, company websites, micro-sites, e-marketing campaigns, and the mobile site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coding in HTML and JavaScript as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain library of all design and collateral assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with marketing team to collaborate creatively on solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The ideal candidate will have the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in graphic design preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses excellent visual design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of user interface design, concept development, branding and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding in how to code in HTML and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very proficient in the Adobe Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum 1-4 years successful corporate graphic design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative brainstorming and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Goal oriented with superior work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Expedient is an Equal Opportunity Employer, promoting a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please submit your cover letter, resume and salary expectations online for consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-web-developer-expedient-data-centers-columbus-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-web-developer-expedient-data-centers-columbus-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience (UX) Developer at Ascendum Solutions in Cincinnati, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Ascendum Solutions is looking for a User Experience (UX) Developer to join our team of talented IT consultants for a client of ours in the Cincinnati, Ohio area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience and portfolio demonstrating front-end user interface design and development of rich web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-End development and web applications including HTML, javascript, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using Javascript frameworks and custom plug-in development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using AJAX/JSON/REST/XHR and development using Web 2.0 techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual design experience using Photoshop and related tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation of front-end HTML, Javascript, CSS and related artifacts for developer consumption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of UI prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with mobile user interfaces—including smartphones and tablets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-End Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS (experience with CSS extension libraries like LESS or SASS would be a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript Frameworks (jQuery, Prototype, Backbone.js, AngularJS, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AJAX, REST/JSON, XHR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual Design Tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photoshop, Illustrator, related tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Ascendum provides:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and Dental benefits to all consultants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) Retirement plan with employer contribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid vacation and sick days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We welcome inquiries from applicants only (We will not accept third parties or agencies for this opportunity). Candidates must be authorized to work permanently in the United States. Due to the volume of resumes that we receive, only those candidates selected for review will be contacted. Ascendum is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pay Range: $85K &amp;ndash; 105K + Full Benefits&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Ascendum Solutions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ascendum is a global information technology (IT) solutions company that delivers &amp;ldquo;Technology Inspired Solutions to Business Driven Challenges.&amp;rdquo; Ascendum works with small, medium, and large firms, including many Fortune 1000 companies, to help them solve business challenges. Ascendum&amp;rsquo;s approach is built on the success of using the right combination of strategy, people, processes, technology, and infrastructure for each client situation, to meet specific business needs/challenges and deliver expected results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Headquartered in Cincinnati, Ascendum has delivery, sales, and support offices worldwide including its Asia/Europe HQ and an offshore development center in the heart of India&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Silicon Valley,&amp;rdquo; Bangalore, and a BPO Center in Ahmadabad, India. We also have strategic partnerships with technology and domain-expertise based consulting companies worldwide&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-ux-developer-ascendum-solutions-cincinnati-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-ux-developer-ascendum-solutions-cincinnati-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at American Chemical Society in Columbus, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;CAS is seeking a Web Developer to contribute to the development of a mission critical customer facing web application, working within an Agile team to code and test features according to customer specifications.  They will be responsible for developing UI modules within a Web framework using GUI best practices according to agile methodology and recommending best approach for developing complex user interactions focusing on application performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional duties include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop both unit and acceptance tests (TDD &amp;amp; ATDD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide oral and written status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance to less experienced members of the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 or more years of software development experience (HTML / CSS / JavaScript)  within an enterprise-wide environment, focusing on web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective communication, technical leadership and teaming skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Object Oriented Analysis &amp;amp; Design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development experience on Windows and UNIX (i.e. Linux) platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a team of application developers and source code repositories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Computer Science or related discipline or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant skills include front-end web development with JavaScript, CSS and HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-american-chemical-society-columbus-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-american-chemical-society-columbus-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>