<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/oh-misc.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Content - Project Manager at Empower MediaMarketing in Cincinnati, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Empower MediaMarketing specializes in communicating to and with its clients’ customers through an integrated combination of media. We are an independent media agency that plans, buys, creates and proves the impact of media.  Located in the consumer marketing and branding hub of Cincinnati, OH, we deliver proof our clients’ media investments are driving real results.  We are part of The Empower Group, an independent network of companies focused on building brands and business for its clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is responsible for the initiation, implementation, ongoing management and culmination of integrated marketing &amp;amp; content marketing initiatives, stemming from Empower’s Content Marketing Practice. This position will report to the content marketing practice lead, and work closely with other Content Marketing Practice personnel and Empower Client Marketing &amp;amp; Management leads. This position has responsibility for ensuring that client and internal programs are on objective, on timing, and on budget, and utilize the appropriate internal and external resources and processes that are at Empower MediaMarketing’s disposal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Principal Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Management (Core)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversees all day-to-day processes associated with creating branded and editorial assets for marketing purposes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishes strong working relationships with other Empower staff, across a range of practices, skill-sets and seniority&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produces and manages documentation and communications to facilitate and drive the creative process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides daily supervision of work-in-process, and ensures that staff and vendors meet requirements for task performance in terms of proficiency and skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritizes and manages resources and workflow to meet deadlines and ensures proper staffing levels are maintained at all times&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves as an additional quality control stop-gap on all creative work coming out of the practice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fosters a creative and productive work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encourages and ensures continual process improvement and innovation in our approach to creating marketing materials for clients and internal constituents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partners with Client Leadership to facilitate the development and sharing of detailed strategic documents, project briefs, and timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Strategy (Developmental)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains and enhances working knowledge of digital marketing programs that include email management, digital creative, website development and sustained consumer engagement through content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains a top-level understanding of the Content Marketing Practice clients’ marketing objectives and measures, and maintains a Return on Investment (ROI), Return on Objective (ROO) and/or other measurement metrics mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focused on ensuring clients’ marketing development needs are addressed and analyzed in order to build efficiencies and greater effectiveness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an acute understanding of internal and external influences on the creative process develops analyses and reports regarding those influences; and communicates to practice, company &amp;amp; clients appropriate action steps regarding those influences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position description is not intended to be all-inclusive and the employee will also perform other reasonably related business duties as assigned by management as required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Education and Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and skills at a level normally acquired through the completion of a Bachelor’s degree or equivalent knowledge or experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least three &amp;ndash; five years experience in interactive production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing and implementing digital marketing plans.?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in planning and managing ambitious web projects in a fast-paced environment, coordinating with the efforts of digital creative resources, and tracking long-term project timelines and deliverables while maintaining an ambitious daily update cycle.?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Required Skills, Knowledge and Abilities:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize work and make resource decisions accordingly.?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent at managing a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interact and communicate well with all stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate mission/?vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred but not required:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with project management tools such as Microsoft Project or Base Camp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Web analytics tools such as Google Analytics or Omniture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Other Skills, Specialized Knowledge, and Abilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of office software such as e-mail, MS Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocate for practice throughout the organization and outside groups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge in social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage and negotiate with 3rd party contractors and vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shows initiative to research new ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly enthusiastic, passionate, curious, confident and tenacious in learning about the medium&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical, detail and negotiation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrates effective business writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior listening skills &amp;amp; creative problem resolution skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple priorities simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-directed, with considerable initiative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands how to schedule and prioritize work in order to meet deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accepts ultimate accountability for own work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/content-project-manager-empower-mediamarketing-cincinnati-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/content-project-manager-empower-mediamarketing-cincinnati-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>