<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/oh-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Support Specialist at OverDrive, Inc in Cleveland, OH</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Technical Support Specialist’s responsibilities include answering and resolving requests related to supported applications, responding to problems that come to technical support, utilizing a support ticket management system, and communicating customer issues to technical staff. In addition, this position occasionally performs quality assurance on internally developed applications and systems, compatibility testing with other supported applications and platforms, and stays informed about new developments and updates for all supported applications and platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in related field; or equivalent experience (technology customer support, help desk, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous customer relations experience, demonstrated customer-focus, calm and patient demeanor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer Proficiency (Microsoft Office Suite).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong reading comprehension skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Written communication skills with the ability to convey complex information concisely and clearly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate effectively and appropriately with client contacts, outside vendors/contractors, and internal staff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to respond to common inquiries from customers and others within organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with multiple browsers and Internet use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a team environment under deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to consistently work and perform under pressure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to learn, work, and research independently, with minimal formal training.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail-oriented and organized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Experience/Background:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to speak and/or write in multiple languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web and Internet technology experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of ebook, audiobook and/or mobile devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please email your resume and cover letter to jobs@overdrive.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-specialist-overdrive-inc-cleveland-oh</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-support-specialist-overdrive-inc-cleveland-oh</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>