<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/or-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr Experience Designer at WebMD in Portland, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;WebMD’s Health  Services business, enables employers and health plans to provide their  employees and plan members with access to personalized health and  benefit information, decision support technology that helps them make  informed benefit, provider and treatment choices and provides telephonic  health coaching services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WebMD is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Sr. Experience Designers (XD) are responsible for creative excellence in user experience, visual design, and asset production. Our designers are versatile and multi-faceted. A deep understanding and passion for web technologies and grasp of the tools is expected. We also encourage designers to nurture their particular interests. The XD will work to implement visual design concepts into pixel-perfect, bullet-proof user interfaces that demonstrate a solid understanding of where visual design, interaction design, information architecture and technology come together to create smart, compelling and usable experiences across channels and devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sr. Experience Designer’s job is to contribute multiple elements of design and production support to the team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspire and collaborate with your co-workers to produce inventive, thoughtful, relevant work for clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with your team to execute on the creative strategy for projects by creating viable design schemes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support all aspects of design and production for your team’s projects, focusing on innovation and quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand and work within project parameters: client goals and requirements, internal goals, usability, technical constraints, as well as budget and schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiment with new tools and techniques to improve our work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate an understanding of industry trends; share your insights with the studio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate ideas. Develop strategies. Have a voice. Share.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6+ years designing rich experiences, with the majority being digital&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work on multiple projects, prioritize, and stay focused under tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive awareness, interest and opinion on emerging technologies, design and strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate ideas, decisions and reasoning clearly and confidently and provide clear, considered, prescriptive creative direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know and design best practices in UX / IXD / UI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of designing intuitive and relevant experiences for digital, offline, and mobile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online portfolio that demonstrates a excellent design execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work autonomously, and execute at a high caliber.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hand coding XHTML/CSS (not relying on an IDE &amp;ndash; i.e. Dreamweaver)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You own Adobe Creative Suite figuratively. Ability to speak the language of multiple programs/language is required, but mastery is not expected. (video programs, scripting languages, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about Design and Life. Someone who wants to crush it every day, no matter the challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great attitude. We love mavericks, but we operate an ego free work zone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you’re the right fit, you’ll share the belief that form is as important as function. You’ll balance innovation with pragmatism. You’ll work hard and play hard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Fine Arts or degree in design related field a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-experience-designer-webmd-portland-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-experience-designer-webmd-portland-or</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at PECI in Portland, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;PECI is a leading national energy efficiency company focused on delivering innovative design and program services to the nation’s utility companies and home owners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PECI is seeking a passionate Graphic Designer to join our talented in-house creative team. The right candidate will have a natural ability for translating strategic objectives into visual messages. We’re looking for someone who’s ready to think outside the box and adapt to a variety of creative tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The right individual will have an opportunity to work on multiple programs within the energy-efficiency industry and will be comfortable designing for our residential markets (homeowners, renters, property managers, contractors, etc.) Projects will consist of, but not be limited to brochures, case studies, leaflets, print ads, technical guides, website maintenance, point of purchase materials and direct mail campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop effective, cohesive visual concepts for print and web that resolve marketing problems in a fresh and unique way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that messages are effectively and consistently delivered within client brand guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with team members and senior designers to brainstorm and gather creative direction and make design recommendations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee all aspects of production, including managing schedules, gathering estimates, sourcing samples and maintaining vendor relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurately scope design projects and work within labor budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meet high standards for quality and accuracy under tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attend internal status meetings and report regularly to Art Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue to grow design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates must have at least 2 years of work experience as a graphic designer producing a broad range of promotional materials, preferably in an in-house or agency environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly creative and imaginative, and curious about clients' products or services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have excellent interpersonal and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to thrive in a fast-paced, team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess good people and project management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to multi-task under pressure and  manage workloads effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to see other people&amp;rsquo;s points of view and constructively take on feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly self-motivated and detail-oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to exhibit client service approach with results-driven performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe CS5 (In Design, Illustrator, Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Acrobat)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of HTML, CSS, and Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate knowledge of Microsoft Office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with CMS platforms and social media a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;How to apply: When applying for this position, please send us a link to your website and your resume OR submit 5 design samples with your resume as one PDF, no larger than 4MB.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PECI is an Affirmative Action / Equal Opportunity Employer and supports Diversity in the workplace. All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, marital or family status, sexual orientation, gender identity, or genetic information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-peci-portland-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-peci-portland-or</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer at Act-On Software in Beaverton, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;What you would do:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of our growing and passionate team you&amp;rsquo;ll participate in everything from initial planning and sketches right through design and implementation. You&amp;rsquo;ll be based in our Beaverton, Oregon office, designing world-class UIs that are perfectly simple and eminently usable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s how we work:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work in an agile team environment. We discuss a project, make prototypes, code them up, then work with developers to make sure those designs look and work exactly as intended. You&amp;rsquo;ll also work alongside our testers, who are great at spotting usability problems. As a designer you&amp;rsquo;re engaged in the whole process – from conception to launch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of modern HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing automation website integration experience required. (Domain expertise)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of best practices for the design of digital interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in interaction strategy, user research/usability testing, and the construction of software prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with visual design, skinning wireframes, icons, and style guide creation preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A demonstrated design sensibility and a knack for producing effective, engaging interaction prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-act-on-software-beaverton-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-act-on-software-beaverton-or</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer at SuperGenius in Oregon City, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SuperGenius is looking for an experienced and talented UI Designer to join the team and work alongside some of the most incredible and talented artist and animators in games. The project is a popular MMO Fantasy Game for the PC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A great UI Designer knows how to guide the player without pandering, convey complex information quickly and simply, and reflect the soul of the game through clear and precise design. A great UI Designer knows how to work with a team and utilize the talent and knowledge of those around them to help build an amazing game. A great UI Designer is what is needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The position is temporary full time with opportunity for extended employment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a very good designer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a very good interactive designer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should know Unreal, or be the type of person who leaps technological hurtles quickly and gracefully enough so that it does not matter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must work in house.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills / Extras&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and skill in other disciplines, such as Concepts, Animation, Characters, Environments, or VFX is always welcome. But please ONLY apply for the UI Designer position. The rest will simply be a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership Potential Admired.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We believe in open source culture. Sharing knowledge is more important than competition. Like-minded individuals preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in games is admired.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-supergenius-oregon-city-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-supergenius-oregon-city-or</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>