<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/or-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Director of Client Services at Swift Collective in Portland, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT US&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swift is a digital experience agency based in Portland, Oregon. We specialize in creating connections between brands and consumers, from social media strategy and management to highly usable web and mobile destinations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Director of Client Services you are a seasoned industry veteran and have a proven track record of managing large teams to deliver successful marketing campaigns. You are a strong collaborator, great presenter and motivate teams and clients with ease. You are adept at identifying areas for growth and new business opportunities with existing clients. The Director of Client Services reports to the CEO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage client relationships across the agency and serve as a strategic leader of the business, responsible for account growth, client satisfaction, and retention&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as a new business resource for growing existing client accounts through active pursuit of new revenue sources and provide leadership in strategic development of new business, such as RFP responses and proposal writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the translation of clients’ visions into business requirements, providing strategic oversight and reviewing team deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with clients to create comprehensive strategies that use social media and other digital marketing techniques to increase brand visibility and support account business objectives and priorities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the account team to ensure clients’ business needs are met and projects are delivered on time and within the project budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee planning deliverables for the client and team, including creative briefs and strategic brainstorm sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead key client meetings and present Swift strategy recommendations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the use of Swift agency best practices and effective processes across clients’ business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Negotiate business contracts and scope of work estimates with clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS &amp;amp; EXPERIENCE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12-15 years in the industry or related experience in developing digital marketing programs and managing large teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience owning senior client relationships and developing long-term trusted advisory positions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience running large engagements with Fortune 500 clients or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong business and analytics knowledge with proven history of delivering business results; ability to use alternative analytical approaches to solve digital marketing problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven negotiation experience, especially contract negotiations, with both clients and partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent public speaking skills and experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing teams of at least 10 full-time employees, including professional development and training, performance reviews and evaluations, and day-to-day mentorship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to define solutions that will generate measurable results for the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vast and deep experience with various project types, including eCommerce, social media strategy, mobile, and traditional website projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior leadership role at a growth-oriented creative or interactive agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-side experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;WHAT WE OFFER&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and a comprehensive benefits package including medical and vision coverage, flex spending account and 401k matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays and solid vacation/personal time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great new space to work in Northwest Portland, convenient to public transportation and dog-friendly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborative team environment and professional development support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to play an integral role in growing our business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If this opportunity interests you, please continue with the application process or send your resume and a note about yourself to jobs@swiftcollective.com. Include the position title in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-client-services-swift-collective-portland-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/director-of-client-services-swift-collective-portland-or</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>