<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/or-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at BCBG MAX AZRIA GROUP in Eugene, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;HEROweb Marketing and Design is a small business working for small businesses. Our chief objective is to provide dynamic, elegant web development solutions for customers using the MightyMerchant™ eCommerce CMS. We’re looking for a Hero like you to join our amazing team as a front-end web developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to help small businesses reach their goals, then this is the gig for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Overall Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project energy, enthusiasm, and knowledge about HEROweb&amp;rsquo;s services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build complete e-commerce websites using the MightyMerchant CMS, Bootstrap, and Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create flexible skins for MightyMerchant web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on user-interface design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the team to improve HEROweb&amp;rsquo;s products and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Essential Functions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use CSS layout and design techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create UI elements using CSS, jQuery, and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document the techniques and solutions you develop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain positive relationships with our customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to development of new technologies and initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become an expert in web usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test sites for functionality and accuracy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate with customers throughout the design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commensurate with experience. Full-time benefits package includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Growth opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Casual work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee incentives program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choice between PC/Mac environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-bcbg-max-azria-group-eugene-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-bcbg-max-azria-group-eugene-or</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface Developer at Webtrends in Portland, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re tackling new challenges everyday so we&amp;rsquo;re looking for an experienced and motivated web application developer to help us build creative, cutting-edge user experiences that transform the power of our big data, streaming analytics, and content optimization platforms into intuitive interfaces. If you&amp;rsquo;re passionate about using the latest web technologies to deliver best-in-class apps and working in a fun, intense environment, where you’ll collaborate every day with our team of talented developers and designers then keep reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who are we?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our development teams focus on enabling our customers to solve their unique business challenges by leveraging the power of our Big Data, streaming data, and content optimization platforms. Our developers design solutions that rely on choosing the right tool for the job, even if it means working with bleeding edge technologies. We offer a highly collaborative work environment where accountability, innovation, and initiative are valued and best practices, coding standards, and a test driven attitude are leveraged to produce software of the highest quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who are you?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a curious, fearless and confident developer who knocks down barriers in order to solve problems. You embrace collaboration and are driven to help your peers and team succeed. You are quick to identify problems and act immediately to find a way to solve them, drawing on your team into the process. You have something to teach us and are not afraid to share it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What will you do?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will spend every day working with and some of the most talented developers in Portland and Seattle to solve some of the most challenging business problems in our industry. As a part of the applications team, your focus will be to design and develop easy to use interfaces and experiences for enterprise customers. Your fellow team members will be doing the same in other cross-functional project teams, but you will all come together in support of maintaining a stewardship of our applications platform through the use of design reviews, best practices, coding standards, and more. And finally, quality is important to us so you will embrace a commitment to constantly improving it through the use of code reviews, unit test, automation, and also by working along side of our QA engineers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What do you need to bring to us?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS degree in Computer Science or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience developing rich, interactive web applications using JavaScript and JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years development experience with Backbone and Underscore or similar MVC web frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years development experience in either Ruby or C# (Ruby preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced hand-coding ability in HTML, CSS and an in-depth knowledge of the DOM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Embraces a test-first development approach, leveraging unit test tools such as NUnit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy working in an agile development environment with aggressive release schedules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and the ability to work well in a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we will be extra impressed by?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiences designing and implementing interactive front-end web applications using the latest HTML, and CSS specs including SASS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design skills, attention to pixel-perfect detail, and the ability to turn concepts and sketches into beautiful designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version control, GIT preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile practices and methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A personal drive for leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Working Conditions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position is located in downtown Portland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel requirements are minimal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Majority of time is spent working at a computer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incumbent must pass a background check&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Webtrends is an equal opportunity/affirmative action employer supporting workforce diversity. m/f/d/v.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-developer-webtrends-portland-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-developer-webtrends-portland-or</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at PlayHaven in Portland, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Front End Developer to work on the PlayHaven Dashboard. You will engineer new platform features into our Front End, enabling game developers to easily market to their players.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years software development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of CSS/JS/HTML5 with jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of object-oriented principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast-learning and adaptable to new code-bases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General familiarity with current trends in front-end tools and frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to see a project from spec to pixel-perfect implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Driven to find the right people/things that can unblock your blockers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Plus:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real test-driven development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of WebDriver or other browser automation tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Server-side (Python) experience or interest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you done Agile before?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we offer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free lunches every day and plenty of snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salaries and awesome paid-for medical, dental and vision benefits plus a 401(k)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited vacation (and we require a minimum of 2 weeks!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Epic ping pong and FIFA battles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A transparent work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A developer community that inspires and works with you to change mobile gaming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-playhaven-portland-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-playhaven-portland-or</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Developer at Janrain in Portland, OR</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Janrain, the leader in user management solutions for the social web, is seeking a User Experience Developer to join our growing UX team. This is an opportunity to make a difference in an exciting space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UX Developer helps bring the vision of the UX team to life. They do this by working closely with designers and engineers to turn new designs into functional interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is a special blend of front-end developer and UI designer. They must empathize with and advocate for the user. A good eye for visual design is important, and strong attention to detail is mandatory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UX Developer is critical to a well-executed UI. They often live in the small details and behaviors that make the difference between an average interface and a great interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They should have a mastery of modern CSS and HTML, be comfortable with JavaScript and a number of front-end libraries and frameworks, and be proficient with Git and other developer tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a passion for creating fast, intuitive interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocate for the user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create interfaces from pixel-level mockups using clean objective markup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create attractive, usable interfaces from wireframes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve upon and maintain our internal UI framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a critical eye for visual design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act as a resident CSS expert.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current with the latest tools, practices, and technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seeks to make data driven decisions, yet is comfortable making decisions with limited information on hand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years in a web or UI design/dev role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree in a related field or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of modern HTML and CSS best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional written and verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter who is highly organized, learns quickly, and is a team player.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seeks to make data driven decisions, yet is comfortable making decisions with limited information on hand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio of relevant work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working at a fast-growing startup company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on a product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with knockoutjs and d3js.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy working in a casual, yet fast-paced environment coupled with a clear mission, send your cover letter and resume to productjobs@janrain.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role is based in Portland, OR. No relocation assistance is offered.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-developer-janrain-portland-or</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-developer-janrain-portland-or</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>