<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/pa-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Operations Developer at Aweber Communications in Chalfont, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Role:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Operations Developer role focuses on pushing forward efforts in system automation and deployment using tools like Chef and Puppet, building REST APIs using Python frameworks like Flask and Tornado, and researching new solutions to help drive platform innovation in any part of the organization. The role also participates in many other initiatives, not the least of which is solidifying and furthering our commitment to collaboration and cooperation between development and operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;A sampling of the types of projects performed by this role might include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building out event-oriented message queuing architectures to increase efficiency and open data streams to multiple applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and/or build new solutions to provide new services and functionality to the internal application platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automate and expand the collection and use of metrics, leveraging new &amp;amp; existing tools to provide visualizations to both business and technical parts of the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re an experienced engineer. You’ve worked on multiple projects in various environments. You’ve put things into production, you’ve had people use them, you’ve failed, you’ve succeeded, you’ve paid your dues, and learned your lessons. You have a passion for technology, and view what you do as a craft. You like your job, but love your work. It’s something you’d do (and have done) even if there were no money or job involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You enjoy working with open source languages, toolchains, systems, and databases, and are always seeking out new solutions to difficult problems. Where those solutions are found lacking, you contribute, and occasionally build your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cringe at the thought of having to make a definitive choice between doing only software engineering or only systems engineering. You like to have your hands in all of it, and to be able to understand and affect change to any part of your work, front end to back end. You strongly resist pigeonholing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You thrive in environments where technological and innovative velocity is high, and the overhead from administrivia is low. You can work well in isolation, but are happy to collaborate in a team setting, and might not even mind doing the occasional pair programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AWeber’s engineering team is a dynamic and exciting place to be. We use open source technologies like PostgreSQL, Python, MongoDB, Redis, Riak, Chef, Ruby, Graphite, and RabbitMQ. We use approaches to software quality like Test-Driven Development, Continuous Deployment, and a healthy addiction to metrics that give us insight into our applications, and how well they’re serving our customers. We have a mode of execution built around Kanban, and a Kaizen culture of continuous improvement. We believe in the kind of transparency, processes, data sharing, collaboration, and communication that foster a DevOps culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid PPO medical, dental, vision, insurance. (including domestic partner benefits)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid Short Term Disability Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid Life Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition reimbursement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully Reimbursed Gym Memberships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 weeks paid time off  (plus increases in paid time off)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K retirement benefits with company match and profit sharing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free lunches everyday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Break rooms stocked with soda, juices, coffee and teas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MacBook Pro laptops and 30&quot; monitors for all development team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple high definition theater rooms fully equipped with xbox, wii &amp;amp; blu-ray players&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-operations-developer-aweber-communications-chalfont-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-operations-developer-aweber-communications-chalfont-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Parx Casino in Bensalem, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Duties will include development and maintenance of our corporate websites, email campaigns, mobile web applications and interactive multimedia content. Minimum 3 years of professional experience. Must be a self starter, highly motivated, able to take ideas and develop them into usable content with minimal supervision. Must provide a portfolio of recent work that showcases both creative and technical ability using a range of different authoring tools and techniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Must have, and be able to demonstrate, experience with the following tools programs and systems:
Web development technologies including PHP, HTML, CSS, XML, JavaScript Frameworks, AJAX and AS2/AS3 is required. Working knowledge of the Adobe Creative Suite including Fireworks, Photoshop and Flash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience with HTML5 and CSS3 a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are proud to be an EEO/AA employer M/F/D/V. We maintain a drug-free workplace and perform pre-employment substance abuse testing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-parx-casino-bensalem-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-parx-casino-bensalem-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>