<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/pa-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>JavaScript Web Developer at The Efficiency Network in Pittsburgh, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Efficiency Network (TEN) is a next-generation energy efficiency integration company located in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania that is revolutionizing the way customers achieve energy and water efficiency goals.  We combine cutting-edge automated technologies with industry expertise to remove excessive costs and complexities from project engineering, finance and construction. Our team of leading energy, software, financial and construction industry professionals provide comprehensive solutions on an accelerated timeline so our customers can start to reap the benefits sooner than with traditional efficiency approaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking an entrepreneurially-minded, solid JavaScript Web Developer with jQuery experience to help create eye-popping front ends to a sophisticated data store, analysis, and machine intelligence platform. This person will work under the supervision of the Senior Software Engineer responsible for web development.  The responsibility of this position is dynamic, challenging and multi-faceted.  We are seeking someone who is interested in a role that will challenge them in many ways and allow them to grow with the success of this company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement interactive user interfaces for TEN’s enterprise level web based applications;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write good JavaScript, HTML, and CSS;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce both working prototypes and production ready features;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a team environment developing and maintaining TEN’s offering;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current with the latest front-end web technologies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create software that meets all user needs &amp;amp; business requirements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Program widgets for the multitude of user interfaces (UI) of the company;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and enable widgets to communicate with the platform through a RESTful API;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform additional assignments, as directed and as required by Senior Software Engineer;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Competencies / Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competent JavaScript development, including use of the DOM, AJAX, writing libraries and APIs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience and knowledge with JavaScript security issues, XSS;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with a JavaScript framework like jQuery;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with HTML &amp;amp; CSS and current best practices;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident working in the Linux environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of github or similar DVCS;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of browser developer tools;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-browser testing &amp;amp; troubleshooting;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pluses: HTML5, usability, an eye for design;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good verbal and written communications skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or related technical field or equivalent experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to set and manage priorities and deliverables well;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good interpersonal skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to articulate ideas to both technical and non-technical audiences;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptionally self-motivated and directed;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work both independently and with others, take initiative, set priorities and see projects through to completion;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keen attention to detail;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior analytical, evaluative, and problem-solving abilities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial spirit;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our salaries are competitive and commensurate with experience. We are a performance-based, entrepreneurial culture and have goal-based incentive programs and generous employee benefits. We also offer flexible spending accounts and a 401(k) with an employer match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this role, we are looking for someone who is interested in being a contributing part of a dynamic, fast-growing organization and, someone who is interested in and committed to growing with the organization long term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company is an equal opportunity and affirmative action employer. All qualified applicants will be considered without regard to age, race, color, national origin, ancestry, sex, sexual orientation or preference, religion, marital status, citizenship or veteran status.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/javascript-web-developer-the-efficiency-network-pittsburgh-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/javascript-web-developer-the-efficiency-network-pittsburgh-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Operations Developer at AWeber in Chalfont, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Senior Operations Developer role focuses on pushing forward efforts in system automation and deployment using tools like Chef and Puppet, building REST APIs using Python frameworks like Flask and Tornado, and researching new solutions to help drive platform innovation in any part of the organization. The role also participates in many other initiatives, not the least of which is solidifying and furthering our commitment to collaboration and cooperation between development and operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;A sampling of the types of projects performed by this role might include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building out event-oriented message queuing architectures to increase efficiency and open data streams to multiple applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and/or build new solutions to provide new services and functionality to the internal application platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automate and expand the collection and use of metrics, leveraging new &amp;amp; existing tools to provide visualizations to both business and technical parts of the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re an experienced engineer. You’ve worked on multiple projects in various environments. You’ve put things into production, you’ve had people use them, you’ve failed, you’ve succeeded, you’ve paid your dues, and learned your lessons. You have a passion for technology, and view what you do as a craft. You like your job, but love your work. It’s something you’d do (and have done) even if there were no money or job involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You enjoy working with open source languages, toolchains, systems, and databases, and are always seeking out new solutions to difficult problems. Where those solutions are found lacking, you contribute, and occasionally build your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cringe at the thought of having to make a definitive choice between doing only software engineering or only systems engineering. You like to have your hands in all of it, and to be able to understand and affect change to any part of your work, front end to back end. You strongly resist pigeonholing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You thrive in environments where technological and innovative velocity is high, and the overhead from administrivia is low. You can work well in isolation, but are happy to collaborate in a team setting, and might not even mind doing the occasional pair programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AWeber’s engineering team is a dynamic and exciting place to be. We use open source technologies like PostgreSQL, Python, MongoDB, Redis, Riak, Chef, Ruby, Graphite, and RabbitMQ. We use approaches to software quality like Test-Driven Development, Continuous Deployment, and a healthy addiction to metrics that give us insight into our applications, and how well they’re serving our customers. We have a mode of execution built around Kanban, and a Kaizen culture of continuous improvement. We believe in the kind of transparency, processes, data sharing, collaboration, and communication that foster a DevOps culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% Company Paid PPO medical, dental, vision, insurance. (including domestic partner benefits)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid Short Term Disability Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid Life Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully Reimbursed Gym Memberships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 weeks paid time off  (plus increases in paid time off)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K retirement benefits with company match and profit sharing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free lunches everyday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Break rooms stocked with soda, juices, coffee and teas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MacBook Pro laptops and 30&quot; monitors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple high definition theater rooms fully equipped with xbox, wii &amp;amp; blu-ray players&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A game room with competition billiard, foosball, and ping-pong tables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-operations-developer-aweber-chalfont-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-operations-developer-aweber-chalfont-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Operations Developer at Aweber Communications in Chalfont, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;The Role:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Operations Developer role focuses on pushing forward efforts in system automation and deployment using tools like Chef and Puppet, building REST APIs using Python frameworks like Flask and Tornado, and researching new solutions to help drive platform innovation in any part of the organization. The role also participates in many other initiatives, not the least of which is solidifying and furthering our commitment to collaboration and cooperation between development and operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;A sampling of the types of projects performed by this role might include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building out event-oriented message queuing architectures to increase efficiency and open data streams to multiple applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and/or build new solutions to provide new services and functionality to the internal application platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automate and expand the collection and use of metrics, leveraging new &amp;amp; existing tools to provide visualizations to both business and technical parts of the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re an experienced engineer. You’ve worked on multiple projects in various environments. You’ve put things into production, you’ve had people use them, you’ve failed, you’ve succeeded, you’ve paid your dues, and learned your lessons. You have a passion for technology, and view what you do as a craft. You like your job, but love your work. It’s something you’d do (and have done) even if there were no money or job involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You enjoy working with open source languages, toolchains, systems, and databases, and are always seeking out new solutions to difficult problems. Where those solutions are found lacking, you contribute, and occasionally build your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cringe at the thought of having to make a definitive choice between doing only software engineering or only systems engineering. You like to have your hands in all of it, and to be able to understand and affect change to any part of your work, front end to back end. You strongly resist pigeonholing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You thrive in environments where technological and innovative velocity is high, and the overhead from administrivia is low. You can work well in isolation, but are happy to collaborate in a team setting, and might not even mind doing the occasional pair programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AWeber’s engineering team is a dynamic and exciting place to be. We use open source technologies like PostgreSQL, Python, MongoDB, Redis, Riak, Chef, Ruby, Graphite, and RabbitMQ. We use approaches to software quality like Test-Driven Development, Continuous Deployment, and a healthy addiction to metrics that give us insight into our applications, and how well they’re serving our customers. We have a mode of execution built around Kanban, and a Kaizen culture of continuous improvement. We believe in the kind of transparency, processes, data sharing, collaboration, and communication that foster a DevOps culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid PPO medical, dental, vision, insurance. (including domestic partner benefits)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid Short Term Disability Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Paid Life Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition reimbursement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully Reimbursed Gym Memberships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 weeks paid time off  (plus increases in paid time off)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K retirement benefits with company match and profit sharing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free lunches everyday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Break rooms stocked with soda, juices, coffee and teas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MacBook Pro laptops and 30&quot; monitors for all development team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple high definition theater rooms fully equipped with xbox, wii &amp;amp; blu-ray players&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-operations-developer-aweber-communications-chalfont-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-operations-developer-aweber-communications-chalfont-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Parx Casino in Bensalem, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Duties will include development and maintenance of our corporate websites, email campaigns, mobile web applications and interactive multimedia content. Minimum 3 years of professional experience. Must be a self starter, highly motivated, able to take ideas and develop them into usable content with minimal supervision. Must provide a portfolio of recent work that showcases both creative and technical ability using a range of different authoring tools and techniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Must have, and be able to demonstrate, experience with the following tools programs and systems:
Web development technologies including PHP, HTML, CSS, XML, JavaScript Frameworks, AJAX and AS2/AS3 is required. Working knowledge of the Adobe Creative Suite including Fireworks, Photoshop and Flash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience with HTML5 and CSS3 a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are proud to be an EEO/AA employer M/F/D/V. We maintain a drug-free workplace and perform pre-employment substance abuse testing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-parx-casino-bensalem-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-parx-casino-bensalem-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>