<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/pa-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Covi Point LLC in Sewickley, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The primary responsibility of this position will be to design the web interface for our micro-scheduling product. The designer will also contribute to the design of the Android and iOS apps, particularly in the generation of image assets such as icons, and logos. Familiarity with modern CSS and HTML will be useful but not required. In particular, basic CSS or HTML editing would facilitate direct modifications and experimentations with the web client prototype.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The website is intended for business-to-business daily use. As such, we are willing to put a premium on quality design and user experience over legacy portability. Support for legacy browsers will not be a priority. Users will be expected to use a major browser (Chrome, Firefox, Safari, or IE) no more than one major version behind. The site will also require that JavaScript be enabled at all times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From a design perspective, the challenging aspects of our application center around the real-time, data-driven nature of our micro-scheduling system. The website is an AJAX powered, single page application so full page reloads will not occur. Experience with animation and dynamic layout design will be preferred. The job description is subject to change by the employer as the needs of the employer and requirements of the job change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior web design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sample design portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in image asset generation and export&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS familiarity (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML familiarity (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Animation design experience (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dynamic layout design experience (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-covi-point-llc-sewickley-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-covi-point-llc-sewickley-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction and Communications Designer at Intermec in Pittsburgh, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Vocollect, a business unit of Intermec, is the number one developer and manufacturer of voice solutions for mobile workers worldwide, helping customers achieve a higher level of business performance through voice. Everyday, Vocollect and its partners enable over 400,000 workers worldwide to distribute more than $4 billion dollars' worth of goods&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vocollect is looking for a world-class Communication Designer to join our global marketing team. As a Communication Designer, you will take internal and external projects from concept to design and execution, while collaborating with a multitude of teams including marketing and product management. We are looking for someone whose creativity touches every aspect of their life. Your work exhibits stylistic breadth, attention to detail, and balances aesthetics, innovation, and usability. Project management comes easily. You are detail-oriented down to every pixel, and you have an eye for color, typography, and layout. You work across various media and are comfortable with both print and web. You have good skills with web design and management and enjoy taking on newer challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead designer responsible for the management and enhancement of the Vocollect brand identity through compelling and consistent visual design across marketing collateral, software interfaces, product presentations and online presence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the management and enhancement of company websites as well as acting in an advisory and support capacity for our international websites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design visual systems for digital and print marketing collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create data visualization and info graphics to succinctly communicate variety of detailed information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support multiple teams with presentation decks, customer deployments, and conference material&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the design and development of lead generation campaigns and various product landing pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and enhance on-line photo library and other digital assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the creative development of collateral and communication materials such as: white papers and written case studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help design and develop enhanced digital communication assets to increase stickiness of Vocollect offerings with customers, partners and prospects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and maintain organizational style guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Position Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Education:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in Communication Design, Interaction Design, Graphic Design or Industrial Design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years of professional experience as a designer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An excellent well rounded portfolio that includes print, digital, and interactive work showing examples of creative thought processes and execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing compelling and engaging PowerPoint presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage and prioritize multiple projects, while adhering to changing deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced skills with the Adobe Creative Suite product (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Microsoft Office (PC edition) with advanced PowerPoint skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate to advanced skills in HTML and JavaScript web page development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with photography, motion graphics, video editing and sound design a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building IOS and Android applications a major plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a CMS is a major plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with WordPress a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly organized and attentive to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to foster teamwork through active communication and listening skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective interpersonal and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Intermec/Vocollect is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-and-communications-designer-intermec-pittsburgh-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-and-communications-designer-intermec-pittsburgh-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Graphic Designer at rue21 in Warrendale, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Web Graphic Designer manages all content related to the corporate website, email marketing, social marketing, and any other emerging marketing channels. The designer works closely with the rue21 Web Marketing Manager to create quality web content compatible with corporate standards and brand guidelines. The Designer is also tasked with assessing any technical challenges in displaying the content. The Web Graphic Designer is expected to have some knowledge of HTML, XHTML, and other common web technologies, coupled with a solid background in creative design. A substantial degree of creativity is expected. The Web Graphic Designer will be required to have experience in graphics, layout, scripting, as well as some web-related programming. Flexibility, adaptability and the ability to learn quickly in various technical and creative environments, while delivering quality work within tight deadlines, are key attributes of this individual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The functions of the Web Graphic Designer are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics Development – Develop and design all of web, email and social graphic designs, color schemes and images, including product, lifestyle, promotional, and corporate images utilizing Adobe Creative Suite and other technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative &amp;amp; Cutting Edge – Creative, dynamic and fully aware of current web design trends and technologies, with the skills and desire to apply these to a forward looking eCommerce operation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized and Detail Oriented – Solid organizational skills with a proactive approach. Capable of multi-tasking in order to meet aggressive deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work under deadline a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action Driven – Must demonstrate a capacity to operate successfully in a fast-paced, rapidly changing environment to make decisions and implement recommendations quickly to drive for continuous improvement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated Communicator – Able to communicate effectively at all levels. Strong team building and collaborative skills required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One+ year experience of graphic design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing or Promotions background preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated strengths in web design, project management, and/or marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with web design applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with all common web browsers (IE 6 &amp;amp; 7, Firefox, Safari, Chrome) required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience with Adobe Creative Suite (especially Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Fireworks and Illustrator) required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CS6 preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, DHTML and CSS (Cascading Style Sheet) experience required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with web Content Management Systems (CMS) is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior retail experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High degree of proficiency in MS Office Suite, Outlook &amp;amp; Internet applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical, prioritizing, interpersonal, problem-solving, and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to operate independently while establishing strong working relationships with co-workers and cross-functional teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong, professional and effective verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to foster a positive and motivating work environment, encouraging feedback and innovation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with critical attention to detail and deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to adapt well to change in direction and priority in a fast- paced and deadline-oriented environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The preceding job description has been designed to indicate the general nature and level of work performed by employees within the classification. It is not designed to contain or be interpreted as a comprehensive inventory of all duties, responsibilities and qualifications required of employees assigned to this job.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-rue21-warrendale-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-rue21-warrendale-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface Designer at Fynydd, LLC in King Of Prussia, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Fynydd is looking for an experienced freelance user interface design specialist. This position would have the potential of becoming a full-time position, but at the moment we&amp;rsquo;re looking to augment our staff on a part-time basis. Applicants should have a portfolio of work which contains web application design (mobile, tablet, desktop), as well as mobile software design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for top-tier talent capable of producing jaw-dropping user interfaces. This designer should be able to work independently to determine needs based on a task assessment, as well as determine the desired image and overall aesthetic for the project. They should also be able to create wireframes, workflows, and design compositions that can be used by software engineers to implement the UI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you work independently, have experience, and can blow our minds with the quality of your work, we&amp;rsquo;d love to talk with you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-designer-fynydd-llc-king-of-prussia-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-designer-fynydd-llc-king-of-prussia-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic / Visual Designer at LuckyVitamin Corporation in Conshohocken, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://LuckyVitamin.com&quot;&gt;http://LuckyVitamin.com&lt;/a&gt; was first established back in 2004 as one of the Internets pioneers for online distribution of health and wellness products in the vitamin and supplement industry. Its founders had many years of experience in the natural health industry and wanted to bring that experience to the masses, hence LuckyVitamin.com was formed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our goal was simple. Carry the best selection of products, with the best prices and offer them to consumers through an attractive, easy to navigate, robust e-commerce portal. All while maintaining top-notch 5-star service to the customer. Years later we still operate on the same basic principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LuckyVitamin continues to expand in 2013 and has a new opportunity for a qualified applicant in our growing marketing department! LuckyVitamin is looking to hire a passionate, enthusiastic and talented Graphic Designer/Visual Designer from the Philadelphia area to join our Creative and Marketing team. This individual will assist with various aspects and oversee the creative direction for various front-end user experience, promotional materials and site design elements for one of the largest and fastest growing health and wellness e-commerce companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a self-driven, rock-star talented creative designer that can produce highly detailed, thoughtful and intuitive web and digital design work with a desire to work in a collaborative, fast paced environment. The Web/Graphic Designer should have solid understanding of user-centered design principles, excellent visual design skills/ great technical know-how, and a proven professional expertise in designing for the Web. Looking for someone with a unique hyper-enthusiastic drive to communicate promotional messaging, obsessed with detail that can make a WOW impact. This individual will have a key responsibility for developing and fueling the companies present and future public image as a premium retailer of over 30,000 diverse health and wellness products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce a wide variety of designs to satisfy consumer-driven merchandising projects as well user interface design solutions, including brand and promotional banners across multiple placements, interface elements, mock-ups, logos, etc…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interpret and progress the website’s style guide into something that WOW’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successfully manage on-site promotional schedule and creative assets from concept to completion, leverage and maintain the brand essence and produce high quality creative work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update and enhance website skinning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fair amount of illustration work may be required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execution of many yet unknown day-to-day web design needs that will certainly arise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must present, rationalize and articulate design ideas and decisions effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to flexibly and quickly without sacrificing a consistently high level of attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimizing graphics for web consumption, less is more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 + years of commercial graphic design with at least 1 year designing for e-Commerce and must be a strong conceptual thinker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengths in advertising, interactive and brand identity with ability to create unique work that focuses on target audience needs and expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of color, typography and all things visual&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing logos and icons; familiarity with print production process is also desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash, Fireworks and have an expert understanding of graphic and web design principles with at least an intermediate understanding of the latest and greatest in current web technologies (HTML, CSS, Javascipt)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well versed in development tradeoffs between speed, design, flexibility and the underlying page architecture. This is important!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a strong communicator able to prioritize and manage work to adhere to critical project timelines, able to work with project criticisms and have a positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem-solving skills that translate business objectives into interactive concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio demonstrating ability to produce effective promotional campaigns and graphic design work across various styles and purposes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In exchange for your talents, we offer a competitive salary and discounts on the products we sell on our website!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please click &amp;ldquo;Apply Now&amp;rdquo; and send your resume and cover letter detailing salary history/requirements and reference position IT-13. Resumes without salary requirements listed will NOT be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is located at our corporate headquarters in Conshohocken, PA. We are only considering candidates who are able to work onsite. Our brand new offices are located across from the Spring Mill train stop. TO APPLY: Please submit your resume and a well-established robust portfolio with relevant web, e-commerce and promotional design work covering a diverse variety of styles and design projects along with a cover letter stating your salary requirements via the link above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LuckyVitamin Corporation is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We will only respond to those we wish to contact for an interview. All inquiries will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-visual-designer-lucky-vitamin-corporation-conshohocken-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-visual-designer-lucky-vitamin-corporation-conshohocken-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Principal User Experience Designer at Red Privet in Harrisburg, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Red Privet is looking for full-time, seasoned designers with demonstrated leadership to work on large, long-term design projects (including mobile and social media).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with client project teams to facilitate design sessions, provide feedback on wireframes, and lead definition of patterns and standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate and consult with clients, team members, and other stakeholders to translate rough ideas and opportunities into clear concept models, tangible prototypes, and elegant screen designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a champion for users' needs from requirements gathering through solution definition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop information architecture, interaction flows and user interface deliverables, including wireframe mockups, detailed visual design mockups, storyboards, flow diagrams, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and facilitate customer research and usability testing activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elicit requirements and fully document design work products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in the full design and development cycle to ensure that creative innovations in user-centered design are faithfully delivered to our clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead Red Privet project teams, report status and escalate issues appropriately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years user-centered design experience (6-10 preferred).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design facilitation skills leading project teams in participatory and collaborative design sessions. Experience with JAD a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong application of interaction design best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear understanding of usability heuristics and experience performing real-time design evaluations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience solving complex user (cognitive) problems through visual design, interaction design, and usability expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated skill applying user-centered design practices, e.g., using ethnography data, user needs analysis, participatory design, end-user observation data, and usability testing data to influence design decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has performed various HCI/IA tasks including personas and use case scenarios, prototyping, flow diagrams, wireframes, card sorting, labeling schemes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to rapidly sketch out user-flows with pencil and paper, whiteboards, or post-it notes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience developing interactive prototypes and documentation to aid evaluation of designs for complex applications. Experience with Axure a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design foundation including adept use of grids, typography, color harmony, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has designed for accessibility, Section 508-compliance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent visual, verbal, and written communication skills, with the ability to effectively engage and convey ideas to technical and business teams with passion and diplomacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with use-cases and RUP-like processes a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a U.S. Citizen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to submit to drug screening and background check (client requirement).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree required, Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s or Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work Environment &amp;amp; Benefits.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Red Privet combines a start-up environment with a team of seasoned professionals to ensure great collaboration, mentoring through weekly design critiques and the opportunity to tackle tough, but rewarding, design challenges for top-tier clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental and vision benefits (100% covered for employee).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) with company match.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11 paid holidays, plus paid annual personal and sick leave.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Work Environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation assistance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public Transit Discounts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit sharing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;No phone calls please. No third parties. No telecommuting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-user-experience-designer-red-privet-harrisburg-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-user-experience-designer-red-privet-harrisburg-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Informatics Studio, Inc. in Pittsburgh, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Informatics Studio is an audience analysis, communications strategy and design firm with distinguished visual design capabilities and a focus on design as a catalyst for positive social improvement. Informatics designs and develops user-centric communication tools and resources, knowledge management systems, culture-specific communication frameworks, marketing, training and visual messaging primarily in five domains:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are seeking talented designers with an analytical approach to solving communication challenges for clients working on some of the most urgent social programs around the world. Studio projects range from complex web-based communication programs to the design of printed materials of all types. Our work includes audience and information analysis, communication strategy, design and technical implementation for clients that include the US government, international development agencies and nonprofits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your resume and work samples to todd@informatics-studio.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-informatics-studio-inc-pittsburgh-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-informatics-studio-inc-pittsburgh-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>