<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/pa-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic / Visual Designer at LuckyVitamin Corporation in Conshohocken, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://LuckyVitamin.com&quot;&gt;http://LuckyVitamin.com&lt;/a&gt; was first established back in 2004 as one of the Internets pioneers for online distribution of health and wellness products in the vitamin and supplement industry. Its founders had many years of experience in the natural health industry and wanted to bring that experience to the masses, hence LuckyVitamin.com was formed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our goal was simple. Carry the best selection of products, with the best prices and offer them to consumers through an attractive, easy to navigate, robust e-commerce portal. All while maintaining top-notch 5-star service to the customer. Years later we still operate on the same basic principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LuckyVitamin continues to expand in 2013 and has a new opportunity for a qualified applicant in our growing marketing department! LuckyVitamin is looking to hire a passionate, enthusiastic and talented Graphic Designer/Visual Designer from the Philadelphia area to join our Creative and Marketing team. This individual will assist with various aspects and oversee the creative direction for various front-end user experience, promotional materials and site design elements for one of the largest and fastest growing health and wellness e-commerce companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a self-driven, rock-star talented creative designer that can produce highly detailed, thoughtful and intuitive web and digital design work with a desire to work in a collaborative, fast paced environment. The Web/Graphic Designer should have solid understanding of user-centered design principles, excellent visual design skills/ great technical know-how, and a proven professional expertise in designing for the Web. Looking for someone with a unique hyper-enthusiastic drive to communicate promotional messaging, obsessed with detail that can make a WOW impact. This individual will have a key responsibility for developing and fueling the companies present and future public image as a premium retailer of over 30,000 diverse health and wellness products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce a wide variety of designs to satisfy consumer-driven merchandising projects as well user interface design solutions, including brand and promotional banners across multiple placements, interface elements, mock-ups, logos, etc…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interpret and progress the website’s style guide into something that WOW’s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successfully manage on-site promotional schedule and creative assets from concept to completion, leverage and maintain the brand essence and produce high quality creative work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update and enhance website skinning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fair amount of illustration work may be required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execution of many yet unknown day-to-day web design needs that will certainly arise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must present, rationalize and articulate design ideas and decisions effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to flexibly and quickly without sacrificing a consistently high level of attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimizing graphics for web consumption, less is more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 + years of commercial graphic design with at least 1 year designing for e-Commerce and must be a strong conceptual thinker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengths in advertising, interactive and brand identity with ability to create unique work that focuses on target audience needs and expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of color, typography and all things visual&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing logos and icons; familiarity with print production process is also desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash, Fireworks and have an expert understanding of graphic and web design principles with at least an intermediate understanding of the latest and greatest in current web technologies (HTML, CSS, Javascipt)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well versed in development tradeoffs between speed, design, flexibility and the underlying page architecture. This is important!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a strong communicator able to prioritize and manage work to adhere to critical project timelines, able to work with project criticisms and have a positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem-solving skills that translate business objectives into interactive concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio demonstrating ability to produce effective promotional campaigns and graphic design work across various styles and purposes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In exchange for your talents, we offer a competitive salary and discounts on the products we sell on our website!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please click &amp;ldquo;Apply Now&amp;rdquo; and send your resume and cover letter detailing salary history/requirements and reference position IT-13. Resumes without salary requirements listed will NOT be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is located at our corporate headquarters in Conshohocken, PA. We are only considering candidates who are able to work onsite. Our brand new offices are located across from the Spring Mill train stop. TO APPLY: Please submit your resume and a well-established robust portfolio with relevant web, e-commerce and promotional design work covering a diverse variety of styles and design projects along with a cover letter stating your salary requirements via the link above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LuckyVitamin Corporation is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We will only respond to those we wish to contact for an interview. All inquiries will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-visual-designer-lucky-vitamin-corporation-conshohocken-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-visual-designer-lucky-vitamin-corporation-conshohocken-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Principal User Experience Designer at Red Privet in Harrisburg, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Red Privet is looking for full-time, seasoned designers with demonstrated leadership to work on large, long-term design projects (including mobile and social media).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with client project teams to facilitate design sessions, provide feedback on wireframes, and lead definition of patterns and standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate and consult with clients, team members, and other stakeholders to translate rough ideas and opportunities into clear concept models, tangible prototypes, and elegant screen designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a champion for users' needs from requirements gathering through solution definition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop information architecture, interaction flows and user interface deliverables, including wireframe mockups, detailed visual design mockups, storyboards, flow diagrams, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and facilitate customer research and usability testing activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elicit requirements and fully document design work products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in the full design and development cycle to ensure that creative innovations in user-centered design are faithfully delivered to our clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead Red Privet project teams, report status and escalate issues appropriately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years user-centered design experience (6-10 preferred).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design facilitation skills leading project teams in participatory and collaborative design sessions. Experience with JAD a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong application of interaction design best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear understanding of usability heuristics and experience performing real-time design evaluations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience solving complex user (cognitive) problems through visual design, interaction design, and usability expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated skill applying user-centered design practices, e.g., using ethnography data, user needs analysis, participatory design, end-user observation data, and usability testing data to influence design decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has performed various HCI/IA tasks including personas and use case scenarios, prototyping, flow diagrams, wireframes, card sorting, labeling schemes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to rapidly sketch out user-flows with pencil and paper, whiteboards, or post-it notes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience developing interactive prototypes and documentation to aid evaluation of designs for complex applications. Experience with Axure a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design foundation including adept use of grids, typography, color harmony, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has designed for accessibility, Section 508-compliance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent visual, verbal, and written communication skills, with the ability to effectively engage and convey ideas to technical and business teams with passion and diplomacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with use-cases and RUP-like processes a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a U.S. Citizen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness to submit to drug screening and background check (client requirement).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree required, Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s or Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work Environment &amp;amp; Benefits.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Red Privet combines a start-up environment with a team of seasoned professionals to ensure great collaboration, mentoring through weekly design critiques and the opportunity to tackle tough, but rewarding, design challenges for top-tier clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental and vision benefits (100% covered for employee).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) with company match.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11 paid holidays, plus paid annual personal and sick leave.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Work Environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation assistance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public Transit Discounts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit sharing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;No phone calls please. No third parties. No telecommuting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-user-experience-designer-red-privet-harrisburg-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/principal-user-experience-designer-red-privet-harrisburg-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Informatics Studio, Inc. in Pittsburgh, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Informatics Studio is an audience analysis, communications strategy and design firm with distinguished visual design capabilities and a focus on design as a catalyst for positive social improvement. Informatics designs and develops user-centric communication tools and resources, knowledge management systems, culture-specific communication frameworks, marketing, training and visual messaging primarily in five domains:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are seeking talented designers with an analytical approach to solving communication challenges for clients working on some of the most urgent social programs around the world. Studio projects range from complex web-based communication programs to the design of printed materials of all types. Our work includes audience and information analysis, communication strategy, design and technical implementation for clients that include the US government, international development agencies and nonprofits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your resume and work samples to todd@informatics-studio.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-informatics-studio-inc-pittsburgh-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-informatics-studio-inc-pittsburgh-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>