<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/pa-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Informatics Studio, Inc. in Pittsburgh, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Informatics Studio is an audience analysis, communications strategy and design firm with distinguished visual design capabilities and a focus on design as a catalyst for positive social improvement. Informatics designs and develops user-centric communication tools and resources, knowledge management systems, culture-specific communication frameworks, marketing, training and visual messaging primarily in five domains:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are seeking talented designers with an analytical approach to solving communication challenges for clients working on some of the most urgent social programs around the world. Studio projects range from complex web-based communication programs to the design of printed materials of all types. Our work includes audience and information analysis, communication strategy, design and technical implementation for clients that include the US government, international development agencies and nonprofits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your resume and work samples to todd@informatics-studio.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-informatics-studio-inc-pittsburgh-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-informatics-studio-inc-pittsburgh-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>