<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/pa-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at Armstrong in Lancaster, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Armstrong World Industries is seeking a qualified eBusiness Project Manager to be located at our corporate campus in Lancaster, PA. The eBusiness Project Manager is primarily responsible for completing projects by; documenting, scheduling, budgeting, implementing, testing, and reporting on projects; supporting operations; managing shared project staff; managing budgets; and resolving competing priorities. eBusiness Project Managers must be excellent communicators, tactful diplomats, problem solvers, thinkers and analyzers; with the ability to understand and respond to customer needs in a rapidly changing business environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successfully plan, manage, and lead projects of all sizes through all phases of the project life cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage web/mobile development projects to extend, enhance and create new capabilities within our portfolio of residential, commercial and international web sites, systems, and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and report project schedules and budgets, as well as proactively resolve all issues that may potentially impede successful project completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balance multiple concurrent assignments with shifting priorities across a shared resource pool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage vendors, as needed, to achieve project deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate to identify business requirements and business process change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review &amp;amp; verify project deliverables before release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-task in a fast-paced and high volume environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree, preferably in a relevant field such as Business &amp;amp; Information Technology, Web Marketing and/or the equivalent combination of education and experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 3-5 years of demonstrated successful interactive, internet project management experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full project life cycle experience managing web development and technical delivery projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of Internet based marketing and web based development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of web/mobile technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working successfully in large, complex, fast-paced organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to establish rapport and work in a team environment with internal and external clients, vendors, consultants, designers, and developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent negotiation skills in order to work effectively with internal and external customers, information technology departments and vendors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer proficiency in MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Project) a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Desired Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project Management Professional (PMP) certification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business Analysis and Quality Assurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with aspects of web design and usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-line commerce background.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working Knowledge of CA Clarity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language fluency in addition to English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer competitive benefits including options and choices to fit your needs such as medical, dental, prescription drug, life insurance, long and short term disability coverage, 401k plan, paid time off, and product discount programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About the Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Established in 1860, Armstrong World Industries, Inc. is a multi-billion dollar global leader in the design and manufacture of floors and ceilings with a focus on innovation, design, and environmental sustainability. Based in Lancaster PA, Armstrong serves both the residential and commercial markets operating plants and distribution centers in eight countries with over 9,000 employees worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Armstrong is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-armstrong-lancaster-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-armstrong-lancaster-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at Razorfish Healthware in Philadelphia, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Razorfish Healthware is a key partner for health and wellness companies who want to grow their business by engaging with and improving the lives of their customers.  With a focus on creating brand experiences that build our clients’ business, we leverage our unique mix of insight, technology, creativity, and industry savvy to transform the health and wellness community so that our clients can build healthy relationships that last. Headquartered in Philadelphia, Razorfish Healthware is a brand of Razorfish, and a member of the Paris-based Publicis Groupe S.A. the world’s third largest communications group, second largest media counsel and buying group, and a global leader in digital and healthcare communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Art Director is responsible for conceptual development and the execution of creative deliverables, including advertising, web sites, email and other forms of interface design. These responsibilities include creating and communicating concepts, implementing marketing strategies and developing interactive design solutions within the healthcare space. The Art Director will work with and lead a collaborative team of designers and copywriters and production specialists.  Balancing creative thinking with interpersonal skills, this person will demonstrate the ability to review and justify concepts to both the client and the project team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Core Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with the Creative Director/Associate Creative Director and department team to develop concepts for interactive marketing communication programs, new-business proposals and presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with IA/UX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with brand development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follows creative briefs by interpreting instructions and disseminating results to team members in an effective manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and/or oversees layouts and designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages design resources for approved projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews and directs work of project teams, taking quality of design, strategic accuracy, and adherence to client goals and brand style guidelines into account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presents creative concepts and designs to clients.  Incorporates client feedback and revisions as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivers products in a timely fashion to meet set deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to edit/QA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with pitches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with video and video editing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversees and prioritizes work effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess the ability to draft concepts, presentations, correspondence and other written materials as required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong verbal communication skills, including the ability to speak effectively before clients, staff or other internal and external groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal skills, a positive attitude and the ability to thrive in a collaborative agency environment with multi-disciplinary teams required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to successfully organize, prioritize and manage multiple projects in a deadline-driven environment is a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to guide others in the artistic development and execution of creative interactive marketing communication programs within pre-defined client objectives required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must demonstrate a solid understanding of current creative media, mediums and trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervisory experience is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on command of major design, interactive and page layout software programs such as Flash, Fireworks, DreamWeaver, Quark XPress, PhotoShop, Illustrator required.  ActionScripting and/or HTML skills are a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must show us a great book!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree (BA/BS) from a four-year accredited college or university in Fine Arts, Graphic Design, Multi-Media Design, or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of four (4) years of relevant experience in the art/creative field within an advertising agency required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic copywriting skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience within the interactive, multi-media or web advertising industry required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equivalent combination of education and experience may be considered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-razorfish-healthware-philadelphia-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-razorfish-healthware-philadelphia-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>