<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/pa-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Customer Support Coordinator at 4moms in Pittsburgh, PA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Would you like to work with a talented team of people at a rapidly growing tech company? Join 4moms, a truly innovative juvenile products company. We&amp;rsquo;ve introduced robotics technology to the juvenile industry with our suite of high-tech baby gear, including the world&amp;rsquo;s first power-folding stroller.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have an immediate need for a process driven, customer focused Customer Support Coordinator. As an important member of the Marketing Team, and reporting to the Customer Support Team Lead, you will have hands-on responsibility for delivering best in class customer support. You will also work extensively with cross-functional partners to drive the success of our brand and products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elevate the customer experience by thinking on your feet to consistently wow the customer while upholding the company mission and values.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Routinely respond to customer questions or concerns via telephone and email.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track customer issues and collaborate with other teams to identify and resolve common issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor web store purchase activity to mitigate risk of unauthorized charges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we&amp;rsquo;re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Communications, Business or related required. Alternatively, 2-4 years of customer support experience will be considered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for developing and executing customer support within a company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to build rapport and instill confidence with customers quickly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated listening skills to fully understand customer issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responding to customers with genuine empathy, patience, confidence and product knowledge. Stays calm and collected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail including accuracy in entering data into databases or spreadsheets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task and be deadline-oriented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In return for your services, we currently offer a generous total compensation plan including a competitive salary, company paid medical, dental, life and disability insurance, 401k with company match, and an iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4moms was honored with the 2011 Kind Jugend Innovation Award, was named #8 on the 2011 Pittsburgh 100 list of Fastest Growing Companies and #560 on the 2011 INC 5000. Our products have also won the JPMA Innovation Award, the 2011 Popular Science Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Best of What&amp;rsquo;s New Award, and the National Parenting Center Seal of Approval.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-coordinator-fourmoms-pittsburgh-pa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/customer-support-coordinator-fourmoms-pittsburgh-pa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>