<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/sc-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Art Director at BFG in Hilton Head, SC</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Art Director is responsible for creative leadership and ownership of multiple design projects. The Art Director mentors, inspires and directs a team of Senior Designers, Designers, UX Designers and Production Designers from design concept to implementation. Art Directors work closely with the Strategy, Client Services and Technology departments to ensure creative concepts and execution meet the established business objectives.  Art Directors communicate with clients in both creative presentations and feedback meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Duties and Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to organize, prioritize, multi-task and work independently, with little or no supervision related to the management of general business operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept creation and development, design direction, management and execution of overall visual language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct Designers, UX Designers and Production Designers regarding interface design and visual hierarchy, establishing the design language, execution of design direction, visual asset creation, HTML production and presentation preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photo and video art direction and participation in both pre- and post-production processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staying up-to-date with current and new design tools and software relating to interactive media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ownership of design and functional continuity throughout the development phase of project work, consistently consulting Sr. Interactive Art Director or Interactive Associate Creative Director for guidance and validation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-facing presentations of creative concepts and design progress throughout the course of project work and creative assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soliciting and assimilating design feedback, establishing priorities and directing/implementing design related revisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active collaboration with Strategy and Creative teams to ensure effective visual communications and overall functionality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in new business opportunity brainstorming and spec work creative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular and reliable attendance and strict punctuality are required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enter time on a daily basis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years’ experience directing and managing creative staff for digital projects (web, email, microsites, mobile, social).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ad agency or design firm experience required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in planning and creating project strategies and concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in social networking and marketing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow all standard agency policies and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is Referral Program eligible. Please submit resume to creativejobs@bfgcom.com.  No phone calls please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above job description is meant to describe the general nature and level of work being performed; it is not intended to be construed as an exhaustive list of all responsibilities, duties and skills required for the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Employees will be required to follow any other job-related instructions and to perform other job-related duties requested by their supervisor. “All employment with BFG is at will”.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-art-director-bfg-hilton-head-sc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-art-director-bfg-hilton-head-sc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>