<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/sc-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr. iOS Developer at Atlatl Software in Charleston, SC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Atlatl™ Software is in the process of developing and marketing several Sales Resource Planning (SRP™) applications. “DART™” includes two (2) modules: the Product Configuration Module and the Quote Management Module. “SPEAR™” is a customer relationship management-like application. It utilizes what we call a “Customer Engagement Engine” to help salespeople become more effective and successful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Atlatl, we believe visualization is at the heart of understanding. Our technology enables organizations to engage and create with their customers in real time.  As our Senior iOS Developer, you will oversee the iOS development team and be responsible for developing cutting edge mobile applications that are the tip of the spear in the Atlatl solution ecosystem.  You meet your commitments on time and produce high quality software that is unit tested, code reviewed, and checked in regularly for continuous integration.  With your technical expertise you will manage individual project priorities, deadlines and deliverables. You will design, develop, test, deploy, maintain, and enhance software solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Atlatl offers you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empowerment – we believe in the power of our people and what they bring to the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenge – we believe in pursuing and producing the highest quality of cutting edge technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellence in Execution – we believe and thrive on a balance of innovation and production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Values – we believe strongly in our core values, live them, and grow within them each day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trail Blazers – we believe in being the first to pave the way in our industry and every person on our team is a trail blazer in their own right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Specific Responsibilities: (include but are not limited to)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help shape the future of our products on the iOS platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop mobile applications primarily in Objective-C and using the iOS SDK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design &amp;amp; Implement new features and optimize existing ones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performance analysis and application tuning will also be a significant responsibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Essential Qualities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with the ability to drive features to delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and collaborative skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for product quality and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with rapid development cycles, tight schedules.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent collaborative and communication skills for both technical and non-technical audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven leadership and problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years mobile development; 10+ years of programming experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance knowledge of Objective-C and iOS SDK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building complex mobile applications on iOS platform that have been successfully delivered to customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capability of architecting, developing and testing complex mobile applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enterprise level B2B experience highly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Xcode IDE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity integrating 3rd party APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding communication skills and ability to articulate best practices in design and development of iOS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of rules engines highly desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with QA teams to develop testing strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience developing apps that integrate seamlessly with a Cloud back end and Web front end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience working within a defined software development cycle; Agile experience is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-ios-developer-atlatl-software-charleston-sc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-ios-developer-atlatl-software-charleston-sc</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Atlatl Software in Charleston, SC</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Atlatl, we believe visualization is at the heart of understanding. Our technology enables organizations to engage and create with their customers in real time.  As our iOS Developer, you will be responsible for developing cutting edge mobile applications that are the tip of the spear in the Atlatl solution ecosystem.  You meet your commitments on time and produce high quality software that is unit tested, code reviewed, and checked in regularly for continuous integration.  With your technical expertise you will manage individual project priorities, deadlines and deliverables. You will design, develop, test, deploy, maintain, and enhance software solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Atlatl offers you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empowerment – we believe in the power of our people and what they bring to the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenge – we believe in pursuing and producing the highest quality of cutting edge technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellence in Execution – we believe and thrive on a balance of innovation and production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Values – we believe strongly in our core values, live them, and grow within them each day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trail Blazers – we believe in being the first to pave the way in our industry and every person on our team is a trail blazer in their own right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Specific Responsibilities: (include but are not limited to)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help shape the future of our products on the iOS platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop mobile applications primarily in Objective-C and using the iOS SDK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design &amp;amp; Implement new features and optimize existing ones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performance analysis and tuning will also be a significant responsibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Essential Qualities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with the ability to drive features to delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and collaborative skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for product quality and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with rapid development cycles, tight schedules.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent collaborative and communication skills for both technical and non-technical audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven leadership and problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ year mobile development; 5-10 years of programming experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance knowledge of Objective-C and iOS SDK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building complex mobile applications on iOS platform that have been successfully delivered to customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capability of architecting, developing and testing complex mobile applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enterprise level B2B experience highly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Xcode IDE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity integrating 3rd party APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding communication skills and ability to articulate best practices in design and development of iOS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of rules engines highly desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with QA teams to develop testing strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience developing apps that integrate seamlessly with a Cloud back end and Web front end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience working within a defined software development cycle; Agile experience is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Our Company:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leveraging the decades of global sales &amp;amp; manufacturing process expertise of its parent company, SixAxis, Atlatl Software is developing a new class of mobile and cloud based solutions that will reshape the B2B product selection and purchasing experience within the manufacturing sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through its Sales Resource Planning solution, Atlatl is re-choreographing the sales process and re-inventing the way sales data is created, captured, managed and used, allowing sales teams to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify the right client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable the client to understand and articulate their needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable the client to take a vested interest in the successful conclusion of the selling process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Radically accelerate the sales cycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No similar product exists that intuitively provides a cohesive, streamlined solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Atlatl is headquartered in Charleston, SC and its product development team is based in Portland, OR.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-atlatl-software-charleston-sc</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-atlatl-software-charleston-sc</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>