<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tn-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at Asurion in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a talented designer to create visually engaging experiences. The design role depends greatly on user-centered design principles and usability testing to guide designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this position you&amp;rsquo;ll work with other team members to define, create and maintain great user experience. The ideal candidate will have great creative, problem solving, and leadership skills. You&amp;rsquo;ll be responsible for all phases of user experience design, from concept to on-going maintenance, ensuring that great design and interaction meet the business, customer and technical requirements. Excellent visual design, written and oral communication skills a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a position for someone that is passionate about web development and mobile. While we will consider all qualified candidates, this is not a position for people looking to diversify their experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Interaction Designer is responsible for helping create world class online user experiences, continually improve pattern libraries and support brand standards through interface design. This role will work closely with the Sr. Manage Online Experience, Process Engineers, Business Architects, Testers and Analytics to define, deliver and measure projects that improve a customer’s experience on the web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years experience creating high design sense with production value websites and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of digital and mobile technologies and trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience working to conceptualize and define web products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working under pressure with aggressive deadline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong visual design sense with clean typography, page and web layout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of UX design processes and methodology, particularly as applied to cross-device experiences and responsive design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototyping skills including sketching, wireframing &amp;amp; information visualization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTML, CSS, Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with jQuery, MooTools, and other JavaScript a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to clearly articulate your design decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with the ability to work independently and collaboratively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with an iterative design process that includes accepting and managing feedback and constructive criticism.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with best practices for web usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;TRAVEL:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position may require up to 10% travel.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-asurion-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-asurion-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at Scripps Networks Interactive in Knoxville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Scripps Networks Interactive (SNI) is actively seeking a Designer in Knoxville, TN. Scripps Networks Interactive is one of the leading developers of lifestyle-oriented content for television and the Internet, where on-air programming is complemented with online video, social media areas and e-commerce components on companion Web sites and broadband vertical channels. The company&amp;rsquo;s media portfolio includes popular lifestyle television and Internet brands HGTV, Food Network, Travel Channel, DIY Network, Cooking Channel and country music network Great American Country (GAC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is key a member of the creative team and responsible for developing and executing the visual brand identity through art direction on promotion campaigns, marketing events and multi platform brand initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages resource expectations of on-air promotional spots, network packages and presentation tapes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and animate a wide range of projects for the marketing and creative team, along with other internal stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with outside designers and producers to articulate creative solutions for promos, network packaging, print material and other projects touching the brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in the entire process from pre-production to delivery of product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates and presents concepts, design solutions and the final end product to the SVP, Marketing and Creative and other decision makers in a professional manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translates project characteristics and creative direction into concepts and design solutions, which further the network identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides art direction for video/film shoots connected to assigned projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly brings to the table fresh ideas and techniques being used in the industry to creatively promote network content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement appropriate processes to sustain organizational flow for fluctuating volume of work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to maintain team-oriented professionalism with a strong ability to take initiative in this position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads, inspires and educates co-workers and reports on new production techniques, styles, and providers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of editing, shooting and directing as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directs third party vendors on priority projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops internal presentations and reels as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of design practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logo design and layout skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage to a deadline in conjunction with other team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work as a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to give creative constructive feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verbal and written communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate visually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage the work of self and others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge in design and animation tools including Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, and After Effects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of 3D animation software, including Cinema 4D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of editing software, like Final Cut Pro or Adobe Premiere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of video production and photography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of post production processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Math skills as they relate to budget management and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Physical Requirements and Work Environment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sedentary work standard office environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May work evenings and travel occasionally, 10% maximum travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Educational and Experience Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelors degree in graphic design or a related field or equivalent year for year experience and 3-5 years progressively complex experience in graphic/layout design, and company branding or a related field.  Exposure to a production, post-production or a broadcast environment and/or 2-3 years experience at Design Firm, or TV required.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-scripps-networks-interactive-knoxville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-scripps-networks-interactive-knoxville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>