<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tn-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at Scripps Networks Interactive in Knoxville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Scripps Networks Interactive (SNI) is actively seeking a Designer in Knoxville, TN. Scripps Networks Interactive is one of the leading developers of lifestyle-oriented content for television and the Internet, where on-air programming is complemented with online video, social media areas and e-commerce components on companion Web sites and broadband vertical channels. The company&amp;rsquo;s media portfolio includes popular lifestyle television and Internet brands HGTV, Food Network, Travel Channel, DIY Network, Cooking Channel and country music network Great American Country (GAC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is key a member of the creative team and responsible for developing and executing the visual brand identity through art direction on promotion campaigns, marketing events and multi platform brand initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages resource expectations of on-air promotional spots, network packages and presentation tapes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and animate a wide range of projects for the marketing and creative team, along with other internal stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with outside designers and producers to articulate creative solutions for promos, network packaging, print material and other projects touching the brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in the entire process from pre-production to delivery of product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates and presents concepts, design solutions and the final end product to the SVP, Marketing and Creative and other decision makers in a professional manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translates project characteristics and creative direction into concepts and design solutions, which further the network identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides art direction for video/film shoots connected to assigned projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly brings to the table fresh ideas and techniques being used in the industry to creatively promote network content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement appropriate processes to sustain organizational flow for fluctuating volume of work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to maintain team-oriented professionalism with a strong ability to take initiative in this position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads, inspires and educates co-workers and reports on new production techniques, styles, and providers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of editing, shooting and directing as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directs third party vendors on priority projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops internal presentations and reels as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of design practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logo design and layout skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage to a deadline in conjunction with other team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work as a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to give creative constructive feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verbal and written communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate visually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage the work of self and others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge in design and animation tools including Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, and After Effects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of 3D animation software, including Cinema 4D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of editing software, like Final Cut Pro or Adobe Premiere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of video production and photography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of post production processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Math skills as they relate to budget management and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Physical Requirements and Work Environment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sedentary work standard office environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May work evenings and travel occasionally, 10% maximum travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Educational and Experience Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelors degree in graphic design or a related field or equivalent year for year experience and 3-5 years progressively complex experience in graphic/layout design, and company branding or a related field.  Exposure to a production, post-production or a broadcast environment and/or 2-3 years experience at Design Firm, or TV required.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-scripps-networks-interactive-knoxville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-scripps-networks-interactive-knoxville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>