<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tn-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Wordpress Graphic Designer at Gannett Local in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a graphic design expert with the urge to join an edgy, forward-thinking start-up company funded by GANNETT? If so, we are looking for you! The Digital Graphic Designer will create, layout, and produce digital graphic designs for a variety of digital formats. They will design by combining the elements of customer provided materials, rough ideas and design concepts. They will also design Facebook pages; prepare material to meet client standards, and review and proof artwork for quality, content and accuracy. The Digital Graphic Designer will play in integral role for our company and our clients by creating micro sites, banner ads, search engine optimization changes, and landing pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At GannettLocal, we assist small to medium size companies by growing their business with online and print advertising.  With the power of Gannett, the company behind USA Today, The Arizona Republic and azcentral.com, we will jump start their online advertising campaigns and drive traffic to their website by acquiring top placement on Google, Yahoo and Bing.  Additionally, we will increase consumer awareness by positioning our client’s business on Google Maps, and ensuring that they stay top-of-mind through attention-grabbing advertisements in The Arizona Republic, the largest local newspaper in Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate should have previous experience in graphic design, with a creative portfolio of previous work. They should also possess strong knowledge and proficiency in Facebook Design, Word Press and iFrames as well as the ability to conceptualize, create and design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High school diploma or equivalent required; college degree preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years graphic design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand and apply image/branding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge and proficiency of Facebook Design, Word Press and iFrames&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to know where to find answers when creating&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent proofreading, spelling, grammar and punctuation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detailed oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple ads simultaneously under the pressure of deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills, with the ability to work in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web ad building skills, including; PHP, CSS, HTML, and FBML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CS4 and greater Adobe Suite for Design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Compensation Structure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive Health, Dental and Vision coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(K) Saving Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Referral Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Time Off (PTO)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Company Holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Mortgage Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adoption Assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Discount Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Gannett Local is an Equal Opportunity Employer and a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/wordpress-graphic-designer-gannett-local-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/wordpress-graphic-designer-gannett-local-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer/Developer at Vanderbuilt University in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Vanderbilt University is seeking a Web developer to provide programming and Web development support for University Web Communications, which is the central Web development office for Vanderbilt University (http://web.vanderbilt.edu/).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a very small, very awesome team that works closely together on all projects. We’re looking for someone equally awesome to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position will be responsible for building and maintaining sites within the University’s two content management systems (OmniUpdate and WordPress), providing training and support for users of those sites and providing overall support for the university’s primary Web presences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the Web developer will provide training for users of the university’s two content management systems, will respond to help desk inquiries, will often be responsible for migration of content from pre-existing systems to our systems, and will develop screencasts and screenshot-based tutorials to assist users with functionality of our systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will be comfortable managing 20-30 open projects, enjoy working with clients and possess a strong desire to learn new skills and tackle new challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position requires an associate’s degree and a minimum of 24 months relevant experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic programming skills: XHTML, CSS, PHP, mySQL, jQuery and JavaScript, with willingness / ability to learn more. Comfortable creating simple CRUD applications for data management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic familiarity with working in Linux, Apache and IIS server environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear understanding and knowledge of Web development best practices, standards, accessibility, information architecture, securing and protecting data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with content management systems. Experience coding within WordPress a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle 20-30 ongoing projects while also taking on new projects and handling emergencies that may arise (should enjoy this type of environment – there will always be multiple projects with simultaneous deadlines)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work within short-turnaround deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable speaking in front of groups (15-20 people) on a regular basis (leading training classes and/or providing informational sessions about the work of the office)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Photoshop (layers, masking, the basics); designing within and without constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in database design and optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work both independently and as a team member.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and ability to communicate effectively with internal and external customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor’s degree preferred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, launch and maintain sites within university-supported content management systems for campus clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, plan, test, and implement product features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide training and support for content management systems clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in management of Help Desk tickets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Migrate content from existing sites to new sites as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop custom applications as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide support and maintenance of university’s YouTube channel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide support for email newsletters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage multiple project requests and timelines simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document software implementation and operation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assure security and privacy protocols are followed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assume additional responsibilities as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time position. Candidate must possess a willingness to work additional hours on evenings and weekends when required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Background screens will be performed and education will be verified prior to employment. Please be prepared to provide required information and/or documentation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Job requires Associates and 2 years of experience or the equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-developer-vanderbuilt-university-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-developer-vanderbuilt-university-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Marriott International, Inc in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Gaylord Hotels is a multi-location hospitality brand guided by a single focus: extraordinary meetings and conventions. From guest rooms and meeting space, to entertainment and dining all in a self-contained environment, Gaylord Hotels makes meeting planning easy and provides attendees great networking opportunities. As a Gaylord Hotels STAR, you&amp;rsquo;ll bring your warm smile, genuine excitement and a “consider it done” spirit to work. In return, you’ll experience the rewards of growing your career among a team of professionals with a passion for excellence. Ready for a change? Take the initiative. Enjoy the Rewards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB SUMMARY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designs and produces marketing materials including, but not limited to, advertisements, collateral, signage, flash pieces, electronic brochures and presentations to drive hotel revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;CANDIDATE PROFILE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education and Experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High school diploma or GED;
  5 years experience in the customer service, call center operations, or related professional area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;OR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associates or Bachelors degree in Computer Graphics or a related field, or related major; 3 years experience in Computer Graphics or a related professional area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;CORE WORK ACTIVITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Graphic Design Operations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops various forms of creative design, computer graphics, production layout and marketing support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and revises print and multimedia collateral to reflect the current brand look&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages the look and feel, concept, visual development and final execution of all design directions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partners with Marketing managers and related operational departments as part of a project team providing design, conceptualization and solutions pertaining to deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains familiarity with customer demographics and develops an appropriate look and feel for all promotion and event related collateral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitors the progress of all projects. Provides continuous communication to the Marketing and/or Project team regarding ongoing projects and status updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executes various aspects of production including scanning, digital retouching, image editing, special effects, file manipulation and layout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoots digital production issues as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains project files and archives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Additional Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides support for escalated support needs via telephone and email and ensures proper resolution of each, including direct contact with stakeholders when necessary. Responds to and handles problems and complaints.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages the communication of trends via prepared reports to the appropriate personnel, as well as corporate headquarters and other service centers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other reasonable requests by management which the associate is capable of performing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-marriott-international-inc-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-marriott-international-inc-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at Asurion in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a talented designer to create visually engaging experiences. The design role depends greatly on user-centered design principles and usability testing to guide designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this position you&amp;rsquo;ll work with other team members to define, create and maintain great user experience. The ideal candidate will have great creative, problem solving, and leadership skills. You&amp;rsquo;ll be responsible for all phases of user experience design, from concept to on-going maintenance, ensuring that great design and interaction meet the business, customer and technical requirements. Excellent visual design, written and oral communication skills a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a position for someone that is passionate about web development and mobile. While we will consider all qualified candidates, this is not a position for people looking to diversify their experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Interaction Designer is responsible for helping create world class online user experiences, continually improve pattern libraries and support brand standards through interface design. This role will work closely with the Sr. Manage Online Experience, Process Engineers, Business Architects, Testers and Analytics to define, deliver and measure projects that improve a customer’s experience on the web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years experience creating high design sense with production value websites and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of digital and mobile technologies and trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience working to conceptualize and define web products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working under pressure with aggressive deadline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong visual design sense with clean typography, page and web layout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of UX design processes and methodology, particularly as applied to cross-device experiences and responsive design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototyping skills including sketching, wireframing &amp;amp; information visualization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTML, CSS, Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with jQuery, MooTools, and other JavaScript a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to clearly articulate your design decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with the ability to work independently and collaboratively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with an iterative design process that includes accepting and managing feedback and constructive criticism.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with best practices for web usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;TRAVEL:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position may require up to 10% travel.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-asurion-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-asurion-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer at Scripps Networks Interactive in Knoxville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Scripps Networks Interactive (SNI) is actively seeking a Designer in Knoxville, TN. Scripps Networks Interactive is one of the leading developers of lifestyle-oriented content for television and the Internet, where on-air programming is complemented with online video, social media areas and e-commerce components on companion Web sites and broadband vertical channels. The company&amp;rsquo;s media portfolio includes popular lifestyle television and Internet brands HGTV, Food Network, Travel Channel, DIY Network, Cooking Channel and country music network Great American Country (GAC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is key a member of the creative team and responsible for developing and executing the visual brand identity through art direction on promotion campaigns, marketing events and multi platform brand initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages resource expectations of on-air promotional spots, network packages and presentation tapes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and animate a wide range of projects for the marketing and creative team, along with other internal stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with outside designers and producers to articulate creative solutions for promos, network packaging, print material and other projects touching the brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in the entire process from pre-production to delivery of product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicates and presents concepts, design solutions and the final end product to the SVP, Marketing and Creative and other decision makers in a professional manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translates project characteristics and creative direction into concepts and design solutions, which further the network identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides art direction for video/film shoots connected to assigned projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly brings to the table fresh ideas and techniques being used in the industry to creatively promote network content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement appropriate processes to sustain organizational flow for fluctuating volume of work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to maintain team-oriented professionalism with a strong ability to take initiative in this position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads, inspires and educates co-workers and reports on new production techniques, styles, and providers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of editing, shooting and directing as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directs third party vendors on priority projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops internal presentations and reels as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of design practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logo design and layout skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage to a deadline in conjunction with other team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work as a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to give creative constructive feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verbal and written communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate visually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage the work of self and others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge in design and animation tools including Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, and After Effects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of 3D animation software, including Cinema 4D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of editing software, like Final Cut Pro or Adobe Premiere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of video production and photography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of post production processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Math skills as they relate to budget management and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Physical Requirements and Work Environment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sedentary work standard office environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May work evenings and travel occasionally, 10% maximum travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Educational and Experience Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelors degree in graphic design or a related field or equivalent year for year experience and 3-5 years progressively complex experience in graphic/layout design, and company branding or a related field.  Exposure to a production, post-production or a broadcast environment and/or 2-3 years experience at Design Firm, or TV required.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-scripps-networks-interactive-knoxville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-scripps-networks-interactive-knoxville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>