<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tn-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Interactive Designer/Art Director at The Buntin Group in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Buntin Group is seeking a senior interactive designer/art director for our growing digital team. This person will work in partnership with the interactive creative director in the development of concepts, design and production across a wide variety of digital initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senior interactive designer/art director will develop interface designs for websites, interactive and rich media banner ads, mobile and iPad apps, online branded experiences, and more. As the digital team grows, this role will be responsible for mentoring designers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate lives and breathes digital design and possesses strong visualization and story telling skills. He/she should be personable, fun, driven and excited to work as part of an award-winning creative team to concept and execute industry-leading creative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re passionate about new technology, an expert at creating clean, functional and responsive web designs that engage and inspire action, and you enjoy the challenges and rewards of working in a dynamic agency, this could be a good fit for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years of digital concept, design and execution experience (digital agency experience preferred).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid portfolio of work across digital mediums for national brands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess a deep knowledge of design tools (Adobe Creative Suite).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem-solver who constantly finds ways to express complex ideas through intuitive, responsive design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work independently and efficiently in a fast-paced, dynamic environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands the agency culture of deadlines and willing to make sacrifices required to meet them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firm understanding of information architecture and interaction design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A comprehensive knowledge front-end development (HTML/CSS) as it relates to design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to lead projects and understand how to weave creative solutions for complex business and marketing objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design for the idiosyncrasies between Firefox, Chrome, Safari, Opera and IE6 &amp;ndash; IE9.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always strives to produce the highest quality digital work that’s on brand and ahead of the curve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interactive-designer-art-director-the-buntin-group-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-interactive-designer-art-director-the-buntin-group-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>