<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tn-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Emma, Inc. in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Emma&amp;rsquo;s development team is on the lookout for a talented, focused front end web developer/designer who has experience with user interface design and creating website mockups and finished products that perform beautifully across multiple browsers and devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this role, you&amp;rsquo;ll work alongside other developers to promote a downright fabulous customer experience, bringing your technical mastery of modern interface design to Emma&amp;rsquo;s unique sense of style and rapidly growing application. It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect opportunity for the detail-minded person who loves collaborating to create delight for users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When inquiring, please include links to samples of previous interface and web development work in your resume or cover note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for candidates who have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in HTML, CSS, jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Backbone.js and a scripting language like Python, Ruby, or PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with HTML5, CSS3 and responsive web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with version control systems, preferably Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with popular open APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideally, two or more years of website design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience being part of teams for multiple websites, with at least one role leading the design and front end development from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-emma-inc-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-emma-inc-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Papercut Interactive in Chattanooga, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Papercut Interactive &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.papercutinteractive.com&quot;&gt;http://www.papercutinteractive.com&lt;/a&gt; is looking for a Front End Web Developer to join our team. This person will participate in the development and implementation of desktop and responsive websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our new developer will be friendly, approachable, and excited about the web and its possibilities. The developer will work with our programming team, designers, and account managers and will have direct contact with clients when necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in mid to large-scale website development efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate expertise with a broad set of development tools/technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a firm understanding of development methods and architectures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide support to the sales effort on new business development pursuits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty satisfactorily. The requirements listed below are representative of the knowledge, skill, and/or ability required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering, or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end and Back-end experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ExpressionEngine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;E-commerce development experience desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to define, create, and complete a technical task with minimal guidance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to articulate a vision of the total solution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to meet deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Creative, Casual Work Environment:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Papercut Interactive is committed to fostering a friendly, productive work environment. Your ideas will be heard and you will contribute directly to the success of the client, Papercut Interactive, and yourself on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe that doing our best work is an important part of life – but it’s just one part. Our team works hard when we’re working, and we aim to live balanced lives. Family, friends, pets, hobbies, events, and causes all contribute to the people we are and will become.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits Include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two weeks of personal time off plus many holidays (including your birthday!), Paid time off for community service, Retirement Savings Plan, Health and Wellness Reimbursement, and a Creative Education Allotment.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-papercut-interactive-chattanooga-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-papercut-interactive-chattanooga-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at cj Advertising in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We offer a comprehensive benefits package including: Medical, Dental, Vision, Life, and L.T.D. Insurance; a generous vacation package; flexible hours; and casual dress environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Front-End Developer develops usable, functional, responsive websites that are optimized for all major browsers on all major operating systems and devices. The Front-End Developer creates current W3C spec (currently HTML5) websites by following and implementing best development practices as determined by industry standards and the Front-End Development Manager. The Front-End Developer reports to the Front-End Development Manager, collaborates with the Web Design, SEO/SEM, and Content Teams, and follows project guidelines and deadlines set by the Project Management Team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a strong knowledge of HTML5, CSS 2, CSS 3, and JavaScript (jQuery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is familiar with the major browsers and operating systems used by web traffic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is familiar with the various versions of major browsers, specifically Internet Explorer, asthey pertain to web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work, collaborate, and play well with others in a team-based environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably has some experience and/or knowledge of PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably has experience working with WordPress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates usable, functional, responsive websites that are optimized for all major browsers on all major operating systems and devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follows the best development practices as outlined by the Front-End Development Manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates clean, solid, semantic markup with as little overhead and redundancy as possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates sites that match site mockups as closely as possible across all major browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains a knowledge and learning of current industry standards and uses them where appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with web designers to ensure that site designs are optimized for practical development solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents code and markup as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support Help Desk and Help Desk tickets as necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-cj-advertising-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-cj-advertising-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at GannettLocal in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;GannettLocal was founded in 2009 to help small- and medium-sized businesses find and retain local customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a division of Gannett Incorporated, which manages popular community newspapers such as The Arizona Republic as well as cutting-edge online properties like CareerBuilder.com, GannettLocal has the resources and expertise to reach potential customers through a powerful, yet affordable, suite of multiplatform solutions (search engine marketing, email, digital display, and geo-targeted print/flyers). Our vision is to serve as a one-stop shop for businesses that want to expand their clientele, increase their sales and stay competitive in today’s market. That’s why we insist that our Local Marketing Specialists become experts in a particular local market and industry and stay on top of what’s working in the local marketing space. Plus, by working with a Specialist, every one of our clients gains a long-term business growth partner who will customize a local marketing solution for their business and then work with them on an ongoing basis to ensure their strategy is up-to-date – and to identify further opportunities for success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At GannettLocal, we know that the local marketing space is crowded with companies and solutions, all claiming to be able to produce results for your business. So, why choose us? It’s simple. We have the experience that comes from being part of the nation’s largest media group, the ability to offer you cutting-edge digital marketing solutions, and the passion for helping small businesses succeed. How many of our competitors can say all of that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a Website Developer II to join our team in Nashville, TN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you a front-end website developer looking for an opportunity in a fast-paced, forward-thinking and growing company? If so, we are looking for you! The Website Developer II will create, layout, and produce our client’s websites from start to finish.  They will develop by combining the elements of customer provided materials, content, images, and professionally designed artwork.   This position does NOT require artwork to be designed, we have Website Designers who do that.  Technologies are primarily all open source CMS systems with a focus on WordPress and Drupal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Presenting a portfolio is a requirement for this role.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High school diploma or equivalent required; college degree preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a minimum of 3 years experience with website design, development and programming, including technologies such as PHP, mySQL, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Drupal and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CMS such as Drupal, WordPress, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with all aspects of creating, launching and maintaining websites and major hardware/software associated with this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe web suite and be able to slice website designs and create HTML pages from documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with all aspects of creating, launching and maintaining websites and major hardware/software associated with this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe webs suite and be able to slice website designs and create HTML and CSS from Photoshop documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Competitive Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also offer a full benefits package which includes medical, dental, vision, life insurance, short-term disability, long-term disability, free onsite fitness center, onsite cafeteria, discount downtown off street parking, employee discounts, employee assistance program, 401(k) with company match and domestic partner benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are continuing to build a dedicated team of hard working, motivated and innovative professionals.  If you want to be part of a talented team who are passionate about the work they do, we want to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer that echoes the diversity of our community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-gannett-local-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-gannett-local-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Digital Reasoning in Franklin, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;INTERESTED IN WORK THAT MATTERS?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital Reasoning delivers Automated Understanding for Big Data with its flagship product Synthesys.  Automated Understanding analyzes unstructured and structured big data to reveal hidden and potentially valuable relationships between people, place and time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Digital Reasoning we push the limits of what’s possible every day, and we are committed to using the most cutting edge, open source tools that are available in order to deliver the next disruptive platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;WHAT WE GIVE YOU.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will provide you with the latest tools, hardware, and services to let you write, test, and deploy code as quickly and creatively as possible.  We will give you the autonomy you need so that you can deliver all of the high quality and groundbreaking code that you want.  We will make you part of a team that focuses on delivering the best product every time without any egos, politics, or red tape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also have unlimited, free soda to fuel your furious coding habits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;WHAT WE NEED FROM YOU.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, we want you to produce top-notch, standards compliant JavaScript and CSS.  This means you know the JavaScript language, and you have working knowledge of jQuery UI, ExtJS, mooTools, or scriptaculous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It means that you can hand roll your own style sheet to make a great looking product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the technology, we want someone who is passionate, driven, and looking to join a company that is here to make a difference in the world, and not someone simply looking for their next job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to hit the ground running and become a contributor quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;WHAT WOULD SET YOU APART?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can churn out quality Python code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in distributed source control tools such as Git or Mercurial.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know LESS, SASS, and the capabilities of CSS3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re comfortable using Linux on Amazon’s EC2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve been the lean on one or more web site, or web application projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re doing something really cool that’s not your job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelors or Masters degree in Computer Science.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To be considered for this position please submit your resume to bruce.strugatch@digitalreasoning.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-digital-reasoning-franklin-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-digital-reasoning-franklin-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>