<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tn-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior iOS Developer at Aloompa in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for a energetic, hungry, fast-learner to join our team at Aloompa as a Senior iOS mobile app developer. Aloompa is the leading provider of turn-key, best-in-class mobile applications for music, food, conference and community focused events in the U.S. and abroad. Some current clients include Bonnaroo Music &amp;amp; Arts Festival, Electric Forest Festival, Mountain Jam, Hangout Music Fest, and many others (more at aloompa.com). We’re not looking for divas. We require someone who wants to grow and reap the rewards that come with working in a small and agile team. You would be responsible for contributing to the full software delivery cycle:  feature definition, planning, estimation, development, testing, deployment and maintenance. Because we work on the bleeding edge of a lot of technologies, you are someone who problem solves creatively, learns quickly, and works productively both independently and collaboratively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Ideal Candidate:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. or M.S. Computer Science or 4+ years in relevant work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Cocoa touch/Objective C programming skills and related frameworks, Multithreading, memory management specific to mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a few great apps on the App Store and/or examples of your work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of mobile development process and experience building apps from the ground up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SQL, CoreData, CoreGraphics, RESTful API Consumption, HTML,  and version control (github-flow)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of design patterns, algorithms and a love for elegant designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototype new and refactor existing features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Personality wishlist:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re happy, humble, and honest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re tenacious… you don’t work around obstacles, you DESTROY them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re a team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re a good shot. (Yeah, we have one of these in our office: http://bit.ly/WzR5jt)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you think you’d be a great addition to our team, please reach out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serious applicants only. No recruiters or international candidates, please!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Aloompa:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2009, Aloompa is the leading provider of turn-key, best-in-class mobile applications for music, food, conference and community focused events in the U.S. and abroad. We love events of all sizes and flavors, and we LOVE to make apps that are functional, beautiful, appropriate, and affordable for any size or type of event. Our primary goal in designing mobile event guides is to eliminate the complications, so that no matter what, even our grandmothers can navigate them with ease. We are always in the kitchen tinkering with new ideas and recipes, trying to create the next best thing in mobile event experiences. Come and join us in the fun!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-aloompa-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ios-developer-aloompa-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front End/Mobile Developer at Vanderbilt University in Nashville, TN</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a member of our awesome web development team, you will design and implement innovative mobile solutions to meet the Medical Center&amp;rsquo;s key objectives, support existing apps and work collaboratively with the technical and design teams for solutions to both web and mobile platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a group environment to plan and design new mobile and web products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, plan, test, and implement product features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perform maintenance programming and updates to existing apps&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in quality assurance planning and testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop standards for mobile development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document software implementation and operation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assure security and privacy protocols are followed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current on mobile technology innovations and trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with server administrators to ensure infrastructure stability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assume additional responsibilities as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years industry-level experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years mobile application development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/MS in Computer Science or related field preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with iOS development and administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of object-oriented development, use of design patterns and system architecture for mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of interactive touch/gesture interfaces, application development paradigms and memory management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in database design and optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with HTML5, CSS, and Javascript and Javascript frameworks (e.g. jquery, script.aculo.us)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task and handle more than one project at a time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to work in a team environment and communicate effectively with internal and external customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Pluses:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Experience with&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Android development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP/MySQL experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;implementing and using unit testing and GIT source control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Job requires Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s and 3 years of experience or the equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-mobile-developer-vanderbilt-university-nashville-tn</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-mobile-developer-vanderbilt-university-nashville-tn</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>