<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Ruby on Rails Developer at PeopleAdmin, Inc. in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You’re a full stack Ruby on Rails developer, you love it, and you’re really good at it. You could code anywhere. You could build a career, work with a strong team, be intellectually and creatively challenged at any number of great companies. But going beyond the code to find a deeper purpose for your efforts is something quite rare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PeopleAdmin pairs trailblazing Rails development with the goal of helping higher education institutions. Our Senior Software Engineers are characterized as intelligent, passionate, driven, curious, inventive and diligent; They’re driving change daily, pushing the Ruby on Rails envelope when crafting elegant solutions to the challenges posed by our high-scale, cloud-based SAAS product suite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our dev team functions in a collaborative environment, adhering to a philosophy of agile practices, open-source involvement, test-driven development, shared ownership and individual as well as team growth. There are no ivory towers here. Only an idea meritocracy where we work together to discover and deliver solutions of value to our business and the greater good of higher education that PeopleAdmin serves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you crave a pathway to drive a deeper impact, a product that will challenge you and a team that works side by side to grow and evolve, PeopleAdmin may be the right place for you. We are looking for senior software engineers with strong combinations of skills and experience in the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core : Ruby and Ruby on Rails, Web application development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front end : Javascript, HTML, CSS, design &amp;amp; interaction, rich interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database : MySQL, SQL, efficient data retrieval&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Middleware : Redis/Resque, Memcached&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architecture : Messaging/Message Queues, Backgrounding, Pub/Sub, Integrations, SOA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ops/Deployment : Capistrano, Chef, *nix skill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Methodologies : Scrum/Agile, TDD, pair-programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enterprise-class Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of full-text search technologies (Lucene, Sphinx, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Rackspace or Amazon Web Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Redis &amp;amp; Resque&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with DevOps for large scale Rails application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong debugging and data spelunking skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Our team members are rewarded for their skill and expertise. Beyond competitive compensation, there are quite a few perks to the job, including…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working with a great team: You’ll have to meet us to see!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non-accrual paid time off: Take the time you need as negotiated with your manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flexible work schedules/locations: Want to work from the Grand Canyon via satellite for a couple weeks? No problem. We have a distributed team and are well set up with tools like Campfire to facilitate working remotely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Company’s investment in you: Whether it’s books, courses, screencasts, or conferences, we provide ways for our developers to keep their knowledge current and their skills sharp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Support for a healthy lifestyle: An on-site
Whole Foods cafeteria and gym/exercise room with shower&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BS Preferred&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Posting Specific Questions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required fields are indicated with an asterisk (*).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How did you hear about this employment opportunity?

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;*  PeopleAdmin Website
*  Employee Referral
*  37Signals
*  Indeed.com
*  LinkedIn
*  github
*  WorkCreative.com
*  Dice
*  University Job Board
*  Other
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you answered &amp;ldquo;Employee Referral&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Other,&amp;rdquo; please provide your referral source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  (Open Ended Question)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Applicant Documents :&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Required Documents : Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optional Documents : Cover Letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-on-rails-developer-peopleadmin-inc-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-ruby-on-rails-developer-peopleadmin-inc-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Ruby on Rails Developer at ZOLL in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between this job and being a super hero? Both involve saving lives, but we actually pay you.
We are the leader for management and training of life saving devices such as defibrillators. We have the resources and stability of a large company, but the nimbleness, ambition, and determination of a startup, because we used to be one.
We have a small, highly motivated team and the most important thing is to be a demonstrated self-starter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What we have to offer you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did I mention super hero? Our office is casual enough you could wear a super hero costume, although shorts and flip flops may be more appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intellectually engaging discussions about software architecture among self-proclaimed experts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appreciation that the work you do makes us a better company (mostly in the form of a competitive salary and benefits, but could also include cookies).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We mean what we say &amp;ndash; We&amp;rsquo;re on Forbes list of 100 Most Trustworthy Companies for three consecutive years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stability &amp;ndash; We&amp;rsquo;re on Fortune&amp;rsquo;s list of 100 Fastest-Growing Companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we are looking for from you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Super hero like ability to adapt to whatever is thrown at you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby on Rails coding skills that would make DHH proud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nearly insatiable appetite to solve difficult problems fast, which may mean the fewest CPU cycles or developer cycles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ok, and maybe some technical prowess with Git/Github, TDD, Postgres, OSX, Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design/front-end skills are a big plus &amp;ndash; particularly standards-based clean, maintainable markup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sense of humor, because really, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t this all be fun?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Ruby on Rails Developer at ZOLL in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between this job and being a super hero? Both involve saving lives, but we actually pay you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are the leader for management and training of life saving devices such as defibrillators. We have the resources and stability of a large company, but the nimbleness, ambition, and determination of a startup, because we used to be one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a small, highly motivated team and the most important thing is to be a demonstrated self-starter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What we have to offer you:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did I mention super hero? Our office is casual enough you could wear a super hero costume, although shorts and flip flops may be more appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intellectually engaging discussions about software architecture among self-proclaimed experts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appreciation that the work you do makes us a better company (mostly in the form of a competitive salary and benefits, but could also include cookies).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We mean what we say &amp;ndash; We&amp;rsquo;re on Forbes list of 100 Most Trustworthy Companies for three consecutive years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stability &amp;ndash; We&amp;rsquo;re on Fortune&amp;rsquo;s list of 100 Fastest-Growing Companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What we are looking for from you:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Super hero like ability to adapt to whatever is thrown at you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby on Rails coding skills that would make DHH proud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nearly insatiable appetite to solve difficult problems fast, which may mean the fewest CPU cycles or developer cycles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ok, and maybe some technical prowess with Git/Github, TDD, Postgres, OSX, Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web design/front-end skills are a big plus &amp;ndash; particularly standards-based clean, maintainable markup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sense of humor, because really, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t this all be fun?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ruby-on-rails-developer-zoll-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at FXCM Inc. in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;FXCM Inc. (NYSE: FXCM) is a global online provider of foreign exchange (forex) trading and related services to retail and institutional customers world-wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of FXCM&amp;rsquo;s client offering is No Dealing Desk forex trading. Clients benefit from FXCM’s large network of forex liquidity providers enabling FXCM to offer competitive spreads on major currency pairs. Clients have the advantage of mobile trading, one-click order execution and trading from real-time charts. FXCM&amp;rsquo;s U.K. subsidiary, Forex Capital Markets Limited, also offers CFD products with no re-quote trading and allows clients to trade oil, gold, silver and stock indices along with forex on one platform. In addition, FXCM offers educational courses on forex trading and provides free news and market research through DailyFX.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a talented Web Developer to join our in-house Design team. The successful candidate, in conjunction with the web team, will be responsible for the front end coding of our suite of websites, working to maintain our existing sites, as well as developing new sites and new functionality as our company continues to expand. The web team is part of a larger marketing team which produces content under strict deadlines, so the web developer often handles several tasks at a time and must be able to complete them in a fast-paced setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new HTML/CSS pages from Photoshop mock-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on day-to-day upkeep and maintenance of existing sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use jquery to enhance user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adhere to design standards set forth by management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liaise with other departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Photoshop, Dreamweaver, and other standard web design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High Proficiency with JavaScript; some familiarity and experience with jQuery is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of AJAX/PHP/JSP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of XML, databases, and content management systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong sense of typography and composition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical thinking and excellent problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong multi tasking skills and able to work under tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills, a resourceful and friendly attitude, and a genuine interest in participating within a team-driven environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications and Requirements:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be eligible to work in the US (No H1 Visa Sponsorship)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience with HTML and CSS; familiarity and experience with HTML5 and CSS3 a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Prior to submitting your resume, the firm requests that you do the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review the firm’s website thoroughly: www.fxcm.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please include a link of your portfolio within your resume (candidates who do not have an online portfolio will not be considered)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please provide your salary range requirement for further consideration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Salary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commensurate with experience plus potential discretionary year-end bonus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We understand that top performers in the current marketplace are attracted to companies offering competitive pay, benefits and opportunities for professional development. In light of this, we offer a Comprehensive Employee Benefits Program that includes the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Savings Plan (401K)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical &amp;amp; Health Care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prescription Drug Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee and Dependent Life Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short Term and Long Term Disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Time-Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pre-Tax Commuter Reimbursement Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Referral Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-fxcm-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-fxcm-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>