<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Web Designer at Music One Live in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The designer will oversee the design and development of multiple client websites, mainly in the music realm.  Responsibilities touch all stages of the development lifecycle, from gathering requirements to managing design and development teams both local and overseas. The person in this role is ultimately accountable for the final product and will serve as the go-to for all requests related to client websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements &amp;ndash;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects at one time across many different  individuals and teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of design principles with a proven track record and stellar portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to date with current technologies and topics in web design (responsiveness, Sass, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great HTML/CSS skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with one or more popular CMS frameworks, especially Wordpress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident but humble personality that enjoys debating opposing ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The drive to be continuously learning and improving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all, a strong passion for your craft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What We Offer &amp;ndash;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A small team that is focused and passionate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relaxed, laid back environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities for growth and education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All the foosball you can handle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Music One Live:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music One Live is an independently owned and operated technology company for music artists, venues, sports, and concert/event promoters. For more information visit our website at www.musiconelive.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-music-one-live-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-music-one-live-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface &amp; Graphic Designer at vAuto in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time position with vAuto, a business unit of AutoTrader Group, located in Austin, TX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an experienced user interface and user interaction designer to help develop user flows and graphic assets for mobile applications, web applications and mobile web applications.  This person’s responsibilities will include conceptualization, design and production of mobile apps, emails, web, video and brochures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;vAuto, Inc. is an industry leading innovator and provider of automotive software solutions. Since the company was founded in 2005, vAuto has launched several first-in industry innovations, including its current site of solutions that deliver a better way to price, appraise and stock pre-owned vehicles. We are a fast-moving technology company specializing in web &amp;amp; mobile application solutions for the Automotive Industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years in user interface design and graphics design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2 years with HTML, CSS, and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience designing mobile workflows and graphics. (At least 1 application available in an app store).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating wire-frames to communicate workflows and ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert proficiency in Adobe products, especially Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong eye for layout, color and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated and self-driven&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to manage multiple projects at once in a fast-paced work environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with current and upcoming trends in mobile and web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-%26-graphic-designer-vauto-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-%26-graphic-designer-vauto-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Liaison Resources in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Liaison is seeking a mid-level Graphic Designer responsible for creating corporate marketing and sales collateral while adhering to the set corporate brand guidelines. In addition, one who is capable of proofing and editing work as needed. This role would be responsible for the design development and execution of multi-component marketing programs to support field marketing efforts by creating such online and print materials as: PowerPoint presentations, email campaigns, brochures, booklets, business forms, newsletters, and other communications.
* Strong, conceptual, layout and design skills with a focus on response marketing;
* Quick, confident technical knowledge and solid design aesthetics required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Background &amp;amp; Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in graphic design or related field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years experience wthin a corporate and/or agency environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web-based portfolio must demonstrate creativity and sophisticated design/marketing concepts, strong emphasis on direct response marketing strategies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having worked successfullywith corporate brand guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Hard Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge and experience with Adobe Creative Suite and Microsoft Office Suite working on PC platforms;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient HTML, savvy in Flash and Dreamweaver;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident proofreader and editor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Soft Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational &amp;amp; communication skills (written &amp;amp; verbal);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work both independently and as a member of a team, from concept to completion;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively participate and contribute in brainstorm sessions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent time-management skills. Able to juggle multiple tasks and aggressive daily deadlines with minimal supervision;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extraordinary attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Details:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time, ongoing position on Liaison&amp;rsquo;s marketing team working onsite at a global computer manufacturing company. Details will be provided during the interview process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Compensation:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full employee benefits package includes 100% Liaison-paid PPO medical and dental insurance, paid vacation/sick and holiday leave, 401k program with company matching, short- and long-term disability insurance and optional supplemental insurance coverage. Details will be provided at time of job offer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-liaison-resources-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-liaison-resources-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Designer at Electronic Arts in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;EA SPORTS is one of the leading sports entertainment brands in the world, with top-selling videogame franchises, award-winning interactive technology, global videogame competitions and breakthrough digital experiences. EA SPORTS delivers personal access to the emotion of sports through industry-leading sports simulation videogames, including Madden NFL football, FIFA Soccer, NHL® hockey, NBA JAM basketball, NCAA® Football, Fight Night boxing, EA SPORTS MMA, Tiger Woods PGA TOUR® golf, and EA SPORTS Active. For more information about EA SPORTS, including news, video, blogs, forums and game apps, please visit www.easports.com to connect, share and compete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Game Designers are responsible for creating games played by millions of people around the world. Game design is a highly creative and specialized craft. Some games can be developed relatively quickly, while others can take many years to go from an idea all the way into the hands of our consumers. Like many other jobs in gaming, game design is becoming increasingly specialized. On the most basic level, it’s the responsibility of the game designer to make games fun. A game designer defines the game and outlines it’s progression in a game design document, which is a blueprint for game design that includes information about the game’s characters, worlds, story, and more. Everyone wants to be the next Will Wright, Steven Spielberg, Neil Young or Alex Ward but few are as the creation of a great gaming experience, holding the attention of millions of gamers for many hours, is a real challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Role Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Game Designers are responsible for devising what a game consists of and how it plays, following the vision of the Creative/Game Director. They plan and define all the elements and components of a game, including its setting, structure, rules, story flow, characters, objects, vehicles, and devices available to the characters; interface design; and game modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originality and creativity are valued, but a thorough knowledge of a game’s target audience and market is equally if not more important. Game Designers should also have a deep understanding of the capabilities and benefits of different hardware platforms (e.g., PC, console, mobile devices), as well as familiarity with software technologies and techniques appropriate to each platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the Game Designer’s responsibility to ensure that the whole team understands and shares the original concept and vision of the game as outlined by the Creative/Game Director. During development, the Game Designer makes adjustments to the original specification to respond to technical constraints and to incorporate new programming and art creation methods developed by the team. The Game Designer also trains testers to play the game, making sure that they understand what is expected of the finished product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What skills does EA look for?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no set route to becoming a Game Designer. However, this is not an entry level role. Game development is a highly complex, intensive process which can last two years or more, so the Game Designer must be able to work closely with teams of programmers, artists, project managers, writers, musicians, and many others. The Game Designer usually has a reasonably high level of industry experience and knowledge. EA usually expects to see a portfolio of work, which can take the form of completed game projects or written game design documents and proposals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Game development is a collaborative process involving multi-disciplinary teams. Designers must be able to communicate their vision to artists, programmers, producers, marketing staff, and others involved in the development process, and accept feedback on their work. This involves presenting their ideas both verbally and on paper, for which they need writing and basic visual design and drawing skills. They should also be reasonably fluent in a range of 2D and 3D graphics and animation packages, such as 3D Studio Max or Maya. Good technical knowledge is required, with some programming skills at least at ‘scripting’ level and awareness of the various games platforms and technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A common route to becoming a Game Designer is to get experience as a Game Tester and/or in Quality Assurance (QA) department for a games company. This offers a good grounding in the development process, access to software and tools, and insight into the different job roles in development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When looking for Game Designers EA values a thorough understanding of gameplay theory. Excellent communication and presentation skills are a must, along with storytelling and narrative development skills. The ideal candidate possesses information design and user interface design skill. They must be able to work both as part of a team and independently. Last but not least, they must display systematic and strategic thinking as well as imagination and creativity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as educational background, Game Designers can study a range of subjects, from the sciences and humanities to art and design. There are also a growing number of games-related degree programs and courses available for study, and a degree in this type of program would be a plus. Prospective Game Designers should check the content of courses, particularly the balance between programming, game art, and game design. Designers need basic programming and 3D design skills, and preferably some drawing ability. It’s also very important to have excellent communication and presentation skills.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-electronic-arts-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-electronic-arts-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Graphic Designer at Protect America in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and update the department&amp;rsquo;s website, email and newsletter templates and landing pages, and other Web properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take the design lead for all new Web properties &amp;ndash; ensuring all elements of the user experience (interface design, navigation, etc.) meet objectives and user needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must interact effectively within the Creative team and other cross-functional teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of computer graphic design techniques, design and desktop publishing software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and designing art work and digital files via computers and output devices, using a Web-editor program that involves reading and writing the HTML coding within documents, using graphics, content, HTML and other Web tools; using specific Web page technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to hand-code standards compliant HTML, CSS, Javascript (HTML5, CSS3, Python / Django, AJAX a plus).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in digital media with an emphasis on web design/production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version control systems such as SVN, Git, or Mercurial is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio demonstrating Web-based graphic design skills and online development concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong artistic and visual eye for design, applicable to both Web and print-based projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of designing for the Web, including its limitations and challenges (responsive, mobile, tablet).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SEO, Web standards, and accessibility compliance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to use design tools to plan, create and execute dynamic website experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of Graphic/Web design principles, including page layout, information architecture, wire-framing, color theory and typography.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to handle multiple projects, organize time and set priorities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Protect America:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Protect America, Inc has protected nearly half a million families nationwide with the state-of-the-art GE Wireless Home Security System. We are one of the fastest growing home security companies in America with customers coast to coast!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among other home security companies, Protect America, Inc. has ranked in the Top 10 in volume of residential security system installations for the last three years according to SDM Magazine. As one of the fastest growing home security companies nationwide, we use cutting-edge computer technology to provide instantaneous product support and 24-hour protection of your home and family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure you are prepared in the event of an emergency anytime day or night. Defend your home and family against the threat of invasion, burglary and forced entry with a GE Wireless Home Security System from one of the best home security companies around!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-protect-america-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-protect-america-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Sam Houston State University in Huntsville, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Posting Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is security-sensitive and thereby subject to the provisions of the Texas Education Code §51.215, which authorizes the employer to obtain criminal history record information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Requisition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;201300036S&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Title&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Graphics Designer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Hiring Salary&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SHSU Salary Table &lt;br/&gt;
$3,846 – $5,279 monthly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Occupational Category&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Professional&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Department&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acad Instruct Tech and Dist Learn&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Initial Closing Date&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;02/11/2013&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Open Until Filled&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Educational and Experience Requirement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Graphics, Design, Advertising or related field. Requires at least two years related experience as a graphic designer in a design group or advertising agency with emphasis on the printed media and some exposure to non-printed media. A combination of education, experience, and training that would produce the required knowledge and abilities could be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Nature &amp;amp; Purpose of Position&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist in the design and production of high quality, creative artwork for printing and presentations using computer graphics hardware and software that support the advancement of distance education, learning technologies, and Sam Houston State University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Develops, designs, and produces a variety of publications to include collaborating with clients to identify design products needed; provides art direction; conceptualizes design work with abstract thoughts; prepares production and cost estimates; tracks time on projects; sets deadlines; and prepares final design for production. Conducts meetings for message formulation; maintains relationship with outside vendors; and produces bid sheets for quotes. Works with administrators; interacts with campus print representatives and outside customer service representatives; and communicates the graphic image of the University to the public. Performs other related duties as assigned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Other Specifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advanced knowledge of personal computer with software associated with publishing, graphics, drawing, and web design; phototypesetting equipment, image scanners, and general office equipment. Effective judgment, tact, diplomacy, and discretion required in all matters. Ability to work effectively with a variety of professionals, administrators, and support staff. Must have strong interpersonal skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Full Time Part Time&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full Time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Screening Questions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required fields are indicated with an asterisk (*).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How did you learn about this Position?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HigherEdJobs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TWC Work in Texas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SHSU Website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Chronicle of Higher Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SHSU Employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;If your response to the question above was &amp;ldquo;Other&amp;rdquo; please indicate from what source.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Open Ended Question)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Applicant Documents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Documents&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover Letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Media Presentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-sam-houston-state-university-huntsville-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-sam-houston-state-university-huntsville-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>