<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Creative Designer at USAA in San Antonio, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a Fortune 200 financial services company with more than $113.5 billion in owned and managed assets, USAA is on a mission &amp;ndash; to facilitate the financial security of our members, the men and women of the U.S. military and their families worldwide. Headquartered on a showcase campus in San Antonio, TX, USAA attributes its long-standing success to its most valuable resource, our 23,000 employees. They are the heart and soul of our member-service culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently Ranked the #1 Place to Work in IT by Computerworld Magazine, we are proud to receive consistently outstanding awards and ratings for member service, employee well-being and financial strength. Everything that happens at USAA is based on our core values: Service, Loyalty, Honesty, and Integrity. These are the foundations of how we do business with our members, as well as how we treat each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking talented Creative Designer for our San Antonio, TX facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PURPOSE OF JOB&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facilitates the creation of moderately complex user experience designs by partnering with business stakeholders to define business requirements. Plans, organizes and manages the design process. Primary deliverables include the information architecture and wireframes for various digital channels (e.g., the web, smart phones, tablets, kiosks, email, desktop, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DUTIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitates the creation of moderately complex design solutions by participating in defining the business and design requirements, developing an information architecture, and developing wire frames.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partners with the designer to create a user interface prototype, and with usability specialists to perform usability testing. Coordinates approvals with legal, the business and other stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitates the development or improvement of design processes, procedures, standards and guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves as a resource to less experienced team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May resolve design and technical issues through an understanding of the business and design principles. Clearly articulates the various facets of the issue and leads the team to resolution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributes to the alignment of member experiences across projects, programs, products and channels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree from an accredited university or 6 years work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years experience in marketing, advertising or digital design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years (combined experience in one or more of the following areas: web, smart phone and tablet design production, digital design or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6+ years experience in marketing, advertising or digital design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The above description reflects the details considered necessary to describe the principal functions of the job and should not be construed as a detailed description of all the work requirements that may be performed in the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At USAA our employees enjoy one of the best benefits packages in the business, including business casual dress environment, comprehensive medical, dental and vision plans, along with wellness and wealth building programs. Additionally, our career path planning and continuing education will assist you with your professional goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USAA also offers a variety of on-site services and conveniences to help you manage your work and personal life, including seven cafeterias, two company stores and three fitness centers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relocation assistance is available for this position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualified applicants must successfully complete a pre-employment background and drug screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USAA is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-designer-usaa-san-antonio-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/creative-designer-usaa-san-antonio-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Experience Designer at Sabre Holdings in Dallas-Fort Worth, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Sabre is a global technology company that touches nearly every aspect of travel. Our innovative software enables more than a billion people around the world to plan, book and experience their travel at a time and price that is right for them. By delivering the technology behind travel, Sabre is working magic behind the scenes every day to make the world a better place, one journey at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sabre Airline Solutions User Experience team creates compelling, consistent, and highly usable experiences for users of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading suite of airline software solutions. You will be a visual and interaction designer in our growing team of dedicated user-centered design professionals, creating innovative, wow-producing visual interaction designs for our entire portfolio. Our applications are complex and our users are demanding, and this position offers a broad variety of design challenges in both web and desktop environments, sure to stretch your creativity and hone your talents. Our strategic design activities have high standards and ambitious goals, and are visible at executive levels. Bring us your best visual and interaction design work, and share in our success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Senior User Experience designer, you will create the User Experience Strategy, including definition of usability goals and requirements and creation of the UX plan, in support of GUI redesign initiatives and/or new product development within the Airline Solutions portfolio.
You will collaborate with the product leadership team, Product Solutions Managers, Business Analysts, and the Development team to develop design concepts and refine requirements, bridging business objectives, technical considerations, and user goals into a holistic entity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will utilize research methods to understand users, their tasks, and their environments. You may develop Personae, User Profiles, and Conceptual Models to communicate dominant characteristics and develop predictable results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will create a product&amp;rsquo;s visual look and feel, seamlessly integrating brand, appearance, usability, and functionality targeting a variety of technology platforms, Desktop, Web, and Mobile/Tablet. You will produce specifications and/or prototypes describing interaction requirements to support evolving software application development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will conduct and/or coordinate Evaluation Techniques, including Design Walkthroughs, User Feedback Sessions and formal Usability Testing to validate proposed design solutions with stakeholders and end users against usability goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;EDUCATION:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor degree or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;EXPERIENCE:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6-8 years related experience in Interaction Design, Visual User Interface Design, and User Experience Research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and training to take on extremely difficult design challenges such as visualization of complex data, rich interactivity in a domain dominated by tables and spreadsheets, and driving common look and feel across a diverse product portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have designed and delivered effective and beautiful interfaces for both desktop and web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are proficient with industry tools, including Balsamiq and the Adobe Creative Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;THE SABRE HOLDINGS PORTFOLIO OF COMPANIES includes Travelocity, Sabre Travel Network, Sabre Airline Solutions and Sabre Hospitality Solutions. Headquartered in Southlake, Texas, Sabre Holdings has approximately 10,000 employees in 60 countries. Our people take initiative, are resourceful and innovative, and are passionate about what they do. In return for their hard work and dedication, Sabre Holdings provides our employees with countless learning and growth opportunities, a healthy work-life balance and a fun, yet productive, work environment.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-sabre-holdings-dallas-fort-worth-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-sabre-holdings-dallas-fort-worth-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Jr UI Web Designer at Mouser Electronics in Mansfield, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Web Designer will work on the visual design and user interface of Mouser’s web site and web communications. This includes the design and usability of web applications, technical content sites, third-party sites and electronic marketing materials. The Web Designer will incorporate user interface design that follows best practices and meets business needs, while ensuring good user experience and consistency across existing web pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ACCOUNTABILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good design capabilities with an understanding of UX, information architecture principles, usability principles and graphic design to create visual interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ecommerce sites/platforms and understanding the needs and interactions of users within those sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to analyze and understand different user segments to tailor interfaces to specific needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good time management skills with the ability to meet, and sometimes exceed, deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balance technical functionality and visual elements to create a system that is not only operational but also usable and adaptable to changing user needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be comfortable following direction and implementing changes based on constructive criticism and be able to balance great design with meeting short deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of basic computer programming principles, tools, and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a Business Analyst to understand requirements and the needs of business stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to read, analyze and understand requirements documents to create wireframes, prototypes, mockups, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide wireframes, content flow and prototypes (paper, Pencil, Visual Basic, Visio, Axure, HTML/CSS, or other methods)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good business writing skills to describe design behavior and function.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;EDUCATION &amp;amp; EXPERIENCE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in a related field or equivalent related work experience preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;SKILLS &amp;amp; CERTIFICATIONS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requires an individual with a team-oriented attitude and a strong work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexibility and aptitude to thrive in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of basic Internet technology and communication, and web server hardware&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of websites in a database driven content environment and how it relates to web site production methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML and CSS, as well as a basic understanding of other website based languages such as JavaScript, and XML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of image optimization standards including compression, file formats, and file size.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with the applications in Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills; ability to handle multiple projects and meet deadline deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly effective teamwork/interpersonal skills with wide target audiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good verbal and written communication skills and ability to interact with internal and external users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-ui-web-designer-mouser-electronics-mansfield-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-ui-web-designer-mouser-electronics-mansfield-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at FireHost Inc. in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;FireHost, a secure, fast-paced, and growth-oriented secure cloud hosting company, has career opportunities for talented and highly motivated individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graphic Designer position requires a self-driven, results-oriented person with a positive outlook, and a clear focus on high quality and business success.  The individual we invite to fill this role will enjoy days filled with a wide variety of tasks, that all require a creative eye with an impeccable attention to detail. Things like: brainstorming a new ad campaign, designing anything from web pages to printed materials to presentations and tradeshow booths will be part of your routine. Ideal candidates are empathic communicators, able to see things from the others  points of view to solve problems effectively and efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities (Additional duties may be assigned as required.)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute digital and print projects that embody the FireHost brand, balancing clarity, relevance and timeliness to reach business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in concept, design, and production tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize and implement structures, processes and procedures to improve efficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate resources and schedules to ensure deadlines are met&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage projects from design to release&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adopt and enthusiastically support the use of industry best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish, facilitate, and maintain regular communication with project teams and internal customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design sensibility – color, composition, typography, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A clear understanding of digital and physical mediums, and how to execute for both&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to create compelling and appealing visual communications that meet specific goals and provide results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to meet deadlines in a fast paced, team oriented environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail-oriented, analytical, self motivated, resourceful and organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to multi-task and resolve multiple inquiries at once and in order of priority&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty satisfactorily. The requirements listed below are representative of the tools in our environment today, but this list will change and grow:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After Effects a plus (motion graphic)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite 6 (Fireworks, Illustrator, Photoshop, Dreamweaver)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash a plus (actionscript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Education and/or Experience&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four-year college degree (preferably in a visual communication field)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of cloud hosting, FireHost’s core services (preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Physical Demands&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While performing the duties of this job, the employee is regularly required to sit and use hands.  Members of the marketing team must be willing to travel locally, across North America and abroad for sales and marketing events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Work Environment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The noise level in the work environment is usually low to moderate. The work environment may be in either an office setting, at client or vendor offices, at trade shows or outside the office at a public location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Benefits&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FireHost pays 100% of insurance premiums for employeeʼs medical, dental and vision coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FireHost covers up to 50% of dependent insurance premiums for medical, dental and vision coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roth and traditional 401K match, up to 6%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;160 hours paid vacation per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-firehost-inc-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-firehost-inc-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Jr. Assistant Designer at Neiman Marcus in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Neiman Marcus Stores are located in the most affluent markets in the United States with a presence in Florida, California and Texas. From the finest designer and luxury merchandise for men and women to precious jewelry, beauty and home decor, we offer our customers an impeccable and irresistible array of choices. Since 1907, Neiman Marcus has served our discerning and sophisticated customers with gracious and attentive service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Works and assists on designs projects for store development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to manage design projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compile and deliver creative design solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate seasonally with design team and develop seasonal collateral signing needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compile and deliver creative design solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist Supervisor with special creative projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide general accounting support as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must work efficiently within a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent time management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have the ability to bring new ideas, materials and concepts to the table&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple tasks and deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiencies in Mac and PC, Adobe InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Microsoft Office Word , Excel  and Sketch Up or  3D programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Work Experience/Education:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of Associates Degree in Graphic Design or equivalent of 1-2 years of Design Graphic or Visual Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-assistant-designer-neiman-marcus-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-assistant-designer-neiman-marcus-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Santander Consumer USA in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Web Designer II shall be responsible for playing a key role in designing all aspects of Santander Consumer USA Inc’s (SC USA) and RoadLoans.com web presence and visual identity including user interfaces, new web site initiatives, social media campaigns, email marketing campaigns, SEO projects, as well as functionality enhancements to our existing sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coding html/css/javascript from Illustrator and/or Photoshop layouts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining/deploying web content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing web interfaces from scratch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing and management of HTML email templates &amp;amp; designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blog/Facebook/YouTube/Twitter management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating content for SEO initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Analytics creation and reporting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Special projects as requested&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other duties as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree; equivalent combination of education and experience may be substituted in lieu of degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three (3) to five (5) years of web design &amp;amp; HTML email experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of web standards and xhtml/css&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keen eye to preserve integrity of the design throughout the entire development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivator/flexible/team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work in a fast pace environment with multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to code html/css by hand including the ability to integrate code into aspx&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to integrate javascript functionality from existing libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mid-level experience with Abode creative suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of aspx code and Interaction Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Visual Studio, version control software, JavaScript, SQL and Adobe Flash preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to maintain confidentiality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Working Conditions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extended working hours may be required as dictated by management and business needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel to multiple facilities may be required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-santander-consumer-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-santander-consumer-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at BergdorfGoodman.com in Irving, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Neiman Marcus Stores are located in the most affluent markets in the United States with a presence in Florida, California and Texas. From the finest designer and luxury merchandise for men and women to precious jewelry, beauty and home decor, we offer our customers an impeccable and irresistible array of choices. Since 1907, Neiman Marcus has served our discerning and sophisticated customers with gracious and attentive service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This individual will support the creation of website and marketing design assets for our online business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead designer for site support and special projects on BergdorfGoodman.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates in the development of project concepts and applies design approaches to a wide range of site content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translates marketing and merchandising strategies into accurate and visually compelling designs for the upper echelon of the Fashion/Retail industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executes designs quickly and performs additional tasks as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fashion and luxury brand experience strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree in Multimedia Design or Web Design or equivalent experience is strongly preferred but not required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in design for web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven expertise in Photoshop CS5, Dreamweaver CS5, Illustrator CS5, HTML, CSS, and Javascript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing high-caliber websites, as well as working knowledge of designing for mobile and other emerging devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent typography and design sensibilities and technical expertise, coupled with an understanding of web usability, information architecture, front-end development, multi-platform and SEO best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and visual communication skills and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to demonstrate creative and strategic problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent time management, resilience, and the ability to work independently as well as in collaboration within a fast-paced team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working under tight deadlines and on multiple projects simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using Flash ActionScript and FinalCut Pro is not required but strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-bergdorfgoodman-irving-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-bergdorfgoodman-irving-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at AIC in Houston, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts International Corporation, an IT services company, is seeking an IT &amp;ndash; Visual Web Designer. We have 40 years of experience in the IT staffing industry and provide our clients with the highest quality custom staffing solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures that user requirements are met in all web components through design and html development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates HTML for high-volume traffic websites, emails, landing pages and micro sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides new features and functionality for existing sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains consistency of site appearance via use of style guides, style sheets and enforcement of established standards and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides all browser compatible HTML code to developers based on design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with developers to implement HTML code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in prototype development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in QA of HTML code and progressive enhancement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in browser testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DocTypes, HTML, HTML5, X/HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Browser Compatibility, Accessible Standards-Compliant Coding, Table-Free Layouts, Semantic Markup, DHTML/AJAX, Jquery, Front-end Optimization, Graphics Tools, Debugging Tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fitting front end code into CMS (SDL Tridion), Mobile Development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accessible Standards-Compliant Coding,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Table-Free Layouts,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Semantic Markup, DHTML/AJAX, Jquery, Front-end Optimization, Graphics Tools, Debugging Tools, Fitting front end code into CMS (Documentum), Mobile Development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We value our employees' hard work and dedication to quality. In addition to a positive environment with opportunities for growth and advancement we offer a competitive salary and benefits package.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental, vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long / short term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock purchase plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-aic-houston-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-aic-houston-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Jr. Graphic Designer at Torchmark in McKinney, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This position is responsible for the design and production of agent field force collateral materials for both print and web, as well as consumer-facing and intradepartmental projects.  The Jr. Graphic Designer collaborates with other designers on staff, Management, Traffic Coordinator, and Staff Writer(s) to execute creative concepts.  Help translate concepts and ideas into viable designs and assist in asset creation and presentation preparation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary duties &amp;amp; responsibilities consist of:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use design software to produce graphic arts and visual materials for conventions, brochures, magazines, applications, forms, stationery, presentation materials, and PowerPoint presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Junior Graphic Designer must possess the communication skills needed to interact with clients, enabling the designer to reproduce artwork in line with the client&amp;rsquo;s needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Jr. Graphic Designer will also be required to collect documents and send to the printer as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ideal candidate should have both strong design skills and production skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient in a Macintosh environment using Adobe CS5 programs Illustrator, Photoshop, Adobe Acrobat Professional and InDesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate should also have a good understanding of MS Word and PowerPoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills, &amp;amp; Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be comfortable working under tight deadlines and on multiple projects. This individual must be precise, accountable, detail-oriented and highly organized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must possess problem-solving skills to creatively resolve issues that arise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education &amp;amp; Work Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of professional studio/agency experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Physical Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occasionally bend/stoop and kneel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rarely squat, reach above shoulder level, crouch or push/pull&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rarely lifts waist to overhead up to 10 pounds and occasionally lifts floor to waist and carries up to 10 pounds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Hours:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday-Friday
8:00 a.m.-5:00 p.m.
Overtime may be required&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-graphic-designer-transwestern-mckinney-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/jr-graphic-designer-transwestern-mckinney-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Visual Designer at Golden Frog in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Visual Designer position is a unique opportunity to work on exciting projects for multiple brands in the technology, software and service verticals.  This position will be responsible for concepting and designing web and print collateral e.g. websites, software interfaces, banner ads, emails, white papers, brochures and datasheets.  This position will also play a key role in driving the direction of the look and feel of the company as well as serve as a mentor for junior designers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With new products coming out regularly in the B2C &amp;amp; B2B spheres, the Senior Designer position will have a unique opportunity to work on unique projects with different audiences, styles, and needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Portfolio of work within the software/technology vertical is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create effective, engaging designs that support business objectives and adhere to established brand guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional web/print design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a self-motivated, highly-creative individual&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have strong team-working skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently, manage multiple projects and meet deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough familiarity with latest Adobe Creative Suite software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2009, Golden Frog is a global software developer of Internet applications focused on reliability, performance, and security. The company debuted its first product release with VyprVPN, a personal VPN solution for individuals, internet service providers and channel partners offering ‘last-mile’ internet privacy from any location and virtually any device. VyprVPN provides a secure, encrypted connection to the Internet; a solid layer of privacy protection unavailable with traditional Internet security software. Golden Frog is in early trial phase of its second major product release with Dump Truck, a professional-grade, highly secure, massive online storage service.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/visual-designer-golden-frog-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/visual-designer-golden-frog-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>