<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer at SpareFoot in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;SpareFoot is looking for a senior level UI Designer.  The UI Designer is responsible for the design of web applications and components for internal and web-facing systems.  The UI Designer will work closely with product, stakeholders, and engineering to design, test and deliver web sites, applications and components.  The designer will have the ability to design web applications and components from the requirements stage, consult during development, and test and iterate following deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLEASE INCLUDE A COVER LETTER WITH YOUR APPLICATION!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SpareFoot operates a network of websites that help consumers comparison shop for self-storage facilities (like Hotels.com for self-storage).  Some of our top sites: www.selfstorage.com, www.selfstoragedeals.com, www.sparefoot.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millions of consumers use SpareFoot to find storage at more than 6,500 storage facilities in the US each year&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re funded by top investors (Silverton Partners &amp;amp; Floodgate), have an awesome team and revenue is growing FAST.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years designing web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent visual design skills, including an eye for typography, icon design, composition, and use of color&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid interaction design and information architecture skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience in development of HTML/CSS, JavaScript, graphics creation with Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in an agile (w/ a lowercase “a”) environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of effective UI patterns and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of design research and usability testing methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product, engineering, and various stakeholders to design intuitive, functional user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate concepts and ideas into workable interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the user experience of a product from conception until launch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain mockups, visual assets, wireframes, prototypes, and specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think at a high level about product strategy (not just “how it should look” but “what we should build”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MVC development experience PHP, Java, Python, Ruby, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Native mobile application experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insurance for you and your family – fully paid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock options (we’re still early enough that these are a big deal)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A ridiculously cool work place – full floor in downtown Austin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Downtown parking pass&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited beer, liquor and other beverages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More free snacks than you have ever seen before (we currently consume 3lbs of pistachios/day)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sake bomb initiation event for all new employees at Imperia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A highly casual and not always politically correct workplace (if you’re easily offended, please don’t apply)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shuffleboard and foosball in our office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work hard &amp;amp; play hard culture with frequent company social events (and cab vouchers to get home safely from those events)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No policy vacation policy &amp;ndash; take the time you need as long as you do so responsibly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-sparefoot-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-sparefoot-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Corgan Associates, Inc. in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corgan seeks a talented Graphic Designer with 3-5 years of experience to join the firm in our Dallas office location. Candidate will create communication pieces and all firm branded materials including print, signage and environmental graphics. Candidate will also work closely with individual studios to produce graphics for general marketing, business development, conventions, branding and advertising. As an in-house Graphic Designer with Corgan, you will be expected to understand and creatively interpret visual identity and brand standards not only for Corgan, but for our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualified candidate must be detail-oriented, collaborative, and a good communicator with strong conceptual and problem-solving skills. Candidate must also be skilled at juggling multiple tasks and prioritizing to meet deadlines. Please be highly proficient in Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, Bridge, and Microsoft Office Suite. A professional degree in Design/Visual Communications or related field is required, along with an ability to work in a dynamic, friendly team environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corgan offers a competitive salary and generous benefits package that includes employer-paid health and dental insurance for employees. In addition to a creative and energetic environment, we offer the ability to work with multiple clients on a variety of projects in our LEED Silver downtown building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please attach samples of your work (preferably in PDF format) to your application. EOE&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-corgan-associates-inc-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-corgan-associates-inc-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web and Print Designer at Axxess Healthcare Consult in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Axxess is a leading provider of consulting, training and technology services to the home health industry. We are looking for a creative and sharp web and print Graphics Designer to join our growing team focused on creating the best possible user experience. The successful candidate will work with the marketing team to promote Axxess' product and services by creating elegant and engaging web and print graphics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing and managing of all promotional printed media (newsletters, brochures, web banners and flyers).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Producing prepress graphics and text to job specifications/requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executing design, layout and typesetting projects accurately and effectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing new and/or making revisions to existing InDesign files and other marketing material as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verifying content and formatting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gathering feedback from the Marketing Team on Web development graphical needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remaining up-to-date on the latest browser, plug-in technology and Web/print style.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilizing various graphical software tools and technologies to transform graphical concepts into specific electronic applications on and off-line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML code behind each Web page, integrating artwork, text, video, and animations within a website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with other staff members in order to complete tasks and achieve budgeted goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to maintain a positive customer service attitude when dealing with internal/external customers and vendors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to produce professional concepts, page layouts with effective/correct integration of copy, photography and illustrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing in-house copy/printer machine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update and maintaining Marketing Collateral Inventory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple projects efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep assigned areas organized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All around team player that could receive art direction from team as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to design concepts that will increase conversion rate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree in Art and Graphic design or related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of web design experience with an impressive online portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years of print design experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail; self-motivated and deadline-oriented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work well independently and/or in a dynamic team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, interpersonal, and organizational skills an absolute must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Branding Development is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Print layout design proficiency, i.e.: color separation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website design proficiency, i.e.: knowledge of slicing images for the Web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience optimizing InDesign files for Web/press use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with printing companies from quotes, digital file transfer, proofing to delivery of final print product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of digital and offset printing issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise of Industry Standard Design software: Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Dreamweaver, Adobe PDF Writer, Microsoft Word, Power Point, Microsoft Excel and Microsoft Outlook.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hand-drawing ability, story boarding and creating sketches is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social media experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-and-print-designer-axxess-healthcare-consult-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-and-print-designer-axxess-healthcare-consult-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at University of Houston in Houston, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researches, conceives and designs university and department publications and other print and electronic communication vehicles. Manages design projects and serves as university liaison for outsourced communication projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages publication and other communication projects from concept to completion; translates marketing objectives into creative strategies as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and executes design concepts; develops artwork for materials such as brochures, invitations, and identity programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitors university advertising for adherence to university graphic and branding standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consults with clients to evaluate individual project needs; prepares cost and time estimates for projects; and reviews printed materials to ensure quality control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with writers, editors, marketing, photographers and other designers on communication projects to meet strategic objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves as primary liaison with vendors for communication projects to ensure quality, customer satisfaction, and adherence to university graphic and branding standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides art direction as needed for internal and outsourced projects, and makes recommendations for the most effective method for meeting client’s objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves as team lead on design projects as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other job-related duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requires a Bachelor’s degree from a college or university or an equivalent in-depth specialized training program that is directly related to the type of work being performed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requires a minimum of three (3) years of directly job-related experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Posting Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Documents:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants must submit 3 pdf samples of graphic design work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Applicant Documents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Documents&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover Letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Misc. Documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-university-of-houston-houston-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-university-of-houston-houston-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Artist/Packaging Designer at Sally Beauty Holdings in Denton, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Sally Beauty Holdings (NYSE: SBH) is the world’s largest wholesale and retail distributor of beauty supplies.  Our world headquarters is conveniently located in the Dallas / Fort Worth Metroplex, just 5 minutes north of Lake Lewisville off of I35E.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We currently have an opening for a Graphic Artist/Packaging Designer.  This person will assist with all product development projects.  Responsibilities include getting files ready for print, releasing art files, some photo retouching, updating and revising current designs, creating mock-ups and creating new layouts/design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggests technical improvements and modifies formats to increase the quality of production and ensure that standards are met. Other technical duties may include scaling, cropping, retouching, repositioning and preflighting, or eliminating defective and excessive imaging. Proofread final art files to ensure there are no errors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to make updates such as updating copy or images to current files or changing art to a new dieline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists with designing and producing new product packaging, labels, point of purchase material, brochures and other graphic images related to product development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some photo retouching: For example &amp;ndash;  changing a color on an image, placing a logo on a dryer, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates mock-up samples for brand managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare, archive and manage electronic art files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs and other duties as requested by supervisor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in Design or related major&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years experience working as a production/graphic artist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have experience preparing and preflighting files before going to printers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a fast-paced, detail-oriented environment with tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work with vendors to coordinate correct digital output and transmission of pre-press artwork prepared.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe Illustrator, Acrobat, Photoshop, InDesign and Microsoft Office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the printing process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We offer a competitive salary, outstanding benefits package that includes medical, dental, vision, life Insurance, paid vacation and sick days, paid holidays, merchandise discounts, tuition reimbursement, profit sharing, and 401(k) with company match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sally Beauty is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-artist-packaging-designer-sally-beauty-holdings-denton-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-artist-packaging-designer-sally-beauty-holdings-denton-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface Designer at Zynga in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Zynga design team is responsible for delivering the highest quality platform solutions, and is at the cutting edge of social interaction.
To help us stay there we need you! We are currently looking for a User Interface/User Experience designer with talent and flair, an eye for detail, and a passion for the digital space in several of our Zynga locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join the Z-revolution, apply now!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Designer – User Interface/User Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Zynga design team is responsible for delivering the highest quality platform solutions, and is at the cutting edge of social interaction.
To help us stay there we need you! We are currently looking for aSenior User Interface/User Experience designer with talent and flair, an eye for detail, and a passion for the digital space in several of our Zynga locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join the Z-revolution, apply now!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here are the requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with a multi-disciplinary design team for user experience planning and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate crisp, innovative, and elegant design solutions for complex online social products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for execution of strong interaction design and visual design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead rapid iterations and testing on a variety of ideas using wireframes and sketches to fully designed comps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiastically partner with user research specialists to understand the goals of multiple user types and create designs that uphold their needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with engineers to collaborate and iterate in fast-paced design-build cycles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitate dialog around end-user requirements and business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help build a dynamic, creative environment in which you can design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a program manager to coordinate project scheduling and resource allocation and ensure solutions are delivered on time and exceed expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researching interaction design trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make a point to understand how Zynga’s audience interacts with its games/services, and make use of this knowledge in the development of the best possible user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The Skills you need:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 + years of professional design/user experience for software, web applications which leverage emergent technologies, consumer electronics and/or mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of user experience design for social applications or rich Internet experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills and the ability to communicate effectively throughout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to work with cross-functional teams and successfully launch new products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of, Flash Photoshop, Illustrator and associated design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with user interface design patters and standard UCD methodologies across multiple platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of, but not a deal breaker- 3D Modeling, Flash, rendering and animation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-designer-zynga-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-designer-zynga-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Designer at Callaway Golf in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This position may be located at our office in Austin TX or at our office in San Diego, CA.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for creation, delivery and execution of best in class web creative that represents the brand in a demonstrably superior and pleasingly different way.  Collaborate with other team members on best practices and execution of webpage designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maintains and provides ongoing design and development of the websites, marketing email campaigns, promotional and advertising banners, seasonal content specials and global content.  Designs and develops html prototypes, user interfaces and interaction of web-based applications. Designs and evaluates visual human interfaces utilizing user-centered design principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Development of the user interface design. Works with the product development team to design online user experiences. Ensures user experience is formulated to achieve the goals of the online entity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and develop web pages, user interfaces, and other marketing collateral using current frontend technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to complete projects on time and within the budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain, update, and enhance content, text, and graphics on the various websites.  Additional modifications include updating images, flash movies, and site layout changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML email creative and production that will drive traffic to the websites and increase consumer engagement with the brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate and enhance websites to strengthen the brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take printed advertising materials and adapt for web applications in a way consistent with a premium brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adhere to corporate style guidelines while incorporating web design best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use innovative design styles that pique consumer interest and enhance the end user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other team members on webpage design and execution to create efficient solutions that will be consumer friendly aesthetically, and technically.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and evaluate how webpage design should work with the end users backend structure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with print advertising team to share ideas, digital assets, and create integrated designs that span various mediums.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Authority to Act&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adhere to Callaway Golf policies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge/expert in web usage of Adobe Photoshop and/or Fireworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to hand-code HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General understanding of JavaScript and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cross-browser support and ability to troubleshoot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of web best practices for efficiency of web images and file size&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly creative and motivated to produce superior creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled at thinking creatively outside the box&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter that takes the initiative to start and complete assignment without direct supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly meticulous/very detailed oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and people skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take ideas from inception to design to production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work with web programmers to make sure design is carried through correctly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to use performance metrics to drive creative/design objectives.  Track general site sales and conversion trends, traffic patterns, search results, and other site metrics Explore and analyze results to increase usability and sales&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Golf knowledge a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of programming languages such as .NET and PHP a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and/or Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of interactive design and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-designer-callaway-golf-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-designer-callaway-golf-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at ReachLocal in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that local businesses are shifting more and more marketing dollars from offline to online? And by 2014, local online ad spending is expected to grow from $15.2 billion to $36.7 billion as local businesses realize the power of the Internet to reach new customers. At ReachLocal, helping businesses advertise online is just one part of what we do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ReachLocal is looking for a multi-disciplinary Senior Graphic Designer with strong conceptual skills and meticulous execution abilities for its growing in-house marketing team. We need strong conceptual thinking, quick wit, strong design sensitivity and someone who is passionate – especially about the interactive space. The ideal candidate will have 5+ years freelance, agency or in-house experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, edit and update online and offline projects, including (but not limited to):&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customer-facing sales presentations &amp;amp; collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promotional items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade show signage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internal sales contests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corporate website &amp;amp; microsites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Banner ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multimedia (flash, video, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unconventional digital marketing projects (viral, guerilla)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop strategy-based creative concepts with Creative Director &amp;amp; CMO of Marketing on internal and field and customer-facing materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface smoothly with fellow creative’s as well as C-level executives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multitask on short-term and long-term projects simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receive direction, constructive criticism &amp;amp; feedback on creative work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage time effectively to meet project &amp;amp; meeting deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree with significant interactive &amp;amp; B2B design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years freelance, agency or in-house experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deeply Internet-savvy, specifically w/r/t the online marketing/advertising industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show initiative and eagerness to learn &amp;amp; continually improve, both personally and professionally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Microsoft Office &amp;amp; major web browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work independently and as part of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Native interest in the latest news, events, products and trends pertaining to the web and online marketing/advertising&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Devoted attention to detail, while being flexible to fresh &amp;amp; evolving interactive &amp;amp; marketing copy trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Drupal CMS platform, a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML 5, a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Other Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated, energetic self-starter with lots of personal integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in an environment that is both fast-paced and trending corporate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiasm for and discipline in creating projects, from conception to final proof&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track record of exceeding expectations and delivering on-time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friendly, personable, enjoyable to work with!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About ReachLocal&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ReachLocal, Inc.’s (NASDAQ: RLOC) mission is to help small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) acquire, maintain and retain customers via the Internet. ReachLocal offers a comprehensive suite of online marketing solutions, including search engine marketing (ReachSearch™), Web presence (ReachCast™), display advertising (ReachDisplay™), online marketing analytics (TotalTrack®), and assisted chat service (TotalLiveChat™), each targeted to the SMB market. ReachLocal delivers this suite of services to SMBs through a combination of its proprietary technology platform and its direct, “feet-on-the-street” sales force of Internet Marketing Consultants and select third party agencies and resellers. ReachLocal is headquartered in Woodland Hills, CA, with offices throughout North America and in Australia, the United Kingdom, Germany, the Netherlands and Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ReachLocal is an equal opportunity employer. Applicants for all job openings are welcome and will be considered without regard to race, color, religion, national origin, sex, age, sexual orientation, physical or mental disability, or any other basis protected by state, federal or local law. It is the intent of the Company to comply with all applicable federal, state and local legislation concerning equal opportunity in employment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This job description is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of all activities, duties or responsibilities required of the employee.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-reachlocal-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-reachlocal-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Web Designer at Music One Live in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The designer will oversee the design and development of multiple client websites, mainly in the music realm.  Responsibilities touch all stages of the development lifecycle, from gathering requirements to managing design and development teams both local and overseas. The person in this role is ultimately accountable for the final product and will serve as the go-to for all requests related to client websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements &amp;ndash;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects at one time across many different  individuals and teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of design principles with a proven track record and stellar portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to date with current technologies and topics in web design (responsiveness, Sass, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great HTML/CSS skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with one or more popular CMS frameworks, especially Wordpress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident but humble personality that enjoys debating opposing ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The drive to be continuously learning and improving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Above all, a strong passion for your craft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What We Offer &amp;ndash;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A small team that is focused and passionate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relaxed, laid back environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities for growth and education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All the foosball you can handle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Music One Live:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music One Live is an independently owned and operated technology company for music artists, venues, sports, and concert/event promoters. For more information visit our website at www.musiconelive.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-music-one-live-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-web-designer-music-one-live-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Interface &amp; Graphic Designer at vAuto in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This is a full-time position with vAuto, a business unit of AutoTrader Group, located in Austin, TX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an experienced user interface and user interaction designer to help develop user flows and graphic assets for mobile applications, web applications and mobile web applications.  This person’s responsibilities will include conceptualization, design and production of mobile apps, emails, web, video and brochures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;vAuto, Inc. is an industry leading innovator and provider of automotive software solutions. Since the company was founded in 2005, vAuto has launched several first-in industry innovations, including its current site of solutions that deliver a better way to price, appraise and stock pre-owned vehicles. We are a fast-moving technology company specializing in web &amp;amp; mobile application solutions for the Automotive Industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years in user interface design and graphics design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2 years with HTML, CSS, and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience designing mobile workflows and graphics. (At least 1 application available in an app store).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating wire-frames to communicate workflows and ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert proficiency in Adobe products, especially Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong eye for layout, color and typography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated and self-driven&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to manage multiple projects at once in a fast-paced work environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with current and upcoming trends in mobile and web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-%26-graphic-designer-vauto-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-interface-%26-graphic-designer-vauto-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>