<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feeds/tx-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/Graphic Designer at Protect America in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and update the department&amp;rsquo;s website, email and newsletter templates and landing pages, and other Web properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take the design lead for all new Web properties &amp;ndash; ensuring all elements of the user experience (interface design, navigation, etc.) meet objectives and user needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must interact effectively within the Creative team and other cross-functional teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of computer graphic design techniques, design and desktop publishing software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and designing art work and digital files via computers and output devices, using a Web-editor program that involves reading and writing the HTML coding within documents, using graphics, content, HTML and other Web tools; using specific Web page technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to hand-code standards compliant HTML, CSS, Javascript (HTML5, CSS3, Python / Django, AJAX a plus).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in digital media with an emphasis on web design/production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced knowledge of Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version control systems such as SVN, Git, or Mercurial is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio demonstrating Web-based graphic design skills and online development concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong artistic and visual eye for design, applicable to both Web and print-based projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of designing for the Web, including its limitations and challenges (responsive, mobile, tablet).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SEO, Web standards, and accessibility compliance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to use design tools to plan, create and execute dynamic website experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of Graphic/Web design principles, including page layout, information architecture, wire-framing, color theory and typography.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to handle multiple projects, organize time and set priorities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Protect America:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Protect America, Inc has protected nearly half a million families nationwide with the state-of-the-art GE Wireless Home Security System. We are one of the fastest growing home security companies in America with customers coast to coast!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among other home security companies, Protect America, Inc. has ranked in the Top 10 in volume of residential security system installations for the last three years according to SDM Magazine. As one of the fastest growing home security companies nationwide, we use cutting-edge computer technology to provide instantaneous product support and 24-hour protection of your home and family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure you are prepared in the event of an emergency anytime day or night. Defend your home and family against the threat of invasion, burglary and forced entry with a GE Wireless Home Security System from one of the best home security companies around!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 12:46:55 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-protect-america-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-graphic-designer-protect-america-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Sam Houston State University in Huntsville, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Posting Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is security-sensitive and thereby subject to the provisions of the Texas Education Code §51.215, which authorizes the employer to obtain criminal history record information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Requisition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;201300036S&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Title&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Graphics Designer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Hiring Salary&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SHSU Salary Table &lt;br/&gt;
$3,846 – $5,279 monthly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Occupational Category&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Professional&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Department&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acad Instruct Tech and Dist Learn&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Initial Closing Date&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;02/11/2013&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Open Until Filled&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Educational and Experience Requirement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Graphics, Design, Advertising or related field. Requires at least two years related experience as a graphic designer in a design group or advertising agency with emphasis on the printed media and some exposure to non-printed media. A combination of education, experience, and training that would produce the required knowledge and abilities could be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Nature &amp;amp; Purpose of Position&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist in the design and production of high quality, creative artwork for printing and presentations using computer graphics hardware and software that support the advancement of distance education, learning technologies, and Sam Houston State University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Develops, designs, and produces a variety of publications to include collaborating with clients to identify design products needed; provides art direction; conceptualizes design work with abstract thoughts; prepares production and cost estimates; tracks time on projects; sets deadlines; and prepares final design for production. Conducts meetings for message formulation; maintains relationship with outside vendors; and produces bid sheets for quotes. Works with administrators; interacts with campus print representatives and outside customer service representatives; and communicates the graphic image of the University to the public. Performs other related duties as assigned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Other Specifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advanced knowledge of personal computer with software associated with publishing, graphics, drawing, and web design; phototypesetting equipment, image scanners, and general office equipment. Effective judgment, tact, diplomacy, and discretion required in all matters. Ability to work effectively with a variety of professionals, administrators, and support staff. Must have strong interpersonal skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Full Time Part Time&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full Time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Screening Questions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required fields are indicated with an asterisk (*).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How did you learn about this Position?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HigherEdJobs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TWC Work in Texas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SHSU Website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Chronicle of Higher Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SHSU Employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;If your response to the question above was &amp;ldquo;Other&amp;rdquo; please indicate from what source.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Open Ended Question)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Applicant Documents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Documents&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover Letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Media Presentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 12:46:55 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-sam-houston-state-university-huntsville-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-sam-houston-state-university-huntsville-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>