<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at C3 Presents in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;C3 Presents is an international leader in the music industry and mass gatherings (Austin City Limits Music Festival, Lollapalooza, Big Day Out, Orion Music and More, Austin Food and Wine Festival, and more.) The Art Director will work with the Creative team to take our brand and visual identities to new levels to thrill our fans and artists and sponsors. This position requires a passion for music and bringing brands to life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PRIMARY JOB DUTIES &amp;amp; RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop branding and identity for C3 properties/clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with the Creative team, other departments and clients to design print &amp;amp; web collateral and on site art installations for festivals, events and artist management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops proposals for prospective C3 properties/clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receiving and routing logos, photos, and various graphic assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivers and implements creative collateral at festival and event sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs merchandise for festival and artist management clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties and projects as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA in Marketing, Advertising or Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6-8 years of experience in design in advertising, marketing or interactive agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to concept ideas, themes, advertising, graphic elements across the various C3 properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to design while adhering to established brand identities, concepts and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of branding, marketing communications, and promotional principles and their application in various channels and mediums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Adobe Creative Suite and Microsoft Office. A basic understanding of CSS, HTML, Flash and interactive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create a file and see it through to production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of file types and how to work with both raster and vector files, as well as transfer methods and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to physically work on site, delivering and implementing creative collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reliability – able to see tasks, ideas or projects through, from start to finish; meet deadlines and budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding planning and organization skills – use organized approach to job responsibilities and able to multi-task and set priorities. Be able to thrive in a high-demand, fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate effectively and present concepts to co-workers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to do writing and editing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented and able to perform job accurately and thoroughly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creativity – use independent and original thought and initiative to improve processes or solve problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated – self-directed and self-responsible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to be flexible, adjust to changing conditions and constraints in order to meet goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great attitude – engage in work; be open and approachable to co-workers, clients, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to travel and work flexible hours, including evenings and weekends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-c3-presents-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-c3-presents-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>