<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-exec.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Project Manager at HP in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The HP.com Tech team in HP IT is looking for talented IT professionals with excellent Project Management experience to join the organization.  We are looking for individuals with the passion to drive significant business outcomes through technical skills, business acumen and leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HP.com Tech team in HP IT, is responsible for providing world class global IT solutions enhancing HP.com’s internal and external capabilities.  The candidate will manage the planning and delivery of these solutions, collaborating with various IT and business partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customers expect rich, meaningful and evolving online experiences. Change happens near real-time, and HP knows that customers have choices. The HP.com Tech team is on a mission to enable excellent user experiences on HP.com by providing high-value capabilities with optimal speed. As a Project Manager delivering Marketing capabilities, you will be responsible for driving rigor, discipline and executive level output across all identified strategy, ops and business planning efforts and will work across ALL functional area of HP.com Tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage our internal Programs/Projects and oversee all aspects of the project including planning, resource estimation, execution, communication with key business partners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishes and maintains relationships with key decision-makers and provides them with program updates and recommendations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage project resources and lead the team/s to achieve on-time delivery and resolve escalations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage external software vendors and HP internal partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure integration between Business process requirements, HP application environment,  and vendor software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that business, function, and geography &amp;ldquo;customers&amp;rdquo; are included appropriately and ensures that they receive sufficient and timely communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leads the due diligence and/or sizing phase of management queries and/or new initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review all deliverables throughout the project lifecycle to ensure completeness, consistency, quality and requirement traceability; Positively represent your designs in architectural reviews;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively identify, analyze and mitigate project and operational risks (resourcing, project/task dependencies and delivery risks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the spirit of continuous improvement, proactively recommend enhancements to existing business and/or IT processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentors and consults with team members and other organizations, customer and vendors on complex issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and Experience Required:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Arts (BA) or Bachelor of Science (BS) degree in Business, Computer Science or a related discipline, M.B.A. or related graduate level degree preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in the computer hardware or software industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience with Agile Software Development Methodologies, particularly Scrum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing application infrastructure and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing large projects with cross-functional and cross-organization teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience delivering web-based software projects and programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience delivering web capabilities such as content management, web publishing tools, authentication, security, search, analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Requirements Management Tools such as Caliber, RequisitePro or HP ALM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in Process Management or Software Development required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise and knowledge in the online space (web, database marketing, privacy, e-business, social media, etc.), including trends and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge and Skills Required:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent facilitation and negotiation skills to influence a broad span of internal and external business partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to lead cross-functional teams based on influence instead of positional authority&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to link interactive plans and activities to business results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of Internet principles and web production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience managing, leading, driving and measuring virtual teams toward common goal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to establish and maintain a high level of business partner trust and confidence across functional areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formal Project Management training, PPM, Six Sigma, ITIL with certification being preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with other software development tools and other packaged applications is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding and experience of modern software development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound analytical and problem solving skills, Excellent consulting skills, Demonstrated leader, Self confident&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills of complex and technical concepts.  Demonstrates strong command of the English language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High internal drive/self-initiative; Ability to work with ambiguous and incomplete information; Resourceful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong relationship building and influencing skills; Able to mediate opposing viewpoints; Work well in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of software test methodologies, and experience with testing automation tools like HP QC, SAP TAO etc is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Critical Competencies to Drive Business Results:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Systems Thinking : Ability to identify potential consequences of changes in processes or system functionality. Ability to recognize trends and patterns as they develop and to assess the strategic and tactical impacts of these trends on the customer experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication : Ability to get ideas across both verbally and in writing, ability to articulate and present vision or concepts that educate and influence thinking, especially in a virtual environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project Management : Ability to balance multiple projects in varying degrees of implementation, and deliver required results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-project-manager-hp-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-project-manager-hp-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Digital Art Director at AdPeople, LLC. in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Digital Art Director is an experienced advertising/design professional who has achieved a track record of success in the new media industry.  The Art Director works with the Creative Supervisor, Account Leads and Producers to provide leadership to junior team members and identifies opportunities to integrate new creative directions into Agency projects. The Art Director is the creative advocate both internally and externally with the Client.  The primary focus for this position is to develop new media concepts and designs; create new and innovative solutions while incorporating the newest technologies.  The Art Director will develop unique and innovative solutions from the creative brief to the final solution.  The Art Director will develop concepts and designs, new media ads, wireless communications, web site content, and other interactive media while integrating with other agency disciplines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct multiple design initiatives and teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insure concept/design consistency across client initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate and prioritize design efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insure brand and design consistency on all interactive projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide team leadership amongst design staff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present concept/design treatments and storyboards to internal and external clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional concept/design projects as required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocate of integration between mediums.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact between brand teams and Enfatico on design issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong conceptual and design ability with comprehensive knowledge of interactive media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Polished client presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational and management skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to envision creative ways to leverage online ideas and technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of proficiency in branding, online marketing, and media concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to integrate the big idea through all mediums.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four plus years design experience, two of those designing specifically for new media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 major launches or site refreshes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge of web-based software tools, such as Macromedia Flash, and animated GIF builders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge of HTML and related web technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of fluency in information architecture, navigation and site standards development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-art-director-adpeople-llc-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/digital-art-director-adpeople-llc-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Manager at iCrossing in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;iCrossing is looking for a Project Manager for their Dallas office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Project Manager leads interactive marketing and Web development projects, oversees creative and technical project teams, interacts with business managers and is responsible for producing projects on time and on budget. The PM also contributes strategic and operational insight on client accounts to promote project efficiency and success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the creation, maintenance and delivery of detailed project plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies and scopes client requirements and deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create goals and milestones that correlate to billable events within a project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies, documents, and manages scope or deliverable change requests required whether initiated internally or by the client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and maintains activity and progress reports for internal and external customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates daily tasks and assigns project resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracks all budget-related information, including billable hours and project expenses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the success of the project while remaining within the scoped time and budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manages and helps ensure client satisfaction in partnership with the internal team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Properly notifies the internal team of any risks, weaknesses or opportunities that could impact the success of the project, escalating to upper management as appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plans for and controls quality by reviewing items before delivery to client; monitoring and enhancing internal and external deliverables/documents; working with internal teams on needed revisions/enhancements, and involving the Quality Assurance team at key project junctures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinates and participates in periodic project and program reviews and strategy meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in and completes training and professional development as detailed within department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintains an understanding of the client’s operating environment and internal processes and procedures that may affect the project’s success; serves as point of contact for clients as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the use of best practices and apply lessons learned from previous projects; share lessons learned with other project management team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of relevant experience managing projects (preferably 2-4 years within an interactive, advertising or marketing agency environment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management principles, methods and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of financial concepts and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to demonstrate experience with professional services processes and tools including workflow development and management, milestone management and quality assurance practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of technical and creative design and development principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing resources, budgets and project timing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience analyzing complex data reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in MS Project, and the entire MS Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business analysis and requirements gathering skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-icrossing-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/project-manager-icrossing-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Manager iOS Delivery at Neiman Marcus in Irving, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Neiman Marcus Stores are located in the most affluent markets in the United States with a presence in Florida, California and Texas. From the finest designer and luxury merchandise for men and women to precious jewelry, beauty and home decor, we offer our customers an impeccable and irresistible array of choices. Since 1907, Neiman Marcus has served our discerning and sophisticated customers with gracious and attentive service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Manager, iOS Delivery will be responsible for certain aspects of the software development life cycle for iOS development projects. These will include, but not limited to, new app development, existing app maintenance, certificate maintenance, managing mobile-device-management processes and app testing. The position will ensure the timely, cost effective, high quality delivery of iOS and potentially other mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage a team of technical analysts, comprised of both internal and external resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staff, develop and train a well-rounded professional department who stays up with current technology and retail trends and who understands how to apply them to the Neiman Marcus environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in the systems architecture planning activities and recommend specific solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in the design of new computer or manual systems based on business needs, hardware and personnel capabilities and existing system integration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure all activities associated with systems/application implementation are done accurately and according to the business specifica tions/needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review status of routine systems performance and efficiency.
*Ensure maintenance is performed on the production apps as appropriate and provide timely support for operations staff and end users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the effective integration of executable and data assets into production editions/builds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in the negotiation of vendor contracts and the resolution of contract issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide input to the Vice Presidents and Directors for budget, long range planning and business systems planning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain knowledge of changing technologies and methodologies and where appropriate, recommend their adoption by Neiman Marcus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain a strong working relationship with appropriate executive sponsors and functional business departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps senior management informed of project status and its effect on business operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain comprehensive knowledge of Neiman Marcus Online business processes as they relate to the design and development of new applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years experience in commercial mobile application development and/or packaged application integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 years experience in a management or project lead position with direct responsibilities for multiple concurrent projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership, mentoring, and staff development skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record in defining and delivering architecturally sound solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated technical thought leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to translate business needs into sound technical solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong planning and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience negotiating with vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree from a four-year college or university or commensurate experience is required&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Currency Employment Status&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full-Time&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/manager-ios-delivery-neiman-marcus-irving-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/manager-ios-delivery-neiman-marcus-irving-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interactive Director at nFusion in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;nFusion seeks an Interactive Director (Digital Strategy) to join our current team and bring a strong business and marketing focus to interactive challenges and opportunities, applying knowledge to develop interactive and technology strategies for our clients. Ideal candidates will be capable of understanding business challenges and developing innovative, technological solutions to achieve measurable results for our clients. Candidates must be confident self-starters, team players, innovative problem-solvers and able to manage multiple projects at once. Candidates need to be attentive to detail, resourceful, work well under pressure and have strong communication skills. Must be effective communicating with technical development team members as well as non-technical resources and clients. The ideal candidates will possess a strong work ethic and a hunger for responsibility and learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and manage interactive strategy, including a full team of interactive developers, producers, and strategists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage execution of interactive projects including: developing and monitoring scopes of work, budgets and schedules during the project lifecycle, managing resource allocation to ensure accurate project delivery and ensuring the final deliverable meets the quality expectations of our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in and lead interactive new business pitches for prospective clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standardize interactive production processes and optimize operations across the agency (including creative, account services)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as a resource and mentor to interactive and development team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop strategies to increase our clients' success through interactive program development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage resource planning, team utilization and continued development of the interactive and development team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead coordination of the establishment of agency point of views for emerging technologies and strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience with:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User experience and information architecture design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile platforms and application development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting online direction and strategy for medium and large corporations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web project management experience in an interactive agency or e-commerce business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent client consulting and relationship management experience (managing expectations, client communications, both written and verbal)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful track record of participating in the business development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience managing both quick-turn and large-scale Web projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven team and project management experience, with ability to act as a mentor and performance coach&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing standardized processes and collaborating across departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong technical understanding of databases, CMS systems, interactive tools and analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of UX and information architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working understanding of all facets of Web development, including strategies, planning, design, implementation, hosting and launching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to meet real-time deadlines, set project budgets and control project quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive project management experience with the ability to handle multiple high-priority projects at the same time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized, detail oriented and a great communicator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Pluses&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive agency experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interaction design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MIS degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MBA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-director-nfusion-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interactive-director-nfusion-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art Director at C3 Presents in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;C3 Presents is an international leader in the music industry and mass gatherings (Austin City Limits Music Festival, Lollapalooza, Big Day Out, Orion Music and More, Austin Food and Wine Festival, and more.) The Art Director will work with the Creative team to take our brand and visual identities to new levels to thrill our fans and artists and sponsors. This position requires a passion for music and bringing brands to life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;PRIMARY JOB DUTIES &amp;amp; RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop branding and identity for C3 properties/clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with the Creative team, other departments and clients to design print &amp;amp; web collateral and on site art installations for festivals, events and artist management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops proposals for prospective C3 properties/clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receiving and routing logos, photos, and various graphic assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivers and implements creative collateral at festival and event sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designs merchandise for festival and artist management clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties and projects as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA in Marketing, Advertising or Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6-8 years of experience in design in advertising, marketing or interactive agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to concept ideas, themes, advertising, graphic elements across the various C3 properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to design while adhering to established brand identities, concepts and standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of branding, marketing communications, and promotional principles and their application in various channels and mediums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Adobe Creative Suite and Microsoft Office. A basic understanding of CSS, HTML, Flash and interactive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create a file and see it through to production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of file types and how to work with both raster and vector files, as well as transfer methods and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to physically work on site, delivering and implementing creative collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reliability – able to see tasks, ideas or projects through, from start to finish; meet deadlines and budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding planning and organization skills – use organized approach to job responsibilities and able to multi-task and set priorities. Be able to thrive in a high-demand, fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate effectively and present concepts to co-workers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to do writing and editing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented and able to perform job accurately and thoroughly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creativity – use independent and original thought and initiative to improve processes or solve problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated – self-directed and self-responsible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to be flexible, adjust to changing conditions and constraints in order to meet goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great attitude – engage in work; be open and approachable to co-workers, clients, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to travel and work flexible hours, including evenings and weekends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-c3-presents-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/art-director-c3-presents-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>