<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Design/Developer at Sheplers Western Wear in Frisco, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating high impact email and website creative designs that engage, attract and sell.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing visually compelling websites and emails following creative direction and brand standards to achieve business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing intuitive user interfaces promoting ease of content consumption&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing responsive design for multiple devices including tablets, phones, desktops and additional devices the market bares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing clean, standards-compliant XHTML, CSS and JavaScript to be viewed by a tiered browser base as presented within analytics reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test one’s own work and following QA processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staying abreast of UID/UXD trends with an mind for future application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS &amp;amp; ABILITIES:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree (Graphic Design, Interaction Design, Visual Communications or Advertising preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years experience in UXD/UID crafting semantic, standards compliant markup with care and consideration to accessibility and SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years experience building with progressive enhancement methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years experience writing JavaScript desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years development experience working with dynamic, server-side languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Q&amp;amp;A processes W3C validation, accessibility and usability audits, tests and debugging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to generate user-friendly web experiences with a strong understanding of typography, color-theory and grid-based design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of effective merchandising principles from concept through completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with responsive website design and mobile/tablet best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building web structures requiring collaboration with backend engineers who specialize in server-side scripting languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and ability to implement search engine optimization into design considerations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized and detail-oriented&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills are required as teamwork and collaboration is a big part of the way we work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willingness and desire to learn new techniques and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to author client-side scripting &amp;ndash; JavaScript &amp;ndash; desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a deadline-driven, multitasking environment like a web development firm or advertising agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective communication with cross-functional teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Western wear and Sheplers has been synonymous for over 100 years. Begun in a modest storefront in Wichita, Kansas, Sheplers has become the world&amp;rsquo;s leading provider of apparel and accessories for the country/western lifestyle including: traditional cowboy wear, fashionable western wear, country inspired casual wear and authentic work gear. Consumers have the ability to shop wherever and whenever it is convenient for them: in one of our 15 stores across the US, online 24/7 at Sheplers.com or via its extensive catalog offering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheplers proudly carries some of the world&amp;rsquo;s best known brands from Wrangler, Levi and Cinch to Justin, Lucchese, Ariat and Nocona, to Stetson to Carhartt and Montana Silversmiths, and much more all under one roof. We cater to men, women and children whether they are looking for a complete outfit, a fun accessory to finish off a special look, or a great piece of home decor. In fact, we carry over 2000 pairs of boots and can fit virtually any size foot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Widely known for its outstanding customer service, Sheplers was recently rated as one of the top ten of all catalogs in terms of customer satisfaction in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheplers, since 1899, and still going strong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-design-developer-sheplers-western-wear-frisco-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-design-developer-sheplers-western-wear-frisco-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Hart Energy in Houston, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Hart Energy seeks a front-end developer to take our suite of websites to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What we do&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Energy is a fast growing company with a great culture, fun atmosphere and fantastic benefits. We are one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading energy industry publishers, providing specialized data/information products and member-only services for the global energy industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s some of what you might do as a developer at Hart Energy:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve usability issues on one of our sites or enhance the current UX;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and implement new ways for our communities to interact;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the editorial teams on new features;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with back-end developers and designers to reinvent our suite of digital products;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be joining a small, but talented team of designers and programmers, who love the web and are constantly working to improve our sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who we&amp;rsquo;re looking for&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have some or all of the following skills and qualities, you&amp;rsquo;d be a great fit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and love improving UX/UI. You use libraries like jQuery or Zepto;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You like to stay abreast of new front-end web development technologies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve worked on small to mid-size news or magazine-style publication sites;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re a self-motivated, organized team player with strong attention to detail;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drupal experience, including theme development (bonus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with backbone.js and node.js a plus (bonus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you get&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hart Energy offers a fun and relaxed work environment, competitive salary, flexible work hours, paid time off, 401k with one of the best company matches around, an awesome medical plan, FSA, dental and life insurance, a coffee machine with 20+ flavors&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-hart-energy-houston-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-hart-energy-houston-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer - Javascript at Volusion in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Volusion is a one-stop shop for all things ecommerce. We’re also a pretty great place to work. Based in Austin, TX, we’re currently serving 40,000+ customers and have big plans for the future. Being an industry leader isn’t easy, but we know how to make it fun. Equipped with our flip flops, free snacks and Nerf guns, we’re leaving our competition in the dust. All we need now is you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volusion is seeking a Front End Web Developer who will be responsible for developing and updating dynamic web sites for our clients. You&amp;rsquo;ll be joining a team that is creative, focused on results, and works together to achieve goals. The Web Developer is responsible for working with project managers and designers to build custom websites. This includes HTML, CSS and JavaScript coding, assisting in the QA, testing and the actual publishing of the websites. JavaScript experience is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and deliver custom designed websites for Volusion Design clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code and update HTML/CSS/JavaScript for assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting in the QA and troubleshooting when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage existing JavaScript libraries to support the engineering and creative needs of client sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate as a member of the Design team, generate new ideas, and creatively discuss ways in which the company can better processes or new services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educate team members on best practices and new technologies, especially HTML5 &amp;amp; CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;SKILLS/QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years of professional web development experience (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write clean, standards-compliant HTML, CSS and JavaScript code that is cross-browser compatible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in web standards and building solutions using semantic markup and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aware of the interplay between JavaScript and HTML &amp;amp; CSS, and can dynamically create, modify, and style elements on a page with ease&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate technical issues with non-technical people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to compile dynamic style sheets using LESS or SASS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using modular script loaders like Require&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project experience working with JavaScript libraries such as Knockout or Backbone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of JavaScript template structures such as Mustache or Jade&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize web frameworks including Django or Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-javascript-volusion-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-javascript-volusion-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Couchsurfing in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You would be responsible for working with engineers and our product team to turn design into reality and build out new features for both our public facing website and our admin interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of web technologies (HTML/CSS/JS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with scripting languages (PHP, Python, Perl, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely detail oriented. Strives for pixel perfect implementation in all browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unmistakable passion for elegant and intuitive user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write well-abstracted, reusable code for UI components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of but not reliant on Object Oriented JavaScript Frameworks (jQuery, MooTools, Dojo, Sproutcore, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with HTML/CSS/JS in high-performance environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for performance debugging and benchmarking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have real world experience and can show us work you&amp;rsquo;ve done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable with agile development practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are excited to help fix the news industry by building something new and exciting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience doing UI/UX design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-couchsurfing-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-couchsurfing-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Volusion in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Volusion is a one-stop shop for all things ecommerce. We’re also a pretty great place to work. Based in Austin, TX, we’re currently serving 40,000+ customers and have big plans for the future. Being an industry leader isn’t easy, but we know how to make it fun. Equipped with our flip flops, free snacks and Nerf guns, we’re leaving our competition in the dust. All we need now is you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volusion is seeking a Front End Web Developer who will be responsible for developing and updating dynamic web sites for our clients. You&amp;rsquo;ll be joining a team that is creative, focused on results, and works together to achieve goals. The Web Developer is responsible for working with project managers and designers to build custom websites. This includes HTML and CSS coding, assisting in the QA, testing and the actual publishing of the websites. The Front End Web Developer will also assist in providing back-up design support when needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and deliver custom designed websites for Volusion Design clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code and update HTML/CSS for assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting in the QA and troubleshooting when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage existing JavaScript libraries to support the engineering and creative needs of client sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate as a member of the Design team, generate new ideas, and creatively discuss ways in which the company can better processes or new services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educate team members on best practices and new technologies, especially HTML5 &amp;amp; CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;SKILLS/QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years of professional web development experience with front end web development (HTML and CSS required; JavaScript preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in using Adobe Creative Suite 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write clean, standards-compliant HTML, CSS and Javascript code that is cross-browser compatible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in web standards and building solutions using semantic markup and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of all major browsers and the special considerations required for all various quirks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aware of the interplay between JavaScript and HTML &amp;amp; CSS, and can dynamically create, modify, and style elements on a page with ease&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to communicate technical issues with non-technical people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-volusion-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-volusion-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Rev Worldwide in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain customer account acquisition websites for prepaid debit card programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the branding guidelines provided by the Marketing and Creative departments for each program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mark up the pages according to the mockups provided by Creative using CSS, XHTML, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement and manage all the copy provided by Marketing, including internationalization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the QA team to help fix bugs and usability issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required skill set:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XHTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics editing and optimizing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordpress or other Publishing Platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-5 years experience developing web applications using XHTML, and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and editing simple graphics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using source control software like Subversion and Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with internationalization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in usability and accessibility a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful candidate will be a self-staring team player with a collaborative work style&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Also prefer experience with the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eclipse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fireworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery or similar JavaScript library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Location:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is located in Downtown Austin TX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Rev Worldwide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rêv Worldwide (Rêv) is a US-headquartered company wholly owned by MPOWER Ventures, LP, a socially committed venture fund that invests in innovative financial service companies benefitting the underserved. Rêv is dedicated to increasing both the diversity and reach of financial products and services for underserved consumers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rêv is a global network of payment companies linked through a centralized technology platform that powers integrated payment solutions, including card payments, money transfers, mobile payments, bill payments, and remittances. This is the world’s first multi-currency, multi-lingual financial service processing platform linking banks, telecommunication companies, and retail stores to underserved consumers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, Rêv has built the largest global branchless banking network of retail partners through which it connects directly to consumers, expecting to reach tens of millions of clients in the coming years through active programs. In more developed countries, this network includes large grocery chains, mobile phone stores, government agencies, and other merchants. In less developed countries, Rêv partners with “mom and pop” grocery and convenience stores, distributor networks, vendor kiosks, and “micro merchants” to connect customers to the payment platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Location(s)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin, TX, US&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;www.revworldwide.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-rev-worldwide-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-rev-worldwide-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>