<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer / Lead at Clarity Ventures, Inc. in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you want to be a part of something big? Are you a creative Web Developer with strong technical and communication skills? Do you operate well in a fun, high-energy environment? Are you a Team Player? Clarity is a profitable, growing business with customers ranging from small businesses to billion dollar enterprises. If you are passionate about developing and designing websites then we want to hear from you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clarity is seeking a Front end Web Development leader who will be responsible for developing and updating dynamic web sites for our clients, coordinating timelines and messaging, and working within our team (alongside our Creative Director) to drive process improvement and the best of breed technologies and methodologies. You&amp;rsquo;ll be joining a team that is creative, focused on results, and works together to achieve goals. The Web Development leadership role is responsible for working with project managers and designers to build custom websites and manage expectations. This includes HTML, CSS, jQuery and javascript coding &amp;ndash; as well as assisting in the QA, testing and the actual publishing of the websites. The Front end Web Developer will also assist in providing back-up design support when needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of professional web development with frontend focus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the web development lifecycle, including QA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience communicating directly with clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High proficiency with the HTML/CSS/JavaScript backed by a sharp, critical eye for detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with the implementation of cross-browser website designs using XHTML, CSS-based layouts and SEO-conscious/semantic markup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to turn sliced designs into professionally rendered, publish-ready deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript experience; DOM scripting; jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite – specifically Photoshop and ideally Illustrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean, standards-compliant HTML, CSS and JavaScript code with cross-browser compatibility. .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Insurance,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit Sharing,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous Paid Time Off,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership Opportunities,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive and Educational Work Environment,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ongoing Training,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rapid Growth,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client Facing Experience,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly Team Lunches .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-lead-clarity-ventures-inc-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-lead-clarity-ventures-inc-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at CIBER in Dallas, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Ciber, Inc. is currently seeking candidates for a Front End Developer position that is available in Dallas, Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Technical skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with standard HTML, HTML5, XHTML, JS, CSS, JSP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Javascript libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong design skills (simple and evolutionary)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test driven development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;General requirements:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing / eager to work in an agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being flexible in the functions performed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work  100% on site (Downtown Dallas) Mon-Fri 8am – 5pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Ciber is a global IT consulting company with 7,000 consultants in North America, Europe and Asia/Pacific, and approximately $1 billion in annual revenue. Client focused and results driven, Ciber partners with organizations to develop technology strategies and solutions that deliver tangible business value. Founded in 1974, the company trades on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE: CBR). For more information, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ciber.com&quot;&gt;http://www.ciber.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as we have built our business on the success of our clients, our continued company growth and achievements are built on the success of our team members. At Ciber we believe our employees are our most valuable asset. Upon contact, a Ciber Recruiter will discuss our benefits package in more detail as it pertains to your individual needs. Some highlights of our full benefits package include: paid time off, paid holidays, retirement savings plan, employee stock purchase plan, medical, dental, vision, life &amp;amp; disability insurance, and tuition reimbursement. Ciber, Inc. is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ciber-dallas-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-ciber-dallas-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Umbel in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a Front End Developer that can implement the front end of our product experience as well as conceptualize new features for our clients. This position will work closely with all members of the product, UI/UX and Dev teams in a collaborative environment, which is diverse and open-minded. A successful candidate will demonstrate best practice front end development while maintaining security, cross-platform/browser compliance, accessibility, scalability and performance standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write terrific front end code for web apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop prototypes quickly and optimize them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be aware of new and emerging front-end technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push back, think creatively and have fun forming products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Expected Experience/Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS, Javascript, HTML5, AJAX mastery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Django/Python (or Ruby on Rails) templating or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimization techniques for performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivered multimedia on a large scale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about interaction design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively blog, tweet and contribute to open source projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in how data can inform critical decisions and deliver tremendous value to any process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a great feel for design and a passion for web standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Google Drive/Docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of Working at Umbel:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% employer paid benefits (medical, dental, vision, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A supportive, challenging and fun team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awesome office location in downtown Austin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to grow your career and skill set&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation including cash and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A company that is young, agile and responsive to great ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-umbel-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-umbel-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI/UX Developer at vtrIT in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;VtrIT is looking for mid / senior-level UI/UX Developer to design, create and deploy front end user interface applications exercising numerous back-end operational API&amp;rsquo;s. This developer should have a good blend of both visual design and coding and will be responsible for rapid development and deployment of customized Web Designs and Front End interfaces supporting high-traffic clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Major Role:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, develop, modify and test PHP/MySQL-based front-end applications, based on CodeIgniter or Zend frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on and improve existing applications built with Object Oriented PHP using the Model-View-Controller (MVC) architecture, with an emphasis on security and reusability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement API&amp;rsquo;s and web services, both internal and external &amp;ndash; using XML, REST, and SOAP from various sources into front end interfaces and templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deploy web applications on Red-Hat based Linux distributions, Linux package management, Subversion, SSH, SCP, SFTP and related technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create clean, professional layouts based on design concepts and PSDs, while following specific guidelines and client requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write semantic XHTML/HTML5 and CSS/CSS3 markup from PSD or other design specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Write scripts with raw JavaScript and jQuery framework/plugins for an enhanced front-end user experience and AJAX&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;BS, BA in Computer Science, Computer Information Systems, MIS or relevant technology degree or Relevant work experience in similar environment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have ability and desire to work in a high-pressure, fast-paced start-up environment and be able to handle several projects and tasks simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years experience in designing/developing and enhancing PHP/MySQL-based front-end applications using PHP, MySQL, XHTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, java script, JQuery, AJAX etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to conceptualize and build &amp;lsquo;outside the box&amp;rsquo; solutions for difficult scenarios while maintaining security and coding standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of (or experience with) security requirements such as those of PCI-DSS and HIPAA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Why choose vtrIT?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like you, we focus on IT, and our industry experience and elite client network enables us to offer several key career advantages:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to exclusive positions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading-edge opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personalized placement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We understand that you have many employment choices, so we work every day to be your best choice for a satisfying career.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-developer-vtrit-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-developer-vtrit-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at uShip in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Begin your next big adventure with uShip!  uShip is the world’s largest and most trusted shipping marketplace. Consumers and businesses can compare and book upfront quotes, name their own price or receive auction-style bids from 300,000 customer-reviewed Transportation Service Providers, ranging from independent owner-operators to the largest freight carriers and brokers.  Since launching uShip in 2004, our mission has been to be the world’s leading online solution for shipping anything, anytime, anywhere. We are passionate about empowering buyers and providers of transportation services to efficiently conduct business on an unbiased, transparent and competitive platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;uShip is seeking talented individuals to join our team as a full time Front End Developer. This individual will be a part of the uShip Development team, which is charged with helping to build and grow the uShip website and marketplace.  If you are a motivated, smart, and driven individual who wants to work in an energetic and entrepreneurial environment with outstanding career and growth opportunities, then this is the opportunity for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop web applications using the MVC, Knockout and Foundation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with project and other developers to delivery new products and features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with product and the UI team to design and build new products and features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of CSS 3, HTML5 and JavaScript experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong UI understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing CSS across multiple browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure and understanding of the latest web standards technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive and mobile design experiences a plus!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Our Ideal Candidate:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with distributed Source Control (Hg/git)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with MVC 4.0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with KnockoutJS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Foundation CSS framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience using JQuery or other JavaScript frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Agile Methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuous delivery/deployment experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-uship-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-uship-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Presentation Layer Developer at Williams-Sonoma, Inc. in Junction, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This individual would own the development of the front end user experience, ensuring that all components follow overall technical architecture and design standards. They would act as presentation layer developer for all front-end presentation changes and updates. The developer should be able to work independently and collaboratively in a fast paced environment, taking on multiple projects at any given time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for architecting and defining the presentation layer framework to solve complex designs and interactions that reflect the creative design direction provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closely collaborate with creative design and technology teams to develop and implement innovative solutions to ecommerce challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in scoping and planning of special projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take features from the design stage through production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively share trends and forecasts of new and interesting technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, maintain, and optimize existing features, as well as ability to prototype and implement new features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build efficient, reusable systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completes tasks within committed deadlines; identifies and escalates any issues that arise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is based in Sydney, Australia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements/ Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s in relevant field or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of front-end development work in an ecommerce environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of HTML, CSS &amp;amp; SASS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High proficiency in writing/editing custom JavaScript (beyond jQuery and other libraries).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of good design principles and ability to adhere to complex design specifications -during implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing web applications for a variety of devices like mobile and touch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with content management systems (CMS) and version control systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with analytics and testing solutions (e.g. Omniture, Test &amp;amp; Target).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A love of web standards, and passionate about web and interface development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational, prioritization, and multi-tasking skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to accurately estimate and scope development work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keen attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with social media development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competency in the Adobe Suite of tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of browser specs and platform issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/presentation-layer-developer-williams-sonoma-inc-junction-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/presentation-layer-developer-williams-sonoma-inc-junction-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Lead Developer at Clarity Ventures, Inc. in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you want to be a part of something big? Are you a creative Web Developer with strong technical and communication skills? Do you operate well in a fun, high-energy environment? Are you a Team Player? Clarity is a profitable, growing business with customers ranging from small businesses to billion dollar enterprises. If you are passionate about developing and designing websites then we want to hear from you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clarity is seeking a Front end Web Development leader who will be responsible for developing and updating dynamic web sites for our clients, coordinating timelines and messaging, and working within our team (alongside our Creative Director) to drive process improvement and the best of breed technologies and methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be joining a team that is creative, focused on results, and works together to achieve goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Web Development leadership role is responsible for working with project managers and designers to build custom websites and manage expectations. This includes HTML, CSS, jQuery and javascript coding &amp;ndash; as well as assisting in the QA, testing and the actual publishing of the websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Front end Web Developer will also assist in providing back-up design support when needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of professional web development with frontend focus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the web development lifecycle, including QA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience communicating directly with clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High proficiency with the HTML/CSS/JavaScript backed by a sharp, critical eye for detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with the implementation of cross-browser website designs using XHTML, CSS-based layouts and SEO-conscious/semantic markup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to turn sliced designs into professionally rendered, publish-ready deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript experience; DOM scripting; jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite – specifically Photoshop and ideally Illustrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean, standards-compliant HTML, CSS and JavaScript code with cross-browser compatibility. .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K, Health Insurance,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit Sharing,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous Paid Time Off,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership Opportunities,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive and Educational Work Environment,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ongoing Training,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rapid Growth,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client Facing Experience,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly Team Lunches .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-lead-developer-clarity-ventures-inc-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-lead-developer-clarity-ventures-inc-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End UI Developer at Golden Frog in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We want to welcome to our talented development team an experienced UI developer who can enhance 4 large-scale websites, develop web applications, build interfaces that interact with mobile and desktop software, and work directly with lead designers and back-end gurus in a strong IT environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t need:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree. Evidence of lifelong learning is more important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You must have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;General&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years web development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio with relevant code samples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong aptitude for learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal responsibility to deliver results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Technical&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML/CSS: Standards-compliant &amp;amp; cross-browser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end website optimization experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Javascript or back-end programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion to develop high-fidelity pages from mock-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sense of design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Nice to Have:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3 &amp;amp; jQuery Animation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile Web Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web App Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Templating systems — Mason/Perl, Lift/Scala, WordPress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unix Command Line&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Environment:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an in-house position at our corporate headquarters in Austin, TX. No extensive telecommuting. No assistance with visas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2009, Golden Frog is a global software developer of Internet applications focused on reliability, performance, and security. The company debuted its first product release with VyprVPN, a personal VPN solution for individuals, internet service providers and channel partners offering ‘last-mile’ internet privacy from any location and virtually any device. VyprVPN provides a secure, encrypted connection to the Internet; a solid layer of privacy protection unavailable with traditional Internet security software. Golden Frog is in early trial phase of its second major product release with Dump Truck, a professional-grade, highly secure, massive online storage service.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-golden-frog-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-golden-frog-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End UI Developer at Golden Frog in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We want to welcome to our talented development team an experienced UI developer who can enhance 4 large-scale websites, develop web applications, build interfaces that interact with mobile and desktop software, and work directly with lead designers and back-end gurus in a strong IT environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t need:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree. Evidence of lifelong learning is more important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You must have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;General&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years web development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio with relevant code samples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong aptitude for learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal responsibility to deliver results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Technical&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML/CSS: Standards-compliant &amp;amp; cross-browser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end website optimization experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Javascript or back-end programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion to develop high-fidelity pages from mock-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sense of design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Nice to Have:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS3 &amp;amp; jQuery Animation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile Web Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web App Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Templating systems — Mason/Perl, Lift/Scala, WordPress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unix Command Line&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Environment:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an in-house position at our corporate headquarters in Austin, TX. No extensive telecommuting. No assistance with visas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2009, Golden Frog is a global software developer of Internet applications focused on reliability, performance, and security. The company debuted its first product release with VyprVPN, a personal VPN solution for individuals, internet service providers and channel partners offering ‘last-mile’ internet privacy from any location and virtually any device. VyprVPN provides a secure, encrypted connection to the Internet; a solid layer of privacy protection unavailable with traditional Internet security software. Golden Frog is in early trial phase of its second major product release with Dump Truck, a professional-grade, highly secure, massive online storage service.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-golden-frog-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-golden-frog-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Designer/Developer at Clarity Ventures, Inc. in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to be a part of something big? Are you a creative Web Developer? Do you operate well in a fun, high-energy environment? Are you a Team Player? Clarity is a profitable, growing business with customers ranging from small businesses to billion dollar enterprises. If you are passionate about developing and designing websites then we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clarity is seeking a Front end Web Developer who will be responsible for developing and updating dynamic web sites for our clients. You&amp;rsquo;ll be joining a team that is creative, focused on results, and works together to achieve goals. The Web Developer is responsible for working with project managers and designers to build custom websites. This includes HTML and CSS coding, assisting in the QA, testing and the actual publishing of the websites. The Front end Web Developer will also assist in providing back-up design support when needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of professional web development with frontend focus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the web development lifecycle, including QA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience communicating directly with clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High proficiency with the HTML/CSS/JavaScript backed by a sharp, critical eye for detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with the implementation of cross-browser website designs using XHTML, CSS-based layouts and SEO-conscious/semantic markup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to turn sliced designs into professionally rendered, publish-ready deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript experience; DOM scripting; jQuery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite – specifically Photoshop and ideally Illustrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean, standards-compliant HTML, CSS and JavaScript code with cross-browser compatibility. .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Perks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Group Health Insurance,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit Sharing Opportunity,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous Paid Time Off,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership Opportunities,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive and Educational Work Environment,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ongoing Training, Rapid Growth,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client Facing Experience,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly Team Lunches .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-designer-developer-clarity-ventures-inc-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-designer-developer-clarity-ventures-inc-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>