<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Rev Worldwide in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain customer account acquisition websites for prepaid debit card programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the branding guidelines provided by the Marketing and Creative departments for each program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mark up the pages according to the mockups provided by Creative using CSS, XHTML, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement and manage all the copy provided by Marketing, including internationalization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the QA team to help fix bugs and usability issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required skill set:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XHTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics editing and optimizing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordpress or other Publishing Platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-5 years experience developing web applications using XHTML, and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and editing simple graphics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using source control software like Subversion and Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with internationalization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in usability and accessibility a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful candidate will be a self-staring team player with a collaborative work style&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Also prefer experience with the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eclipse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fireworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery or similar JavaScript library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Location:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is located in Downtown Austin TX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Rev Worldwide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rêv Worldwide (Rêv) is a US-headquartered company wholly owned by MPOWER Ventures, LP, a socially committed venture fund that invests in innovative financial service companies benefitting the underserved. Rêv is dedicated to increasing both the diversity and reach of financial products and services for underserved consumers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rêv is a global network of payment companies linked through a centralized technology platform that powers integrated payment solutions, including card payments, money transfers, mobile payments, bill payments, and remittances. This is the world’s first multi-currency, multi-lingual financial service processing platform linking banks, telecommunication companies, and retail stores to underserved consumers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, Rêv has built the largest global branchless banking network of retail partners through which it connects directly to consumers, expecting to reach tens of millions of clients in the coming years through active programs. In more developed countries, this network includes large grocery chains, mobile phone stores, government agencies, and other merchants. In less developed countries, Rêv partners with “mom and pop” grocery and convenience stores, distributor networks, vendor kiosks, and “micro merchants” to connect customers to the payment platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Location(s)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin, TX, US&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;www.revworldwide.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-rev-worldwide-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-rev-worldwide-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>