<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Volusion in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Volusion is a one-stop shop for all things ecommerce. We’re also a pretty great place to work. Based in Austin, TX, we’re currently serving 40,000+ customers and have big plans for the future. Being an industry leader isn’t easy, but we know how to make it fun. Equipped with our flip flops, free snacks and Nerf guns, we’re leaving our competition in the dust. All we need now is you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volusion is seeking a Front End Web Developer who will be responsible for developing and updating dynamic web sites for our clients. You&amp;rsquo;ll be joining a team that is creative, focused on results, and works together to achieve goals. The Web Developer is responsible for working with project managers and designers to build custom websites. This includes HTML and CSS coding, assisting in the QA, testing and the actual publishing of the websites. The Front End Web Developer will also assist in providing back-up design support when needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and deliver custom designed websites for Volusion Design clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code and update HTML/CSS for assigned projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting in the QA and troubleshooting when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage existing JavaScript libraries to support the engineering and creative needs of client sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate as a member of the Design team, generate new ideas, and creatively discuss ways in which the company can better processes or new services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educate team members on best practices and new technologies, especially HTML5 &amp;amp; CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;SKILLS/QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years of professional web development experience with front end web development (HTML and CSS required; JavaScript preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in using Adobe Creative Suite 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write clean, standards-compliant HTML, CSS and Javascript code that is cross-browser compatible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in web standards and building solutions using semantic markup and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of all major browsers and the special considerations required for all various quirks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aware of the interplay between JavaScript and HTML &amp;amp; CSS, and can dynamically create, modify, and style elements on a page with ease&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to communicate technical issues with non-technical people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-volusion-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-volusion-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Rev Worldwide in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain customer account acquisition websites for prepaid debit card programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the branding guidelines provided by the Marketing and Creative departments for each program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mark up the pages according to the mockups provided by Creative using CSS, XHTML, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement and manage all the copy provided by Marketing, including internationalization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the QA team to help fix bugs and usability issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required skill set:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XHTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics editing and optimizing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordpress or other Publishing Platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-5 years experience developing web applications using XHTML, and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and editing simple graphics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using source control software like Subversion and Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with internationalization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in usability and accessibility a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful candidate will be a self-staring team player with a collaborative work style&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Also prefer experience with the following:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eclipse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fireworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery or similar JavaScript library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Location:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is located in Downtown Austin TX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Rev Worldwide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rêv Worldwide (Rêv) is a US-headquartered company wholly owned by MPOWER Ventures, LP, a socially committed venture fund that invests in innovative financial service companies benefitting the underserved. Rêv is dedicated to increasing both the diversity and reach of financial products and services for underserved consumers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rêv is a global network of payment companies linked through a centralized technology platform that powers integrated payment solutions, including card payments, money transfers, mobile payments, bill payments, and remittances. This is the world’s first multi-currency, multi-lingual financial service processing platform linking banks, telecommunication companies, and retail stores to underserved consumers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, Rêv has built the largest global branchless banking network of retail partners through which it connects directly to consumers, expecting to reach tens of millions of clients in the coming years through active programs. In more developed countries, this network includes large grocery chains, mobile phone stores, government agencies, and other merchants. In less developed countries, Rêv partners with “mom and pop” grocery and convenience stores, distributor networks, vendor kiosks, and “micro merchants” to connect customers to the payment platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Location(s)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin, TX, US&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;www.revworldwide.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-rev-worldwide-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-rev-worldwide-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>