<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Lead Ios at HCL Technologies in Houston, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years iOS native application development experience using Objective C with Xcode as IDE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 year experience in managing the team and providing technical inputs to the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in providing solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in estimating Complex Mobile application..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform Unit testing and Performance testing of UI using different standard tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and Implement enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating iOS apps with APIs and other enterprise web services and third party API.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of  4 applications developed and published in App Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand the Web service (Restful and SOAP) and needs to be hands on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in HTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in Open GL and third party API for charts etc..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good process background in Agile methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact with customer/onsite co coordinator and provide technical solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide solutions and present as an acceptable format to customer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with iPhone mobile application development technologies is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Cross platform mobile application development tools/technologies is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; We have various opportunities across US – NewYork, Houston, New Jersey.
Candidates with prior work experience in the US and  Valid US Work Authorization need apply only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All applicants will have equal employment opportunities with HCL America. Employment will be based solely on HCL America&amp;rsquo;s need and the individual&amp;rsquo;s qualifications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HCL America, as part of it&amp;rsquo;s employment process will conduct background checks for all it&amp;rsquo;s applicants. All applicants are required to complete these checks prior to an offer extension from HCL America.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-lead-ios-hcl-technologies-houston-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-lead-ios-hcl-technologies-houston-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at Sogeti in Houston, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Roles/ Responsibility/ Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a talented Android Application Developer with Mobile App and Platform experience. Individuals applying for this position should have a portfolio that demonstrates their ability to develop compelling Android applications&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full time position with Sogeti in Houston, Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Function as Developer responsible for programming hybrid HTML5/CSS3 Android OS Applications as well as native Android OS Applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide proven knowledge in Android OS application functionality &amp;amp; limitations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cooperate with designers and apply Android Interface guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years of Android development in a production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ Android Marketplace or iPhone App Store published applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience with JavaScript, JSON and interfacing Android applications to server side API`s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTTP and client-server interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well organized and self-motivated with the ability to prioritize workload&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An excellent communicator, able to apply a wide range of interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User Interface design savvy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS automated &amp;amp; unit testing experience useful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML5 libraries such as PhoneGap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of the software development lifecycle, including scoping, planning, conception, design, implementation, deployment and maintenance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with other mobile platforms or mobile-web development a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Sogeti USA:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking to join a company with a proven record of success and limitless growth opportunities, start with Sogeti USA. We are a premier provider of information technology services to businesses and public sector organizations. Operating in 23 U.S. locations, the Sogeti USA business model is built on providing customers with local accountability and vast delivery expertise. Sogeti USA is a leader in helping clients develop, implement and manage practical IT solutions to help run their business better. With over 40 years of experience, Sogeti USA offers a comprehensive portfolio of services including Advisory Services, Application Development with New Technologies, Business Information Management Services, Engineering Services, Infrastructure Management, Cloud and Security Services, Mobile Services and Testing Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of the employee experience at Sogeti USA is working for a company that truly values the individual. We are committed to establishing and maintaining a relationship with each each member of our team and our mission to exceed our employees' expectations in the same way that we exceed our clients'. At Sogeti USA, that begins with what we believe is a highly competitive benefits package.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-sogeti-houston-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-sogeti-houston-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>