<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/tx-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Intern at ChaiONE. in Houston, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have a passion for the web and mobile applications? Would you like the opportunity to help build the next generations of web and mobile solutions? If this sounds interesting and you are looking for an environment where the discovery of new and innovative ways of solving problems is the norm then this is for you. Come learn all you need to know about today&amp;rsquo;s Mobile world.?Chaione is a digital agency that specializes in creating web applications and mobile &amp;amp; touch experiences for consumer, B2B, and enterprise clients. We are looking for a Sr. Web Developer who will be engaged in creating web and mobile applications for Chaione and Chaione clients. The ideal candidate will be an exceptionally skilled developer with intensive experience building websites and web applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need command of all facets of web development, including how to properly build out a standards based front-end (HTML/CSS as well as the hard core development stuff). ?You will need to have strong interpersonal skills because there will be lots of team and client interaction, on top of that you will need excellent written communication skills. An ability to discern when to follow the tried and true and when to propose fresh creative solutions is key. ??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The ideal applicant should have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A self starter with a passion for the entire web &amp;amp; mobile development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of leading and coaching while still rolling up your sleeves and coding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some knowledge of HTTP, REST, JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General knowledge of Javascript, jQuery experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked with Ruby on Rails or other modern web development language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Somewhat familiar with various API integrations, CMS applications, XML or JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with current web standards and hand-coded HTML &amp;amp; CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Versed with implementing visual design, human factors, usability and standards to ensure an engaging and consistent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What will you do?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create advanced web &amp;amp; mobile applications (iPhone, android platforms)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with scoping small and large scale web sites and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with client during the course of the project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with and analyzing wireframes &amp;amp; storyboard in order to build prototypes and applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply for this position:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience developing web applications with a tableless HTML/CSS based layout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A live project example of your code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A college degree (computer science, MIS) or equivalent real world experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of iPhone and/or Android platforms a big plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with basic IIS and Apache administration a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Amazon EC2, S3 and other web services a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Objective-C, Xcode, iPhone SDK, Eclipse and Android SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self Learner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team Player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technically Savvy and Passionate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Git a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using or contributing to open source projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Ruby on Rails a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;We will offer you:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An internship that offers you hands-on experience with enterprise size clients as well as start-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The chance to learn from some of the best creative minds in the field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An international client list, including big names in business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An informal fun and social work environment where enthusiasm and hard work are rewarded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to make impact and contribute on the quality of our environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-intern-chaione-houston-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-intern-chaione-houston-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at Volusion in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Volusion is a one-stop shop for all things ecommerce. We’re also a pretty great place to work. Based in Austin, TX, we’re currently serving 40,000+ customers and have big plans for the future. Being an industry leader isn’t easy, but we know how to make it fun. Equipped with our flip flops, free snacks and Nerf guns, we’re leaving our competition in the dust. All we need now is you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;ESSENTIAL DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect and implement highly interactive native iOS applications supporting our ecommerce offerings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize REST endpoints for service calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore emerging technologies such as location-awareness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive innovation across our mobile offerings by designing world-class interaction models and creating disruptive applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foster engagement with gamification techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full Agile (SCRUM) SDLC participation from ideation to production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive design planning process, including process improvements and project scoping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate business objectives and user needs into functional, navigation, and user interaction requirements and design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with product management and influence the product vision for major feature additions and enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;SKILLS/QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years of experience developing in the iOS ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 currently available iOS apps containing your contributions available on the Apple App Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Objective-C skills, additional OO semantics preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of touch interfaces and available frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ecommerce background is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with User Research, Usability Testing, and Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organization, communication and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS or equivalent combination of work experience and education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrives in fast-paced environment, a self-starter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EDUCATION/EXPERIENCE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS or equivalent combination of work experience and education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-volusion-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-volusion-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile UI Designer (Android, iOS) at Data Foundry, Inc. in Austin, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking to hire a talented Mobile User Interface (UI) Designer to help us design new and exciting applications based on our VPN and online storage technologies for Android and iOS.  Our applications are in use by hundreds of thousands of customers in over 50 countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contract/freelance opportunities also available&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the lead Mobile User Interface (UI) Designer you will help create unique experiences for our customers that solve real problems.  You will also be key in developing and unifying all of our existing products into a coherent visual brand.  You&amp;rsquo;ll gain valuable experience and engage with a cross-disciplinary team to contribute to the conceptualization, design, and specification of innovative consumer/business products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years professional experience in User Interface design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of Android and iOS design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The creativity and desire to create unique user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to self-manage multiple projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity working with development and QA teams to address issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and collaboration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional portfolio that focuses on User interface design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eagerness to work in a fast-paced startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous QA testing experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data Foundry, Inc. provides comprehensive wholesale and retail data center outsourcing, colocation, and disaster recovery services. The company provides its customers with secure premium facilities for servers and equipment, emergency workspace and carrier-neutral network accessibility, supported by experienced onsite technicians and customer support 24/7/365. The company supports more than 1,000 enterprise customers across a variety of industries including energy, healthcare and financial services. Founded in 1994, Data Foundry, Inc. was the first Internet Service Provider in San Antonio and one of the first 50 Internet Service Providers in the United States. Today, Data Foundry, Inc. operates data centers in Austin and Houston and owns private networks in Austin, Houston, San Antonio and Dallas.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-ui-designer-android-ios-data-foundry-inc-austin-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-ui-designer-android-ios-data-foundry-inc-austin-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Technical Lead Ios at HCL Technologies in Houston, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years iOS native application development experience using Objective C with Xcode as IDE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 year experience in managing the team and providing technical inputs to the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in providing solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in estimating Complex Mobile application..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform Unit testing and Performance testing of UI using different standard tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and Implement enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating iOS apps with APIs and other enterprise web services and third party API.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of  4 applications developed and published in App Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand the Web service (Restful and SOAP) and needs to be hands on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in HTML and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in Open GL and third party API for charts etc..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good process background in Agile methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact with customer/onsite co coordinator and provide technical solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide solutions and present as an acceptable format to customer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with iPhone mobile application development technologies is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Cross platform mobile application development tools/technologies is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; We have various opportunities across US – NewYork, Houston, New Jersey.
Candidates with prior work experience in the US and  Valid US Work Authorization need apply only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All applicants will have equal employment opportunities with HCL America. Employment will be based solely on HCL America&amp;rsquo;s need and the individual&amp;rsquo;s qualifications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HCL America, as part of it&amp;rsquo;s employment process will conduct background checks for all it&amp;rsquo;s applicants. All applicants are required to complete these checks prior to an offer extension from HCL America.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-lead-ios-hcl-technologies-houston-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/technical-lead-ios-hcl-technologies-houston-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at Sogeti in Houston, TX</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Roles/ Responsibility/ Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a talented Android Application Developer with Mobile App and Platform experience. Individuals applying for this position should have a portfolio that demonstrates their ability to develop compelling Android applications&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a full time position with Sogeti in Houston, Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Function as Developer responsible for programming hybrid HTML5/CSS3 Android OS Applications as well as native Android OS Applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide proven knowledge in Android OS application functionality &amp;amp; limitations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cooperate with designers and apply Android Interface guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years of Android development in a production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ Android Marketplace or iPhone App Store published applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience with JavaScript, JSON and interfacing Android applications to server side API`s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTTP and client-server interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well organized and self-motivated with the ability to prioritize workload&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An excellent communicator, able to apply a wide range of interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User Interface design savvy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS automated &amp;amp; unit testing experience useful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML5 libraries such as PhoneGap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of the software development lifecycle, including scoping, planning, conception, design, implementation, deployment and maintenance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with other mobile platforms or mobile-web development a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Sogeti USA:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking to join a company with a proven record of success and limitless growth opportunities, start with Sogeti USA. We are a premier provider of information technology services to businesses and public sector organizations. Operating in 23 U.S. locations, the Sogeti USA business model is built on providing customers with local accountability and vast delivery expertise. Sogeti USA is a leader in helping clients develop, implement and manage practical IT solutions to help run their business better. With over 40 years of experience, Sogeti USA offers a comprehensive portfolio of services including Advisory Services, Application Development with New Technologies, Business Information Management Services, Engineering Services, Infrastructure Management, Cloud and Security Services, Mobile Services and Testing Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of the employee experience at Sogeti USA is working for a company that truly values the individual. We are committed to establishing and maintaining a relationship with each each member of our team and our mission to exceed our employees' expectations in the same way that we exceed our clients'. At Sogeti USA, that begins with what we believe is a highly competitive benefits package.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-sogeti-houston-tx</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-sogeti-houston-tx</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>