<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ut-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP Web Application Developer at UtahTechnologyJobs.com in Salt Lake City, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Full-time position available with 12-year-old Salt Lake City firm to manage and maintain our multi-site e-commerce platforms. Emphasis will be on user interface, design, and some back-end work. We are in the process of upgrading our user experience and front-end design initiatives. On the back-end we want to maintain and strengthen existing processes. This position is part of the management team and will participate in evaluation, strategy, and operational discussions, while managing technical aspects of our customer-service team workload.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Technical Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP5 – Candidate should be a top-notch PHP developer, familiar with the latest PHP features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MySQL – Modern database development expertise, words like ‘trigger’ and ‘view’ should be part of your vocabulary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XHTML/CSS/Javascript/AJAX – Expert level Javascript/XHTML/CSS development will be necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JQuery experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Oriented Development / CS Background – Idea candidates should understand object oriented development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Services – Experience building /consuming modern web services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Linux administration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to troubleshoot a Linux stack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Apache administration skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Skills and Attributes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with MS Office (Outlook, Word, Excel) and MS Exchange&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience providing written and oral technical error synopsis and corrective remedies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uses best practices in external and internal technical, team, and business relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively driven to improve existing processes and elegantly craft new ones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacity to understand client requirements and meet functional expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate mentorship ability; able to give and receive constructive feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented, thorough, organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-sufficient; capable of working independently and as part of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hard-working, attendance to task, responsible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Education and Experience&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree in Information Systems, Computer Science or related field preferred but not required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of web-application development with hands-on experience in PHP / MySQL environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-web-application-developer-utahtechnologyjobs-com-salt-lake-city-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-web-application-developer-utahtechnologyjobs-com-salt-lake-city-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at AtTask, Inc. in Lehi, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Would you like to be part of an award winning, profitable, fast-growing, privately held company located in Lehi, UT? Are you passionate about the chance to use your skills and experience to make a difference with an exciting and innovative organization? Do you believe that good user experience is a worthy challenge? Then you might want to join us at AtTask. We need you in our Marketing UX group to work closely with UX, Design, and Content Marketing to help develop and maintain our online presence (including mobile).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with user experience designers to developing user-centric interfaces for both web and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain testing/QA processes to ensure consistency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create code that validates and complies with current standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create templates with guidelines and documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enforce web standards compliance and ensure that web pages and content are tested across multiple platforms and browsers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduce and implement innovative techniques and technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help manage and complete production tasks to create and update web content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-manage completion of projects and work with internal customer to ensure satisfaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get the work done, but have fun at the same time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in object-oriented PHP5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in HTML/XHTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing/extending WordPress to provide solutions for translation/localization, site search, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Eloqua and SalesForce.com integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with responsive web design techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of current web standards and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced JavaScript knowledge including AJAX and frameworks such as JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and Fireworks to cut images from given design files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Top notch communication skills—both verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent problem solving and creative thinking skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to self-motivate, think analytically, and work with great (bordering on obsessive) attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated to research and learn about new technologies and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation &amp;amp; Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Competitive salary commensurate with experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-attask-inc-lehi-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-attask-inc-lehi-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Ecommerce Web Developer at Black Diamond Equipment Ltd. in Salt Lake City, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black Diamond is seeking a Web Developer to work as part of a smart, dedicated team to help design and build ecommerce sites for a rapidly growing multi-brand, multinational company. If you enjoy the challenges and opportunity of working in a fast-paced start up environment with the benefits of a mature company, then Black Diamond may be for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Skills and General Experience:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience extending and integrating with complex systems via SDKs and APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with web services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the latest in web standards like HTML5 and CSS3 modules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced JavaScript experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AJAX and JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Git or other version control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appreciation for web standards, best-practices and high quality user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Nice to have&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with payment gateways and billing systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Demandware&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years web development experience (ecommerce experience a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ecommerce-web-developer-black-diamond-equipment-ltd-salt-lake-city-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ecommerce-web-developer-black-diamond-equipment-ltd-salt-lake-city-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>