<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ut-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer at Instructure in Sandy, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Instructure is a successful, fast-moving technology company that is disrupting the Learning Management System (LMS) market by setting a new standard for education technology, and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for some top-notch people to join the team. Our company has been featured on TechCrunch, CNBC, and The Motley Fool (to name a few).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our UX team is looking for designers who want to shape and mold the user interface of Canvas LMS as well as our mobile products. If you’re an Interaction or Visual Designer who lives for exceptional product design, we want to talk to you. You will work closely with product managers, and developers to architect, design, and optimize our applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what you will be doing:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, iterate, and refine UI and UX concepts for the company&amp;rsquo;s core products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve complex interactions design challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use findings from user feedback to create designs that will satisfy their needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop wireframes, visual comps, functional prototypes and process flows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and deliver elegant, detailed design solutions to our engineers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are highly collaborative&amp;hellip;in a good way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you need to know and have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Years of experience do NOT matter, your talent and a portfolio will speak for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTML, CSS, and web standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of the latest web technologies and their capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative with exceptional design and analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously in an Agile development environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;You will need to include a digital portfolio of your best work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will provide relocation support&amp;hellip;come snowboard, mountain bike and hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;100% Employer Paid Benefits for You and Your Qualified Dependents (We got you completely covered!):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical (United Healthcare).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental (LifeMap).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life/AD&amp;amp;D (Assurant).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Time Off:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of paid time off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 paid holidays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;More perks&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fully stocked break room. Equipment provided. That&amp;rsquo;s right, you get a MacBook (and we&amp;rsquo;ll even throw in a desk and chair). Just saying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We participate in eVerify. EEO.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-instructure-sandy-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-instructure-sandy-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Graphic Designer at Instructure in Sandy, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Instructure is a successful, fast-moving technology company that is disrupting the Learning Management System (LMS) market by setting a new standard for education technology, and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for some top-notch people to join the team. Our Company has been featured on TechCrunch, CNBC, and The Motley Fool (to name a few).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a highly creative, talented graphic designer who gets excited about creating unique, strongly branded marketing and promotional materials as well as soundly designed web experiences that are easy to use. This person will be responsible for design through the entire creative process: from abstract concepts to tangible designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for someone who enjoys pushing beyond current design trends and thrives in a collaborative team environment. Candidates must have a stellar portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what you need to know/have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in concepting and designing branded marketing materials and collateral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in creating trade show materials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of web standards, design principles, and dynamic web user interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Icon and glyph creation experience as well as mad typography skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open to receive instruction, accept constructive criticism and feedback well and have a willingness to redesign until we “get it right”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a copywriter while developing ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and experience in company branding, layout, color theory and typography in digital media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects at once and meet deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience quoting and managing print jobs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to read long lists. Congrats. You passed your first test.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, you will need to include a digital portfolio of your best work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Culture:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instructure has a pretty relaxed atmosphere. No one has an office, we actually like working with each other so we sit together. We care a lot more about what people do than how they dress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% Employer Paid Benefits for You and Your Qualified Dependents (We’ve got you and yours covered!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical (United Healthcare)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental (LifeMap)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life, STD/LTD (Assurant)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Time Off:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of paid time off (ask us about this one)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;More perks…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity. Fully stocked break room. Equipment provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We participate in eVerify. EEO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-graphic-designer-instructure-sandy-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-graphic-designer-instructure-sandy-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI/UX Designer at OveractDev Technology Partners in St. George, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We work with Fortune 500 companies and funded startups to develop enterprise software applications that make a difference for these companies and make a big impact on people’s lives. We have a massively talented team of engineers, designers, marketers, engagement managers, and admin colleagues. Many of our clients have been with us since the beginning because of our exceptional team that uses discipline and creativity to create quality applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently in a growth period where we are looking to immediately fill a UI/UX Designer position to meet the demands of our expanding clientele.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years of professional work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Ajax, HTML, XHTML, XML, XSLT, CSS, DHTML and WordPress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to rapidly execute hi-fidelity mockups with a strong attention to detail, consistency, and craftsmanship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A high quality portfolio that can be viewed online (please submit with application).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in graphic design, human-computer interaction, interaction design, or other related fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We work very hard to create an environment that people want to work in, from the  transparency about our business to the team focus to the flexibility and laid back atmosphere. Here are some of the benefits you can expect when you work for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenging projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talented mentors and colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of opportunity for growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited vacation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical and dental insurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(K) plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocked break room.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Friday lunches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is available immediately, so if all of this sounds good to you give me a call at 855-683-7228 or submit your resume and portfolio by clicking on the Apply button.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-designer-overactdev-technology-partners-st.-george-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-designer-overactdev-technology-partners-st.-george-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>