<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ut-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at ISO in Orem, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Xactware Solutions provides computer software solutions for professionals involved in estimating all phases of building and repair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1986, Xactware opened for business with Xactimate, its flagship estimating system. Xactimate helped contractors and insurance adjusters estimate repairs much faster and more accurately than they ever could before. Since then, Xactimate has evolved into a high-powered package complete with a patented plan-sketching program, and Xactware has become much more than just Xactimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today 22 of the top 25 property insurance companies in the U.S. use Xactware property insurance claims tools. Xactware features software solutions for every phase of a building&amp;rsquo;s life: from remodeling to totally replacing a building, from determining the cost of rebuilding a structure to preserving and repairing a home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xactware also provides tools to estimate personal property, emergency repairs, and more. Xactware users can work on a desktop, laptop, tablet, smartphone, or &amp;ldquo;on the cloud&amp;rdquo; using browser-based solutions. Estimating products are connected to a comprehensive set of tools that includes an assignment network, analytical reports, cost research, project management, and third-party products. The online training center provides users with high-quality training on Xactware solutions and the construction industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xactware reinvests heavily in research and development as well as in the quality of people who develop its products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xactware is a member of the Verisk Insurance Solutions group at Verisk Analytics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xactware is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist product teams in defining functional interaction requirements specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop mockup/prototype interaction designs, navigation structures, information designs, user interaction models, information architecture, wire frames and screen flows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with usability specialists to conduct customer studies of mockups, prototypes and existing interfaces; and iterate designs based on usability test results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use storyboards and mockups to effectively communicate designs to product management and development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in product development teams working on user interface designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with user-centered design/human factors specialists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of how to best design to solve business and user problems. Ability to understand the needs of customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design fundamentals including information design, visual design, industry UI standards for desktop and web-based applications, and ease of use best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with design tools, including Photoshop, Visio, Microsoft Expression Blend, other related.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-iso-orem-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-iso-orem-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at Verisk Analytics in Orem, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Xactware Solutions provides computer software solutions for professionals involved in estimating all phases of building and repair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1986, Xactware opened for business with Xactimate, its flagship estimating system. Xactimate helped contractors and insurance adjusters estimate repairs much faster and more accurately than they ever could before. Since then, Xactimate has evolved into a high-powered package complete with a patented plan-sketching program, and Xactware has become much more than just Xactimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today 22 of the top 25 property insurance companies in the U.S. use Xactware property insurance claims tools. Xactware features software solutions for every phase of a building&amp;rsquo;s life: from remodeling to totally replacing a building, from determining the cost of rebuilding a structure to preserving and repairing a home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xactware also provides tools to estimate personal property, emergency repairs, and more. Xactware users can work on a desktop, laptop, tablet, smartphone, or &amp;ldquo;on the cloud&amp;rdquo; using browser-based solutions. Estimating products are connected to a comprehensive set of tools that includes an assignment network, analytical reports, cost research, project management, and third-party products. The online training center provides users with high-quality training on Xactware solutions and the construction industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xactware reinvests heavily in research and development as well as in the quality of people who develop its products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xactware is a member of the Verisk Insurance Solutions group at Verisk Analytics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xactware is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist product teams in defining functional interaction requirements specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop mockup/prototype interaction designs, navigation structures, information designs, user interaction models, information architecture, wire frames and screen flows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with usability specialists to conduct customer studies of mockups, prototypes and existing interfaces; and iterate designs based on usability test results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use storyboards and mockups to effectively communicate designs to product management and development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience in product development teams working on user interface designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with user-centered design/human factors specialists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of how to best design to solve business and user problems. Ability to understand the needs of customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design fundamentals including information design, visual design, industry UI standards for desktop and web-based applications, and ease of use best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with design tools, including Photoshop, Visio, Microsoft Expression Blend, other related.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-verisk-analytics-orem-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-verisk-analytics-orem-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>HTML Email Designer at ICON Health &amp; Fitness, Inc. in Logan, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;ICON Health &amp;amp; Fitness is looking for an individual who has basic front end web design skills such as knowledge of typography and principles of design. They also need to know HTML and use of tables as well as in line CSS. They must be able to work as a team player and be able to meet deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML and use of tables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to save images for the web (slicing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hand Coded HTML skills a must &lt;strong&gt;cannot rely on WYSIWYG editors alone&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive email design a plus. AAP/EOE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Instructions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please apply at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.iconfitness.com&quot;&gt;http://www.iconfitness.com&lt;/a&gt;
Or
Apply Online Now&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This employer participates in E-Verify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal law requires all employers to verify the identity and employment eligibility of all persons hired to work in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Este Empleador Participa en E-Verify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La Ley Federal le exige a todos los empleadores que verifiquen la identidad y elegibilidad de empleo de toda persona contratada para trabajar en los Estados Unidos.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/html-email-designer-icon-health-%26-fitness-inc-logan-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/html-email-designer-icon-health-%26-fitness-inc-logan-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer at Cogent Infotech Corp in Salt Lake City, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Group of 15 strategic designers, developers, videographers and marketers seeking a talented and experienced UI designer with vision &amp;amp; charisma. Company is growing tremendously and have recently expanded to the east coast. This position requires a strong graphic design background and a portfolio to reflect that. The UI Designer will act as a liaison between design and development departments to develop killer web and mobile UX and UI solutions. Candidate should display the ability to advocate a sanctimonious marriage of Form and Function . The team is young and ambitious and is constantly striving to push the envelope in the industry. Current clientele consists of Google, Marriott, Saks Fifth Avenue, and as such, growth and brand require only the best talent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years UI web development field experience with a solid online web portfolio to prove it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A love for learning and creative thinking above all else&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of IA, UX and UI principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An appreciation and understanding of information architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An aptitude for wire framing and design programs, specifically Photoshop, Illustrator and Indesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A die-hard work ethic and the ability to work well in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A stellar smattering of graphic design and UI design samples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undergraduate degree or equivalent is highly preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation &amp;amp; Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary:45,000 + DOE&lt;br/&gt;
Benefits: Health, 401k, Gym Membership, Timeshare point (free vacations)&lt;br/&gt;
Perks: Fun, creative environment; Bean bags &amp;amp; Wii in the office.&lt;br/&gt;
Location: SLC or Logan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Execuwin:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great companies stay great by hiring the very best, and the best employees bring more to a job than just superior skills &amp;lsquo; they also fit the culture and vision of the company they work for. At Execuwin, we refer to this as company-candidate &amp;ldquo;alignment,&amp;rdquo; and it makes all the difference. We&amp;rsquo;re confident our candidates will become our clients highest-impact team members. There is nothing more valuable than finding that &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; candidate. So when there&amp;rsquo;s no time to waste and no margin for error, let us help you win. Execuwin, Recruitment Agency. People. Perfectly Aligned.™&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-cogent-infotech-corp-salt-lake-city-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-cogent-infotech-corp-salt-lake-city-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI Designer at Instructure in Sandy, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Instructure is a successful, fast-moving technology company that is disrupting the Learning Management System (LMS) market by setting a new standard for education technology, and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for some top-notch people to join the team. Our company has been featured on TechCrunch, CNBC, and The Motley Fool (to name a few).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our UX team is looking for designers who want to shape and mold the user interface of Canvas LMS as well as our mobile products. If you’re an Interaction or Visual Designer who lives for exceptional product design, we want to talk to you. You will work closely with product managers, and developers to architect, design, and optimize our applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what you will be doing:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, iterate, and refine UI and UX concepts for the company&amp;rsquo;s core products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve complex interactions design challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use findings from user feedback to create designs that will satisfy their needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop wireframes, visual comps, functional prototypes and process flows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and deliver elegant, detailed design solutions to our engineers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are highly collaborative&amp;hellip;in a good way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you need to know and have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Years of experience do NOT matter, your talent and a portfolio will speak for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTML, CSS, and web standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of the latest web technologies and their capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative with exceptional design and analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously in an Agile development environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;You will need to include a digital portfolio of your best work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will provide relocation support&amp;hellip;come snowboard, mountain bike and hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;100% Employer Paid Benefits for You and Your Qualified Dependents (We got you completely covered!):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical (United Healthcare).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental (LifeMap).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life/AD&amp;amp;D (Assurant).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Time Off:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of paid time off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 paid holidays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;More perks&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fully stocked break room. Equipment provided. That&amp;rsquo;s right, you get a MacBook (and we&amp;rsquo;ll even throw in a desk and chair). Just saying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We participate in eVerify. EEO.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-instructure-sandy-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-designer-instructure-sandy-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Graphic Designer at Instructure in Sandy, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Instructure is a successful, fast-moving technology company that is disrupting the Learning Management System (LMS) market by setting a new standard for education technology, and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for some top-notch people to join the team. Our Company has been featured on TechCrunch, CNBC, and The Motley Fool (to name a few).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a highly creative, talented graphic designer who gets excited about creating unique, strongly branded marketing and promotional materials as well as soundly designed web experiences that are easy to use. This person will be responsible for design through the entire creative process: from abstract concepts to tangible designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for someone who enjoys pushing beyond current design trends and thrives in a collaborative team environment. Candidates must have a stellar portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Here’s what you need to know/have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in concepting and designing branded marketing materials and collateral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in creating trade show materials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of web standards, design principles, and dynamic web user interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Icon and glyph creation experience as well as mad typography skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open to receive instruction, accept constructive criticism and feedback well and have a willingness to redesign until we “get it right”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a copywriter while developing ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of and experience in company branding, layout, color theory and typography in digital media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects at once and meet deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience quoting and managing print jobs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to read long lists. Congrats. You passed your first test.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, you will need to include a digital portfolio of your best work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Culture:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instructure has a pretty relaxed atmosphere. No one has an office, we actually like working with each other so we sit together. We care a lot more about what people do than how they dress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% Employer Paid Benefits for You and Your Qualified Dependents (We’ve got you and yours covered!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical (United Healthcare)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental (LifeMap)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life, STD/LTD (Assurant)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Time Off:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of paid time off (ask us about this one)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;More perks…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity. Fully stocked break room. Equipment provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We participate in eVerify. EEO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-graphic-designer-instructure-sandy-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-graphic-designer-instructure-sandy-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UI/UX Designer at OveractDev Technology Partners in St. George, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We work with Fortune 500 companies and funded startups to develop enterprise software applications that make a difference for these companies and make a big impact on people’s lives. We have a massively talented team of engineers, designers, marketers, engagement managers, and admin colleagues. Many of our clients have been with us since the beginning because of our exceptional team that uses discipline and creativity to create quality applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently in a growth period where we are looking to immediately fill a UI/UX Designer position to meet the demands of our expanding clientele.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years of professional work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Ajax, HTML, XHTML, XML, XSLT, CSS, DHTML and WordPress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to rapidly execute hi-fidelity mockups with a strong attention to detail, consistency, and craftsmanship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A high quality portfolio that can be viewed online (please submit with application).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in graphic design, human-computer interaction, interaction design, or other related fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We work very hard to create an environment that people want to work in, from the  transparency about our business to the team focus to the flexibility and laid back atmosphere. Here are some of the benefits you can expect when you work for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenging projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talented mentors and colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of opportunity for growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited vacation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical and dental insurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(K) plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocked break room.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Friday lunches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is available immediately, so if all of this sounds good to you give me a call at 855-683-7228 or submit your resume and portfolio by clicking on the Apply button.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-designer-overactdev-technology-partners-st.-george-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ui-ux-designer-overactdev-technology-partners-st.-george-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>