<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ut-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer at Qualtrics, Inc. in Provo, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualtrics makes sophisticated research simple. Our company is a worldwide leader in enterprise data collection and analysis. Founded in 2002, Qualtrics has more than 4,500 customers including 1,300 universities worldwide, all of the top business schools, and half the Fortune 100. Companies use Qualtrics solutions for a wide range of market, customer, and employee research, including consumer research, product evaluation, voice of customer measurement, employee feedback and sentiment surveys, etc. Now let’s move on to the fun stuff…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal web designer will help our marketing team take over the world. Likely projects will consist of maintaining and updating the current Qualtrics.com website, designing and developing new product landing pages (both static pages and WordPress themes), and assisting in the design of sales assets. We are not looking for “that’ll do” kind of work. We are looking for, “sweet sassy molassy, that is awesome”, work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position will require a minimum of 20 hours of work per week with full time potential for the right fit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Position Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Both personal and work experience designing and developing websites, presentation of a portfolio alongside a resume will be required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong eye for design, particularly web-focused&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe’s Creative Suite software (PS/AI are a must)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know HTML and CSS like the back of your hand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of JavaScript and PHP a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem solving skills, with ability to think analytically and find creative solutions to problems and difficulties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player. Cool person. No divas allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ad agency experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must also like free food and laughing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;How to Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact hiring@qualtrics.com for more information&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-qualtrics-inc-provo-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-qualtrics-inc-provo-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>CSS/HTML Developer at Marketecture in Orem, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;CSS/HTML Developer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Job Description&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced CSS/HTML developer to help code/upload website designs/layouts to our proprietary website builder. They should be well versed with uploading custom design themes to multiple website platforms and manipulating design elements. They should be able to efficiently and independently troubleshoot coding issues. The candidate will also have Junior CSS/HTML staff assigned to them, so they must be willing to train, mentor and oversee the quality of production for members of their team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Position Information:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current number of openings: 1 Position: Full-Time
Benefits: Health, Dental, Vision and HSA benefits available
Compensation: DOE
Perks: Exciting/Energetic Work Environment, Foosball, Ping Pong, and Mini Basketball Tournaments, Fountain Drinks &amp;amp; Pebble Ice, Monthly Company Luncheons, Paid Holidays, and Gold&amp;rsquo;s Gym Membership&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML/CSS Advanced-Level Knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of accessibility, bandwidth and cross-browser compatibility issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be proficient at testing on different operating systems and browsers/email clients (e.g.Macs &amp;amp; PCs: Safari, Firefox, Chrome, IE7-9)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to code table and table-less layouts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to code rudimentary CSS/DHTML/Javascript for front end UI features and effects while maintaining semantic HTML and clean CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with themeing or skinning popular CMS platforms (ie. Drupal, Wordpress,Magento, etc.) a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a team with project managers, designers and programmers to develop dynamic, interactive web sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide input into CSS/HTML site development standards and processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Photoshop (e.g. basic image slicing/production)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Javascript frameworks, e.g. jQuery, a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to handcode without the use of Dreamweaver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates must be well organized, detail-oriented, and creative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS or equivalent required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code clean HTML/CSS table and table-less layouts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code HTML/CSS for both emails and web pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rudimentary CSS/DHTML/Javascript coding for front end UI features and effects (rollovers, tabbed interfaces, image swappers and overlays etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage in overall quality assurance testing with an emphasis on troubleshooting cross browser/email client issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating and sharing a knowledgebase on front end developer-related issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee training and quality of work for Junior staff assigned to the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;How to Apply&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send a completed Employment Application form and a copy of your resume to hr@marketecture.com for consideration. Thank You.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/css-html-developer-marketecture-orem-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/css-html-developer-marketecture-orem-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Insidesales.com in Provo, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are an award-winning provider of hosted automation tools for companies who primarily use the telephone and Web technologies to qualify sales leads, and close deals. With recognition from the INC 500, Stevie Awards, Best of State, and Utah Business IQ Awards, InsideSales.com has been leading the pack in the lead management industry since 2003, and we have no plans of relinquishing our position. That’s where you come in. We’re sending a call out to all up-and-coming Accountants who have a desire to work for an award-winning and industry innovative software company. Our technologies are a mash-up of web and telephony tools which offer a rewarding opportunity to push yourself to higher levels, and to be on the ground level of a new technological revolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer stellar compensation plans, a fast-growth career track, and sweet benefits&amp;mdash; including medical, dental, life, disability, time-off, a gym membership, creative allowance, cross-function training, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Position Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track and analyze website usage data to establish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build landing pages and perform split tests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain monthly reports and dashboards and participate in monthly and quarterly business reviews as well as in the annual product planning process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in other Marketing projects as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain primary responsibility for tracking key metrics and performance around website conversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Position Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years+ experience specializing in Internet marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong work ethic, and a high level of professionalism&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical: ability to analyze multiple data points and develop clear hypotheses and actionable from the results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated self-starter who can multi-task and respond to changing work activities with pressing deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High proficiency with Excel including pivoting capabilities and analysis modules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of basic statistics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail-oriented and able to maintain a high level of ownership and accuracy on all work activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to adapt and operate within a high-performance culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-insidesales-com-provo-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-insidesales-com-provo-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Designer/Developer at Fusion-io in Salt Lake City, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Fusion-io is immediately seeking to add additional talent to our creative marketing organization by adding a senior-level digital design expert equally comfortable with creating truly unique and high quality design but also coding them to life with an expertise in the latest web standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blend the vision of our creative web designs with the functionality supplied by our back-end systems to create professional, highly usable, standards-compliant online experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a top notch, world-class designer and develop inspired work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be the ultimate design and creative lead with the perfect mix of technical savvy and an eye for design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills/Qualifications/Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master with the full set of Adobe CS tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working on the latest/greatest hardware and software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent, standards-based HTML coding abilities (HTML 5, CSS, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years proven experience; Typically prefer 7+ years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate well with a team, drive deliverables and collaborate with all stakeholders in a project; Project management experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nit-picking attention to detail; Must hit all deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong commitment to quality and usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to work in fast paced environment; positive and proactive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superb organizational and time management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Company Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fusion-io is the pioneer of a new storage memory platform that significantly improves the processing capabilities within a data center by moving process-critical, or active data closer to the CPU where it is processed. Called shared data decentralization, this significantly reduces latency while increasing data center efficiency. Fusion’s integrated hardware and software solutions leverage non-volatile memory for enterprise-grade performance, reliability, availability and manageability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2006 by a management team with experience in transaction processing, high-performance networking, storage, superclusters, and computing and image processing, Fusion-io recognized that mechanical storage architectures do not keep pace with advances in digital processing power. This meant that despite major advances in technology, data processing was limited to the speed of legacy storage infrastructures. Without a solution designed to maximize their capabilities, modern CPUs sit idle while they wait for data to process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fusion-io solves the data supply problem with a new purpose-built solution. By combining hardware and software to develop a reliable storage memory platform, Fusion-io gives servers native access to data to accelerate enterprise databases and applications. This allows enterprises to significantly reduce complex and expensive high performance storage, high performance networking, and memory-rich servers.In addition to accelerating performance, Fusion’s storage memory platform also reduces energy consumption and total cost of ownership&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-designer-developer-fusion-io-salt-lake-city-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-designer-developer-fusion-io-salt-lake-city-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End UI Developer at PayPerks in Provo, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;BambooHR is the #1 HR software for small and mid-sized businesses. We help our customers save money and time by empowering them with tools previously provided only from complicated and expensive systems. We move them out of spreadsheets and into an easy-to-use online tool that saves time and money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position will work closely with UX designers and back-end engineers to build snazzy user interfaces for BambooHR using the latest cross-browser development methods. We are looking for someone with both the excitement and abilities necessary to build modern, dynamic, user interfaces in a way that supports our vision of delivering a world class experience to our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role requires a strong attention to detail and the ability to produce a highly interactive front-end for an enterprise-level web application. Expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and JavaScript frameworks (e.g. jQuery) are essential skills for this position. You will collaborate heavily with other designers and engineers as you create complex web UI components and pages. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got mad skills and love building awesome web UI&amp;rsquo;s, we want to talk to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Stuff About You That Makes Us Happy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to produce super sweet user interfaces from Photoshop or Fireworks files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to effectively build modern UI components from scratch (date pickers, interactive lists, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of web standards and cross-browser web development best practices, and the ability to mentor others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work samples demonstrating proficiency in building highly interactive web based applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What We Offer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Small team, big impact. Everything you do makes a difference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great team members. People you&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy being around.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customers worldwide. From well-known brands like Pinterest to the dentist around the corner, we serve businesses around the globe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible schedule. Not an early bird? We can accommodate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rest and relaxation. Paid time off and paid holidays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary. Based on your skill and experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;When applying, please include a link to your portfolio so you can show us what you&amp;rsquo;re capable of bringing to the table. We saved a seat for you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-payperks-provo-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-ui-developer-payperks-provo-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Developer / User Experience Designer at Property Solutions in Lehi, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are in search of a full-time Front-End Developer / User Experience Designer to add creative thought leadership to our products while battling for the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with in-house analysts and product managers to define product specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute out-of-the-box thinking while assisting in product brainstorming and feature molding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage users to identify their thoughts, visions, strategies, goals and processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm and wireframe user workflows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Construct working HTML/CSS prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform user testing to evolve designs and interactions to maximum efficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced front-end dev skills (HTML &amp;amp; CSS &amp;ndash; jQuery is a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in creative problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent listener and facilitator who knows how to draw out real information from data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely organized with high attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to establish a course of action for self or others to accomplish a specific goal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently and manage multiple tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Base Wage/Salary:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Annual Salary, DOE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PTO &amp;amp; Paid Holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work Schedule and Location:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday-Friday during normal business hours (40 hour workweek)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lehi, UT office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel: This role may require travel from time to time for on-site researching and testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Benefits Package&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k with matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short-term and long-term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free gym membership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Application Instructions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send an email to resumes@propertysolutions.com with a resume attached and Front-End Developer / User Experience Designer in the subject line. Property Solutions participates in E-Verify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Property Solutions International, Inc. is the largest portal and online payment provider in the U.S., servicing over 3.5 million apartment residents nationwide. Founded in 2003, Property Solutions is a uniquely positioned B2B SAAS company serving the multi-family industry. Our suite of technology solutions enable our customers to manage all aspects of the critical functions necessary to run a multi-family management company, from property-level operations all the way up to corporate management and marketing. Our vision is to enable more efficiency and productivity for our clients through the development, distribution, and support of world-class software.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-user-experience-designer-property-solutions-lehi-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-developer-user-experience-designer-property-solutions-lehi-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>