<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ut-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at OveractDev Technology Partners in Orem, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We work with Fortune 500 companies and funded startups to develop enterprise software applications that make a difference for these companies and make a big impact on people’s lives. We have a massively talented team of engineers, designers, marketers, engagement managers, and admin colleagues. Many of our clients have been with us since the beginning because of our exceptional team that uses discipline and creativity to create quality applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently in a growth period where we are looking to immediately fill an iOS Developer position to meet the demands of our expanding clientele.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed iOS apps in the last 2 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in Objective-C/Cocoa/iOS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your iOS solutions have included significant server-side development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with Agile methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love to take on a challenging problem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a computer science degree or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We work very hard to create an environment that people want to work in, from the  transparency about our business to the team focus to the flexibility and laid back atmosphere. Here are some of the benefits you can expect when you work for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenging projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talented mentors and colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of opportunity for growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited vacation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical and dental insurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(K) plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocked break room.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Friday lunches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is available immediately, so if all of this sounds good to you give me a call at 855-683-7228 or submit your resume by clicking on the Apply button.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-overactdev-technology-partners-orem-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-overactdev-technology-partners-orem-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>