<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ut-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Lead iOS Developer at MoneyDesktop in Provo, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;MoneyDesktop is well positioned in the financial technology space as an award-winning provider of financial management and online and mobile banking tools. We are seeking a Sr. iOS Developer to architect, build and maintain MDs mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why work with us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are a well-funded, early stage technology company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We all love what we do and put in the effort that shows it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We truly work hard and play hard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer much more than a job. We offer the opportunity to build something great with great people and have a great time doing so&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we look for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for quality, design and user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong team player, highly collaborative work style&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience executing clean and engaging designs/features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dynamic portfolio highlighting your quality work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What we give in return:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborative work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company paid lunches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health, dental and vision benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open vacation policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-ios-developer-moneydesktop-provo-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/lead-ios-developer-moneydesktop-provo-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Software Developer at Pearson in Sandy, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Pearson is the global leader in educational publishing, assessment, information and services, helping people of all ages to learn at their own pace, in their own way. For students, Pearson provides effective and innovative curriculum products in all available media, educational assessment and measurement for students and teachers, student information systems, and teacher professional development and certification programs. Pearson&amp;rsquo;s respected brands include Scott Foresman, Prentice Hall, AGS, PowerSchool, SuccessMaker, TeacherVision and many others. The company&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive offerings help inform targeted instruction and intervention so that success is within reach of every student. Pearson&amp;rsquo;s other primary businesses include the Financial Times Group and the Penguin Group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a Mobile Device Software Developer to participate in software development of Pearson&amp;rsquo;s mobile native and web-connected software applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain mobile applications in Objective C.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Estimate development efforts and enter estimates into Agile project tracking tool. Provide daily updates to your progress within the tracking tool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow Agile and ATDD methodologies on all development projects, including Release Planning, automated testing, and regular iteration reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and develop prototype products as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot and remedy programming bugs and errors as documented and prioritized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in daily project stand-up meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver products that meet business goals and financial objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in team environment and share knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate new technologies and software products to determine feasibility and desirability of incorporating their capabilities into the platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;LI-JM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience in the development and deployment of mobile device applications, including Objective C for iOS (school projects acceptable).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the design of web service architectures for mobile-connected applications (school projects acceptable).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Agile Software and Test Driven Development methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in technical field such as Computer Science or Engineering (or 5+ years of equivalent programming experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Segments:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developer, Curriculum, Engineer, Media Publishing, Information Systems, Technology, Education, Engineering, Publishing&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-software-developer-pearson-sandy-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-software-developer-pearson-sandy-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at OveractDev Technology Partners in Orem, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We work with Fortune 500 companies and funded startups to develop enterprise software applications that make a difference for these companies and make a big impact on people’s lives. We have a massively talented team of engineers, designers, marketers, engagement managers, and admin colleagues. Many of our clients have been with us since the beginning because of our exceptional team that uses discipline and creativity to create quality applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently in a growth period where we are looking to immediately fill an iOS Developer position to meet the demands of our expanding clientele.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed iOS apps in the last 2 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in Objective-C/Cocoa/iOS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your iOS solutions have included significant server-side development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with Agile methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love to take on a challenging problem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a computer science degree or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We work very hard to create an environment that people want to work in, from the  transparency about our business to the team focus to the flexibility and laid back atmosphere. Here are some of the benefits you can expect when you work for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Benefits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenging projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talented mentors and colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of opportunity for growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited vacation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical and dental insurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(K) plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocked break room.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free Friday lunches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position is available immediately, so if all of this sounds good to you give me a call at 855-683-7228 or submit your resume by clicking on the Apply button.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-overactdev-technology-partners-orem-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-overactdev-technology-partners-orem-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>