<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/ut-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Support Technician at Spillman Technologies, Inc. in Salt Lake City, UT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Provide the initial support to customer inquiries, to ensure customers are receiving the highest level of customer support by ensuring efficient operation in the application environment. The Support Technician I position represents the beginning level in the Technical Support Department. Support Technician I personnel will work in a help desk environment to facilitate proper troubleshooting methods and customer service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Requires a basic knowledge and skill using Unix OS including knowledge of Unix command lines.  Should be able to work in a terminal environment understanding and navigating within the command lines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Requires a basic knowledge of network trouble shooting skills.  Ability to listen, determine and  provide corrective action measures to connectivity problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Includes FREE medical benefits and a annual salary of $36,000.00.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answers incoming customer service calls in a timely manner. (Calls may originate via internal Spillman, web, e-mail, phone, fax or other means)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the nature of incoming problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates customer inquiry record and enters them into the customer support database.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resolves basic customer inquiries pertaining to the Spillman software and moves second level customer inquires to available Level 2 technical support technicians.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducts required testing of modified programs to ensure that changes operate correctly and that changes have no adverse impact on programs or systems operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directs activities to contribute to the overall performance of the Technical Support operation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs administrative support activities for customers, Support Department Manager, Customer Services Vice President, and Support Department Technicians.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Places appropriate priority on problems reported by customers or internal personnel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other duties and tasks as given by their Supervisor, Support Department Manager, or Customer Services Vice President.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The above items describe the nature and general level of work performed. They do not constitute an exhaustive list of all duties. Additional responsibilities may be assigned, as required, by Spillman Technologies, Inc. The employee must possess the essential knowledge and skills described below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Special Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess excellent written and verbal English communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to professionally work with irate customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work under high stress conditions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess good problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be self-motivated and dependable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work well in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have good organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work under moderate supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should have a high energy level and enthusiasm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;High School graduate, one to two years formal technical education in computer related field such as Computer Science or Business Information Systems preferred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prefer 0 to 1 years previous customer service or Help Desk Technician experience to include telephone skills in a customer service environment, typing skill of 45 30-60 words per minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Support Technician must be able to demonstrate skills and abilities in a technical environment grasping basic technical concepts; including familiarity with servers and connectivity trouble shooting skills. Experience using Unix, or Linux, and Windows operating systems is preferred. A Unix OS is strongly used and previous knowledge, skills, and abilities are encouraged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prefer experience understanding and troubleshooting basic networking problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An exposure or some experience with software programming languages is helpful in the position. Familiarity with any of the C-languages, Visual Basic, Perl, and/or scripting is a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Position is funded by the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/support-technician-spillman-technologies-inc-salt-lake-city-ut</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/support-technician-spillman-technologies-inc-salt-lake-city-ut</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>