<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/va-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP Developer at WillowTree Apps in Charlottesville, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;WillowTree Apps is seeking an experienced PHP web-application engineer to develop, manage, maintain, and update PHP application products. If you yearn to work for a tech company on the cutting edge, like collaborating with a group of talented people and want to actually enjoy going to work everyday then WillowTree Apps may be the place for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use GitHub, embrace continuous integrations and testing, prefer “scrum”-style stand-ups and hang out on our own secure IRC channel (svn users are welcome, but we will convert you).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CS Degree and/or 5 years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least four years of experience in PHP and MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with testing in PHPUnit, SimpleTest, or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with one or more of the following frameworks:  Symfony, Zend or CodeIgniter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong front-end development skills in Javascript with jQuery or similar, HTML5, and CSS 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with git, svn, or other modern version control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magento development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;WillowTree Apps is one of the largest and most respected mobile development companies in the US. Our entire 40+ person team is located in our Charlottesville, VA headquarters. Nothing is outsourced overseas. Our open office environment is designed to facilitate collaboration both among our teams (e.g. a developer walking over to the design team for a clarification or a design tweak) and within each team (e.g. a senior iOS team member pair programming with a junior member).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our developers are second to none &amp;mdash; with expertise across the nuances of iPhone, iPad, Android, Windows Phone 7, Blackberry and mobile web/HTML5 design best practices. Our team members are frequent speakers at mobile design conferences. We hire the best in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-developer-willowtree-apps-charlottesville-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-developer-willowtree-apps-charlottesville-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>PHP Developer at GBTI Solutions, Inc in McLean, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand functional and technical requirements, and translate requirements into technical design for a web application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop both front-end website, as well as back-end database code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, test and maintain web application as it is developed and enhanced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Migrate website functionality, develop new functionality, and provide application maintenance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer Science Bachelor degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong programming background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong academic computer background&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, CSS, Unix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CodeIgniter framework, PHP, Drupal knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The team works in a flexible work schedule environment with an opportunity to work independently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The compensation package includes salary, and standard benefits such as medical, dental, vision, vacation, holidays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested, please send resumes to GBTI HR at perminder.kaur@gbtisolutions.com with your contact information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-developer-gbti-solutions-inc-mclean-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/php-developer-gbti-solutions-inc-mclean-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Back-End Developer at Huddler in Herndon, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for emerging superstars &amp;ndash; developers that are still hungry and looking for exciting opportunities, but who also have a few years of relevant experience. Experience with scalability (caching, database sharding, etc.), performance tuning, community growth, and SEO are all considered major pluses, but ultimately great developers are problem solvers regardless of the challenge. You should be comfortable leading a small team of engineers and working collaboratively with our front-end team under tight deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Oriented PHP5 experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database schema design and optimization (PostgreSQL a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working with other engineers on a small team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast learner and natural problem solver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript (YUI even better)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimization, scalability, database sharding and caching (memcached)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Security-aware&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience implementing and customizing site-wide search (Lucene/Solr a big plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search Engine Optimization experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management/distribution of large email lists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/back-end-developer-huddler-herndon-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/back-end-developer-huddler-herndon-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Software Developer II - US Job at Rackspace in Blacksburg, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Rackspace is seeking a talented Software Developer to help build a world class interface for customers to manage their IT infrastructure. Fanatical Support starts with a
Control Panel that enables our customers to get things done faster and simpler than ever before. You&amp;rsquo;ll work with a strong, passionate engineering team to turn our public
REST APIs into a responsive and beautiful web interface that leads our customers to rave about their experience with our products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write thick client front-end code in Javascript, HTML, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ship new features and fix bugs in a continuous delivery environment (5-10 production deploys per day)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write clean and maintainable code using engineering best practices (unit testing, continuous integration, automation, design patterns, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with other software engineers, product managers, user experience designers, and operations engineers on a daily basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide Fanatical support of all production software on which you currently work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The ideal candidate will have the following:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science or related field with 2-5 years practical engineering experience in building large-scale web-based applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with a server-side framework like Django or Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of DOM manipulation (jQuery, Dojo, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disciplined approach to testing and quality engineering (Jasmine, QUnit, YUITest, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing in a Linux environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communications
Top candidates may also have some of the following:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building applications with an object oriented Javascript framework (Google Closure, Backbone, Spine, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good sense of what is required for a great user interface and experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to turn mocks from designers into the right HTML and CSS/LESS/SASS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity or experience with Agile engineering practices (test driven development, continuous integration and pair programming, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Rackspace, a world leader in hosting delivers enterprise-level managed hosting, cloud hosting, and e-mail hosting services to businesses of all types and sizes globally. Today we serve thousands of customers from data centers around the world. Rackspace integrates the industry&amp;rsquo;s best technologies and practices for each customer&amp;rsquo;s specific needs delivering it as a service via the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to Fanatical Support®. We serve as an extension of our customers' IT departments enabling them to focus on their core business. Rackspace was founded in 1998 and since then has had significant growth year after year. There are now over 4,000 Rackers employed worldwide dedicated to providing customers our premier hosting services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rackspace Hosting is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above information has been designed to indicate the general nature and level of work performed by employees in this classification. It is not designed to contain or to be interpreted as a comprehensive inventory of all duties, responsibilities, and qualifications required of the employee assigned to this job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Type of Job(-US Only) 0&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nearest Major Market&lt;/strong&gt;: Blacksburg
&lt;strong&gt;Nearest Secondary Market&lt;/strong&gt;: Virginia
&lt;strong&gt;Job Segments&lt;/strong&gt;: Developer, Engineer, Computer Science, Linux, Web Design, Technology, Engineering, Creative&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/software-developer-ii-us-job-rackspace-blacksburg-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/software-developer-ii-us-job-rackspace-blacksburg-va</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>