<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/va-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designers at LongView in Falls Church, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;As a Web Designer, you will be responsible for designing and prototyping user interface for the web, PC and emerging mobile platforms, to include a mobile version of the organization&amp;rsquo;s web sites. You will work with project team, enterprise architecture, product managers, implementation group, and other stakeholders to understand requirements, information architecture and user flows, and convert them into a simple but functional design. You will be expected to make recommendations on best architecture approaches, libraries, framework recommendations in order to support the standardization of an architecture that will support the needs of the user experience and the user interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be involved in developing web sites for multiple projects and to standardize the approach against these projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in discussions with clients about user definition, web development and help them think through how best to achieve their business objectives through quality user experience and user interface design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iterate, produce, and present project deliverables such as user flows, wireframes, and concept designs to demonstrate and sell recommended solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within development teams to ensure conformance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Technical Experience Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of HTML, CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise using a standard design tools (Photoshop, Illustrator, Fireworks, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of web design best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Application Architecture design experience is a HUGE plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating wireframes, storyboards and prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing on various platforms such as browsers, tablets and smart devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess an advanced knowledge of web and mobile user interface design. For mobile, understand when mobile web apps are appropriate as opposed to dedicated native applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with SiteCore Content Management System a HUGE plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of web development across browsers, including design, development support, implementation, user experience feedback, and iterative improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant degree, such as a BA in Computer Science, Human factors, Human computer interactions, Interaction Design, or Industrial Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designers-longview-falls-church-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designers-longview-falls-church-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience (UX)/Interaction Designer at MANDIANT in Alexandria, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you passionate about designing applications that solve real problems? Do you have an interest in building products that help national security and Fortune 500 companies protect their networks from evil? Are you smart and analytical, with an insatiable curiosity about how things work?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mandiant, a fast growing information security company, is seeking a User Experience/Interaction Designer. At Mandiant, UX doesn’t just make things look pretty, we are involved at every level of the process—from kickoff meetings, to interaction design, to help documentation. The ideal candidate is someone who can move easily between strategy and implementation and who is able to develop a deep understanding of the business, our users, and the technology. You must have great people skills and the ability to communicate and build trust with stakeholders, customers, managers, and developers. If you love building applications, but are tired of shopping carts and social media, we have some wonderfully complex and technical design problems you can really sink your teeth into.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your typical day here might include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting out with doing user research with internal users and customers, then a meeting with developers to nail down feature requirements and scope. Proceeding to a rapid sketching session with the team. Partaking in lunch (yes, there is such a thing as free lunch, catered every Friday and delicious) and catching up on the latest activity of evildoers. Next, a kickoff workshop with stakeholders to develop a product roadmap. Then you’ll create annotated wireframes to release to developers and finish the day with knocking out a few buttons in Photoshop in time for a product release. If this energizes you then please read on:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create user interface designs that delight our highly technical end users by discovering what they really need through user interviews and other creative research methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create context-appropriate deliverables such as sketches, wireframes, task flows, scenarios, and personas to communicate designs, drive decisions, and reach consensus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employ user-centered methodology to design applications with cohesive organization, elegant navigation, and effective labeling and search&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitate stakeholder meetings and workshops&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help build a sustainable UX practice that can scale with the company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze, report on, and incorporate feedback from usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create production assets from design comps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building and refining interface designs on projects with highly technical stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to establish technical credibility when working with developers to negotiate implementation direction and options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;History of planning and delivering UI projects involving both usability and development activities in a timely manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience performing usability testing in an agile context or on a small, &amp;ldquo;Rocket Surgery&amp;rdquo; scale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in OmniGraffle, Visio, or comparable wireframing tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Valued Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enterprise application design experience desired, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience conducting user research and task analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual design experience. Data visualization experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong technical skills—HTML, CSS, javascript are useful, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with version control systems, such as GitHub and Subversion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail, including grammar and spelling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education/Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. or B.A. in Computer Science or comparable work-related experience in Interaction Design, User Experience, HCI or Information Architecture, visual design, or related technical platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position may be located in our office in Alexandria, VA (headquarters) Reston, VA or New York City&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are unable to sponsor or transfer work visas at this time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EEO-M/F/D/V&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-ux-interaction-designer-mandiant-alexandria-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-ux-interaction-designer-mandiant-alexandria-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Associate Designer at K12 in Herndon, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are a brand with the clear purpose of bringing the JOY of learning back into education. For design this means a rare chance to use your skills to change minds, change lives and an even history. To get there we need your help. We’re looking for the right addition to our design team to fill the role of Associate Designer. The ideal person will be deeply passionate about great design, proficient in the standard Adobe CS, detail-obsessed and relentlessly self-motivated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary role of the Associate Designer will be applying approved designs and concepts to a final format – ready for either final print or digital production. This includes projects such as resizing ads to various specs, ongoing tweaks to collateral materials, and any production level work needed to keep us moving smoothly.
We also ask and expect this person to contribute creatively by being part of all team brainstorm sessions with an ongoing expectation to contribute ideas and opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply approved concepts and designs to a wide-range of sizes, specs and formats across various print and digital mediums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow existing style guidelines and contribute to the creation of new campaigns and designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production of artwork, revisions, approvals and accuracy of information as well as file set-up, spec requirements, testing and file uploads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage expectations with proactive communication with design team and project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years of design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of HTML and CSS (Know the lingo and how it works)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert level abilities in Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator * Solid portfolio of projects (student and paying) showing your ability to design for both print and digital media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and troubleshooting skills * Well-organized with a strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-designer-k12-herndon-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/associate-designer-k12-herndon-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at HNTB in Arlington, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;HNTB is currently seeking a Graphic Designer to work in our Arlington, Virginia marketing department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For nearly a century, HNTB has helped create infrastructure that best meets the unique demands of its environment. With client relationships spanning decades, we understand infrastructure life cycles and have the perspective to solve technical challenges with clarity and imagination. We see and help address far-reaching issues of financing, legislation, design, construction, community outreach and ongoing operations. As employee-owners committed to the highest levels of performance we enable clients to achieve their goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate will help support marketing efforts for a multi-state region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with marketing coordinators and technical staff to develop, design and produce graphics for proposals and presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The candidate will work with staff to develop and produce advertisements, brochures and collateral materials for various clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must be able to work overtime (paid) and to travel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree in Communications, Art, Graphic Design, or related area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years art and graphic design, video production marketing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of InDesign, Photoshop and Illustrator required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Job will also require extensive use of Keynote and Powerpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding grid systems is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The HNTB Companies are an equal opportunity employer and does not discriminate on the basis of age, race, gender, religion, color, sex, national origin, marital status, genetic information, sexual orientation, pregnancy status, physical or mental disability, veteran status or other status protected by law. In compliance with the Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1986, we will hire only U.S. citizens and aliens lawfully authorized to work in the United States (if the position is or will be one which is subject to U.S. law). We will provide reasonable accommodation for qualified individual with a disability where appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-hntb-arlington-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-hntb-arlington-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Graphic Designer at HNTB in Arlington, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;HNTB Corporation is currently seeking a Senior Graphic Designer in our Arlington, Virginia office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new designer will leverage their expert knowledge of InDesign, Photoshop and Illustrator to design and coordinate the development of a wide range of print and multimedia materials.  They will creates original graphic design and comprehensive layout concepts and coordiantes production of materials and may even oversee the work of less experienced staff members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HNTB is a major Engineering /Planning/Architecture firm with an open and collaborative atmosphere!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The new HNTB graphic marketing group leader will do the following:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help support marketing efforts for a multi-state region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with creative and technical staff to develop, design and produce graphics for proposals and presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with staff to develop and produce advertisements, brochures, annual reports and other collateral materials for various clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Other activities may include:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate and coordinate with outside print vendors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine which vendor can suit the project needs and supply in the most efficient and cost effective manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with clients to understand their needs and to develop direction, concept and specifications for assigned projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, choose and coordinate with vendors for printing/publication services as appropriate per project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate graphic photo “library” and maintain electronic records.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine which approach to take in design or print/multimedia materials to best serve client needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform miscellaneous job functions such as photo/document scanning and electronic document creation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with team leader to determine workload distribution and determine the need to bring in additional resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine if in-house documents are best distributed in print or electronic format. Project Manager makes final decision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BFA in graphic design or equivalent required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years graphic design experience preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of InDesign, Photoshop and Illustrator required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidate must be able to work overtime (paid) and to travel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;***  Please include a portfolio with resume!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HNTB Companies are an equal opportunity employer and does not discriminate on the basis of age, race, gender, religion, color, sex, national origin, marital status, genetic information, sexual orientation, pregnancy status, physical or mental disability, veteran status or other status protected by law. In compliance with the Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1986, we will hire only U.S. citizens and aliens lawfully authorized to work in the United States (if the position is or will be one which is subject to U.S. law). We will provide reasonable accommodation for qualified individual with a disability where appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-hntb-arlington-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-graphic-designer-hntb-arlington-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at VBrick Systems in Herndon, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Chances are you’ve watched &amp;mdash; and really enjoyed streaming video. Chances are you realize that the video market is about to explode with all kinds of content being delivered to all kinds of devices.   If this excites you as much as it does us – you will enjoy being part of the VBrick team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VBrick brings the power and benefits of streaming video to corporations, educational institutions, healthcare facilities and government entities.  We initially transformed the business of network video by delivering the first MPEG 1 encoding and decoding device.  Fast forward 14 years and VBrick continues to be the leading Enterprise IP video innovation leader with an entire end-to-end suite of products that efficiently enable the capture, management, distribution and display of video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VBrick hires talented individuals and offers the creative freedom to explore and reach your potential.  We offer a full benefits package, including Incentive Stock Options. VBrick is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please see our job openings below and send us your resume. We are headquartered in Wallingford, CT with offices in Boston and the San Francisco Bay area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Graphic Designer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate is proficient in both print &amp;amp; online mediums (with an emphasis on online mediums). He or she will be expected to work quickly and efficiently to create designs that effectively represent the VBrick brand. The ability to take ideas all the way from concept to execution is a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Specific job responsibilities include:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize, create, implement and maintain all corporate web assets (websites, blogs, landing pages, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize, create, and implement graphic assets for sales collateral, presentations, lead generation campaigns and newsletters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize, create, and edit cutting edge video assets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create graphic assets needed by the software development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Details:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in Adobe Creative Suite for both print and web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong HTML knowledge (HTML5 experience a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong foundation in CSS (CSS3 experience a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of JavaScript (JQuery experience a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to build and maintain WordPress-powered (or like) sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to build and maintain Video assets a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptual and strategic thinker who can bring a fresh and relevant perspective to creative design concept meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated with good time management, prioritization, and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A. or B.S. degree in Web Design, Graphic Design or equivalent professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;How to Apply :&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VBrick Systems is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-vbrick-systems-herndon-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-vbrick-systems-herndon-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at RealNetworks in Reston, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;RealNetworks®, Inc. is a global Media Software and Services company headquartered in Seattle, Washington. RealNetworks creates innovative applications and services that make it easy to connect with, share, and enjoy digital media. Check us out at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.realnetworks.com&quot;&gt;http://www.realnetworks.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mobile Entertainment team at RealNetworks is seeking a talented Graphic Designer to join their team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mobile Entertainment group, a leader in music/Ringback tones/ringtones, is looking for a creative designer that is proficient with graphic creation software suites including Adobe Photoshop and has a demonstrated ability to deliver creative images and designs in a production environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you will build, own, and be accountable for:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create images for mobile and web services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate with service partners for content programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create graphic designs for promotions and other marketing activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support icons and images for in house application development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Candidates must have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree in related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to produce detailed work product in a fast-paced, deadline-driven environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to support multiple projects simultaneously, managing priorities against urgent ad hoc requests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player with strong written/verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Ideal candidates will offer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website creation experience is strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;RealNetworks®, Inc. is proud to offer our full time employees an extensive benefits package, including vacation, medical, dental, vision, 401K, an employee stock purchase program and subsidized commuting options. Additional benefits include our charitable matching program, learning and development programs, employee wellness plans and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RealNetworks is an equal opportunity employer (EOE)day.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-realnetworks-reston-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-realnetworks-reston-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Artist/Website Designer at Siber Systems in Fairfax, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Siber Systems produces popular software products designed to make a users’ Internet experience easier and more secure. Our software is used by millions worldwide and has been reviewed by several top-tier media companies including the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, Washington Post, and many more. We are seeking a highly motivated, enthusiastic individual with 3-5+ years experience in graphic design and web design including flash, print design, with Software GUI design a big plus. Ideal candidate must have a good knowledge of Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Illustrator, and other design tools. Knowledge of HTML, XHTML, CSS and other related development tools is also important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re an experienced graphic artist with prior software UI design experience and a keen understanding of web site design, take this opportunity to join a leading software company and work with a great team of creative and motivated professionals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a well-rounded graphic artist who can wear many hats. In particular, this person will assist with website design, production of online and offline marketing materials, as well as icon creation and product design. The ideal candidate will also have some software GUI design experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Periodically update website design and create landing pages. Create and customize different effects, including: navigation animation, video, text, etc. Visual concepts and interactive content must communicate key ideas, product features and promotions while addressing online brand and user-friendly issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design various eye-catching online and offline promotional materials such as banners and magazine ads, landing pages, email templates, newsletters, logos, and software icons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create rapid design concepts for review and iteration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop new ideas and approaches to existing creative design process where appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate product requirements into graphically pleasing UI software design concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create software icons for specific functions, both for software and the website, designed to make a users' experience easier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have online portfolio showcasing creative design solutions and digital body of work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA, BS or Associate’s Degree in Graphic or Interactive Design or a related communications or marketing degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5+ years of experience designing for the web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing online and offline advertising materials for a variety of audiences and project types.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of website design, page layout, and usability standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth understanding of the latest web design standards and proficiency with various software tools (Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash, and Microsoft Office) are required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to design and optimize landing pages used to sell products and services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing software Graphical User Interfaces (GUI), with particular attention to usability, is a big plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video knowledge a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working with software and the latest technologies a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of the principles of design, typography and color, and ability to evaluate current design templates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills; able to explain web design proposals and decisions to stakeholders and project requestors. Able to work with web programmers to make sure design is carried through correctly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects and under tight deadlines with minimal supervision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player able to work on cross-functional marketing and development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of search engine optimization and how it applies to website design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;ABOUT SIBER SYSTEMS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1995, Siber Systems creates and markets software products to consumers and businesses around the world. Our software is highly acclaimed and has received numerous awards including PC Magazine Editor’s Choice, CNET’s Best Software of the Year, and PC World’s “25 Products We Can’t Live Without.” The company’s flagship products, RoboForm and GoodSync, are used by millions of people worldwide, with registered customers in over 100 countries. As part of the company’s strong commitment to customer satisfaction, its software comes with a risk-free trial. Headquartered in Fairfax, Virginia, Siber Systems is privately held.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;QUALIFIED CANDIDATES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified candidates should send resumes and cover letters to resumes@roboform.com.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position must be located in Fairfax, VA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are looking for an in-house employee. Please don&amp;rsquo;t apply if you are a graphic design studio or service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-artist-website-designer-siber-systems-fairfax-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-artist-website-designer-siber-systems-fairfax-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Shentel in Edinburg, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for executing designs and layouts from creative concepts for wireless and telco units. This position supports marketing management, sales, stores, distributors and other corporate needs. The position encompasses the creation of graphics for a variety of media, including mass media (TV, print, outdoor), multimedia, retail stores, marketing events, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan and prepare advertising and promotional materials to increase sales of products or services, working with marketing management, sales and outside agencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop creative design concepts around branding and promotions strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspect layouts and advertising copy and edit scripts, audio and video tapes, and other promotional material as needed prior to market launches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acts as point of contact for potential web design or content management system (CMS) changes. As needed, create efficient and accurate web site design graphic images.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide presentation and product demonstration support during the introduction of new products and services to field staff and customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support visual design concepts by researching particular industry niches for defining trends and styles that contribute to the prevailing “look and feel” within that particular marketing realm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for following, supporting, and enforcing internal project control processes and procedures and assist with other marketing communication duties in the department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovates across Shentel’s major lines of business (wireless, wireline (inc BtoB), video, broadband) by testing new ideas and assisting in Shentel’s positioning strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive design experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualification Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education:  4 year degree in Graphics Design or Commercial Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience:  Minimum 2-3 years experience in Commercial Graphic Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative thinking, critical analysis and problem-solving skills along with flexibility/adaptability are essential. Must be a team player.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated proficiency in some mix of the following: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator Indesign, Adobe PageMaker, Flash, Premier Pro , Office Suite and Macintosh.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position description is only meant to be a representative summary of the major duties and responsibilities performed by incumbents of this position. The incumbents may be requested to perform tasks other than those stated in this description.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-shentel-edinburg-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-shentel-edinburg-va</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>