<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/va-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Content Developer at Olgoonik Global Security, LLC in Arlington, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This Web Content Developer will be working within the Office of Fraud Prevention Program of the State Department’s Bureau of Consular Affairs (CA) and will use Rhythmyx web content management tool to keep the Office’s web content relevant and up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become familiar with the Office’s web content editing tool (Rhythmyx)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receiving guidance from management in the Office of Analysis, Systems &amp;amp; Training, upload text, graphics and links to ensure the CA web content is relevant and current&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confirm that data, links, and graphics provided for use on Consular Affairs web is consistent with the mission, policies, and requirements of the Office of Analysis, Systems and Training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned i.e., webinar/multi-media support, commercial database access, maintenance, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Supervisory Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are no supervisory responsibilities associated with this position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Education/Knowledge and/or Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in computer science or a related field is desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equivalent and proven work experience as a web manager, content developer or content specialist may be substituted in lieu of a degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be proficient with the Microsoft Office products suite including; Word, Excel and Outlook&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of PHP, HTML, CSS and/or JavaScript is a signature plus, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working the Rhythmyx web content editor is also a plus, but not required, as the incumbent will receive in-house training upon placement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must demonstrate a good attitude and ability to work effectively under a minimum of supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to multi task efficiently, work in a fast paced environment on multiple projects, and have a strong attention for detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Security Clearance:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;SECRET Level Required&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess an active US Government SECRET Personnel Security Clearance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a U.S. Citizen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must also be able to maintain a US Government SECRET clearance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Physical Demands:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The physical demands described herein are representative of those that must be met by an employee to successfully perform the essential functions of this position. The employee must be able to stand, walk and sit for a prolonged period of time; use hands and/or fingers to handle or feel objects, tools or controls; operate office equipment; reach with hands and arms; climb stairs; balance; stoop; kneel; talk and hear. Specific vision abilities required by the job include close and distant vision. The employee must occasionally lift and or move up to 25 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work Location: General office environment in the downtown Washington, DC area.  Travel outside of Washington, DC is not anticipated except for infrequent off-site meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-content-developer-olgoonik-global-security-llc-arlington-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-content-developer-olgoonik-global-security-llc-arlington-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Application - UI Developer at Resonate Networks in Reston, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking a Web Application / UI Developer to join our growing team.  For the position, previous experience developing scalable, rich, internet application user interfaces is a must. The individual must have the desire and ability to learn quickly.  The environment here is fast paced with changes and challenges on a daily basis, and so the ability to keep up with this environment is a necessity. The candidate will be responsible for implementation of the platform user interface, and will work closely with the product manager and data visualization designer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you enjoy the challenge of a fast-paced start-up environment and like to break innovative new ground, we want to talk to you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UX/UI implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop &amp;amp; maintain front end code as well as some mid-tier code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement new, ground-breaking interaction and visualization interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop UI that provides incredible rich user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely and effectively with the middle tier and database development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications &amp;amp; Experience Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-8 years experience in launching successful interactive web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in advertising network, digital media agency, or other advertising related experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in developing rich internet applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adept with web standards and cross-browser development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert at UI/UX Web Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Visualization/Dashboard Design experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Skills&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert skills with JavaScript, AJAX, HTML and CSS technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience building Web Application User Interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with MVC or MVP preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with various Web API’s (GoogleMaps, GoogleChart, Twitter, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flash/Flex expertise a strong plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Web Toolkit (GWT) experience a strong plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Educational Requirements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To apply please send cover letter and resume to techjobs@resonateinsights.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Our Company&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resonate enables advertisers to reach audiences based on the nuances in consumers’ belief systems and values. Our proprietary platform allows marketers to build rich consumer profiles to power online advertising campaigns, and gain actionable consumer insights before, during, and after execution. Resonate’s insights power the campaign performance of leading brand and political advertisers.  Resonate is a cutting-edge online advertising company, recently voted one of America’s Most Promising Companies by Forbes Magazine.  We have pioneered a completely new way to identify and reach highly-targeted audiences online through our proprietary platform and our methodology called Insights Driven Media.  Resonate has transformed audience targeting into a game-changing advantage.  Be a part of the team that changes the industry!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;More Information:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resonate is headquartered in Reston, Va. with offices in Chicago, Los Angeles, New York, and Washington D.C.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information visit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.resonateinsights.com&quot;&gt;http://www.resonateinsights.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resonate offers a competitive compensation and benefits package&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-ui-developer-resonate-networks-reston-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-ui-developer-resonate-networks-reston-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interface Engineer / Web Developer at RedEngine Digital in McLean, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;RedEngine Digital, an integrated online marketing agency with big brand clients in the not-for-profit, association and business sectors, is seeking an experienced Interface Engineer/front-end Web Developer who will be a key member of our campaign team. The ideal candidate loves to produce efficient, accessible, and semantic Web-standards code that takes advantage of all that current browsers can do with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. If you think of yourself as a collaborative UI developer with a good sense for design and an understanding of back-end programming, we want you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Interface Engineer is responsible for coding and implementing Web/microsite templates and pages, emails, landing pages, forms and more to support email marketing, search, advertising and social media campaigns that will drive donations, sales, leads and membership acquisition. Experience implementing themes for content management systems, such as WordPress and Drupal, is a major plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to hand-code design comps into optimized, standards compliant HTML/CSS/JS (jQuery).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and test/validate cross browser/platform compatible templates, pages, and sites, including mobile devices such as tablets and smartphones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with producers, designers, and IAs in the use of standards-based and semantic HTML and CSS to solve design problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate an understanding of Web design best practices and innovation, including the evolving use of HTML5 and CSS3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify emerging tools, templates, and techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate complex technical details to a non-technical audience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be willing and able to work with clients (technical and non-technical) in the creation of requirements and/or issue resolution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent experience preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working within or for nonprofit organizations a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years experience coding Web assets from designs created by other team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in HTML, CSS; knowledge/familiarity with JavaScript and Flash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with CMS development, especially WordPress and Drupal, and eCRM systems such as Convio or Blackbaud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of PHP and MySQL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of web standards, search engine optimization methods, and accessibility guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multitasking of several concurrent Web implementation projects at different stages of process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Working at RED&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RedEngine is an online marketing agency with big brand clients in the not-for-profit, charity and association sectors. We specialize in using search, email, advertising and social media to grow our client&amp;rsquo;s revenue and expand awareness of their issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RedEngine offers a competitive salary based on experience, generous vacation, a bonus program and a great working environment in McLean, VA, only minutes outside DC. We value and expect commitment, enthusiasm, creative thinking, hard work and dedication. You can expect respect and excellent career opportunities in a rapid growth industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You will Receive:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 weeks paid vacation per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 days paid sick leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11 paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee dental and health insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual performance-based bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) Retirement Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Candidates should send a cover letter and resume to jobs@redenginedigital.com with &amp;ldquo;Interface Engineer Resume&amp;rdquo; in the subject line. No phone calls, please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interface-engineer-web-developer-redengine-digital-mclean-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interface-engineer-web-developer-redengine-digital-mclean-va</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>FrontEndDeveloper (Contractor) at Gridpoint in Arlington, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GridPoint is an established leader in smart energy solutions, providing Fortune 1000 enterprises, government agencies and utilities with the tools to implement and maintain sustainable energy management practices that improve operational efficiency and maximize energy savings. Founded in 2003, GridPoint is headquartered in Arlington, Virginia, with offices in Austin, Texas, Roanoke, Virginia, Seattle, Washington, and Ottawa, Ontario.
Job Description&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GridPoint is looking for an experienced front-end developer to join our engineering team as a Contractor. We are a small company with a startup culture that has seen rapid expansion in the past year. We have product offerings in a wide range of exciting areas including electric vehicle management, energy management, solar integration, and more. This position is in the core engineering team responsible for delivering the front-end interfaces (both web and mobile web) for our products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;If you’re passionate about&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building a clean, efficient energy future&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with business, quality, and ops teams to deliver real customer/business value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning about and using new technologies and taking on new technical challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working on cutting edge technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Then this might be the right job for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties/Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, develop, test, and deliver high quality code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help design and implement front-end interfaces for all of GridPoint’s products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work independently and within a  team to construct high quality software components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unit test own code and implements system level testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS in Computer Science or related technical discipline (or equivalent)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Required: Minimum of 5 – 7 years of experience in web development using one or more of the following: Struts, JSF, Spring MVC, Tapestry, Seam, GWT or OpenXava&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Required: Minimum 3 – 5 years of FLEX development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Required: Minimum 1 – 3 years of mobile web development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Required: Minimum 1 – 3 years of graphing toolkits like js Charts, jqPlot, jQuery, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Grails a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in iOS or Android development is a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using HTML5 is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GridPoint is an Equal Opportunity Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, or disability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/frontenddeveloper-contractor-gridpoint-arlington-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/frontenddeveloper-contractor-gridpoint-arlington-va</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>