<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/va-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Mobile App Developer (iPhone, Android, Etc) at Visual Soft, Inc. in Chantilly, VA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;IMMEDIATE NEED:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are in search of a senior mobile app developer to lead the design, development and maintenance of applications. The developer will lead the entire app life cycle from concept until delivery and post launch support. In addition to delivering the product the successful candidate will be heavily involved in driving the mobile strategy but also will be responsible for setting up, and maintaining the hardware and software that support the mobile apps. Work directly with other developers and project manager to conceptualize, build, test and realize products. Gather requirements around functionality and translate those requirements into elegant functional solutions. Build prototypes at tech scoping stage of projects. Work with other web developers to create and maintain a robust framework to support the apps. Create compelling device specific user interfaces and experiences and optimize performance for the apps.
No Calls Please&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coding experience using HTML and XML.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with mobile wireless technology including tablets and smart phones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with/experience using Apple programming environment including Objective-C preferred (Java, C/C++, C#/.NET) Xcode Cocoa/Cocoa Touch Mac OSX iOS Adobe Flash (AS2/AS3) Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web concepts: Flash, AIR, HTML5, JavaScript, AJAX Server-client technologies (.NET, JDBC) Graphics API.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intel Agency&amp;rsquo;s experience highly recommended.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Visual Soft, Inc. is an Equal Opportunity Employer. Prospective employees will receive consideration without discrimination on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, veteran status or disability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-app-developer-iphone-android-etc-visual-soft-inc-chantilly-va</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/mobile-app-developer-iphone-android-etc-visual-soft-inc-chantilly-va</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>