<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/vt-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Designer and Web Technologist at Middlebury in Middlebury, VT</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Middlebury Interactive Languages is a leading edge technology start-up transforming how students learn world languages. We are seeking an energetic and multi-talented designer with solid front-end development skills—techies with search and analytics knowledge to the front of the line! Join a dynamic team with the shared goal of increasing the company’s visibility and audience engagement. The ideal candidate has excellent visual design skills and a solid understanding of web technologies and concept development. This position reports to the Director of Marketing and Communications and has significant advancement potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and maintain websites including graphics, wireframes and navigation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop dynamic web campaigns, emails, landing pages and branding elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a consistent and cohesive brand identity; develop style guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize and manage image library and graphic standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with marketing, sales and support social media efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure intuitive and logical layout, navigation, and hierarchies of content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop high quality and consistent UI and UX across multiple sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create interactive multimedia campaigns and product presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure compatibility across browsers and email clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with print designs such as sales support collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage relations with hosting, e-commerce and other third party vendors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with back-end development to ensure seamless e-commerce integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Middlebury Interactive Languages™ is the academic leader in world language instruction for K-12 students. A joint venture between Middlebury College and K12 Inc., Middlebury Interactive delivers superior world language programs and digital school solutions that provide students with the skills to be competitive in today’s global marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;REQUIREMENTS:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BFA/BA in graphic design, related field or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years professional design experience on the client side or at an agency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of visual and typographical hierarchies and brand strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Adobe CS5/CS6 including Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign and Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with web standards (XHTML and CSS layouts) and some JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with ExpressionEngine or other CMS platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience creating and editing audio and video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting with cross-browser and various email clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player with excellent interpersonal and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and/or interest in world languages and cultures a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Candidates must include a link to their online portfolio. This is a full-time, in-house position based in Middlebury, Vermont. Benefits include health, dental, life, vacation and 401K.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Middlebury Interactive Languages™ is the academic leader in world language instruction for K-12 students. A joint venture between Middlebury College and K12 Inc., Middlebury Interactive delivers superior world language programs and digital school solutions that provide students with the skills to be competitive in today’s global marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-and-web-technologist-middlebury-middlebury-vt</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/designer-and-web-technologist-middlebury-middlebury-vt</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>