<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wa-bdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web/UX Developer at CHC Consulting in Bothell, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Develop solutions to business problems/processes leveraging technology to provide marketing differentiation, performance improvements, and better user experience. Provide extensive JavaScript architecture/design, development and testing for the att.com web domain. Architecture/design responsibilities include assessment of business and design requirements for feedback and technical design of proposed solutions. Development involves use of JavaScript primarily, and ActionScript rarely, to implement solutions in prototype form, in test environments, and in the att.com production environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 to 5 years experience in web page development and browser compatibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 to 4 years experience with web scripting languages for construction of complex interactive applications using AJAX, jQuery or similar features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 to 2 years experience in AJAX, XML, XSLT and basic UI, object oriented design and design patterns, SOAP and Web Service API usage. Preferred Skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 to 2 years experience in mobile design development and testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 to 2 years experience in Adobe ActionScript development for Flex.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Telecom/Wireless experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skill Required with Intermediate Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flex/ActionScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile video development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skill Desired with Entry Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-ux-developer-chc-consulting-bothell-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-ux-developer-chc-consulting-bothell-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Amazon in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Amazon Web Services developer documentation team is looking for a web developer to help us build the next generation of our developer documentation website. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone with strong web development and project management skills to help us build a dynamic user-friendly developer documentation site that delivers a variety of content including HTML, PDF, Kindle, and video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since early 2006, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has provided companies of all sizes with an infrastructure web services platform in the cloud. With AWS you can requisition compute power, storage, and other services–gaining access to a suite of elastic IT infrastructure services as your business demands them. For more information, go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://aws.amazon.com&quot;&gt;http://aws.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating interactive prototypes for review&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing and maintaining web analytics instrumentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzing current site traffic trends and user behavior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building user-friendly web applications that scale to fit a variety of platforms and screen sizes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimizing website performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in XHTML, Javascript, CSS and general Web 2.0 techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a Unix/Linux environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience tracking and analyzing metrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Computer Science or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Responsive Design, web services, CSS3, and HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with XML and XSLT technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building fast and efficient web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a fast-paced and agile development environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SEO experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong customer focus and obsession with quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-amazon-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-amazon-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer - Contract at Z2LIVE in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Product and Marketing to build great online user experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement web interfaces for our games, marketing campaigns and internal initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a key role in new feature development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/MS in graphic design, interactive design, user interface, computer science or related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-4 years of experience building dynamic, customer facing sites in HTML, CSS, JQuery, PHP, and JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Adobe Creative Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in short, agile, iterative development cycles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in PHP, JavaScript, JSON, DOM Scripting and website front-end development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with database management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong collaborative and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Extras&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on UI/UX design for the mobile platform a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Expression Engine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-contract-z2live-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-contract-z2live-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Backend Web Developer at En Masse in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you an engineer who is passionate about creating user interfaces within scalable frameworks that are easy to maintain? If so, we want to talk to you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En Masse Entertainment is looking for a Senior Rails Applications Engineer to work with us in our efforts to establish a network of sites aimed at supporting our current and future games. The ideal candidate will be someone who is familiar with building complete websites using Rails and who stays current on emerging and changing technologies that can be used to enhance existing sites. This candidate should be someone who realizes that a web site is never &amp;ldquo;done&amp;rdquo; and is constantly looking for ways to tweak our framework and applications to polish an awesome user interface even further. Lastly, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who is passionate about the gaming industry and eager to work on projects that span the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;To give you an idea of typical tasks, over the last few months, our web developers:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;worked with the maintainers of the RefineryCMS open source project to optimize and enhance the underlying framework of our site&amp;rsquo;s content management system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;created a development environment capable of automated deployment by both developers and designers using Chef and Vagrant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;worked with our Network Operations department to ensure that current and future site technology will deploy to QA and production environments using Chef.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;developed a Ruby app (using Sinatra) to utilize a series of RESTful API calls for a web storefront&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;implemented security patches to site dependencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;made our automated tests more robust&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;wore a wizard hat when they broke the production site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bragged over their current position on the in-house leveling leaderboard for TERA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If these tasks sound like fun to you and you would thrive at performing these tasks with beautifully elegant code, send us your resume!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience developing web-based frameworks and applications (using Ruby/Rails, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;familiarity with version control systems, especially Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;passion for video games, especially massively multiplayer online role-playing games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Fun Factors&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;game area and LAN center on site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;free snacks and sodas in the kitchen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;open floor plan where team members collaborate with one another on the fly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;great location in the heart of downtown Seattle—can you say, “awesome views”?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;En Masse employees also enjoy abundant opportunities for professional growth and the potential to learn on the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Applying for this Position&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When applying for this position, please include the following items in a compressed .zip file:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;code samples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;portfolio of previous work (if applicable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;your favorite meme (and brief explanation why)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;You may include links to online versions of these resources provided they are universally accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/backend-web-developer-en-masse-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/backend-web-developer-en-masse-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Developer at Big Fish in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Big Fish Games, we offer thousands of easily accessible games that allow our customers to relax, have fun, and feel good. The Big Fish platform now includes Mac, PC, online, mobile, social, and console games, developed both in house and in partnership with more than 500 game developers around the world. Our team is located throughout the world, including our headquarters in Seattle, and our offices in Oakland, California, Vancouver, Canada, Cork, Ireland and Luxembourg. We release A New Game Every Day!® and publish the industry&amp;rsquo;s leading casual game brands. Since our founding in 2002, we have distributed more than 1 billion premium casual games across numerous genres to customers in more than 150 countries and 10 languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re a savvy technologist and you have the portfolio to prove it.  Your bag of tricks includes a strong command of CSS, HTML5, Javascript (including applied knowledge and use of DOM methods / properties), cross-browser and cross-platform development techniques. You dream about the best way to implement javascript state machines, and have a passion for and demonstrated experience in UI design and development.  If you are a person who gets excited about being able to develop products that would be used by millions of people on mobile devices and desktops all over the world, and be at the forefront in delivering exciting new multi-platform applications, then this is the perfect opportunity for you. Come join a team developing rich web UI enabled mobile and desktop applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You – doing this:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop optimized, cross-platform front-ends in CSS/HTML5/Javascript, and work with the middle-tier PHP code to support it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work as a team member to ensure that implementation details translate through to shipping products and services that serve business needs. Emphasis on teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show product ownership through collaboration with product managers, designers, other front-end developers and back-end engineers to refine the user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show strong inter-personal and communication skills, including clear and concise writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface with the UI and developer communities to absorb the latest trends and emerging technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Do you have skills?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of relevant web programming experience, or 7+ years in CSS, HTML, Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven track record of launching interactive internet sites/applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must demonstrate strong interaction and rapid prototype engineering skills across a broad spectrum of technologies including:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML / XHTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript: DOM manipulation and Ajax&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP / MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XML / JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SVN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You have these?  You have our attention:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree or higher, preferably in CS or a combination of education and applicable experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience as key member of a UI development team participating in the complete product development lifecycle of several successfully launched software applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to switch rapidly between different projects in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Come be the next Big Fish in the Pond!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-big-fish-programming-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-developer-big-fish-programming-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Big Fish in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Big Fish Games, we offer thousands of easily accessible games that allow our customers to relax, have fun, and feel good. The Big Fish platform now includes Mac, PC, online, mobile, social, and console games, developed both in house and in partnership with more than 500 game developers around the world. Our team is located throughout the world, including our headquarters in Seattle, and our offices in Oakland, California, Vancouver, Canada, Cork, Ireland and Luxembourg. We release A New Game Every Day!® and publish the industry&amp;rsquo;s leading casual game brands. Since our founding in 2002, we have distributed more than 1 billion premium casual games across numerous genres to customers in more than 150 countries and 10 languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a savvy technologist and you have the portfolio to prove it. Your bag of tricks includes a strong command of CSS, HTML5, Javascript (including applied knowledge and use of DOM methods / properties), cross-browser and cross-platform development techniques. You dream about the best way to implement javascript state machines, and have a passion for and demonstrated experience in UI design and development. If you are a person who gets excited about being able to develop products that would be used by millions of people on mobile devices and desktops all over the world, and be at the forefront in delivering exciting new multi-platform applications, then this is the perfect opportunity for you. Come join a team developing rich web UI enabled mobile and desktop applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You – doing this:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop optimized, cross-platform front-ends in CSS/HTML5/Javascript, and work with the middle-tier PHP code to support it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work as a team member to ensure that implementation details translate through to shipping products and services that serve business needs. Emphasis on teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show product ownership through collaboration with product managers, designers, other front-end developers and back-end engineers to refine the user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show strong inter-personal and communication skills, including clear and concise writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface with the UI and developer communities to absorb the latest trends and emerging technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Do you have skills?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of relevant web programming experience, or 5+ years in CSS, HTML, Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven track record of launching interactive internet sites/applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must demonstrate strong interaction and rapid prototype engineering skills across a broad spectrum of technologies including:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML / XHTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript: DOM manipulation and Ajax&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of jQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP / MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XML / JSON&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SVN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You have these? You have our attention:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree or higher, preferably in CS or a combination of education and applicable experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience as key member of a UI development team participating in the complete product development lifecycle of several successfully launched software applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to switch rapidly between different projects in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Come be the next Big Fish in the Pond!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-big-fish-programming-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-big-fish-programming-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at University of Washington Medical Center in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Who We Are&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The University of Washington (UW) is proud to be one of the nation’s premier educational and research institutions. Our people are the most important asset in our pursuit of achieving excellence in education, research, and community service. Our staff not only enjoy outstanding benefits and professional growth opportunities, but also an environment noted for diversity, community involvement, intellectual excitement, artistic pursuits, and natural beauty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UW Information School (iSchool) is a community of diverse disciplines, professional fields, and areas of expertise engaged with the study of information and its use by people and organizations.  We conduct rigorous research and create challenging learning environments that make a difference throughout the region, the state of Washington, the nation, and the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are an open, ethical, highly engaged and collaborative community based on trust, transparency and mutual respect.  We believe in the importance of quality of life, embracing diversity, making a difference and having fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sustained engagement with global communities of practice allows our work to remain relevant and cutting-edge.  We are dedicated to attracting and nurturing a diverse group of students, faculty and staff and we are committed to helping all members of our community to achieve their fullest potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About The Postion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iSchool is looking to hire an outstanding individual to serve as a Web Developer/System Administrator**. Under the general direction of the Lead Web Developer and System Administrator, the Web Developer/System Administrator primarily designs, implements, tests, and maintains custom-built web applications and packaged system solutions in support of School needs. This individual will also assist in the management, operation, design, configuration, deployment, backup, performance monitoring, security, and maintenance of systems and servers that meet the academic, administrative, and research needs of the iSchool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Developer/System Administrator is a key participant in the continued enhancement of the Information School’s web presence.  This individual is responsible for making platform and technology recommendations to the Lead Web Developer and Systems Administrator and for building applications on top of that platform to support organizational goals.  The Web Developer/System Administrator will analyze business processes, work with Lead Web Developer and Systems Administrator to design solutions, then architect and deploy solutions to address security, operational, performance, integration, and maintainability considerations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Information School is at the forefront of using technology to solve organizational problems.  Most solutions today are delivered via the web and other units are looking to the iSchool as a leader in the innovative and effective use of web based systems.  The individual in this role will make significant contributions to the direction of the iSchool’s web presence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary responsibilities for this position are:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;WEB DEVELOPMENT&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement requirements by writing code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and support operation of test scenarios. Develop test scripts.  Engage in usability testing as required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support and enhance existing sites in compliance with specifications and security standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review and re-write previously-written code to improve and/or adapt code to changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incorporate UW policies regarding security, data encryption and user access management into the site and web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze site problems and correct them promptly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review system logs and messages to identify events and errors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide routine technical assistance for problem diagnosis, resolution and ongoing maintenance activities for web application and server users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incorporate UW policies regarding security, data encryption and user access management into the site and web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;SYSTEM ADMINISTRATION&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the deployment, operation, backup, security, and maintenance of servers, related network equipment, and software (e.g., operating systems, web services, application software, communication/collaboration tools).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and analyze system capacity, utilization, backup, cloud opportunities, and disaster recovery.  Plan and implement necessary improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide support to resolve system problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor and optimize performance of server equipment and software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to system alerts and take corrective action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;PROJECT MANAGEMENT&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In collaboration with Lead Web Developer and System Administrator gather user needs, schedule and attend fact-gathering sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage complex projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draft specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop data flow diagrams, process models, and system documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and conduct software application and system operational training for staff such as explaining features and functionality; training users on use of applications; developing effective help screens.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;MISCELLANEOUS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Represent the Information School on campus-wide committees related to web and custom applications development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attend School meetings and University meetings relating to web and server infrastructure technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This position requires a high level of technical expertise, specifically knowledge of web development, 508 compliant front-end code, and Windows and Linux server administration. The School’s web and server infrastructure supports many critical business, educational, and research operations, and has numerous stakeholders.  Ongoing communication with stakeholders regarding project status and site or server functionality changes will be required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some evening and weekend work will be required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or equivalent experience in informatics, computer science, management information systems or related technical field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum two years web development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of HTML, CSS, and web standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong PHP 5 and MySQL 5 development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of Windows Server and Linux Server, including installation, support &amp;amp; troubleshooting, security, methods of automation such as scripting, and performance monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with RESTful Web Services, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, cross-platform/browser compatibility issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to deliver projects on time and within specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be detail oriented, possess strong organizational skills and have a good sense of design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills with exceptional inter-personal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work both independently, and as part of a collaborative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated success working with diverse populations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with sound usability practices, user interface design, accessibility (508)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Equivalent education/experience will substitute for all minimum qualifications except when there are legal requirements, such as a license/certification/registration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Desired:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One year of experience with the Drupal Content Management System including custom theming, custom module development, and Views&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One year of Apache, and Linux server administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Windows Active Directory, including design, administration, troubleshooting, and best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Windows Group Policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying and managing various other types of servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with cloud vendors and cloud services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of emerging technologies such as HTML 5 and CSS 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Google Analytics and Search Engine Optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;QA testing experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with a Content Versioning System such as GIT or SVN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Condition of Employment:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some evening/weekend work is required.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A satisfactory outcome from a criminal background verification will be required prior to hire.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;As a UW employee, you will enjoy generous benefits and work/life programs. For a complete description of our benefits for this position, please visit our website, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.washington.edu/admin/hr/benefits/forms/ben-summaries/prostaff.pdf&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Process:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of the application process for this position includes completing an online cover letter assessment as well as the Employment Eligibility Assessment to obtain additional information that will be used in the evaluation process.  The assessment(s) will appear on your screen for you to complete as soon as you select &amp;ldquo;Apply to this Position&amp;rdquo; on this job announcement. Once you begin the assessment, it must be completed at that time. If you select to take it later, it will appear on your &amp;ldquo;My Jobs&amp;rdquo; page to take when you are ready. Please note that your application will not be reviewed, and you will not be considered for this position until the assessment is complete.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-university-of-washington-medical-center-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-university-of-washington-medical-center-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>