<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wa-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Application Designer at Pacific Northwest National Laboratory in Richland, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Pacific Northwest National Laboratory is seeking highly-qualified candidates with expertise in web application design with a focus in human computer interaction. This includes but is not limited to compiling, analyzing and interpreting project requirements, designing graphical user interfaces (GUIs) for web applications, building demonstrable and functional prototypes, and building new pieces of deployment-ready software.
This position will support the PNNL Knowledge Discovery and Informatics team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The position requires contributing to technical proposals, presentations and publication; managing individual assignments for multiple projects, performing assignments with minimal oversight and working within software development teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participation in professional activities is encouraged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The successful candidate will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;contribute to the translation of client requests and needs into a set of project requirements and tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demonstrate a strong background in Human Computer Interaction by applying in-depth knowledge of design principals to a defined set of software requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;apply practical experience with prototyping to project requirements and designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;participate in the software design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;implement and design of graphical user interfaces (GUI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;construct functional web applications and prototypes in the languages of HTML, CSS, PHP, jQuery, and Java&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;develop for and extend the functionality of web content management systems such as Semantic MediaWiki, Drupal, and Wordpress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;facilitate and prepare collaborative websites for use in small teams, groups, and divisions at the lab&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;development on Linux, Macintosh and Windows environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;development of client server and database aware applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;creation and management of software documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;use of source code revision control tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;effectively manage individual tasks, schedule, workload, budget, and deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;work to broaden and deepen own technical knowledge and skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;work effectively within software development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exhibit a spirit of cooperation, teamwork, and mutual respect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;contribute to technical presentations and demonstrations of designs, prototypes and operational software to existing and potential clients; group, division, and sector managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;contributions to publications and proposals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The staff member is expected to develop knowledge of the goals of any projects to which they are assigned and the clients they support. The staff member is expected to maintain a customer-service focus commensurate with this position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staff normally receives task instructions from the project manager, which are performed with minimal oversight. The incumbent will report directly to the Knowledge Discovery and Informatics (KDI) Technical Group Manager. The incumbent will work as a staff member under the direction of project managers and senior software scientists. The incumbent will be expected to attend regular project meetings and KDI group meetings. The incumbent must be able to attend offsite team meetings with other team members, clients, and users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Science or Master of Science in computer science or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;0-1 years experience in user experience, web, or other related design field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong HTML, CSS, and jQuery skills. Basic knowledge of Java, PHP and MySQL a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in web content management systems (Semantic MediaWiki, Drupal 6.x-7.x, Wordpress 2.x-3.x, and PHPbb preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with task management software (Jira, Redmine, ActiveCollab etc.) preferred
Equal Employment Opportunity
Pacific Northwest National Laboratory (PNNL) is an Affirmative Action / Equal Opportunity Employer and supports diversity in the workplace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, marital or family status, sexual orientation, gender identity, or genetic information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All staff at the Pacific Northwest National Laboratory must be able to demonstrate the legal right to work in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position requires the ability to obtain a federal security clearance in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Which requires:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US Citizenship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background Investigation: Applicants selected will be subject to a Federal background investigation and must meet eligibility requirements for access to classified matter in accordance 10 CFR 710, Appendix B.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drug Testing:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;All Security Clearance (L or Q) positions will be considered by the Department of Energy to be Testing Designated Positions which means that they are subject to applicant, random, and for cause drug testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, applicants must be able to demonstrate non-use of illegal drugs for the 12 consecutive months preceding completion of the requisite Questionnaire for National Security Positions (QNSP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Note:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants will be considered ineligible for security clearance processing by the U.S. Department of Energy until non-use of illegal drugs for 12 consecutive months can be demonstrated&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-designer-pacific-northwest-national-laboratory-richland-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-designer-pacific-northwest-national-laboratory-richland-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer - Windows Design Team at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Microsoft Windows User Experience team is seeking exceptional senior interaction designers to make the personal computer more powerful, engaging, and rewarding to use. This is an opportunity to reinvent how people interact with computers, to turn new technology into positive user experiences, and to deliver a product that reaches millions of customers. If you are inspired by these plans, then this is the team for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an Interaction Designer, you will work alongside some of the world’s most talented product designers, usability specialists, and software developers to build the future generation of the Windows operating system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will help set the vision for the future Windows user experience, serving as a user advocate to ensure the highest level of usability, desirability and customer satisfaction. You will research, design, and prototype product experiences that meet demanding quality standards, and you will drive your work through the software development process. You will collaborate with teams across the company to ensure we maintain industry leadership, delivering innovative, exciting and emotionally engaging products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates should have outstanding skills in designing interaction and visuals for software or the web. We require a proven ability to work from an array of prototyping techniques to develop and communicate the benefits of concepts and solutions, and show experience applying user research throughout the design process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications include&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a 4-year degree in industrial design,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;interaction design, or related field,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;plus 3-5 years of industry experience developing software products for large markets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of major multimedia, design, and operating system software (Photoshop, Flash or Director, Windows, Office) is expected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Resumes need to include an online portfolio to be considered&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WDJobs&lt;br/&gt;
W:WE&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-windows-design-team-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-windows-design-team-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Kinect is the fastest-selling tech device of all time according to the Guinness Book of Records. It has already changed the way people interact with the Xbox, so we asked ourselves: What would happen if we made Kinect available for Windows? The answer is: almost anything you can imagine!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve already seen a groundswell of interest and innovation from designers and developers around the world, and demand from our partners and customers is growing every day with the recent release of the Kinect for Windows SDK and new hardware device. Now, we’re expanding our horizons to new verticals and markets. Therefore, we need a Senior Interaction Designer to help envision and build the next generation of Natural User Experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Senior Interaction Designer, you must have a clear understanding of each facet of the design process &amp;ndash; information architecture + interaction design, research + usability, rapid prototyping, visual + motion design, brand integration, and content creation. You have demonstrated ability to effectively partner with product planners and managers, program managers and development and test team members to shepherd end to end experiences from concept to ship. You have deep knowledge of natural user interface (NUI) paradigms and have demonstrable experience in designing experiences with multiple input modalities. You are a great creator, collaborator, and communicator and coach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead/facilitate design brainstorming and work sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce scenarios, process flows, information architecture diagrams, wireframes, and other artifacts required to develop and evolve user experience designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go deep on NUI and create an interaction design model that gracefully accommodates multi-user, multi-modal input across a broad set of experiences and contexts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help develop, manage, and refine UI pattern libraries and interaction guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate with developers through implementation phase to realize design vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate, defend, and build consensus around experience architecture and interaction design direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with the User Experience Architect, project experience design efforts within Kinect for Windows’ portfolio of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified candidates should have at least 5-7 years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise creating a variety of interaction design documents including user scenarios, task flows, conceptual models, competitor analysis, heuristic analysis, and annotated wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and managing UI pattern libraries and interaction guidelines ideally across a large organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to and understanding of variety of design, project management, and development processes and methodologies including agile development methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience shipping innovative and complex software products within milestone deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing multi-discipline design teams and design vendors in shipping compelling user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in current design and media trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable ability to work confidently with Program Management, Development, Product Planning, Brand, Marketing and Usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess ability to think conceptually about design and information architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the array of technical constraints, user goals and business requirements that shape current and future products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Visio, Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash, After FX and all related business and design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly produce elegant and easily understood diagrams, wireframes, and other artifacts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills and an attention to detail
Startup experience is a plus!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of a BA/BS degree in Interface Design, Interaction Design, Communication Design, Architecture or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Portfolio review required&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Mortgage Advisory Group in Everett, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Mortgage Advisory Group is a highly successful, full circle mortgage broker and banker leader in the Pacific Northwest. Our top-notch customer service is the core of our outstanding reputation in the mortgage industry. We pride ourselves on extensive knowledge of mortgage loan programs as well as our state-of-the-art business processes, facility and equipment that help us deliver high-value services, quickly and accurately. At the heart of Mortgage Advisory Group is our team of mortgage professionals, everyone of them empowered, well-trained and equipped to provide world-class service. We don&amp;rsquo;t rest on our laurels, though. We&amp;rsquo;re always on the lookout for improvements, implementing changes wisely wherever they&amp;rsquo;re warranted. From our senior leadership to our new recruits, we&amp;rsquo;re dedicated to serving our client&amp;rsquo;s needs today, and for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join Our Team!  Mortgage Advisory Group has an immediate opening for a highly motivated, top quality candidate for the position of Graphic Designer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Graphic Designer is responsible for developing graphic artwork for all Mortgage Advisory Group products and advertisements. In addition, prepares a variety of graphic design and layout work for preparation of various newsletters, flyers, advertisements, brochures, catalogues, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate is able to immediately perform the following major job duties and responsibilities at a competent level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and design graphics for all layouts of marketing merchandising.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operates various graphic design programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain advertising placements in business trade directories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confers with management regarding project specifications and creative direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in the coordination of our SEO, SEM, SMM and SMO to handle the ongoing strategic placement of our company website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, analyze, and implement a wide range of marketing efforts, to include emails, campaigns, flyers, mailings, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting in writing and editing sales and marketing materials, which include articles, presentations, white papers, and collateral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, produce, and publish company’s monthly newsletters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creates and designs technical drawings and illustrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop various advertising materials to meet customer’s specifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for quality control and proof reading of all marketing materials created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide graphic and design support to Marketing as well as other departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performs other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;MINIMUM:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education: Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Graphic Arts or design related field or equivalent based experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience: Has at least 3 years of Graphic Design experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of all stages of graphic design from concept to production to print&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing and editing skill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong research and problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High degree of organization and initiative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle deadlines and changing priorities with good judgment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of Adobe CS4 (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Dreamweaver, Flash, and Acrobat), and premium programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;DESIRED:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree in Graphic Design or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience as a Graphic Designer in the Mortgage/Banking Industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with content management system for website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mortgage Advisory Group offers an excellent benefits package, containing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Vision and Dental insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PTO (Paid Time Off)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AFLAC benefits available&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legal Insurance available&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly company lunch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partnership discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional benefits to recognize a job well done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The is a full-time position, Monday through Friday, 8am to 5 pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your experience to be considered, please submit a resume in Word or PDF format through the company website at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mortgageadvisorygroup.com&quot;&gt;http://www.mortgageadvisorygroup.com&lt;/a&gt;.  No phone calls/faxes/walk-ins please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mortgage Advisory Group is an Equal Opportunity Employer.  Your Future is Our Focus!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-mortgage-advisory-group-everett-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-mortgage-advisory-group-everett-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Designer at General Dynamics - IT in Fort Lewis, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;General Dynamics Information Technology plans to release a proposal for software development contract work to support the Defense Centers of Excellence for Psychological Health and Traumatic Brain Injury (DCoE for PH&amp;amp;TBI) at the National Center for Telehealth and Technology (T2). There is an immediate requirement for a Sr Designer, Web at Joint Base Lewis-McChord. Specific job functions include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Job Functions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front-end development of web applications using agile/scrum methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concepting, wireframing, and designing website page layouts, display graphics, and demos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate effectively with technical team members as well as business subject matter experts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain awareness of new and emerging technologies and the potential application on client engagements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify opportunities for improvement and make constructive suggestions for change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelors Degree in an applicable field, or the equivalent combination of education, technical training, or work experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-8 years of related web design experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undergraduate degree, Associates degree, or equivalent experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have a minimum of 5 years experience that is directly related to the essential job functions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated expertise in front-end web development using HTML, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, and Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of creating browser-independent designs (i.e. Firefox, Chrome, Internet Explorer)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with content management systems (Joomla, Drupal, etc.) is helpful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Java, Spring MVC, Apache Web Service, and Tomcat is also helpful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DoD experience particularly in a medical or health care setting helpful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should have the ability to get up to speed on new technologies and APIs quickly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be self-motivated and have the ability to break through technological hurdles with minimal supervision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-designer-general-dynamics-it-fort-lewis-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-designer-general-dynamics-it-fort-lewis-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Itron in Liberty Lake, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Itron, we’re dedicated to delivering end-to-end smart grid and smart distribution solutions to electric, gas and water utilities around the globe. Our company is the world’s leading provider of smart metering, data collection and utility software systems, with over 8,000 utilities worldwide relying on our technology to optimize the delivery and use of energy and water. Our offerings include electricity, gas, water and heat meters; network communication technology; collection systems and related software applications; and professional services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Itron’s Corporate Headquarters in Spokane, WA has an exciting new career opportunity for a talented entry-level Web Designer willing to take on a new challenge! The Itron Web Designer role often considered part of the Marketing function, generally focused on the look, feel, operation, and functionality of a commercial website. The Web Designer creates internal/external company web pages including graphics, animation and functionality, as well as designs web page layout and online content, user interface graphics, icons, color schemes, content and infrastructure for new product release and new web-hosted product offering. The individual in this capacity performs web usability testing, partners with Web Administrator to implement pages or applications into production, develops, assesses and communicates website usage and security policies and standards. In addition the Web Designer provides technical assistance to Site Administrators and may assist in the planning of overall company strategy involving internet usage. The individual in this role may make hardware and/or software purchasing recommendations or decisions regarding web development and they may perform overall administration of sites at a company-wide level. The role requires knowledge of commercial internet/web tools and protocols.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide web and digital design services, from concept development through design and production, to support corporate web strategy and marketing group objectives. Work with marketing and key project stakeholders to define and create website and web page structures, including interaction flows, page wireframes, prototypes and interface requirements that promote ease of use and a positive user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply best practices website usability principles, including user scenarios, usability testing and website analytics review, to continuously optimize the design and structure of internal and external websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in developing, implementing and communicating corporate web branding standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually monitor, research and recommend web and digital technologies to apply to Itron websites and marketing tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position requires a minimum of 2 years of related experience with web design using HTML and CSS (Cascading Style Sheet).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SharePoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive web design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with enterprise websites/technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Web or Graphic Design/Development – highly preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in related field or equivalent experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Certification(s):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt; n/a&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About Itron Itron is an EOE AA Employer. If you require an accommodation in order to apply to this position, please contact Accessibility@itron.com. Itron is the leading provider of energy and water resource management solutions for nearly 8,000 utilities around the world. We offer end-to-end solutions that include electricity, gas, water and heat measurement and control technology; communications systems; software; and professional services. With nearly 10,000 employees doing business in more than 130 countries, Itron empowers utilities to responsibly and efficiently manage energy and water resources. To realize a sustainable future, start here: www.itron.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Primary Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Spokane/Liberty Lake&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-itron-liberty-lake-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-itron-liberty-lake-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer-IEB-XBOX Live at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft‘s Interactive Entertainment Business delivers world class entertainment experiences you want with the people you care about wherever you are…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IEB Design (designers of Xbox) leads the design of entertainment experiences for customers worldwide. The entertainment experiences we create are for a diverse audience &amp;ndash; from intense gamers to family timers &amp;ndash; and are enjoyed in many contexts &amp;ndash; TV, PC, Web and Mobile. We partner closely with IEB business and technology team members to envision, design, define, validate and deliver entertainment experiences that are effortless, intuitive, delightful and unified. IEB Design ensures that the entertainment experience our customers enjoy &amp;ndash; from TV to music to games to video &amp;ndash; is simply the best in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IEB Design is seeking an Interaction Designer to join our team of producers, user researchers, and interaction, industrial, motion, visual, sensory, brand, and integration designers to help us reinvent entertainment led from the living room, powered by the cloud, and available across multiple screens. You have demonstrated ability to effectively partner with product planners and managers, program managers and development and test team members to shepherd end to end experiences from concept to ship. You have knowledge of natural user interface (NUI) paradigms and have experience in designing experiences with multiple input modalities. You are a great creator, collaborator, and communicator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead/facilitate design brainstorming and work sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce scenarios, process flows, information architecture diagrams, wireframes, and other artifacts required to develop and evolve user experience designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with user researchers to coordinate testing efforts, interpret test results, and incorporate results into design efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help develop, manage, and refine UI pattern libraries and interaction guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate with developers through implementation phase to realize design vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate, defend, and build consensus around experience architecture and interaction design direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified candidates should have at least 5 years of experience including experience with information architecture, interaction design user research, and usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise creating a variety of interaction design documents including user scenarios, task flows, conceptual models, competitor analysis, heuristic analysis, and annotated wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and managing UI pattern libraries and interaction guidelines ideally across a large organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing and conducting a variety of both qualitative and quantitative research including ethnographic research, contextual inquiries, guided explorations, and usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to and understanding of variety of design, project management, and development processes and methodologies including agile development methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience shipping innovative and complex mobile, web or software products within milestone deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in current entertainment and social media trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable ability to work confidently with Program Management, Development, Product Planning, Brand, Marketing and Usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess ability to think conceptually about design and information architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the array of technical constraints, user goals and business requirements that shape current and future products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Visio, Photoshop, Illustrator, and all related business and design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly produce elegant and easily understood diagrams, wireframes, and other artifacts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills and an attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of a BA/BS degree in Interface Design, Interaction Design, Communication Design, Architecture or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portfolio review required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IEBCRjobs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J2WERPL1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nearest Major Market:&lt;/strong&gt; Seattle&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Nearest Secondary Market:&lt;/strong&gt; Bellevue&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Job Segments:&lt;/strong&gt; Engineer, Program Manager, Graphic Design, Cloud, Testing, Engineering, Management, Creative, Technology&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-ieb-xbox-live-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-ieb-xbox-live-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Web Designer at triplenet technologies in Bellevue, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Come be part of our Winning Team!!! We have a full time opportunity for a Junior to Mid Level  Web Designer for a client that is the fastest growing Software Company in Washington State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Designer will be responsible for creating the look and feel of World Wide Web pages for a client&amp;rsquo;s and Company’s Web sites. This involves developing a graphic design that effectively communicates the ideas being promoted by the Web site. A web designer may take part in the initial planning of a Web site, meeting with the client to discuss ideas for the layout and organization of the site, the types of colors or images to use (photos, illustrations, logo, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of professional web design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in CSS, HTML and JavaScript with understanding of cross-browser design issues and lean work-arounds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of online media production practices, such as Web and cross-browser support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge of the following a definite asset(Desirable):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of version control, especially Subversion, is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Japanese language skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Key Traits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work independently as well as collaboratively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortably give and receive creative critiques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to function well within a high paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take both initiative and direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Location: Bellevue, WA
Duration: 4 Months with a strong possibility of Temp to Permanent for the right candidate
Rate:$16-$18 per hour&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-designer-triplenet-technologies-bellevue-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-designer-triplenet-technologies-bellevue-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>