<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wa-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Quardev, Inc. in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Quardev, Inc., a premier technical services provider is looking for exceptional people to join our team. We have a fast-growth, community-minded culture that is built on integrity, innovation, and fun, with a commitment to Doing-What-It-Takes to get the job done for our clients. Our five-star service standard, along with our professionalism and personable, partnering approach to doing business has earned us a 100% return rate with our testing clients since opening our doors in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create images that present a compelling theme for each online ad campaign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the schedule for merchandising ads for our client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and acquire photos from stock services and other low cost sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform photo retouching, enhancement, and create realistic photo composites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Render finished layouts of ads in web-ready format. Write image text and captions .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update, test, and monitor HTML code for merchandising.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage asset database of archived photos and artwork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current on all advertising inside and outside our client&amp;rsquo;s site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work cooperatively with outside resources on promotional campaigns to create online banner ads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize overall project visions and goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with marketing managers to design and complete promotional campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with developers to design and complete interactive pages or objects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Storyboard and execute dynamic interactive marketing pieces using Javascript animation (jQuery/scriptaculous), and animated GIFs .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US Citizens and Green Card holders are encouraged to apply. We are unable to sponsor visas at this time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local Seattle Metro area candidates ONLY&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Agencies Quardev does not accept unsolicited resumes from third party vendors. Any unsolicited resumes sent to Quardev from any third party will not be recognized and such agency or party will have no recourse from Quardev&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are ready for a challenge with a fast growing, exciting company send your resume and cover letter to us at resumes@quardev.com. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-quadrev-inc-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-quadrev-inc-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer - Windows Phone at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Help us change the way people think about mobile phones. The Mobile Studio will redefine the mobile phone for millions of everyday users around the world. We are looking for an intuitive and driven Interaction Designer with the ability to conceptualize and build the design of features built for mobile phones. This is an exceptional opportunity for someone who is excited about making a real impact on future mobile products and experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The candidate will be part of a team that is responsible for extending and evolving the functionality of Windows Phone. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone that is forward-thinking and willing to challenge &amp;amp; provoke new ways to connect with our consumers. This position requires strong design, communication, and organization skills, and the ability to work across teams. You&amp;rsquo;ll also be expected to quickly broaden your technical understanding as new technologies become available. A deep understand of our customers and creating great product experiences is a must!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The candidate will work closely with a team of UI designers, industrial designers, user researchers, design managers, brand marketers and software engineers in a highly collaborative environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;JOB REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years of experience in user interface design for consumer product experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An open-minded, creative and human-centered approach to problem solving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for creating simple, playful, and seamless product experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong interest in design and technology trends. Familiar with current mobile design paradigms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support our creative vision and preserve the brand&amp;rsquo;s design assets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work collaboratively with other designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;PREREQUISITES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Design, or equivalent education or experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in relevant design industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work samples that show strong graphic design and typography skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to execute design solutions in Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Fireworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to strategically solve problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills and the ability to make presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mobile Studio is a multidisciplinary team whose charter is to design world-class end-to-end experiences that are desirable, thoughtful, consistent, and easy-to-use to the Windows Phone platform. Our goal is to ensure full integration of brand, industrial design, user interface, graphic design, usability, and business strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tri.WPEDesign&lt;br/&gt;
WPD.WPE.LC&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-windows-phone-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-windows-phone-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Designer at Efinancial in Bellevue, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Efinancial is looking for a Web Designer to help us make history. We&amp;rsquo;re not only changing an industry but we are making a profound difference in people&amp;rsquo;s lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Design and update the user interface and overall customer experience for company web sites and applications including changes to existing websites, content management of websites and various other graphical design and programming projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Must Haves:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS 2/3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MVC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Front End / UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Fireworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice To Have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some understanding of programming techniques, classes/objects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual Studio, TFS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consult with managerial and technical personnel to clarify program intent, identify problems, and suggest changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform systems analysis and programming tasks to maintain and control the use of software applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write, analyze, review, and rewrite programs, using design diagrams, and applying knowledge of computer capabilities, subject matter, and symbolic logic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop graphical user interfaces for web applications developed by in-house programming staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create mock-ups and develop page layout and navigation for projects.  Provides design elements, comps, templates, and finished solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document design standards including colors, fonts, logos, photos and company brand in coordination with the marketing staff.  Develop alternatives and revise sites as necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with company departments in the development of websites and other digital media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determines user&amp;rsquo;s needs, strategies, and goals and develop sites/designs/products that meet those needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct various testing cycles and trial runs of programs and software applications to be sure they will produce the desired results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform or direct revision, repair, or expansion of existing programs to increase operating efficiency or adapt to new requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compile and write documentation of program development and subsequent revisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write or contribute to instructions or manuals to guide end users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Supervisory Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This job has no supervisory responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty satisfactorily. The requirements listed below are representative of the knowledge, skill, and/or ability required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Established portfolio of creative and innovating Web &amp;amp; Graphic design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Planning and problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task in a fast-paced, multi -deadline environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to coordinate with internal and external groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound analytical and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education/Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Associates degree (A.A.) from two-year College in web development, multimedia, or computer science and 2 years of recent experience in web and interface design for consumer websites and applications; or equivalent combination of education and experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing website content or other content such as product demonstrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in web site development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Computer and Technical Skills:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate skills in MS Office Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in commercial web product development, including HTML, CSS, Flash, Photoshop, video editing tools, technical design and writing, and development standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with or familiarity with search engine optimization (SEO) concepts a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Certificates and Licenses:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No certifications needed
EEOC/Other:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Language Ability:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ability to read, analyze and interpret business documents.
Ability to write reports, and procedure manuals
Ability to effectively present information and respond to questions from group of employees, managers and customers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Math Ability:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ability to apply advanced mathematical concepts such as exponents, logarithms, quadratic equations, and permutations
Ability to apply mathematical operations to such tasks as frequency distribution, determination of test reliability and validity, analysis of variance and sampling theory&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Reasoning Ability:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ability to solve problems and deal with a variety of concrete variables in situations where only limited standardization exists
Ability to interpret a variety of instructions furnished in written, oral, diagram, or schedule form.
Inductive and deductive reasoning skills&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Physical Demands:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The physical demands described here are representative of those that must be met by an employee to successfully perform the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific vision abilities required by this job include close vision and ability to adjust focus to read a computer screen and various documents.
While performing the duties of this job, the employee is frequently required to sit and use hands and fingers for keyboarding or similar use of
hands. The employee is occasionally required to reach with hands and arms and occasionally required to talk and hear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Work Environment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work environment characteristics described here are representative of those an employee encounters while performing the essential functions of this job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work is performed in a typical office environment.  The noise level is usually moderate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-efinancial-bellevue-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-designer-efinancial-bellevue-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer, Javari, Mobile at Concur in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;If the prospect of working on an international brand with presence in four countries, two continents and a focus on designer shoes, bags and accessories sounds fun to you, a position with Javari may be right for you. Come help us define one of the fastest growing and biggest online industries with your innovative ideas and best-in-class mobile shopping experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an innovative, self-motivated user experience designer to help us define the future of mobile retail. Working in close collaboration with product management, technology, business teams and design peers, the designer will be relied upon to create efficient, elegant, and customer-focused designs that meet business requirements and provide our customers with an unrivaled mobile retail experience. The ideal candidate will exhibit an unfailing passion and capacity to advocate on behalf of our customers and an uncanny sense for providing elegant, mainstream yet-locally relevant presentations of expansive content and features across a manifold of product lines, client devices, and locales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create user-centered designs by considering market analysis, customer feedback, site metrics, usability findings, and following the user-centered design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use business requirements and market research to develop scenarios, use cases, and high-level requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design the UI architecture, interface, and interaction flow of applications and experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop conceptual diagrams, wireframes, detailed visual mockups, click-throughs, and prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain detailed user-interface specifications and design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present design work to the user experience team, product team, and Amazon executives for review and feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with cross-functional teams and collaborate with designers to achieve holistic objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsibly and effectively advocate for the customer in a corporate environment; fostering a shared understanding of the customer-centric intersection between design, content, business and marketing values.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Estimate design initiatives and own track work queue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 3 years of experience as a user experience designer, interaction designer, information architect, or similar role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 2 years experience in the mobile space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An online portfolio or samples of work demonstrating experience creating great user-centered design solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation, and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a collaborative team and working directly with developers for implementation of designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work gracefully, multi-task and have a bias for action in a fast-paced, often ambiguous environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectiveness in working across organizational boundaries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to drive the design review cycle and close on design requirements independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in best practices for web-based information architecture and design, as well as strong knowledge of usability principles and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the technical considerations needed when designing for the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in design, human-computer interaction (HCI), or equivalent professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in a variety of design tools such as Photoshop, Illustrator, Fireworks, Visio, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to creative interactive prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A clean sense of design aesthetics, and a natural propensity towards simplification over complication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An enduring sense of humor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability and passion to design for a foreign context&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prototype with HTML, JavaScript, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail/E-commerce design experience in a global context&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with international teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-javari-mobile-concur-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-javari-mobile-concur-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are a fun, passionate group of Microsoft Office designers focused on creating innovative, meaningful experiences for modern productivity, specifically around graphics, data and data visualization across the Microsoft Office suite. We are looking for an experienced interaction designer with proven real-world experience working on deep, complex graphics and data visualization problems and creating compelling solutions. Come help us shape the future of productivity and the way people work with graphics and data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an interaction designer, you must have a clear understanding of each facet of the design process that facilitates a superior shipping Product: information architecture + interaction design, research + usability, rapid prototyping, visual + motion design, brand integration, and content creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have demonstrated ability to effectively partner with product planners and managers, program managers, and development and test team members to shepherd end to end experiences from concept to released product. You have strong passion for graphics, data and data visualization and have demonstrable experience in designing experiences that use data visualization to make data both meaningful and beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a great creator, collaborator, communicator and coach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your Primary Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead/facilitate design brainstorming and work sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce scenarios, process flows, information architecture diagrams, wireframes, and other artifacts required to develop and evolve user experience designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create compelling design solutions that meet people&amp;rsquo;s need and delight them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help develop, manage, and refine UI pattern libraries and interaction guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate with developers through implementation phase to realize design vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate, defend, and build consensus around experience architecture and interaction design direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in interaction design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience creating a variety of interaction design artifacts including user scenarios, task flows, conceptual models, competitor analysis, heuristic analysis, and annotated wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience working with Visio, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign and all related business and design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of a BA/BS degree in Interface Design, Interaction Design, Communication Design, Architecture or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to and understanding of a variety of design, project management, and development processes and methodologies including agile development methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience shipping innovative and complex software and hardware products within milestone deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in current design and media trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable ability to work confidently with Program Management, Development, Product Planning, Brand, Marketing and Usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to think conceptually about design and information architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of the array of technical constraints, user goals and business requirements that shape current and future products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly produce elegant and easily understood diagrams, wireframes, and other artifacts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills and an attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Visual Designer (UX) at University Physicians, Inc in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Do you enjoy creating compelling visual and delivering exceptional products? We are looking for a Visual Designer to develop product visuals in partnership with the User Experience Design team, Software Development, Product Managers and Technical PMs. The ideal candidate will have experience creating multiplatform visuals for consumer product while striking a balance between creative designs and business deliverables. The key to success for a UX Visual Designer is that you can deliver exciting customer centric designs and experiences in a rapidly evolving environment and deliver compelling consumer products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop visual designs, style, layouts and movement for Digital products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently deliver visuals, on time in partnership with the UX interaction designers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept and deliver designs across an entire product experience- developed all visual material necessary to ship a fully integrated consumer product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are a strong Visual Designer who can prioritize well, translate the product vision, compellingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have relentlessly high standards (is never satisfied with the status quo).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have passion and convictions and the innate ability to inspire passion in others; strong results orientation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills / Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years in Visual Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive hands on design experience and a deep understanding of how a Design team integrates with Technical partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge and experience with current digital design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years as a Visual Designer for a consumer and/or entertainment products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in 3D motion and graphics a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with an e-commerce or consumer products company is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a member of the Design team you should have the ability to think creatively, strategically and tactically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive Key Design issues across the product team and advocate for the best solutions both technically and from a design perspective&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;s•com is an Equal Employment Opportunity Employer. People from racial minority groups, veterans, and the disabled are strongly encouraged to apply. Copyright 2011&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To apply directly to CORESTAFF Services- Washington, please click the link below. Another window will open and allow you to apply directly online.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/visual-designer-ux-university-physicians-inc-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/visual-designer-ux-university-physicians-inc-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Flash Designer at YP.com in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Advertising Design Experience team is seeking a talented, customer-obsessed rich media designer to create innovative advertising experiences for a variety of global brands. The ideal candidate will combine exceptional visual design with interactive development skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and build rich media advertising experiences for web and mobile platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take an idea from concept to reality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand usability principles that help drive successful designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze marketing challenges and create on-brand design solutions that meet measurable business goals and requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create customer-centric designs by integrating marketing objectives, target audience and creative assets into advertising designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support sales teams by bringing big ideas to life through ideation and creation of high fidelity designs for sales presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills / Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in Flash, preferably Actionscript 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing on mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter who is a customer-obsessed, detail-oriented, and enthusiastic team player.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation, and interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of professional experience working as a rich media designer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An online portfolio or samples of work demonstrating visual design skills and innovative interactive work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task and meet tight deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in a variety of design tools such as Photoshop, Illustrator, Fireworks, Visio, and Dreamweaver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in HTML5, JavaScript, and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in an advertising or creative agency environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advertising experience across a range of media including online, mobile and print. CORESTAFF Services is an Equal Employment Opportunity Employer. People from racial minority groups, veterans, and the disabled are strongly encouraged to apply. CORESTAFF Services is not associated with Core Staffing Services, Inc, which operates in the New York metro area.  Copyright 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Application Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To apply directly to CORESTAFF Services- Washington, please click the link below. Another window will open and allow you to apply directly online.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/flash-designer-yp-com-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/flash-designer-yp-com-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Starbucks in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This job contributes to Starbucks success by participating on design teams and developing visual product presentation plans and standards for Starbucks retail stores and other assigned Starbucks business units. Models and acts in accordance with Starbucks guiding principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Summary of Key Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities and essential job functions include but are not limited to the following:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assists other designers and manager or director in project briefings, presentations and project reviews with internal clients. Supports the department with creative and brand research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhances the Starbucks experience for customers by collaborating with department management and project team members to develop and define the visual strategy for basic graphics standards, promotions, events, and product launches for Starbucks retail stores in North America. Works in conjunction with Prepress designers and Procurement managers to ensure quality products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participates in special projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works with Design lead on specific aspects of each design project. Maintains project schedules, timelines and budgets, and assists in preparation for team and project meetings. Acts as a leader and mentor within the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Summary of Experience&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design experience with a design firm, advertising agency or marketing department (3 years)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-end brand design development (3 years)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual presentation and display design (3 years)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Required Knowledge, Skills and Abilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work as part of a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of desktop publishing software, including QuarkXpress, Adobe Illustrator and PhotoShop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of digital prepress process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of procurement process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize and meet deadlines within short time frames&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-starbucks-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-starbucks-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Application Designer at Pacific Northwest National Laboratory in Richland, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Pacific Northwest National Laboratory is seeking highly-qualified candidates with expertise in web application design with a focus in human computer interaction. This includes but is not limited to compiling, analyzing and interpreting project requirements, designing graphical user interfaces (GUIs) for web applications, building demonstrable and functional prototypes, and building new pieces of deployment-ready software.
This position will support the PNNL Knowledge Discovery and Informatics team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The position requires contributing to technical proposals, presentations and publication; managing individual assignments for multiple projects, performing assignments with minimal oversight and working within software development teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participation in professional activities is encouraged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The successful candidate will:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;contribute to the translation of client requests and needs into a set of project requirements and tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demonstrate a strong background in Human Computer Interaction by applying in-depth knowledge of design principals to a defined set of software requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;apply practical experience with prototyping to project requirements and designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;participate in the software design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;implement and design of graphical user interfaces (GUI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;construct functional web applications and prototypes in the languages of HTML, CSS, PHP, jQuery, and Java&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;develop for and extend the functionality of web content management systems such as Semantic MediaWiki, Drupal, and Wordpress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;facilitate and prepare collaborative websites for use in small teams, groups, and divisions at the lab&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;development on Linux, Macintosh and Windows environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;development of client server and database aware applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;creation and management of software documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;use of source code revision control tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;effectively manage individual tasks, schedule, workload, budget, and deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;work to broaden and deepen own technical knowledge and skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;work effectively within software development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exhibit a spirit of cooperation, teamwork, and mutual respect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;contribute to technical presentations and demonstrations of designs, prototypes and operational software to existing and potential clients; group, division, and sector managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;contributions to publications and proposals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The staff member is expected to develop knowledge of the goals of any projects to which they are assigned and the clients they support. The staff member is expected to maintain a customer-service focus commensurate with this position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staff normally receives task instructions from the project manager, which are performed with minimal oversight. The incumbent will report directly to the Knowledge Discovery and Informatics (KDI) Technical Group Manager. The incumbent will work as a staff member under the direction of project managers and senior software scientists. The incumbent will be expected to attend regular project meetings and KDI group meetings. The incumbent must be able to attend offsite team meetings with other team members, clients, and users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Minimum Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Science or Master of Science in computer science or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;0-1 years experience in user experience, web, or other related design field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong HTML, CSS, and jQuery skills. Basic knowledge of Java, PHP and MySQL a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in web content management systems (Semantic MediaWiki, Drupal 6.x-7.x, Wordpress 2.x-3.x, and PHPbb preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with task management software (Jira, Redmine, ActiveCollab etc.) preferred
Equal Employment Opportunity
Pacific Northwest National Laboratory (PNNL) is an Affirmative Action / Equal Opportunity Employer and supports diversity in the workplace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, marital or family status, sexual orientation, gender identity, or genetic information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All staff at the Pacific Northwest National Laboratory must be able to demonstrate the legal right to work in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position requires the ability to obtain a federal security clearance in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Which requires:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US Citizenship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background Investigation: Applicants selected will be subject to a Federal background investigation and must meet eligibility requirements for access to classified matter in accordance 10 CFR 710, Appendix B.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drug Testing:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;All Security Clearance (L or Q) positions will be considered by the Department of Energy to be Testing Designated Positions which means that they are subject to applicant, random, and for cause drug testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, applicants must be able to demonstrate non-use of illegal drugs for the 12 consecutive months preceding completion of the requisite Questionnaire for National Security Positions (QNSP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Note:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants will be considered ineligible for security clearance processing by the U.S. Department of Energy until non-use of illegal drugs for 12 consecutive months can be demonstrated&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-designer-pacific-northwest-national-laboratory-richland-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-application-designer-pacific-northwest-national-laboratory-richland-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>UX Designer - Windows Design Team at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The Microsoft Windows User Experience team is seeking exceptional senior interaction designers to make the personal computer more powerful, engaging, and rewarding to use. This is an opportunity to reinvent how people interact with computers, to turn new technology into positive user experiences, and to deliver a product that reaches millions of customers. If you are inspired by these plans, then this is the team for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an Interaction Designer, you will work alongside some of the world’s most talented product designers, usability specialists, and software developers to build the future generation of the Windows operating system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will help set the vision for the future Windows user experience, serving as a user advocate to ensure the highest level of usability, desirability and customer satisfaction. You will research, design, and prototype product experiences that meet demanding quality standards, and you will drive your work through the software development process. You will collaborate with teams across the company to ensure we maintain industry leadership, delivering innovative, exciting and emotionally engaging products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates should have outstanding skills in designing interaction and visuals for software or the web. We require a proven ability to work from an array of prototyping techniques to develop and communicate the benefits of concepts and solutions, and show experience applying user research throughout the design process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications include&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a 4-year degree in industrial design,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;interaction design, or related field,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;plus 3-5 years of industry experience developing software products for large markets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of major multimedia, design, and operating system software (Photoshop, Flash or Director, Windows, Office) is expected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Resumes need to include an online portfolio to be considered&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WDJobs&lt;br/&gt;
W:WE&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-windows-design-team-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ux-designer-windows-design-team-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>