<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wa-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Designer at Hacker Group, Inc. in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You will use your ability to visually articulate an integrated marketing strategy every single day. As a Senior Designer, you’ll have the opportunity to inspire your peers. You’ll learn to present your work with skill, confidence and enthusiasm. We need someone who moves the needle creatively, keeps their eye on the goal, sees the glass as half full and knows how to have serious fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hacker Group is a 200+ person digital/direct agency that serves brand-name clients nationwide and provides its employees with incredible growth opportunities. We have an accountable culture – one that generously rewards its successful teams. By revenue, we are the largest agency in Seattle and Advertising Age ranked us as the 26th largest direct marketing agency in the nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you’ll do:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop innovative design solutions for print marketing materials and other media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Combine artistic skills with business knowledge to create visual designs that sell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create layouts for direct mail, print advertising, online, email and collateral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uphold client brand standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct photo searches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare files for release to prepress and ensure all creative deliverables are met&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;How to qualify:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in graphic design, visual communications or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years' direct marketing or general agency design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in Adobe CS and general office applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of print, Web and email production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of 3D, interactive and video editing apps are a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Apply for this job:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply for this job online&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forward this job to a friend or colleague&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;It is the policy of the Hacker Group to provide equal employment opportunities to all employees and applicants for employment without regard to race, religion, color, ethnic origin, gender, gender identity, age, marital status, veteran status, sexual orientation, disability, or any other basis prohibited by applicable federal, state, or local law. EOE/AA/M/D/V/F&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-hacker-group-inc-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-hacker-group-inc-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Experience Designer at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We believe in the power of stories. And we love transforming data into insights. We help people tell compelling stories with data &amp;ndash; data of all sizes, shapes, and kind; through highly interactive, visually rich products that are used anytime, anywhere (desktop, web, mobile, and more…).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are the design discipline within the Microsoft Data Platform Group, the second largest business within Microsoft. We work as an integrated product design team with program management, development and test &amp;ndash; to envision, create, craft and deliver next generation experiences for Microsoft’s data platform in the areas of business intelligence, big data, information services and information visualization on the cloud, based on deep understanding of what makes our users tick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our world-class product design teams are expanding, and we are looking for Senior UX Designers to own the design leadership and execution of key end to end experiences for our next generation end user tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This person must be an excellent hands on designer that can create exciting results on their own, and both participate in and lead a cross-functional team through a collaborative design process to deliver rapid prototypes, user stories, concept sketches, experience storyboards, information architecture, interaction design, visual design, motion design, design research and usability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senior UX designer needs to be competent in all of facets of the design process, and exceptionally talented and skilled in at least one major area (e.g. Visual and motion design, or Interaction and information architecture design). Most importantly, the senior designer needs to have sufficient conviction in their designs to own the emotional dimensions of the product, ensuring that the experience delivered is ultimately emotionally irresistible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;This might just be you, if you are…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As passionate about data and data visualization as we are.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A well-rounded UX professional who connects the dots between business needs, innovation and good design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced at driving a user experience from start-to-finish that delivers results, connects emotionally, and makes customers smile again and again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obsessed with good user-centered design practices and have an eye for detail (That font. That grid. That color. That gesture. That motion. &amp;ldquo;Ahhh!&amp;rdquo;.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you have at least 5 years of UX design experience (and the portfolio to prove it), then you are someone we want to talk to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advanced degree in Human Computer Interaction, Digital Media Design, Industrial Design, Fine Arts or related field is desired.
Strong skills in visual and motion design preferred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualification:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 5 years as a key, hands-on interaction/visual designer of a UI/UX team through the product development cycle of successfully launched web, mobile, and/or software applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why be just a part of the future when you can actually create it? Apply today to join our talented team of inter-disciplinary designers, design researchers, program managers and product developers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Designer at POP in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The senior designer has ability to take a creative strategy and translate it into a memorable digital experience, collaborating with UX architects, copywriters, and interactive developers. This role focuses on digital creative for automotive clients in particular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the business needs of our clients, and have the ability to concept and design compelling solutions that align with overall creative strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create interactive design concepts for major automotive brands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design user interface software features, mood boards, storyboards, interactive page layouts, site grids and interface demos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build working physical prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop visual specifications for web pages and create style guides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform high level photo retouching and enhancements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee production of digital assets for delivery to production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capable of working on multiple projects, small or large, with various project leads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the development team to ensure designs are implemented correctly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years’ progressive experience developing large-scale interactive design for web, mobile, social and emerging platforms required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience developing creative advertising for the automotive brands required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience developing comprehensive style guides for major brands required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated hands-on experience creating exceptional digital brand experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working through the entire design life cycle, from producing rough concepts to delivering a polished design solution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a strong skill-set in typography, motion, interactive and mobile design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Photoshop, Illustrator, and Flash required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with prototyping graphical user interface software (i.e. HTML5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with JavaScript and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with clients and internal partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BFA in Graphic Design or Digital Media Design required; MA preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-pop-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-pop-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer at Apptio in Bellevue, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;At Apptio we are focused on changing the world by making every IT organization that we work with into a more efficient and cost-effective service provider to the business. Apptio&amp;rsquo;s Technology Business Management (TBM) SaaS platform provides revolutionary automation in transparency, planning and performance management required for IT to run like a business. From the founding of the company we set out to disrupt the existing enterprise software market by designing purpose-built, on-demand applications capable of managing the cost, quality and value of IT services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, Apptio is on track to become the fastest growing company in the history of enterprise software. Leading global enterprise organizations such as Bank of America, Boeing, Cisco, Facebook, JPMorgan Chase, Microsoft, St. Luke&amp;rsquo;s Health System, and Swiss Re rely on Apptio to reduce costs and align IT with business priorities. Backed by some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most prominent financial institutions including T. Rowe Price, Andreessen Horowitz, Greylock Partners, Madrona Ventures, Shasta Ventures, Apptio is building the next major enterprise software category. Come join our team!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Position:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are passionate about creating quality user-centered design. You live for facing down and solving tough design problems. You thrive in fast paced, iterative design environments and possess clear, effective communication skills. You work collaboratively across the organization – while also working independently. You pay attention to the details without forgetting the big picture. You have vision, moxie, and a track record that shows both. You love working with a small, quirky UX team that preaches, teaches, and gets their hands dirty in the name of getting things done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, wireframe, and document user interfaces and user experience improvements for an enterprise cloud-based software solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively with the UX team, product managers, and developers to design next-generation user interfaces and solve ongoing usability problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a positive, engaging force for UI and UX within the organization and proactively find opportunities to improve our customer’s success.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and present your design work in industry standard mockup and wireframing tools (and ideally in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience designing enterprise and/or technical web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record for designing compelling, accessible and standards-based user experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert user of design and prototyping tools (e.g. Axure).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of the advantages and limits of web pages as design surface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively with disparate, cross-functional groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-task, prioritize and communicate progress effectively to multiple stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synthesize feedback while maintaining ownership of the design process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong sketching/drawing skills and/or wireframing electronically (e.g. Balsamiq).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in a relevant field (e.g. Informatics, Design, Computer Science).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML, CSS and Javascript (JQuery) prototyping skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of usability and user research best practices and techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of typography, color, imagery, composition and other graphic elements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile and Scrum development process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Portfolio:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please include a link to your portfolio with work samples when applying. Indicate your role and contribution for each. Be prepared to present your portfolio during your interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Location:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is located at our HQ in Bellevue, WA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apptio, Inc. provides equal employment opportunities (EEO) to all employees and applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, sexual orientation, national origin, age, disability, genetic information, marital status, amnesty, or status as a covered veteran in accordance with applicable federal, state and local laws. Apptio, Inc. complies with applicable state and local laws governing non-discrimination in employment in every location in which the company has facilities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-apptio-bellevue-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-apptio-bellevue-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Perkins Coie in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This position will support the firm&amp;rsquo;s business development efforts and develop the firm&amp;rsquo;s graphic brand by designing, creating, and producing collateral materials presentations and other graphics in a way that differentiates Perkins Coie from other law firms.  Will establish the company&amp;rsquo;s visual brand excellence by developing and maintaining consistent  branded templates and marketing collateral for office openings/closures, national and regional advertising campaigns, tradeshow and event collateral, brochures and informational sheets that support firmwide business development efforts.  Will also design innovative online advertisements, publications, HTML emails, front end web development and other related multimedia channels such as social media and graphic assets for videos.  Additional responsibilities will be to create PowerPoint presentations for prospective or existing client proposals, presentations and other uses and staying abreast of ongoing changes and trends within the graphic, communication and multimedia world and continue to keep the firm&amp;rsquo;s brand identity fresh.  This includes keeping client relations peers up to date regarding best practices that improve the use of technology in firm communications and business development efforts.  Will also serve as the central point of contact for outside print vendors to ensure brand consistency and management of project deadlines and as a central point of contact for internal/external production artists/graphic designers; coordinate project allocation and brand consistency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;This position requires&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;expertise in the Adobe Creative Suite and Windows programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to communicate and execute concepts with storyboards, wireframes and/or design layouts that follow the marketing team&amp;rsquo;s communication goals and templates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great deal of professionalism, creativity, flexibility and superb attention to detail is required to maintain quality and keep pace in a deadline driven environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Flash animation and working with Wordpress templates, as well as corporate branding experience is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with standard concepts, practices, and procedures within the legal field a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position requires a minimum of 5 years graphic design experience or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;EOE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perkins Coie is an Equal Opportunity Employer and does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, veteran status, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity,  disability or any other category prohibited by local, state or federal law. This policy applies to all aspects of employment, including recruitment, placement, promotion, transfer, demotion, compensation, benefits, social and recreational activities and termination.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-perkins-coie-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-perkins-coie-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Visual Designer at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Who are we?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are fun, passionate group of Microsoft Office designers focused on creating innovative, meaningful experiences for modern productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who are we looking for?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a seasoned Visual Communications Designer with proven real-world experience to join our team and create leading software + services experiences especially around consumer and IW scenarios. Come help us shape the future of productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You create visual design languages that simultaneously supports functional design while conveying the emotional dimensions and brand of a product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Senior Visual Communications Designer, you must have a clear understanding of each facet of the design process that facilitates a superior shipping Product: information architecture + interaction design, research + usability, rapid prototyping, visual + motion design, brand integration, and content creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have demonstrated ability to effectively partner with product planners and managers, program managers, and development and test team members to shepherd end to end experiences from concept to ship. You have a highly refined sense of aesthetics, a deep knowledge of communicating ideas and emotions through visual media, and plenty of raw talent as a visual artist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a great creator, collaborator, communicator and coach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your Primary Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead/facilitate design brainstorming and work sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce mood boards, storyboards, design briefs, sketching, visual language guidelines, motion studies and other artifacts required to develop and evolve user experience designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work (primarily) with interaction and motion designers to ensure the visual design enhances the overall user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with brand designers to ensure the visual design is reflective of and additive to the brand strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with user researchers to coordinate testing efforts, interpret test results, and incorporate results into design efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate with developers through implementation phase to realize design vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate, defend, and build consensus around visual design direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with the Creative Director, lead a significant experience design effort within Office Design’s portfolio of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Who are you?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of product design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience working with Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects and other related business and design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree in Graphic Design, Communication Design, Interface Design, Interaction Design, or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely strong visual sensibilities, ability to use visual thinking, storyboards, sketching, and communication design to create breakthrough interaction design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of fundamental visual design disciplines (typography, iconography, composition, color, composition, layout, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise creating a variety of visual design documents including mood boards, storyboards, creative briefs, motion studies, and visual style guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meticulous sense of detail and ability to seek out simple solutions to complex design challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always approach a project from multiple angles, and deliver a variety of solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to and understanding of variety of design, project management, and development processes and methodologies including agile development methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience shipping innovative and complex mobile, web or software products within milestone deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in delivering production assets to development counterpart on time and with quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in current entertainment and social media trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable ability to work confidently with Program Management, Development, Product Planning, Brand, Marketing and Usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess ability to think conceptually about design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the array of technical constraints, user goals and business requirements that shape current and future products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly produce stunning and elegant visual treatments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills and an attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Portfolio review required&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MOD:OFF
MOD:ENG&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-visual-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-visual-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Designer at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We believe in the power of stories. And we love transforming data into insights. We help people tell compelling stories with data &amp;ndash; data of all sizes, shapes, and kind; through highly interactive, visually rich products that are used anytime, anywhere (desktop, web, mobile, and more…).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are the design discipline within the Microsoft Data Platform Group, the second largest business within Microsoft. We work as an integrated product design team with program management, development and test &amp;ndash; to envision, create, craft and deliver next generation experiences for Microsoft’s data platform in the areas of business intelligence, big data, information services and information visualization on the cloud, based on deep understanding of what makes our users tick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our world-class product design teams are expanding, and we are looking for Senior UX Designers to own the design leadership and execution of key end to end experiences for our next generation end user tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This person must be an excellent hands on designer that can create exciting results on their own, and both participate in and lead a cross-functional team through a collaborative design process to deliver rapid prototypes, user stories, concept sketches, experience storyboards, information architecture, interaction design, visual design, motion design, design research and usability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senior UX designer needs to be competent in all of facets of the design process, and exceptionally talented and skilled in at least one major area (e.g. Visual and motion design, or Interaction and information architecture design). Most importantly, the senior designer needs to have sufficient conviction in their designs to own the emotional dimensions of the product, ensuring that the experience delivered is ultimately emotionally irresistible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;This might just be you, if you are…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As passionate about data and data visualization as we are.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A well-rounded UX professional who connects the dots between business needs, innovation and good design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced at driving a user experience from start-to-finish that delivers results, connects emotionally, and makes customers smile again and again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obsessed with good user-centered design practices and have an eye for detail (That font. That grid. That color. That gesture. That motion. &amp;ldquo;Ahhh!&amp;rdquo;.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you have at least 5 years of UX design experience (and the portfolio to prove it), then you are someone we want to talk to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Required Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years as a key, hands-on interaction/visual designer of a UI/UX team through the product development cycle of successfully launched web, mobile, and/or software applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of interactive and/or visual design experience (and the portfolio to prove it).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Basic Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Human Computer Interaction, Digital Media Design, Industrial Design, Fine Arts or related field is desired.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong skills in visual and motion design are a big plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Why be just a part of the future when you can actually create it? Apply today to join our talented team of inter-disciplinary designers, design researchers, program managers and product developers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-designer-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Marketing Multimedia Designer at Onvia in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced marketing multimedia design professional to help us tell our solution story. The multimedia designer will create stories and designs for our website, marketing campaigns and sales tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will be a flexible, highly motivated individual who has the creative experience and ability to present our story using innovative multimedia design concepts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Located in our Seattle office, this full-time position reports to the director of marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing videos for client success stories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating videos for company promotions and events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with internal and external design teams to create compelling content for campaigns, web and social media, to support pipeline growth for targeted marketing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Desired Skills and Experience:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A creative thinker who can quickly get a concept and bring it to life visually.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in Adobe Premiere, After Effects, Illustrator and Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional background in producing web-delivered videos including pre-production planning, shooting quality video/ audio, editing and designing titles/graphics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong sense of story and the ability to single-handedly manage an interview/shoot and get compelling content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in image composition, lighting and shooting techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional background in designing for the web including banners, landing pages, icons and illustrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with HTML(5) and CSS. Additional skills with javascript/jquery and PHP would be excellent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently to prioritize projects and to wear multiple hats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A team player who collaborates well with others and enjoys people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly attentive to detail with a solid focus on quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter with strong self-management and excellent interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Company Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more than 12 years Onvia (NASDAQ: ONVI), has been successfully delivering the research, analytics and tools to companies rely that rely on government business, and a $5.5 trillion market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onvia tracks, analyzes and reports the spending of more than 89,000 federal, state and local government agencies, giving companies a single source for conducting open, intelligent and efficient business with government. Along with providing an exclusive suite of integrated business tools for a wide variety of industries, Onvia offers DemandStar, the automated system that streamlines agency procurement processes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To apply directly, email your résumé to careers @ onvia.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/marketing-multimedia-designer-onvia-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/marketing-multimedia-designer-onvia-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>User Experience Designer at Amazon Corporate LLC in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Customer Service Design team is seeking an experienced User Experience Designer. We’re looking for someone with strong user interface, usability and visual design skills to create scalable applications to improve the customer experience on the Amazon websites, and for our internal CRM application, which is used by representatives worldwide, in multiple languages to satisfy millions of customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years professional experience in Design, as a user experience designer, interaction designer, or equivalent field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree, preferably in design or human-computer interaction (HCI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An online portfolio with samples of work demonstrating user-centered design solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with CSS and HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated visual design expertise; capacity for creating fun, highly usable designs and layouts, and a propensity towards simplification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to turn around rigorous wireframes and mockups in an iterative, agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to scope design initiatives accurately and prioritize work items appropriately&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation, and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail and eCommerce design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with web standards and accessibility compliance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Adobe tools is highly desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-amazon-corporate-llc-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/user-experience-designer-amazon-corporate-llc-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at Quardev, Inc. in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Quardev, Inc., a premier technical services provider is looking for exceptional people to join our team. We have a fast-growth, community-minded culture that is built on integrity, innovation, and fun, with a commitment to Doing-What-It-Takes to get the job done for our clients. Our five-star service standard, along with our professionalism and personable, partnering approach to doing business has earned us a 100% return rate with our testing clients since opening our doors in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create images that present a compelling theme for each online ad campaign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the schedule for merchandising ads for our client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research and acquire photos from stock services and other low cost sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform photo retouching, enhancement, and create realistic photo composites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Render finished layouts of ads in web-ready format. Write image text and captions .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update, test, and monitor HTML code for merchandising.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage asset database of archived photos and artwork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay current on all advertising inside and outside our client&amp;rsquo;s site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work cooperatively with outside resources on promotional campaigns to create online banner ads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualize overall project visions and goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with marketing managers to design and complete promotional campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with developers to design and complete interactive pages or objects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Storyboard and execute dynamic interactive marketing pieces using Javascript animation (jQuery/scriptaculous), and animated GIFs .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US Citizens and Green Card holders are encouraged to apply. We are unable to sponsor visas at this time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local Seattle Metro area candidates ONLY&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Agencies Quardev does not accept unsolicited resumes from third party vendors. Any unsolicited resumes sent to Quardev from any third party will not be recognized and such agency or party will have no recourse from Quardev&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are ready for a challenge with a fast growing, exciting company send your resume and cover letter to us at resumes@quardev.com. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-quadrev-inc-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-quadrev-inc-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>