<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wa-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Interaction Designer-IEB-XBOX Live at Microsoft in Redmond, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft‘s Interactive Entertainment Business delivers world class entertainment experiences you want with the people you care about wherever you are…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IEB Design (designers of Xbox) leads the design of entertainment experiences for customers worldwide. The entertainment experiences we create are for a diverse audience &amp;ndash; from intense gamers to family timers &amp;ndash; and are enjoyed in many contexts &amp;ndash; TV, PC, Web and Mobile. We partner closely with IEB business and technology team members to envision, design, define, validate and deliver entertainment experiences that are effortless, intuitive, delightful and unified. IEB Design ensures that the entertainment experience our customers enjoy &amp;ndash; from TV to music to games to video &amp;ndash; is simply the best in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IEB Design is seeking an Interaction Designer to join our team of producers, user researchers, and interaction, industrial, motion, visual, sensory, brand, and integration designers to help us reinvent entertainment led from the living room, powered by the cloud, and available across multiple screens. You have demonstrated ability to effectively partner with product planners and managers, program managers and development and test team members to shepherd end to end experiences from concept to ship. You have knowledge of natural user interface (NUI) paradigms and have experience in designing experiences with multiple input modalities. You are a great creator, collaborator, and communicator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Primary Responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead/facilitate design brainstorming and work sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce scenarios, process flows, information architecture diagrams, wireframes, and other artifacts required to develop and evolve user experience designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with user researchers to coordinate testing efforts, interpret test results, and incorporate results into design efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help develop, manage, and refine UI pattern libraries and interaction guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively communicate with developers through implementation phase to realize design vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate, defend, and build consensus around experience architecture and interaction design direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualified candidates should have at least 5 years of experience including experience with information architecture, interaction design user research, and usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise creating a variety of interaction design documents including user scenarios, task flows, conceptual models, competitor analysis, heuristic analysis, and annotated wireframes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating and managing UI pattern libraries and interaction guidelines ideally across a large organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing and conducting a variety of both qualitative and quantitative research including ethnographic research, contextual inquiries, guided explorations, and usability testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to and understanding of variety of design, project management, and development processes and methodologies including agile development methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience shipping innovative and complex mobile, web or software products within milestone deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in current entertainment and social media trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable ability to work confidently with Program Management, Development, Product Planning, Brand, Marketing and Usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess ability to think conceptually about design and information architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the array of technical constraints, user goals and business requirements that shape current and future products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Visio, Photoshop, Illustrator, and all related business and design tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly produce elegant and easily understood diagrams, wireframes, and other artifacts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills and an attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of a BA/BS degree in Interface Design, Interaction Design, Communication Design, Architecture or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portfolio review required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IEBCRjobs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J2WERPL1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nearest Major Market:&lt;/strong&gt; Seattle&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Nearest Secondary Market:&lt;/strong&gt; Bellevue&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Job Segments:&lt;/strong&gt; Engineer, Program Manager, Graphic Design, Cloud, Testing, Engineering, Management, Creative, Technology&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-ieb-xbox-live-microsoft-redmond-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/interaction-designer-ieb-xbox-live-microsoft-redmond-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Junior Web Designer at triplenet technologies in Bellevue, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Come be part of our Winning Team!!! We have a full time opportunity for a Junior to Mid Level  Web Designer for a client that is the fastest growing Software Company in Washington State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web Designer will be responsible for creating the look and feel of World Wide Web pages for a client&amp;rsquo;s and Company’s Web sites. This involves developing a graphic design that effectively communicates the ideas being promoted by the Web site. A web designer may take part in the initial planning of a Web site, meeting with the client to discuss ideas for the layout and organization of the site, the types of colors or images to use (photos, illustrations, logo, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of professional web design experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in CSS, HTML and JavaScript with understanding of cross-browser design issues and lean work-arounds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Flash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of online media production practices, such as Web and cross-browser support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Knowledge of the following a definite asset(Desirable):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of version control, especially Subversion, is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Japanese language skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Key Traits:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able to work independently as well as collaboratively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortably give and receive creative critiques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to function well within a high paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take both initiative and direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Location: Bellevue, WA
Duration: 4 Months with a strong possibility of Temp to Permanent for the right candidate
Rate:$16-$18 per hour&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-designer-triplenet-technologies-bellevue-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/junior-web-designer-triplenet-technologies-bellevue-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>