<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wa-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-end Web Developer at MobileDevHQ in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re hiring our first front-end web developer to translate designers' beautiful
ideas into an amazing web application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;App marketers are spending too much time and money on paid app marketing
channels, leading to unprofitable downloads. We believe there&amp;rsquo;s a better way:
organic app marketing. MobileDevHQ helps mobile app marketers get more
downloads by understanding and improving organic marketing channels such as
app store search. We are a TechStars Seattle company with seed funding from a
slew of fantastic investors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a world-class front-end web developer with a strong understanding of
user experience who can turn designs into reality through code. You have strong
opinions about building beautiful web applications and strive for excellence in
everything you do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll be doing at MobileDevHQ:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with our product team to understand users' pains and use cases for our product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a designer to help build UIs to solve these pains and use cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement these interfaces into our product with your
HTML/CSS/JavaScript skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What you need to be hired at MobileDevHQ:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience taking Photoshop work and turning it into a living, breathing web page with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Bonus points for Ruby on Rails (or HAML and SASS) experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love for mobile and marketing. Apps are taking over the world, and we help large enterprises succeed in the app ecosystem through smart marketing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building beautiful dashboards for businesses to complete complicated workflows and feel good while doing so is a huge bonus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with responsive design is also a bonus, given that our users are frequently working on desktops, tablets, and phones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A willingness to learn that trumps everything else. We aren&amp;rsquo;t building an average company, and we don&amp;rsquo;t want average employees. We hire
employees who love learning and aren&amp;rsquo;t afraid to dive head-first into the unknown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Why you want to join MobileDevHQ:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re crushing it&lt;/em&gt;. Users are finding our tools to be an indispensible part
of their app marketing. We&amp;rsquo;ve signed up hundreds of active paying
customers in just a few short months and are well on our way to
becoming the single dashboard for all organic app marketing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Well compensated&lt;/em&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;re a startup, but we offer a full compensation
package. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive salary, equity (in the form of stock options), and benefits (medical, dental, vision, and basic life insurance).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Awesome team&lt;/em&gt;. Our team is the best, and we treat each other like family. We&amp;rsquo;re a group of talented, diverse, and fun people. We include
sports fans, musicians, foodies, rock climbers, and more. We have competitive ping pong games daily &amp;mdash; you&amp;rsquo;ll receive a fancy ping pong paddle upon joining the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-mobiledevhq-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-mobiledevhq-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>