<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wa-mdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Android Developer at TrygTech in Bellevue, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;TrygTech is looking for a software developer to build the basis of an Android application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Necessary skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be a proficient C/C++ developer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must understand the API set backwards and forwards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must know how to do background processing and cross process API&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be knowledgeable of object oriented design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be knowledgeable in building apps for Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Bonus skills:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be comfortable with ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Additional requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of expereince&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BSCS/BSCE/BSEE or other scientific degree with equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be willing and able to provide exceptional customer service, including direct interfacing with clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong teamwork and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must enjoy a dynamic work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn fast and work independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good multitasking and priority management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated troubleshooting, problem solving and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-trygtech-bellevue-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/android-developer-trygtech-bellevue-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at 5celsius in Bellevue, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We have several existing and deployed apps that require an internal iOS developer to hop into and continue developing. We are a small and very fast moving company that is funded and growing. Our apps are used by our enterprise clients (Brooks Shoes and Titan Electric) in the field, retail stores, and at expos. Your work will be extremely visible and public, our ClearGait app is in use in 40 states and 16 countries. You need to have mastery of CoreImage as CG involves a lot of video and image manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is a contract to hire, we are looking to trial someone and hire them full time as an essential member of the team. Our environment is very much that of a startup, and you&amp;rsquo;ll need to do a lot of heavy lifting and independent work. Our office is in Bellevue and is a loft-style open office with giant windows and high ceilings. Be ready to work hard and make some waves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-5celsius-bellevue-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-5celsius-bellevue-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>iOS Developer at 5celsius in Bellevue, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;We have several existing and deployed apps that require an internal iOS developer to hop into and continue developing. We are a small and very fast moving company that is funded and growing. Our apps are used by our enterprise clients (Brooks Shoes and Titan Electric) in the field, retail stores, and at expos. Your work will be extremely visible and public, our ClearGait app is in use in 40 states and 16 countries. You need to have mastery of CoreImage as CG involves a lot of video and image manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position is a contract to hire, we are looking to trial someone and hire them full time as an essential member of the team. Our environment is very much that of a startup, and you&amp;rsquo;ll need to do a lot of heavy lifting and independent work. Our office is in Bellevue and is a loft-style open office with giant windows and high ceilings. Be ready to work hard and make some waves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-5celsius-bellevue-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/ios-developer-5celsius-bellevue-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Developer (iOS Mobile) at Quardev in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Developer (iOS Mobile)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quardev, Inc., a premier testing and technical services provider is looking for exceptional people to join
our team. We have a fast-growth, community-minded culture that is built on integrity, innovation, and
fun, with a commitment to Doing-What-It-Takes to get the job done for our clients. Our five-star service
standard, along with our professionalism and personable, partnering approach to doing business has
earned us a 100% return rate with our testing clients since opening our doors in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an iOS mobile developer (for a key client) to define, design and support our iOS
applications. As a developer you will work closely with other developers and designers to drive the
evolution and expansion of mobile apps into the next generation Airlines Mobile Assistant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Technical Skills Needed:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong Experience with iOS, Objective C or Cocoa Touch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience in mobile application development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fundamentals in object-oriented design, data structures, algorithm design, problem solving, and complexity analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in, at least, one modern object-oriented language such as Objective C (preferred), C++, or C#&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Other Requirements:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. degree in technical discipline or strong background in CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building complex iPhone Apps that have been successfully delivered to customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with iOS app testing, packaging and publishing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with Agile programming and Scrum development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good organizational and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good team player who is self motivated and well organized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Desired but not required:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Version Control, MySQL, XML, JSON and Web Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;US Citizens and Green Card holders are encouraged to apply. We are unable to sponsor visas at this
time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local Seattle Metro area candidates ONLY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agencies Quardev does not accept unsolicited resumes from third party vendors. Any unsolicited
resumes sent to Quardev from any third party will not be recognized and such agency or party will have
no recourse from Quardev.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are ready for a challenge with a fast growing, exciting company send your resume and cover letter
to us at resumes@quardev.com. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/developer-ios-mobile-quardev-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/developer-ios-mobile-quardev-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web and Mobile Producer at Bungie in Bellevue, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Bungie is seeking a Senior Producer to be a critical part of launching our new universe into the hands and minds of game players everywhere. The Producer will work under minimal supervision of the Production Director, and use independent judgment to produce success in Web and Mobile devices teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will have internal technical development experience, work well in a creative environment, be an excellent communicator, analytical, detail oriented, highly organized, and have a passion for the successful orchestration of complex projects from concept through sustained release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This position will require the production of internal and external projects, supporting marketing and PR initiatives &amp;ndash; balancing the external development timelines with the resource commitments of the game development team and our publisher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Centralize the vision coming from the stakeholders for web and mobile initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce the internal technical team responsible for the execution of web and mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act as the primary communication point for external project development. Balancing schedules, team morale, and the overall vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish, maintain, and enhance relationship management of external partners. Collaborating with our publisher(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive the assessment of potential partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From concept to release, lead and drive all production tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitate communication and collaboration with other disciplines, teams and stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schedule and coordinate the details for all necessary meetings, and ensure action items are followed up on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track and manage progress against budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage risks, and establish risk mitigation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive the goals of milestones in conjunction with the wider production team and the game development timeline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with limited supervision and use independent judgment outside of established procedures when necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May train and mentor junior members of production staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the planning and direction of the development and production of all Bungie’s projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure studio compliance with company policies and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strive to improve production practices at Bungie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Required Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to reliably schedule technical teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to self-motivate and motivate others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results oriented, focused and composed under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exemplary communication skills: Listen to, speak with, and resolve conflicts with members of varied disciplines and external partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding analytical skills: Understand, simplify, and solve or seek the solution to any problem in a fast-paced and ever-changing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail oriented and organized: Prepared to speak to and produce documents for all aspects of specified area at any given time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience in internal games production and/or enterprise web application production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completed a minimum of one complete large scale game cycle from start to finish or two or more web production cycles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in MS Office Suite, TFS or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion, enthusiasm and knowledge of the games industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Nice-to-have&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publisher Production experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;External development production experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-and-mobile-producer-bungie-bellevue-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-and-mobile-producer-bungie-bellevue-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>