<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wa-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Cloud Support Associate at Amazon in Seattle, WA</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Introduction Amazon.com has built a reputation for excellence with most recent examples being named #5 most admired company in the US, #2 most innovative, and # 1 in Customer Service. Amazon’s technology business is carrying on that tradition while leading the world in Cloud technologies. As a member of the AWS Cloud Support team, you will be at the forefront of this transformational technology with interactions with leading companies in this space and engineers within Amazon developing the capability. You will be surrounded by people that are wickedly smart, passionate about cloud computing, and believe that world class support is critical to customer success. AWS Cloud Support provides technical support to a global list of customers that are building mission-critical applications on top of AWS services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overview We are seeking people with strong customer support and technical skills. Do you have experience troubleshooting problems spanning multiple systems? Do you have a background in networking or operating systems? Do you have experience providing world-class customer service? If you fit the description, you might be the person we are looking for! Every day will bring new and exciting challenges on the job while you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn and use groundbreaking technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply advanced troubleshooting techniques to provide unique solutions to our customers' individual needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact with leading technologists around the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with Amazon Web Service architects to help reproduce and resolve customer issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage your extensive customer support experience to provide feedback to internal AWS teams on how to improve our services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive customer communication during critical events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or at least two years of experience in a Technical Customer Service role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Installation and/or Troubleshooting of:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS Administration (Windows or Linux)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network Essentials (TCP/IP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Internet Fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong customer focus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to juggle many tasks in a fast-moving environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited about technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Cloud Computing concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AWS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with scripting / programing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with database administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For more information on AWS please visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://aws.amazon.com/&quot;&gt;http://aws.amazon.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/cloud-support-associate-amazon-seattle-wa</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/cloud-support-associate-amazon-seattle-wa</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>