<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wi-des.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Sr Digital Art Designer at Mattel in Middleton, WI</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;American Girl is one of the nation&amp;rsquo;s top multi-channel marketers, with direct, retail and a publishing division to serve the American Girl brand and its customers. A wholly-owned subsidiary of Mattel, headquartered in Middleton, Wisconsin, American Girl celebrates girls through our premium quality dolls, books, clothing, and accessories. Come and experience play at American Girl!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have an opening for a Sr Digital Art Designer who will be responsible for creating the visual assets needed to support the digital content for Innerstar University, the Play @ American Girl website, and applications. The responsibilities include; the creation of original game artwork, 3D modeling of avatars and outfits, and spot art illustration and webpage designs that represents the American Girl brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associates or Bachelors degree in Web Design, Development or a related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In depth familiarity with Photoshop, Illustrator, and Maya or Blender (basic mesh modeling and rendering)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General knowledge of game art creation (including texturing, environments, and props), flash development, and HTML/HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-digital-art-designer-mattel-middleton-wi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/sr-digital-art-designer-mattel-middleton-wi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior Web Designer at CORESTAFF Services- Washington in Madison, WI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Great Lakes, a national industry leader in student loan services, is seeking an experienced Senior Web Designer with proven creative and design talent to join our Design Team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will do hands-on design, and work as part of a talented design team that helps internal departments throughout the corporation articulate concepts and ideas in a creative way. You’ll create conceptual designs and build web experiences. This includes designing web apps and pages, mobile apps, interactive pieces, multimedia, and infographics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your essential duties will include:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with multiple departments across the corporation to determine needs and to present concepts for review&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating user experience concepts that translate corporate needs to potential solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating visual design concepts consistent with the Great Lakes brand across all channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing new user experiences or features based on approved concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorming new concepts or technical approaches to gain us an edge over our competitors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Producing web pages, supporting graphics, interactive elements, user interfaces and overall user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in this job opening, please visit the About Us section of our website at www.mygreatlakes.org and then click Careers. Select the option to apply online, create your profile, then fill out the application for the job opening you are interested in. Your information is saved and you can return later to apply for other available positions and upload materials including a cover letter, resume, or portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great Lakes is an Equal Employment Opportunity / Affirmative Action employer. We invite all applicants to complete the Voluntary Affirmative Action questions when submitting application materials.  The questions are found at the end of the online application process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry, H-1B sponsorship (initiation or transfer) is not provided/ available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Skills / Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for an experienced and creative individual who has a substantial web design portfolio that highlights work you’ve done in the commercial or private sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;You should also have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three or more years of experience creating graphical concepts, website or mobile web content and user experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced skills in aesthetic and graphic/visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven proficiency with Adobe Photoshop, Fireworks, Illustrator, or similar applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with CSS and HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge equivalent to a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in computer science, fine arts, graphic design, web design, UX/UI design or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience implementing creative solutions that support a business or project’s objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills and an eagerness to be a team player who collaborates and helps others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ability to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take a broad design direction and move it to a specific design implementation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meet deadlines, sometimes with short notice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow and implement organizational and industry best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be self-sufficient in developing creative solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Juggle multiple projects with short turnaround times on a daily basis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-designer-corestaff-services-washington-madison-wi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-web-designer-corestaff-services-washington-madison-wi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Information Architect / User Experience Designer at 7Summits, LLC in Milwaukee, WI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;7Summits is a rapidly growing Social Media agency working with Fortune 1000 companies across the country.  We’re changing the way business gets done – it’s really cool.  For us user experience is at the core of everything, from socially-enabled interactive websites to destination communities for our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in growing your craft by utilizing Web 2.0, social media, and community design principles to create compelling and engaging designs, then 7Summits may be the place for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Passion drives our company to do great things.  We’re taking on some massive mountains, and we want you to be sipping hot cocoa with us when we reach the summit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with project &amp;amp; solution teams to understand business &amp;amp; design goals, and then select the best approach to create a highly usable and engaging solution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meet with users, conduct customer interviews, and gain an understanding of users and their goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop user profiles &amp;amp; personas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design &amp;amp; create conceptual models, flows, sitemaps, and navigation schemes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform heuristic &amp;amp; competitive analyses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboratively develop user interface designs &amp;amp; interactive prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct usability testing to validate &amp;amp; enhance architectures &amp;amp; designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, maintain, and promote usability standards, procedures, best practices, and knowledge across the organization encompassing screen design &amp;amp; workflow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow industry research, trends, and evolving platforms &amp;amp; technologies related to user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Job Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years direct IA/UX experience developing information architectures &amp;amp; highly usable interface specifications and prototypes.  Some agency &amp;amp; social media experience also required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge &amp;amp; experience with User-Centered Design practices; contextual inquiry &amp;amp; user research, persona development, heuristic evaluation, competitive analysis, interface design, rapid prototyping and participatory design, usability testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with user research techniques &amp;amp; interface prototyping tools (e.g. Axure, Visio, iRise, Photoshop).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio of UX deliverables for both new experiences as well as iteratively enhanced existing ones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills &amp;amp; attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation, and interpersonal skills including the ability to communicate complex, interactive design concepts clearly &amp;amp; persuasively to diverse audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent prioritization, organization, and time management skills &amp;amp; ability to work with minimal supervision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to consistently deliver projects &amp;amp; customer value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently &amp;amp; handle change &amp;amp; shifting work priorities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or equivalent work experience required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Human Factors, Human Computer Interaction, Usability Engineering, Cognitive Psychology or related field is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web analytics experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Compensation &amp;amp; Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7Summits offers a competitive salary &amp;amp; benefits package including health &amp;amp; dental insurance, paid holidays, vacation, sick leave, and career development opportunities.  We are a fun, fast-paced, team-oriented agency.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/information-architect--user-experience-designer-7summits-llc-milwaukee-wi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/information-architect--user-experience-designer-7summits-llc-milwaukee-wi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Graphic Designer at ShopBop in Madison, WI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Shopbop has a position available in our New York office for a visual designer who understands the aesthetics of modern fashion. We’re seeking a hands-on creative; a savvy modern branding designer; an accomplished visual experimenter and risk-taker; a composer of exquisitely balanced image, type, and message. This position reports to the Graphic Design Manager and will be a key member of a thriving collaborative culture of diverse and talented photographers, stylists, editorial writers, and graphic designers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with Creative Director, Senior Art Director, Senior Stylist, and marketing and PR teams to create our dynamic daily front window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and production of corporate print collateral and packaging elements. Act as the internal champion of the Shopbop visual brand across all internal communications and outward-facing printed materials and presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the development of visual branding elements and standards for Shopbop and our private label brands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow market visual trends and apply a keen understanding of the fashion marketplace to make decisions that will maximize the effectiveness of creative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design online advertising content for affiliate websites and for the Shopbop site and apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan project timelines and work effectively within budgets and objectives established by project sponsors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to take on other special projects relevant to past experiences and areas of special expertise and interest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 4 years of relevant experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery of the Adobe Creative Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obsession with typography with sample work that shows a highly refined sensibility applicable to fashion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to execute entire design projects from project definition through print production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively with high levels of autonomy and ambiguity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of interactive programs a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Apply through the Shopbop careers page and provide a link to your work on your resume. Please include in the link: 15+ samples that show a proven ability to design for a relevant audience, with a strong connection to the Shopbop aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;About Shopbop&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shopbop is the premier online shopping destination for what’s new and what’s next in fashion and style, offering women around the world the best selection from both established and emerging designers. Working with more than 500 international brands, Shopbop offers women in 165 countries a selective and nuanced fashion-forward assortment of ready-to-wear and accessories with fast, free global shipping. Shopbop is part of the Amazon.com Inc. group of companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shopbop is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-shopbop-madison-wi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/graphic-designer-shopbop-madison-wi</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>