<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wi-fdev.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Web Developer at Renaissance Learning in Wisconsin Rapids, WI</title>
				<description>&lt;h2&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re on a mission.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Renaissance Learning our mission is to accelerate learning for all. Every day, we have a positive impact on millions of K-12 students in over 70,000 schools worldwide. Now we are taking that mission to greater and greater heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Make a difference&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for talented, passionate front end Web Developers ready to play a large part of driving a seismic change in the technology, user experience and reach of our platform. If you&amp;rsquo;re not comfortable taking ownership of a product from the back of a napkin all the way to deployment and driving positive change and innovation along the way, stop reading right now.
Experience and Skills:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;We are interested if you are…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A rock star when it comes to Javascript/jQuery/AJAX and your arsenal of frameworks/libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone who thrives in a highly iterative, collaborative environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aggressively learning new things, and even more passionate about sharing them with others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with current best practices around responsive design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reading this on your phone or tablet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;And have…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of progressive enhancement and how to support a wide variety of browser/device capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed front ends for high-volume web apps and know how to optimize for performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built web sites or apps that deliver great mobile experiences in terms of layout, interaction, performance and features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A keen eye for visual/interaction design and an understanding of user driven design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working knowledge of CSS3 media queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;You really rock if you…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can show us something you&amp;rsquo;ve built using responsive design approaches that is as usable on my phone as it is on my tablet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have used HTML5, CSS3 and modern Javascript on your recent projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;About Us:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renaissance Learning is a leading provider of technology-based school improvement and student assessment programs for K-12 schools. Our products help educators make the practice component of their existing curriculum more effective by providing tools to personalize practice and easily manage the daily activities for students of all levels. Whether you are based at our corporate headquarters in beautiful central Wisconsin or at one of our other many locations, you can make a real difference in education. We offer competitive compensation, enviable benefits, and smart, friendly co-workers—all in a relaxed, fun atmosphere where you&amp;rsquo;ll have the opportunity to excel each day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Additional Information:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Job Level: Any&lt;br/&gt;
Number of Openings: 1&lt;br/&gt;
Years of Experience: 2 &amp;ndash; 5 Years&lt;br/&gt;
Level of Education: BA/BS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-renaissance-learning-wisconsin-rapids-wi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/web-developer-renaissance-learning-wisconsin-rapids-wi</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Front-End Web Developer at Lands' End in Madison, WI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Lands’ End, a premier source of apparel and gear for women, men, kids and the home – sold by catalog, online, and nearly 300 Lands’ End Shops at Sears, is currently looking for a Front End Web Developer. Since 1963, we’ve earned a reputation for quality, value and exceptional customer service embodied by one simple promise: everything we sell is Guaranteed. Period.®&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lands’ End is a proud member of the Sears Holdings Corporation (NASDAQ: SHLD) family of companies. The Front End Web Developer is responsible for the functional and structural construction of the visual presentation of landsend.com and landsendcanvas.com. FEWD will Concept, Design, Develop, Test, Train, Deploy and own all front end code including user interactions that are within the interactive space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept, Design, Develop, Test, Train and Deploy user interactions that fully utilize the digital channel to drive profitable sales growth and position landsend.com to be a leader in not only the retail and fashion industry but also web experience and design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspire creative and business team with best in class web experiences that are created with tried, trusted and tested web development techniques and practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept, Design, Develop, Test, Train and Deploy best practices in HTML, CSS and interaction design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept, Design, Develop, Test, Train and Deploy and Maintain reusable content that is easy to understand and implement by non-web savy team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with the Marketing, Merchandising, UX, Creative, IS and many other business teams to execute strategies and encourage change of existing interactive practices to grow and align brand awareness on all interactive platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development responsibility for UX prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, Develop, Test, Train and Deploy the functional side of the customer engagement strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Front End Web Developer will possess the following qualities:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in and passion for web development and design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A extensively detailed level of understanding of landsend.com programing languages which include HTML, CSS, JavaScript (focus on jQuery), JSP and Apache and Tomcat Server Environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategic and Analytical thinker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self motivated and driven to learn outside of work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to deliver measurable financial results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands the brand and can articulate the brand message via current and future the web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-channel and multimedia experience (includes Adobe Flash and Video Editing) a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to dictate simple to complex web experiences eloquently and with out fault for the understanding of individuals or groups that have little or no sense of web technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-lands%27-end-madison-wi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/front-end-web-developer-lands%27-end-madison-wi</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>