<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Work Creative</title>
		<description>Job Notification Feed</description>
		<link>http://workcreative.net/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://workcreative.net/feeds/wi-sup.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Senior User Experience Designer at Weather Central, LP in Madison, WI</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Innovative and creative professional will be part of a multi-disciplinary team of user experience designers, visual designers and product managers committed to developing innovative, easy-to-use, best-of-breed next-generation weather applications. The Senior User Experience Designer will provide mentorship and direction to members of the design team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Essential Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and iterate user interaction concepts through wireframe mockups, storyboards, and/or prototypes (paper and/or online).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design user interface details, including creating wireframe mockups and writing detailed user interaction functional specifications for new functionality and behaviors. Maintain and update design specifications during development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track progress and work with Designers and Product Managers to resolve design challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with development, product managers, marketing, and customers to evaluate, prioritize and clarify requirements and future enhancements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with development on implementation issues and resolve all questions of software behavior.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate, identify and implement relevant industry standards, best practices into WSI products and the development process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Embed design processes into the product development life cycle. Will identify and recommend process improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the usability testing/user research activities and establish and evangelize user interface guidelines and design patterns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will work on multiple projects at once.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All other job responsibilities as deemed critical to the job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Education and Training&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree, Masters preferred, in Human Factors, User Interaction Design, Information Design, or a related discipline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years experience as an interaction designer or user interface designer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing interactive applications for Windows, Web and mobile platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Skills, Experience and Abilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in user research including formal usability testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing User Models and application designs from initial concept to product release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with all flavors of user-centered design methodologies and processes including:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of customer use cases and extraction of requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diagramming of business processes and interaction flows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and implementation of usability studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track record of being a strong project team leader and a go-to person.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong writing and presentation skills as well as demonstrable visual communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to interact effectively with other design professionals as well as developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating wireframe mockups using Visio or similar products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be self-motivated to prioritize and manage work load, and meet critical project milestones and deadlines. Project estimation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weather industry knowledge a real plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Work Environment and Physical Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Normal office environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sitting for extended periods of time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in a confined area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using a keyboard to enter, retrieve or transform words or data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lifting and/or carrying objects 20-50 pounds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Climbing ladders, scaffolding, and the like.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working alone with limited interaction with other personnel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;To Apply:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please, email your resume, cover letter, salary expectations to jobs@wxc.com. Please, put code: SUID-25 in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-weather-central-lp-madison-wi</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://workcreative.net/jobs/senior-user-experience-designer-weather-central-lp-madison-wi</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>